GOMU GOMU NO…
HANABI!
[Hanabi:Fireworks]
White Berets…
They beat them.
The insane poor!
You should have listened to me
well nicely!
White Berets…
are the nicest guards
and understanding of the Divine Earth.
But “them”… They
will not be so lenient!
You are now
criminals of Class 2!
You will beg in vain…
Priests of Upper Yard…
… will regulate your fate!
Heso!
One can séchapper?!
Ordalies of God start!
It is what their problem?!
There is more serious…
We are condemned!
Did this old woman say it, not true?
“You can pass.”
Now that we are here one
we regards as the clandestine ones?!
What a swindles!
I would flank a beating well to him!
You said it!
In any event one would have come
even if it had prevented us.
Closes it to you!
Despite everything, this situation
is really embarrassing.
Now that you are
criminals of Class 2, us…
… let us not can help you!
Why you speak about also far?!
Bah, that done anything!
One with the practice to be required.
By the way…
Why returned to you?
Hein?
One left for an great adventure there
where one should never put the feet…
Not, I want to say… to seek you!
Be really too foreseeable for you.
WHAT A great adventure?!
You did not listen to me?!
There are only the rough ones
bloodthirsty men on this island!
You did not see them then
do not make the malignant one!
I do not know if it were God or not,
But this horrible capacity
and without limits was real!
I will not go back there!
Not on this island!
From agreement, one goes there,
you ace that to wait here.
Not! They will pursue me!
One draws from here!
One draws?! Not average!
What is more
important, the adventure or your life?!
MY LIFE!
And then money!
And then it is me?
The farm!
Wait, with the fact!
One was so in a hurry
to reach the celestial island…
that one ever wondered
how to go down again.
Said, there is one
sure means to return?
Can we turn over
on the Blue Sea?
Considering your current location, I cannot
not really to say that it is sure, but…
There exists a means.
Appointment at the end of the cloud,
until reaching the “edge of the Clouds”.
The “edge of the clouds”?
How one goes there?
The “edge of the clouds” is
completely in the East of the cloud.
To go there, you will have initially
to go down on the White Sea.
Very well! Then one can return on
is our sea in this way, it well that?
Not! I do not return.
He, you want to remain here
and to make you carry out?
In any case, you would do nothing but attract
problems with Conis and his/her father!
Oh, it does not obstruct us…
Lastly, even if one fled, perhaps
that one will not escape these guy.
If it is the case, where that one
goes, it will be similar.
They know where we are,
thus one must quickly move from here.
Go the guy! The veils are raised!
Yes…
Conis, Oji-san, thank you for all!
Ah, ouais!
Wait, Luffy!
He, Papi!
That there
does it have?
One can take with us
remains it puffs out?
Yes, of course, go ahead!
Super!
Sanji, prepares to us that!
You leashes nothing to pass you.
In this case, me also I have
a favor to be asked you.
Grandfather, you are
engineer, not true?
I can take to you some
materials to repair our boat?
Yes, without problem.
They are at the house.
He! Where you like that go?!
I will seek puffs out!
You them guy, prepare
the boat for the adventure!
It wants to go always there!
They is very dangerous over there!
And then?
Me that is equal for me!
Pas la pains of you
to pass the nerves on me!
Chopper!
You are on my side, not true?
Does not threaten it!
Heavy Not!
I was on the point
to install the scale.
Oups.
You do not include/understand? You
donot can convince Luffy.
Even if everyone there
puts, it will not listen.
Very well.
Then I remain here!
Ouais, make as you want.
“Make as you want”?!
I will be made kill by these nuts!
Well, make as you want then.
Why you…
Robin?
Could you help me to strike Luffy?
It is impossible.
I imagine that one will have to get rid
our prosecutors one by one.
These White Berets must surely seek
men to continue us again.
You to continue? Ridiculous.
God and his priests are too
immutable that a mountain.
They wait to judge the imprudent ones which
dare to come to defy them on the crowned ground.
When they are in anger,
Ordalies start!
You will be automatically lead…
towards the prohibited crowned ground!
Upper Yard!
Excuse me, I have
something to say to you.
There exists current cloudy special
to turn over on the White Sea?
Yes, by taking it, you
will be able to cross quickly…
this part of the sea for
you to return to the White Sea.
After that, you will reach the “edge
clouds " without any problem.
Really?
If you manage to take this current, it is
not very probable that somebody is able to follow you.
It is enough nothing to say to Luffy and of
to guide the Vogue-Merry towards this current!
Time that it realizes,
it will be too late, hein?
Then, knowledge if it will give up
or not, it is another history.
I can lead you to the point
of entry by using our Waver.
Well, it is necessary to arrive over there
before this idiot does not include/understand.
I can manage for that.
Well in this case, weigh the anchor
and please await me here.
Of agreement!
We are indebted for you, Conis!
Oh, it is nothing…
They is delicious!
He, stops puffing out our provisions!
There is full!
You can eat some too!
Be to you all eating!
Conis! Papi!
Do it
yourself!
Hein? Conis-chan left.
She says goodbye to everyone.
Here is your tea.
You are the carpenter of the ship?
Not, at all.
I am the gunner.
Oh, it is even more impressive!
Ouais, we do not have yet
of carpenter in the crew.
But it is not a problem!
Ca means that they must count on my
All-powerful Skill in all to repair!
What a responsibility!
Without me, this boat
would not make failure.
Even as a gunner, it is
almost me which plays the part of Captain.
It is besides for that
everyone calls me…
CAPTAIN… USOPP!
Oh, but this decoration is
true a oeuvre d'art!
Hein?
Exactly!
It is an art to present a meal!
Goodbye, Conis!
Heso!
One has finally a glimmer of hope!
With all that is
passed, I believed in it more!
But, this current
does there really exist?
Hein?
If there existed really one
so practical current…
it would be easy to meet
survivors of the celestial island on the Blue Sea.
Bah, let us go!
It was said to us that very few people
arrived up to now of the first blow.
Of course, rare are
those which escape.
And perhaps that the majority of them were not enough fast to escape their attackers.
It rightly. If one does not leave
in time, one ends up being killed.
Dispatch we to hoist the veils!
Weigh the anchor!
Chopper, uses this Heavy
Ball and deals with that!
Ca is called Heavy Point…
WHAT?!
Not nothing…
And Zoro awakes!
It is impossible.
Not engraves. I will arrive there!
If one does not make quickly, one
would misuse the kindness of Conis.
Heavy Not!
Just here…
Not, that does not go…
I will leave it there red…
And to place green emerald here…
Cool. Ca gives well!
Those will be for
Nami-san and Robin-chwan.
Ah, one would say almost that it
is not food!
Not, not. I excuse myself. I
would not have, really…
Ah yes?
This one is for
you, Conis-chan!
You made some for me too?
But of course!
I decided to entitle this meal…
“The Love is Ordalie, it
Meal of a Downward Angel ".
Oh!
Bah, that has anything of
special when it is eaten.
Would be a little more polished!
Listen, food must front
all to have the air delicious!
Good Ah?
Look at, it is similar!
You ate it without same looking at it!
Good Ah?
Perfect.
Ouais, always similar.
Always same taste.
You must initially enjoy with your eyes!
One of fout.
You cannot eat with your eyes, if?
I did not say that!
Perhaps that I can
to eat by the nose…
DO NOT EAT LIKE CA!
Oh, so much worse.
As soon as Luffy and them
others are of return…
Perfect!
Chopper!
What occurred?!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
It is what this brothel?!
Perhaps that one is
already on this current!
He!
There is a problem with the boat!
What?!
That there is,
Usopp?
Look at over there!
It would be said that they howl!
They have fun the festival?
Not cool, they have fun without us!
Nami-san!
Why…
Why it
wear a Tee-shirt?!
It is all that worries you, stunned?!
The boat from goes away!
But why?!
What they make?!
Where they go?!
It sail with move back!
They is super!
Not! They do not sail!
Look under the boat!
Wait one minute…
What occurs here?
It is what that?!
Was the current taken?
Not, it would be said that it
acts of another thing.
C-C' is what that?!
It is…
A single species of the Sea of Opal!
The Lobster Super Express train!
What?!
Where it takes us along?!
He, everyone evacuates the ship!
It is not yet too late!
And the boat then?!
If it takes the boat…
Do not make any you!
I remain on board!
You cannot…
What hope you to make all alone?!
I will find a means!
Ca does not go…
Y' has result.
Ok, that will go.
Unfortunately, I
believe that it is useless.
Go back to edge!
What?
Even if you succeeded, there are
others which will come by behind.
Look at!
What?
Enormous celestial monsters.
They sink on us
open large mouth.
One will not be able to return
with the stroke without danger.
And even if one succeeded
to get rid some…
There is probably
others which wait.
Any fight of our share will be vain.
It is undoubtedly the beginning.
The judgment celestial, not true?
Instead of coming to seek us,
one delivers to us on a plate.
Crafty ones, dumbs!
Then… one takes us along on this island?
LUFFY!
USOPP!
SANJI-KUN!
Why?
Why a Tee-shirt?
You always speak about that you?!
He, Luffy, that fear!
And now?! What does one make?
They left where?
Where?! Is it really…
Where?
Where
Where they are
Where are parties?
The Lobster Super Express train
is a servant of God.
All that it transports
is used as offering.
If it is well the case…
Their destination is thus
the North-East of Upper Yard…
Towards the Sacrificial Furnace bridge.
Sacrificial?!
Nami-san, Robin-chan
and these types?!
These types?!
They will be sacrificed?!
This dirty God…
This dumb…
You want to rub with me?!
Salt son of…
Wait please!
I am sorry!
It is not what you believe!
What?
I intended to say that those
who will be sacrificed…
… receive one of both
forms of the Celestial Judgment.
The sacrifice, or Ordalies.
They are so to speak
between the hands of God.
Prisoners with destination
sacrificial Furnace bridge!
Hostages?
Consequently, those which
are judged in this moment…
… it is you here three.
Hein? What does that want to say?
If I had a chart on me…
If you need one
chart of Skypiea, I have one of them.
It does not go back to yesterday.
But the topology of
islands seems to me correct.
Is all well, Conis-chan?
Yes.
But…
Do not worry you!
I know them well!
All will be well!
Assertion without bases.
We are here.
The Sacrificial Furnace bridge is in
high on the left, in the North-East.
And it is possible only one to go there.
You must take Milky
Road starting from this island…
… and to use a boat with Dial for
to cross the forest where the Priests reside.
Not, wait, Grand-père!
One could not simply take
a boat and to make the turn of the island?
It is like that this lobster
went in Upper Yard, not?
Not, even if you accost
in the neighborhoods,
you will be able to never reach
the Furnace bridge of the Sacrifices to foot.
Something changed between this
chart and Upper Yard of today…
it is Milky Road which
fly over the very whole island.
This river of clouds?
Yes.
I intended to say that Milky Road
count several hundreds of affluents.
And thus, the only means of going over there is to sail to the heart of the island while following Milky Road.
I see.
Some is the place where one accosts,
we will be blocked by this river.
Yes…
And this river is populated
fish man-eaters.
Fish man-eaters?!
What a kindness!
In any case, if one wants to find
our companions and our boat…
It is necessary to pass by the main door.
Here thus Ordalie
that one must undergo…
The Celestial Judgment?
Yes, you must face the power
unimaginable of the four Priests of Upper Yard.
What? Then it is all considering.
To make short… Botter is owed
is the bottom as of these Priests, it that?
You take that with light like always.
The things become interesting.