Under the orders of Wiper,
the Shandia warriors…
having learned the dispute between Gan Fall
and the Priests, benefit from the occasion…
to launch an attack on Upper Yard.
Our goal is the Sanctuary of God!
Do not fear Eneru!
The Large Karugara Warrior
we will protect forever!
OUAIS!
You here is, Shandia!
A little further, after having overcome
Satori, Luffy and its crew…
took again the road in
direction of the Sacrificial Furnace bridge.
Meanwhile, Gan Fall, casualty,
and Chopper, survivor of water,
were saved by the strange ones
birds of the island of Jaya.
A band of Birds of the South…
But, why? Why
are they so large?
It is you who saved us?
This man is God?!
During this time, Nami, Zoro and Robin,
reach the shore of Upper Yard
and do one surprising discovered.
It is a piece of the same island…
A piece of Jaya!
What Norland had discovered in bottom…
The gold city did not run.
For 400 years, Jaya had been
there, floating in the sky!
Jaya, Country of floating Gold!
The Sanctuary of God!
Thank you, God!
After all these efforts for
to reach the celestial island…
and finally to discover
that it is about the Country of Gold!
It is to reward me to have
summer a nice girl, not true?
My God!
You! I believed that this
island of God terrified you.
Hein? God?
He has value?
More what gold?
You do not come from
to say, “Thank you, God”?
This chick becomes senile!
Useless!
Is He, it what this place?
According to me, it is the zone
next Ordalie.
Another Priest will point himself.
Remain on your guards.
Oh not, only one Ordalie me
was largely enough, brothel!
It will be what this time?
Wire?
Iron?!
Marshes?!
Ca has me all the air of a banal meadow.
Ca does not have anything banal!
Open your eyes and looks at well!
All these craniums on piles!
Ouah! You ace reason!
It is what these tricks?
Another of these
monstrous Prêtres will emerge?
Ca with the air is delirious!
On which Ordalie one will fall?
Cretin!
If one is made kill by a Priest,
one will finish on piles like them!
Do not worry you!
One will not lose!
A trick approaches.
What?!
Iron?
Wire?
Marshes?
They all arrive at the same time?!
Ca would regulate the problem.
HERE THEY ARE!!!
Dumb!
GOMU GOMU NO FUUSEN!
[Fuusen = Balloon]
It was what?!
Paramécia.
He ate a Fruit of the Demon which
he get superhuman capacities.
Does Wiper, one face it?
Not, leave it.
Hein? This guy…
He, why you ace does that?!
You seek me?!
Cretin, come to beat you!
It, isn't this is you?
Inhabitants of the Blue Sea
who foutent the brothel on Skypiea.
He, Luffy.
It is the masked warrior who one
crossed on the White Sea.
It is what that…?
He splits the clouds!
He! Stop! What do you want?
You will release!
He wants to fight!
Ca is appropriate to me.
What? What?
Alarming! Alarming!
The alarming celestial island!
If you hold with the life,
turn over on the Blue Sea.
If it came you to the idea to try
anything on this island…
… we will eliminate you
how we will eliminate Eneru!
Do these types intend to overcome Eneru?
What means that
warriors and God…
are not in the same camp?
They are not Priests?
Then we do not occupy
they and draw us, Luffy!
You seek me, dumb?! Come here!
I will burst you!
Stop! Please,
leave them quiet!
I arrive!
Remain where are to you!
Prepare to take
shaken your life!
He insists…
I do not know if you will be
able to leave this island.
Who are these types?
All that we know, it is that they
have a tooth against Eneru God…
and against us too.
Whore…
Ca fears, this island…
Let us carry on our road.
Oh, my disease of “I--must-not
enter-in-this-jungle " begins again to me…
Good, I have the flagstone.
How can you to think of puff out?!
I cannot even rise!
Ok, Luffy.
We change the ideas into
singing the song of Sanji!
Ok.
Give me your hand!
NOT! It is not like that!
I cover you!
Profit to leave!
Now!
Something approaches! Somebody
approaches! I am sure!
They will not leave us
to leave also easily!
They arrive in group,
in herd, horde…
[Note:Zorozoro = in group, with the file]
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
He, that done one moment
that one sails, Sanji.
He, Sanji!
Ouais.
We crossed this
meadow without encumbers.
Let us continue in
series nothing--himself-passes!
Ouais, one will be left there, it is sure!
Q-what still?
What?
Look at-that, Usopp!
It is terrible!
Why one turns?
One goes where like that?!
I have the tournis!
Ca goes quickly!
Not, imbecile…
One falls!
A thing is sure,
Milky Road is too is delirious!
I will be sick…
He, it starts to make night.
Will Ca be like that to the Furnace bridge?
The sun lies down…
I do not manage to see
through the clouds.
There are also couchers
of sun on the celestial island.
Wiper, Kamakiri is by there!
They need assistance over there!
Chopper!
Where are you?
It occurred something, Chopper?!
Answer me!
He, it has there no more mast on Merry.
What did it still adulterate?
You ace nothing included/understood!
It was made attack!
Chopper!
Afflicted to have been so long!
You can leave now!
You are there, hein?!
Stop hiding you!
Answer me, Chopper!
It was perhaps done
to cut out of pieces.
Stop saying such horrors!
He, Chopper! Be to you there or not?!
What occurred?!
Speak!
R…
Nothing…
It did without anything terrible!
Of agreement, agreement.
You are large and strong.
Now, say to us
what occurred.
One is again
above the trees!
This time, it is a giant tree!
He, you should take
that more with serious, Luffy.
What is it?
Ca does not feel good…
There is something with the end?
I have like the impression
that at the end of Milky Road,
the Priests are in
train awaiting us.
It is brilliant!
I adore this trick!
One still will turn?!
He, there is something in bottom.
Over there!
They is surely the Priests!
Not, they are celestial sharks.
Oh, then they are not the Priests.
They are right some sharks
He, He, He, He, be serious for you?!
They are enormous! They
will swallow us very believed!
GOMU GOMU NO GATLIN GUN!!
One is soaked!
He, look at!
They were found!
It is the Merry Vogue!
Ca must be the Furnace bridge!
Hello, Nami-san…!
Robin-chwan…!
You missed me…?
I exceeded Ordalie of the Love!
What? It was Ordalie
what one faced?
You were not too afraid?
You reassure, now that
the Usopp Captain is there!
Mellorine! Mellorine!
They have the air in form.
Ah, here me is relieved.
The mast is…
Party.
Heu, Usopp… I am sorry.
I have do all that I could, but…
Ca burned everywhere, and…
Are He, you well?
Yes.
This guy with his lance
flamer must be dangerous.
But at least you did not cramé with!
One will deal with the boat later.
I will become the man on whom
everyone can count!
He, Chopper!
How you are
removed from this Priest?
I made use of the whistle.
The Knight of the Sky came to help me.
Where is the odd one the pépé now?
All that because of one
whistle that it gave us,
It fought for us.
If the Knight of
Sky had not come,
the boat and me let us not be
already more this world.
I have full with tricks to ask him,
But that will wait until it awakes.
And thank you with you too.
Luffy!
Considering the state of the boat and
the night which approaches,
we will not be able to turn over
on Angel Island before tomorrow.
For the moment, let us go down in the forest
and let us install the camping on the bank.
Why?
If us here are attacked, the boat
will undergo even more damage.
You should think of this type of things!
Without forgetting that it is easier
to fight on the bank that here.
Of agreement, one camps!
It is the festival!
He, wait!
One is in enemy territory, here!
You want to camp?!
Go, start with one
barbecue of celestial sharks!
They is delicious!
Cretin, would swallow you anything!
He, they is good.
Silence!
We will listen
the report/ratio of each one!
We went in the Forest
Lost, where one fell on…
a Priest called Satori which
made use of Bubble-Surprises.
One galéré with these Bubble-Surprises which floated in the air without knowing what they contained.
But the worst, it was this Mantra which it
used to guess our movements.
A Priest, name of Shura,
emerged from nowhere…
while making use of its
launch which burned all!
Moreover, it could
to envisage my movements.
I tested all
kinds of attacks on him,
But he dodged them.
The bird which it assembled spit of
fire and started to burn the mast…
Then, it impaled
the Knight of the Sky…
You passed dirty
fifteen minutes, the guy.
But, we discovered that this
island was in fact a piece of Jaya.
The Gold City does not have
run at the ocean floor.
It was propelled in the sky!
Good!
Thank you with all for your reports/ratios!
We drew from invaluable
information of all this!
Bird fire-eater! Launch flamer.
The celestial island is in fact what we thought cast,
Jaya!!
The Priests use something called
“Mantra” to envisage our movements.
This island is the Gold City that them
Forces Alliées Saruyama sought!
REALLY?!
I have just said it!
If not, it is what this
history of Mantra?
No idea.
Perhaps a species of instinct.
Instinct?
Does Chopper, that suit you like that?
Yes, it is sufficient for
that it can swallow it.
Its digestive system was touched.
Gold, hein?!
It is this kind of adventure
that I waited!
I am in a hurry to be there!
Quite known as! Then one is ready!
He, He, Luffy!
You would have forgotten what
did the warriors say?
God will be furious.
And it is alarming.
One will not be bored, not truth?
Pirates cannot leave
to pass the chance to steal a treasure.
And it is stuffed enemies over there.
It will be necessary to survive.
Ca promises!
L them guy…
We must be wary of God!
Do not come to feel sorry for you
if you all are damnés!
OK!
HOWEVER, US HERE!