Luffy accepted Davy Back Fight which opposes it to Foxy.
In the first test, Donut Race
the pirates of the straw hat lost.
We will start by taking some
one… and that which I chose are…
YOU! The doctor, Tony Tony Chopper!
Okay, made as you want!
to recover Chopper,
they will have to gain the second sleeve, Groggy Ring.
Surprised?
At all.
SECOND ROUND!
SHOOTER IN THE GROGGY BOXING RING!
Our warriors, still unconquered in Groggy Boxing ring,
will put full the sight of it to us against…
The cook bastonnor, Sanji!
It is the cook of “first class”
And, with a premium of 60 million Berrys…
The hunter of pirates, Roronoa Zoro!
I wondered which was our adversaries
so that one calls upon us…
Isn't this, Big Bang?
Hein?
He did not hear you.
It is what these guys?
This part will indicate which will make the kickoff.
Crush.
And you?
It already chose, that is used for nothing…
It is pile.
Ground or ball?
Ball.
Our Groggy Monsters chose the ball!
The ball of the team of the straw hat must
to place itself in the central round of the unfavourable ground!
Which side?
One of fout.
During this play there will be two man-balloon
that one will recognize thanks to their cover-chief.
It is enough to put the ball in
the unfavourable buoy to gain!
You dispatch!
The ball.
Grouille of going in your place.
Oï, Oï…
It is you who decided ace all alone.
I ever agreed to be the ball.
Why should I carry this weak trick?
Stop feeling sorry for you.
Oh? Does the ball that suit you well you know?
THE FARM! YOU BELIEVE THAT I
WILL FALL INTO THE PANEL!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Put to them a beating!
Make return Chopper, please!
There are not any more an other choice because of my defeat.
It is the first time that I see a giant man-fish.
It is not as large as a true giant.
Encourage them as much as you
will want, that will not be used for nothing.
Our team is expert of Groggy Ring.
You ace a problem? Head of puzzle.
He still said it!
Iyan, Oyabi.
Would not be so hard, straw hat!
Good, I think that there is no reason
so that I interfere in the play.
I will be spectator, like you.
Does Ca pose a problem to you?
What? It is also possible to obstruct in this sleeve?
Idiot! You can intervene
in any sleeve!
But there are teams which play honestly.
And there are of them others which want to cheat.
It is according to the tastes of each one.
Moreover, those which complain to have
summer obstructed by cheaters,
are larvae which did not include/understand anything with the life of pirate.
What do you want to say by there?
And what does it occur with your team?
They do not have any esprit d'équipe.
Say what you want. When the match
will start, these deux-là…
You cheated ace!
You ace carried out your movement after me…
At all! I gained in the rules!
It is because I am stronger than you.
Hein?!
About what you do speak?
It is Janken.
[Rock-Paper-Chisel]
And you lost ace.
Dispatch you to indicate the ball, you two.
They are still in the train of chamailler…
Sanji-kun, this ball suits you to charm!
I will be the ball!!
I am the best for that!!
Ouais, that suits you really well…
You resemble a prince…
… the prince of the idiots.
Begin this match, good blood!
Hey, the weapons go against the rules!
Leave your katana.
Ah? Really?
Ouais, it is a play of ball!
You already saw a play of ball
where the weapons are authorized?
In any event the result will be the same one.
Are Oï, to you on that will go?
A epeist without his swords, it is.
It is what?
It is idiot and that is used for nothing.
Will you play or not?!
Then?!
Now, finally…
The ball “Sanji” of the team of the hat of
straw is ready for the kickoff.
I hope that you will be made re-silver, cook.
The farm.
Crush them, Big Bang!
The encouragements become intense!
Big Bang.
Let us stop quickly!
He did not hear you.
You know… He He… you ace need
to listen more attentively…
As usual, Groggy monsters have
air to have fun in their corner!
During this general giggle, I go in
to profit to state the rules!
There is no limit of time!
Mark a point and it is the victory!
Nothing simpler, to gain I have just with shooter
this giant to place it in the buoy behind him.
And one loses if the head of the cook enters our buoy…
The crew of the straw hat
will it be able to recover its reindeer?
Burst them!
Or the crew of Foxy
a novel member will still gain?
It is pitiless Groggy Ring!
And we await the signal now…
The match can start!
Now, how the ball “Sanji” will move?
It will attack or move back?
It left!
Pickles makes the first movement with Tackle Demon!
Yosh.
I will finish some all alone.
I do not want to occupy me of you!
My only target, it is him!
If I release you in the other side of the ground, one will gain!
It is a face-to-face discussion between the two balls!
What?! The skin of this type is all slipping!
Sanji, the cook, slips on the tended arm of Big Bang!
But it was foreseeable!
Big Bang is an man-eel giant,
its body is thus extremely slipping!
What you insane?!
Species of cretin!
An opening!
To you be reached brain or what?!
Hey, which it is that is reached of the brain here?!
Here it is!
The super long master key of Big Bang!
Sanji!
Hamburger runs to catch the ball…
And Roronoa Zoro pursues it closely.
If you tombs with an aim, I kill to you!
The farm! It is because you stays speaking to me!
Hein?
Pickles has just entered the unfavourable ground!
And now, Hamburger… will be able it
to catch Sanji in full flight?
Yes, it is done!
Well, well!
Pickles awaits it firm footing!
Wait, jerk! You dared ace!
Roronoa arrives at any pace!
How…?
Pickles makes rebound the ball “Sanji” in the airs!
Sanji!
Big Bang will put the final key!
It returns Hamburger which fell!
And Hamburger catches up with Sanji!
It is…!
The buoy is with range of shooting!
Cretin of rolled eyebrows!
He will do it, it is the Hamburger dunk!
What you insane?
Made something! Zoro!
Sanji!
Is the match about to be completed?
You ace not with me to point out it…
You think that I will let these assholes gain?!
Of course that it is not finished.
I am still with the signal.
If I let this epeist help himself…
I would never have my moment of glory!
I would not lose!
No the goal!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
MUGIWARA-TEAM
No the goal!
Sanji will not return with an aim so easily!
I defend you to intervene!
You reacted ace too late, imbecile!
A duet able to embank Groggy
Monsters by the force appeared!
An impressive match will take place!
It is never considering, it is without precedent!
The giants are struck!
Crowd is amazed!
The team of the straw hat is very strong!
Do not think that I needed your assistance.
I did that because one cannot trust you.
These guy are monstrous.
These dumbs balanced Pickles!
And struck Hamburger.
Be to you really that a good with nothing.
You merits even not your statute.
Iyan. What do you await Hamburger?
You ace not interest to lose!
You want to fight, PERVERSE COOK?!!
I said that I was going to also overcome them, EYEBROWS ROLL!
And you…
Do what I say to you and CLOSES it!
Be to you IDIOT or WHAT?!
Let us see, see.
The crew of the straw hat acts curiously…
The balls are in their own half of ground.
The play continues, but they fight
still as so of nothing was not.
They are barges, these deux-là.
Cretins!
Do Zoro, Sanji, what you foutez at the end?
It is your chance! The ball is all alone!
And you of it occupy stop beating you!
Wanting to take the match in hand,
Big Bang seizes its chance!
It is…
Why you run?! This guy is the ball!
I know that, but…
This guy has knives under
soles of its shoes!
He the referee L
The weapons are supposed being prohibited!
He, the referee! Why you do anything?! Reacted!
- Useless, It looks in another direction.
Te insane step of me!
Not, not that, Sanji-kun!
Dumb! You ace all considering and it is what all this
sweat which dégouline of your mug, hein?!
I do not have…
I do not have anything considering.
Salt lying!
Hey, is calmed, it is the referee.
Sanji of the crew of the straw hat, Carton Jaune!
What?! Species of dumb!
Calm yourself, I said to you to calm yourself!
We had it! The first carton jaune of the match!
If Sanji receives some another, it will be excluded from the ground!
Who will be excluded from the ground?!
To be caught some with a referee, what a weak!
Your mouth if not you will be the next one!
A weak truth.
In any event, the weapon of it…
But await… it is an axe?!
It is a coïcidence, I do not have anything considering.
He, subdues to me that, the referee!
It is an axe this time, it uses an axe!
He, is calmed! What
will happen if you are excluded?
I in do not have anything to wax! I cannot
blairer this referee of shit!
Mets not in anger! Do not fall into their play!
Never!
Calm yourself! It is for the good of Chopper!
I will stick good to him!
I beg you, does not complicate the things!
Sanji-kun, gains this match!
I will gain!
I would never include myself/understand.
Go, it left!
Pas la pains to begin again where were to you!
The situation does not improve one would say.
I believe that I have measuring rod his weak point.
It is time that the things change!
This time the hunter becomes driven out!
Mets not on my way!
I can occupy myself some all alone!
, You cooperate are supposed being a team!
Finally, the counter-attack is launched!
One cannot attack it directly
on the skin, it slips.
One little to attack his hands,
its feet, its mask or its shorts.
Shit!
Here it is! Lifting Racing Circus!
They can slip indefinitely on its back!
I will not twice be made have,
it is like iceskate!
Impossible to escape!
I will stack!
You beat seriously!
During this time, two other players
were raised and return in the play!
He, they returned! Come them botter the bottom!
Oh not! It would seem that they were re-equipped!
Hamburger has steel fists and…
kinds of sharp-edged circular coudières.
Its Pickles fellow-member covered
shoulder pads provided with peaks!
We point out that arm are prohibited!
What a coincidence!
The referee stretches and turns the back on the play!
I am really irritated, Leader.
Allons-y!
I have the head which turns…
Go! One goes there!
It left!
The players ghosts counter-attack!
It is not a question of the ball.
He aims at the epeist, Roronoa, with his steel fists!
Zoro!
The attack is not finished!
Without delay, Big Bang prepares its attack!
Hamburger is put in position. It places its
elbows with the steel discs ahead!
Not!
It does not go…!
They is dangerous! Ca can really badly turn!
An arrow would be said!
Zoro!
It is a direct blow!
Naturally, in Groggy Boxing ring,
the participants can die.
My head turns.
The crew of Foxy does not leave them any respite!
I feel badly…
Here a blow of shoulder covered with peaks mortals!
Sanji, releases from there!
A blow directed towards the ball, Sanji.
Hamburger strikes it in the back!
It would be said that it does not aim the goal!
Groggy Monsters connected
several terrible attacks!
They are really cruel.
Zoro!
Sanji!
The team of the straw hat will not belong itself to as soon as!
It was an easy victory!
They are really groggy!
Now, they do not have any more but to put
the ball in the circle…
and it will be our second victory.
Invincible,
incredibly strong,
they are Groggy Monsters!
One still gained!
He, cook.
You do not want to help me ten seconds.
Ca would have…
us to be enough…