In order to recover Chopper, Zoro and Sanji
take part in the second Round:Groggy Boxing ring.
Hamburger catches up with Sanji!
It has the goal in full line of sight!
You believe that I go…
to let these assholes mark!?
It is out of the question which I leave this cretin…
of swashbuckler to steal me once again the high-speed motorboat!
They start to type me on the nerves, leader.
The enemy is really groggy!
It does not remain any more but with…
to trail the ball with an aim and it is gained!
He! Cook!
You can help me, just 10 seconds?
That would have…
to be sufficient.
ATTENTION WITH THE CARTON ROUGE!
GROGGY BOXING RING
We are in the second round of
this Davy Back Fight, Groggy Boxing ring!
I do not think that they will be concerned as soon as!
It was obvious, nobody cannot beat our monsters!
The team of the straw hat valiantly fought,
but it did not have any chance to be left there!
There remain to me nothing any more to comment on,
the match arrives at its end!
He, look at! They…
They are upright! The team of the hat
of straw was raised!
What a appalling tenacity!
Roronoa the epeist and Sanji the cook…
Will they succeed in reanimating the combat?
Go! Smash to them the mouth!
I wonder whether there remain to them forces to fight?
He, you three…
“Monster Burger” and that jumps!
Qu-Quoi?
I wonder what it is…
Ah? Hold! They sell burgers in the corner?
But of course that not!
Oh the cow! Oyabin has just ordered
“Monster Burger”!
He! They do what? They had funker of the weapons!
“Initially one will chop, Hamburger!”
“Then let us cut them in sections, Pickles!”
The ingredients are?!
“Of the salad green and yellow cheese!”
“And two large bread sections to do one of them…”
“MONSTER BURGER”!!
And here!
Their the most powerful and vicious combined attack!
They are without pity! They violate without
care rules of the game!
The team of the straw hat is foutue in advance!
Oh! Thus look at that!
The referee continues his heating!
And the back turns to the play!
BUT WHAT YOU GLANDS YOU!?
Await Luffy!
But, it…!
You ace not yet measuring rod? They want
that you attack the referee!
You must keep your calm, Luffy!
All is avoided! The attack of Groggy
Monsters can start!
We cannot be held responsible
of its consequences…
Their target is obviously the ball “Sanji”.
They are chopping it, cutting out it and on the point of crushing it!
I wonder what it will resemble like hamburger!
It will be hard of concocter a decent dish
with similar ingredients…
But I could tenderize your flesh without problem.
Let us chop them!
It is fast!
That is badly!
Stop crushing!
Leader!
How oses you?!
One trains a team, does not forget.
Bastard…
I will cut out you in parts!
It is what that!?
Big Bang is made slice by the blades of Pickles!
I cannot stop bordeeeel!
Finely “good mannerss”…
Pa-Pa-not-believable!!
It succeeded in stopping Big Bang in its fall!
What a kick devastator!
Big Bang do not fall but it is very sounded!
What you will make, Pickles?!
The team of Foxy is in dangeeer!
Look at! Zoro the sword-man will benefit from it!
Its target is without any doubt the Big Bang ball.
You will not pass!
You obstructed the passage…
You and the other referee of shit!
He shooté Pickles crushes on the mouth of the referee!
It is a true terror this Master cock!
Bastard…
How oses you to be caught some with the referee…
PAPERBOARD ROU… HE?!
But that…
Where are my paperboards… and my whistle?
Unpleasant girl…
It is a day before practice.
Oh, still a problem with the straw hats?
There remains only Big Bang to be cut down,
but they still seem to dispute.
Incredible!
Big Bang…
What?!
Not possible!
Its gigantic body…
has just ejected itself!
GO!!
It aims at the goal!
Impossible!
GOOOOOOOOOOOOAL!!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
MUGIWARA-TEAM
Pa-Pa-not-believable!
It flies away!
GO!!
Impossible!
It is finished!
GOAL! GOAL! GOAL!
Super!
Zoro!
Sanji-kun!
It was mortal!
Zoro!
Sanji!
You are terrible!
Brilliant!
One gained!
I do not want to lose my Choppy…
I do not return from there!
These guys are too balèzes!
Cheer! Cheer!
I have the tears with the eyes of them…
You assure serious the guy!
Bandage morons!
Our adversaries did not glorifiez!
How they could…
to embank our Groggy Monsters!?
You are awaked Mister the referee?
Dispatch you to blow in it.
Go! Quickly! One hurries!
Oooh, ah yes…
Its deplorable control must be sanctioned…
I will exclude it from the ground!
And it is the final whistle!
It is the end of Groggy Ring!
They was too cool!
Played well! Zoro! Sanji!
Ah! Thank you for the knack!
In the second round of Davy Back Fight,
they beat invincible Groggy Monsters…
and gained the match…
Which bright victory for
the team of the straw hat!
How if Zoro and Sanji could lose!
Nami-swaan!
Robin-chwaan!
You saw that!? You like me?
You were marvellous.
You have me foutu the tokens to make the idiots like that…
Stop striking me.
Fortunately how I was there!
You speak… anything did you.
Now, winners of this round Groggy
Boxing ring, the crew of the straw hat…
can take is a member of Foxy
Pirates, is their pirate flag.
Which will be the decision of the captain to the straw hat?
Oh… I believe that the choice is clear.
Hein? It is… me?
Then…
Then it was me whom they wanted!
Oï Oï…
I do not feel ready mentally…
He saw me!
Oh not, it will take to me…
Then it is really me…
what it chose?
That could be me!
If I am taken, I should separate me from all my pals…
These types…
It is me whom they like…
Luffy…
Hurry.
Yosh! I go…
Wait a little!
Why that, Nami?
In the third handle…
Oyabin still will try to have to us.
If one is taken in his Noro Noro Beam,
though one makes to leave oneself there…
One will be foutu in advance.
But! If one takes their Oyabin now to them,
there will be less difficulties for the third handle!
Indeed, if one takes Chopper as of now,
one could again lose it
at the time of the third handle.
In other words, if one takes Oyabin now,
then one is certain not to lose Chopper afterwards.
Ah! This girl…!
She wants to take our Foxy Captain?!
He, but it is cheating!
And to say that I believed you cool!
Bandage cheaters!
You with the honest one beat!
It is not contrary with the rules, but…
If you take the unfavourable leader as of the second round,
what a dishonor it would be for your reputation of pirate!
But what a vicious! This woman
succeeded in making me chialer!
Nami, the navigatrice!
Bandage puffiness! You to take some in Nami like that…!
I go you battered the mouth!!
In all the history of Davy Back Fight, nobody has
dared to resort to such loose and pitiful methods!
I ask it to you with you spectators, one
is such victory a true victory!?
NOT!!
One swore on Davy Jones to deliver a combat
regular! Can one ridicule such a promise!?
NOT!!
They are malicious!
It is ok when it is them which cheat,
but not when it is us…
CHEATERS! CHEATERS! CHEATERS! CHEATERS!
What you have a problem?!
I am of agreement with Nami!
Do not cry Nami, all that it is of your fault.
You will close your mouths?
You want to be made knock?
We are sorry.
Well well… it does not matter after all, because what counts…
it is the final decision of Monkey D. Luffy!
It is free to choose one of our fellow-members.
It is all considering, it will take to me…
I should close my eyes for step that he sees me.
Who could it take of other besides me?
Not… Do not look at me!
Pity, not… wait a little!
Please, not me, I love too my crew.
Then it is me to finish?
It is me whom one will take it is that?
It is not…
It is thus me whom they will take?
Straw hat… dumb…
Then it is me whom you want hein?
Obviously… Who of other that could be?
Good-bye, my Foxy Pirates!
We trained a beautiful team.
I promise not to cry when they separate us.
Aaah! It is undoubtedly my charm which allured you.
It is true that I am the missing link for
how the crew of the straw hat is perfect!
Said, Miss the navigatrice.
It is true that your plan is logical, but it means
that this Oyabin will integrate our crew definitively.
One does not want any.
Oyabin lost consciousness with the emotion!
These people are not aware of the sensitivity of Oyabin…
Iyan Oyabin, you are irreplaceable in our hearts!
It is true that, Oyabin!
Friends…
Let us show them what one is worth!
Ouais! One goes marrer to the next round!
You are loved, Oyabin!
Oyabin!
Friends…
It is true…
The only comrades which I need it is you.
I am sorry!
Stop this comedy, buffoon.
Oyabin!
It would seem that the crew of the hat of
straw does not want Oyabin, then…
Who will be thus the elected official?
They is good… I chose.
Return by here…
SHELLY!
Pa-Pa-Pa-not-believable!
That which Monkey D. Luffy wants is it
chevaaaaal adored of Tonjit, Shelly!
But of what does he thus think?
You ace an idea of what you come
to make, imbecile of captain?!
Ouais, of course.
But did brothel, what still take this time to you?
You make always very through!
Ch' it-insane-likes, do not stretch me the fissage like cha…
From now, Choppy us
will belong for always.
If you did not want Oyabin, it is
Chopper that it was necessary to take!
But it is that I make some wanted…
I recovered Shelly for you, Ossan.
Friends…
You will be together from now on.
Thus said both of the bottom, you
seem well badly in point.
You are well?
It is because of this light-haired boy
who trailed in my legs.
Obviously you are occupied.
Afflicted… and thank you.
Forget that.
Yosh yosh yosh yosh...
Then it was for that.
I imagine that one could not make differently.
Return to see me one day, one will eat a cheese end.
PAS QUESTION!
I am really sorry.
I really thank you, thank you.
No the roblème Ossan!
Will that go with your companion? He is always…
It is true, Luffy.
You should a little more think so that Chopper feels.
Luffy.
Chopper…
Afflicted, Chopper.
One will gain the next test
and to bring back for you to the fold,
thus has patience still a little.
Be hard, not true for you?
Does my decision pose a problem to you?
Absolutely none!
Chopper…
Do not worry you one controls the situation!
Serious, is necessary for you that stop you playing it to you…
I wonder what will resemble the next play.
Is necessary to hurry, one must go there.
One must bring back Chopper as fast as possible!