Where am I?
You should not move!
Chief, the Belfry of Gold!
Our duty is
to always protect it.
Abrupt step, Wiper.
Vearth does not reject anybody.
Yes.
For people gathered here, the war
is the most unthinkable thing which is.
It is the festival!
400 long years of war
on Skypiea are finished,
the festival étreignant the country
continued throughout the night.
I came here!
weaving of Poneglyphes
Not… Not…
I can more nothing drink…
Found!
He!
What?
Nami, awakes the guy!
Why?
One will prick a little gold
and to leave on vacation with!
You found ace of gold?
Imbecile!
You speak too extremely!
And then?!
You shout twice more extremely than me!
He! You ace shouted more extremely when you ace
known as how it was me which shouted!
Ca it is what then?! You shouted ace even more extremely when you ace says that I said that you shouted more extremely!
You shout MUCH,
MUCH more extremely than me!
You make fun of me!
It is you which shout!
The farm!
How somebody can it sleep here?!
Usopp struck me!
Would He, why I have done that?
Do not try to show me!
But you struck me
with your arm! BAM!
BAM, straightforwardly on my belly!
Inhabitants of the Blue Sea
really like to have fun the festival.
It is as if they were
tired at all.
They are not human.
Then, it is that the plan!
Ouais, the guy.
It was our only chance
to visit the celestial island!
Let us not leave any regret behind us!
It is so cool!
I tremble about it of excitation!
Chief! We have
found the Gold Bell!
What?!
He, be sure for you?!
Yes, it was wedged
on Giant Jack!
Everyone tests
to tear off now!
That all warriors into good
health go on the west coast!
Quickly! As quickly as possible!
Ok, bring as much of
people that you can!
Let us go quickly on the west coast!
We found the Belfry!
Where is it?
On the west coast.
Ok!
Be sure for you?
Ouais!
Grouillez you!
The Bell fell into
sea, but it is always there!
Ouais!
That all those which can move
we join on the west coast!
We found the Belfry!
Go on the west coast!
The Belfry?
Still!
Loan, and…
Draw!
Shit, one does not have enough men!
It is the pride of Shandora,
our ancestral city!
We must recover it!
Yes!
Be ready to draw!
Loan, and…
Draw more extremely!
A rubber band?
You call that a rubber band?
Exact. And 90% of the power which cut down it
Giant Jack was provided by Usopp Wagomu!
[Note:Wagomu = elastic]
Mashed potatoes!
I am only in all
blue Sea to have some!
Incredible!
But wait, there is another thing
who could interest you…
A metal plate!
Is Ok, which my offer?
It is not a plate
of ordinary metal!
Abused through crushing
tests of Large Line…
and the pitiless attack of Eneru,
the Merry Vogue is always intact!
Our mast is always upright thanks to
metal plates like this one!
Then? You want metal?
I sell that one to you
for some Dials!
Not, I will take the rubber band!
I exchange it to you against Dial!
I want some too!
You still have some?
Me too!
Is this reality?
For me too!
Water.
The light.
Fire.
The elements which destroy.
Even things without
substance can be…
crossed!
Too much chance! Too much chance!
You seem content with you, Usopp.
I am so lucky!
Did the market occur well?
He, looks at that!
Look at all Dials which I have!
Look at that one!
Like you?
Content for you.
It is brilliant you want to say!
I can make full with
things with these shells!
The workshop of Usopp will be revolutionized!
Say what of it to you?
I would make of tone katana
an aromatized sword…
and you will be submerged by the odor
melons during your drive!
They is good.
It is true! I can make
improvements on Clima Tact of Nami!
And my pachinko balls will make fear!
Besides, where passed
teams of Luffy and Robin?
The team of Luffy is still there.
Robin started from his side.
He Ben, this snake sleeps since
one good moment now.
He danced all during the night.
I do not know what made it so happy.
But more important still, if they
do not leave from here quickly,
it will awake and the things
will turn to the vinegar quickly.
Hein?
This so sympathetic snake?
Imbecile. You did not see this
thing when it becomes insane!
This so sympathetic snake?
I said just that you say that parce
that you did not see it in anger!
This so sympathetic snake?
He, you me listenings, Usopp?
It was the Audio-Dial!
DECREE WITH THIS WEAK SHIT!
Weak! Weak! It
that called weak!
What, brothel?
What it ate
this snake?
You ace finally found, Luffy?
Look at! It is there!
Whaaaaaa!
Ca, it is a business!
It is so beautiful!
How that of the monkeys!
Ouais! Ouais! Ouais!
Look at all that!
Too much cool, hein?
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
It is gold?
Which marvellous vision.
You can feel his pride
only by looking at it.
It is a shame which one
columns is broken.
Ouais, but nothing there can.
He, wait.
Look at over there!
It is Ponéglyphe!
Stone that our ancestors have
protected with the danger from their lives!
But what that said, Chief?
Something which it is to better be unaware of.
We only have…
“Keep the truth in your
hearts, the closed mouth. “
“We are those who
will weave the history, “
“With the sound of the Large Belfry.”
How do you know these words?
They were registered in
ruins of Shandora.
You were charged to keep that
during generations, exact?
You want to say that you
can read this inscription?!
Having the name of a god,
the antique arms, Poséidon.
It gives its site.
How that?
She said ancient!
An ancient weapon?
Why would she say that?
Ouais, why?
Another weapon.
Different from Pluto of Alabasta.
Pluto. Of only one gust, it can destroy
a whole island without leaving the least trace.
To say that a thing also méprisable
tapit still in this world…
As I thought it,
still another dead end.
It is not what I want to know.
He there!
This trick registers with dimensions in
does it also form part?
What?
Gol…
D…
Roger.
What?
“I came here…”
“and I will carry out it
passage au boils of the world. “
“Gold D.Roger the Pirate”
The Lord of the Pirates!
Ca wants to say that it is
come on the celestial island?!
But what means this inscription?
Not, more important still, how
did it know to use this writing?
It is the name of Roger?
You know it?
It is a pirate of the Blue Sea which
there came here is more than twenty years.
Its name
is registered over there?
Yes.
I cannot know how
it could reach this bell…
But this is the proof that it did it.
Now that I think of it…
There are two types of Ponéglyphes:
Those which contain information and
those which give the site of the others.
These is a stone which
contains information.
“I came here and I will carry out
this passage at the end of the world. “
To carry out the passage…
To carry out…
Would like he to speak about Rio Ponéglyphe?!
Chief.
This Ponéglyphe has fully
achieved its task.
Its task?
Yes, there is of Ponéglyphes which contains
information scattered in the world.
By reading them separately, they must form
a passage which fills the vacuum in the history.
In other words…
The joined together, complete text.
This still unknown text
is Rio Ponéglyphe.
The Lord of the Pirates, Gol D. Roger…
must have carried it
passage to destination.
Therefore, now…
You known as…
what our duty was accomplished?
Us…
We… will not have…
to beat us more?
I see.
The wish of our
ancestors was exaucé!
Chief!
Hold good!
Thank you my god! Thank you my god!
He was exaucé!
Yes.
That wants to say…
that I must carry the passages
of Ponéglyphes which I read…
to the island with the end
of Large Line, Raftel.
Say to me, Miss…
This boy with the straw hat
makes me the same impression as Roger.
Is this my imagination?
Its name is Monkey D. Luffy.
I am also interested in him.
“D”? I see.
Ca is appropriate to him to have
a name of only one letter.
Yes, all that will certainly have
great historical consequences.
Forgive me, Miss.
I remember that you were
here to find gold.
Ca has more value than Vearth
on isn't the Blue Sea?
Yes.
Then why not take
the broken column of the belfry?
Of course, us
let us can give you the Bell.
It is an good idea!
After all, we must thank you you
and your crew for what you did!
Ouais, it rightly!
Do not be timid.
Are you sure?
The others will be certainly
happy to have it.
Yes!
Ok!
Let us carry that on the boat
inhabitants of the Blue Sea!
Each one on a side!
Ca will be hard to carry!
We will give it to
savers of our country!
Heu, it is enormous.
What makes Robin? It spends time of them.
Oh, I start to be hungry.
The guy, this place is deserted.
What occurs?
Where they passed
warriors and angels?
Not, so much better if there is nobody.
If they see what one has on
backs, they will have some after us!
After all, one flew this
however to make a station-wagon, not?
They will not be very content
when they realize some.
Nami and Conis have all
prepared for our departure.
Grouiller is needed.
And then, Sanji, you ace
not a trick to be eaten?
All is on the boat.
Go, you must have well
something. Give me in.
Which wound.
Why one would have
to await this woman?
I will embark on the boat.
Cretin, does not even think of it!
Cretin!
Cretin of Marimo!
Marimo Cretin!
He, look at! It is Robin!
Robin-chan!
He, Robin!
Quickly, quickly!
One slips by!
One flew full of gold!
Morons! Do not say that!
Look behind it!
They all return!
There is a whole army!
Oh shit! Oh shit!
One is in a large shit!
It is Q-what that?!
It is a giant gun!
It is a gun! I am sure!
Thus they all arrive at the same time.
Will run towards the boat!
One cannot remain longer!
There, looks at! One has
full bags to the brim!
One is rich!
They took all
their luggage with them!
Me known as step which they leave already!
He, wait!
Wait!
Look at, they have some after us!
Cassos!
Good, it belongs to me of
to stop in their race!
You stop there! Not
means that one waits!
He! You say to them, Usopp!
We put our lives in danger
to reach the celestial island…
Quite known as!
and to find the legendary Gold City!
Robin-chan, quickly!
They will capture you!
Never a proud pirate
would leave the empty handeds!
To capture?
About what they do speak?
One wants just to thank them!
Won't He, you take this gold?
I think that they do not want any!
What?!
Flee!
There are tons of money!
Then, Zoro? I am quite occupied!
Ouais, it was impressive!
Robin-chwan, quickly!
WAIT!
Ok, the guy!
Will run to the edge of the cloud!
OUAIS!