God alone knows it.
Trying to escape from Upper Yard,
Nami and its team move towards
east coast when Eneru makes its appearance.
It roasts Sanji and Usopp,
before disappearing.
I am called Hotori!
I am called Kotori!
On its territory, the brothers triplets of Satori, Hotori and Kotori, unload in search of revenge.
Sometimes, it is me
who must protect them!
During this time, four others
southern full leader towards the ancient city…
are separate after their
confrontation with a giant python.
Their ancestors had to set it up
after the city did not fall.
Shandora.
It was the name of the ancient city.
Who is there?
Where am I?
I did not have anything against you.
I will accept the challenge:Survival.
What a negligence!
This guy is stupid or what?!
Each one meets an adversary and
engage in an inescapable combat.
During the last confrontation,
Chopper puts the Gedatsu Priest at the carpet!
KOKUTEI
[The Cross of the Sharp Shoes]
CROSS-COUNTRY RACE!
Invincible capacity!
The true nature of Eneru appears
Is all well, Kamakiri?
Do not make any you for me.
Look at rather around you.
Look at!
Over there, in the clouds!
I see Giant Jack!
The ruins of Shandora are close!
And Eneru is at the top.
What do I can for you?
I am just there.
What did you want?
Kamakiri, Warrior of Shandora.
Eneru, species of dumb!
With which believe you to be addressed?
I am God.
You would like to know well
why I am descended.
Mantra?
I do not need me in
to be useful! Ca is read on your face.
But, I do not want you.
In theory, I do not see
interest to face you.
But this time, I
take part in the play of Survival.
And I will leave soon these grounds.
I have just made
my good-byes with Gan Fall.
You call that a play?
What a connery!
You seem impatient to kill me.
Very well.
As you are a warrior,
I will reward you to have surmounted
obstacles to arrive until me.
An outline of the leniency of God.
Let us see seeing…
What would you say five minutes?
During five minutes, I
will not move of an inch.
What?!
I will not dodge your
attacks, and I will not counteract.
Make me pass to
pan. I am at your mercy.
Dumb!
But once these five minutes spent,
You will become aware by
yourself of the existence of God.
DUMB!
BURST, ENERU!
Moron!
You cannot reach us!
Stop!!
STOP IMMEDIATELY!!
One will not stop!
I AI KNOWN AS STOP!
They are unconscious!
And then?
It is them which wounded
our brother, Satori!
Wounded our brother!
And now, they will pay!
Brothel!
Thank you for the impact!
An Impact?!
Beurk! It is what this odor?!
I see.
They use four
kinds different of Dials.
It is exact!
Impact!
Flavor!
You memorized?
You will not be able to follow!
Now, which is
Hotori, and which is Kotori?
That there is in
each hand?
It is so funny to imagine
what you will receive!
SURPRISED DIAL ILLUSION!
I know the various kinds
now. Let us not waste time.
I type myself of it knowledge which is which!
A typhoon approaches!
Failure!
And now, which Dial
is in my right hand?
It was still my fart!
Imbecile!
You expected to see
to leave fire, not true?
Fire is in my right hand!
The gas will take fire!
Odd knight!
This imbecile!
He flew away!
Which stupid turn of kid.
You underestimated me.
Kotori!
Return…
Cyclone Tempo!
He! Young girl.
Find my glove in bottom
on the bridge and it completes.
Odd knight, your
was wound reopened?
Do not occupy you of me!
It soon will return!
A glove?
A glove, a glove…
Is He, it what a glove?
Ouah, it is heavy!
It is made of iron
coming from the Blue Sea.
A Dial Impact was
embedded inside.
Use it as I have you
shown presently.
I included/understood how it goes, but
this trick is too heavy for me!
YOU WILL PAY IT!
I believe that I
will not have the choice.
Initially, my Satori big brother, and
now, my Kotori little brother!
Even your prayers you
will not save now!
It is him which makes use of fire.
Its body is soaked and
the air is in charge of moisture…
Mailbox
It is what?
It is more and more
cold… It is all?
Yes, completely!
You of fire, isn't this makes use?
You insane of me?!
Ca will not be enough with
to counter my Dial Flame!
I will reduce to you in ashes!
Hot air in contact with the cold air
will create a condensation of moisture…
A fog will be formed!
FOG
TEMPO
It is what that?!
Y' has fog everywhere!
I do not see anything!
What you make?!
What?! What you make?!
All my excuses.
IMPACT
AÏÏÏÏE!
I failed to tear off me the arm!
Why you made
that, odd Knight?!
Hold out.
You were superb, my expensive.
But, good!
I protected the boat and the crew!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
Must I call you
Aisa-san?
You know really which road have
taken pirates of the Blue Sea?
Yes.
Which astonishing gift.
In spite of the distance, you can
to hear their voice since the forest.
But first of all, you feel well?
You did not stop trembling
since we collected you.
It is…
What?
It is because I never have
be also afraid of all my life.
All voices…
All the voices which disappear…
Yes, I am sorry.
We must hurry, Conis-san.
Yes, Father.
He! Where you go,
Odd knight?!
Afflicted, but I must find Eneru and…
What you say?!
You will leave one
all alone woman?!
I already did you my excuses.
I must know why
Eneru came in the forest.
It is perhaps…
Perhaps…?
When Eneru appeared, 650 Soldiers
under my command were captured.
I do not have time to explain you,
but my men are in danger.
Not, it is the country all
entirety which is in danger.
Can you fly, Pierre?
Wait!
I leave you the glove and
the impact which is inside.
You should be able
to clear up you.
What?
RETURN IMMEDIATELY!
SPECIES OF MONSTER WITHOUT HEART!
AND YOU ARE CAUGHT FOR GOD?!
RETURN HERE!
REFLECT A LITTLE!
I WILL CRY!
For the moment, I must give
first aid with these deux-là.
You are alive the guy, not true?
Chopper, hurries to return…
C-C-C' was
what?!
Nami-san! Heso!
Conis?
Heso.
And his/her father?
What you made here?
And you cannot
to stop this trumpet?!
Let leave to me!
Not! You must remain there!
If you venture all there
only, you will be made kill!
We promised
not to remain a long time!
Let leave to me!
Who is this child?
Ah, it is called Aisa and…
Does not approach you, unpleasant
girl of the Blue Sea!
I go you écrabouiller!
I am warlike of Shandora!
Ouais? And then?
You want to fight?
I will give you an Impact to be chewed.
Oh not, they are carbonized!
They should be looked after immediately!
At all events, forgive me…
Please, could you direct
your boat towards our way?
We used Milky Dial
to create this new river.
While following it, you will arrive
directly with the Sea of Opal…
before the enemy does not find us.
You could not be one
little more discrete then?
Ah, yes, there is something
that I wanted to give you.
To give me?
Waver!
I repaired Waver that you
had brought back Blue Sea.
Now, take it, I
you requests some. It is with you.
Ouah! Really?!
Yes.
Brilliant!
However, this Waver
is a little particular.
Its power is
higher than the normal.
I am sorry.
Oh.
Be to you still there?
Afflicted.
I had calmed down.
That there
does it have?
You seem to suffer, Kamakiri-kun.
As promised, I did not do anything.
I…
donot can you
v-to overcome, isn't?
Yes, it is right.
You included/understood, now.
I am the lightning.
No matter what they make, men
nothing against the lightning will never be able.
Having always lived in the sky, you
ace inevitably already considering a flash by far.
Since old times, the men have
allocated with God the mysteries of nature.
As all that they could not
to include/understand and which frightened them.
All that humanity underwent
was allotted to the will of God.
The men accepted their impotence
vis-a-vis the natural disasters.
And I am myself one.
I am regarded as
God. You include/understand?
Oh.
[Note:Breath = breath]
burn blade!
I must inform Wiper!
We cannot
to gain this battle!
It is suicide!
Even if it is sacrificed, it
Reject will not have any effect!
It is a little late to flee.
We must revalue the danger!
If not…
If not!
You believe capacity to move
more quickly than the lightning?
Your five minutes are past.
It is my turn.
1.000.000 Vari volt
FLEE, WIPER!!
It was what?
NOT!!
What? What?!
What did it occur?
What is there?
Voices…
The voices disappeared…
Thin then.
My electricity seems to be
propagated in Milky Road.
20 other voices disappeared
after the electric shock.
The poor imbeciles.
On Upper Yard,
81 people started
play of Survival.
Two hours are
run out and 56 fell.
There remains 13 of my holy guard about it…
5 of the crew of Straw hat…
and 7 in the Shandia rows.
What wants to say that they
are nothing any more but 25.
It is more than I had envisaged.
It does not matter.
I must pay attention
with the figures.
Who will join me finally?
This collar is out of gold!
The Gold City is perhaps
in this cave!
I hope to find some yakiniku…
[Yakiniku = Flat meat Japanese]
Good go!
Where I am?!