The POLICE INTRIGUE OF the CHIEF
LUFFY WITH THE STRAW HAT
Here Large Jipangu.
It could resemble a region
having existed at a certain time…
But, let us pass the details for this time!
It is the special episode of end of the year after all!
Then… Here Large Jipangu.
Although it is the end of the year.
spring reigns on this region.
The season when the flowers of cherry trees open out.
This area is an haven of peace,
and the people enjoy happy days fully.
But…
Is all well, owner?
Here what arrives when one
burst of laughing in smoke.
That… What did it occur?
Somebody has just smashed the entry of the store.
That does not advance me. I will see…
Do not go there!
I will see who am the person in charge.
It is me.
You must be quite trustful
to dare to defy the Family Clown.
Cl… Family clown?
Ever intended to speak.
Then you go soon the knowledge!
Listen…
Retain this name well!
Because we will be soon Masters of these places!
Species of kabukimono!
Perhaps you believe that the authorities will leave you…
Kabukimono? It is amusing!
[Kabukimono:Organizes]
You think that all that would be done
if we fear Okappiki?
Stop this sweet talk, gangster!
And why you carry this false nose?!
He, remembers to you of a thing.
It is not a false nose.
It is a truth…
A true red nose…
and I hold to with it much.
They is for that I insane in bad temper
as soon as people say similar silly things!
It is unforgivable.
Owner, it is not reasonable to use this trick here.
I include/understand what you feel,
but to recover the money is our priority.
Isn't this?
Shit!
You of him occupy the guy!
Yes!
He, Onami! Another, another!
Not! It already is too!
Hein? Already?
Do you know how much you owe us already, Oyabun?!
To eat free just because U are a okappiki!
Would not be if radine…
Aren't the money, that go, that come?
Then I go…
You are unaware of me there, not?
Ah it is true!
I had also come to refund my debt!
Ah… yes yes yes yes, I had it
completely forgotten while I ate.
Then, say to me how much.
And I could also pay in advance.
Then what think you, Onami-its…
Fantastic! I can all take?!
Of course!
I will not make my skinflint! Take all!
Brilliant!
What a class, Oyabun!
- Be super for You!
The service is rather unforeseeable here…
About what you do speak? Te do not make a concern!
Sanji-kun!
Prepare a good-natured meal for Oyabun!
No the problem.
And here!
The dinner gastronome of Kazaguruma!
Itadakimasu!
Stupid Oyabun…
You accumulated not badly money, after all…
Then you will not need more to pay now.
It was money without interest after all…
Honestly, I thought that you would have
known as that you were encircled enemies…
But they is good. I forgive you.
You are entirely forgiven.
As long as will have you money,
I will forgive you all your faults.
How you ace made to pile up all that?
In fact, I stopped criminals recently.
Oh! It is the reward of a large company?
Not, I infiltrated,
and there was much money which trailed.
And you took some?
It is not a little illéga…
Just a little, it is not serious!
Otento-sama you E will not want either.
Then, it was which these criminals?
Ah! It was a gang of counterfeiters.
THEN It IS COUNTERFEIT MONEY!!
I was enough idiot to believe it.
Do not cry, Onami-san. I am there.
I will return to you forever happy.
Sanji-kun.
Hello, can one have a fruit dish?
Mellorine! Immediately!
Special dresser of Kazaguruma!
Your beauty is like
the lightning tearing the limpid sky.
Ouaah! Splendid!
You find?
But we did not order something of so large.
No problem.
You will not need to pay me.
Of course, it is…
Taken directly on the wages of Sanji-kun.
That made how much time this morning, Sanji?
If that continues, you will work without being paid.
It is terrible-terrible-terrible!
Hey! Oyabun!
Oyabun with the Straw hat!
What still? Be too noisy for you.
Is Oyabun there?
I intended to say that he ate.
What you made Oyabun,
while the Family Clown showed himself downtown…
Family clown?
It is a terrible family which takes control by
the force of all the cities and shops which it crosses.
It has just arrived downtown.
In this moment even, the office
of exchange of main street is attacked.
At the moment, in full day?
Why did you avoid?
Will stop them!
Ah! Euh… I cannot do that all alone.
What? Make, it is to it all.
Thus they operate.
They do not have any pity towards those which resist to them.
For this reason all the mond is afraid
and do not dare to denounce them.
Like it there forever of complaints,
one cannot intervene.
What a band of cowards!
Hey! You will just be unaware of them for that?
Why do you believe that one lets you eat here free!?
Rise quickly!
I would have agreed to rest me but…
When it is question of food…
And that one cannot let them make like that…
Then ok! I will stop them!
Bring to me in one!
Of agreement! Is Hiuchishi, it that?
But not! A cake and food!
BREAK FROM HERE!
It is all that you have?
Yes, all is there.
Detach me!
It would be said that it still remains you of energy.
You others!
Retain this well!
From now,
all the money of this city belongs to me.
Do not seek to hide it!
If you done it…
I will explode you with this ball
Special Baggy, then not of entourloupe.
Would not be too optimistic, buffoon!
What!?
You did not hear me?
Are your ears there to decorate or what?
Lastly, I hope at least…
that it is not the case for your eyes.
I am one of the gardiens de la paix of this city,
with Oyabun with the straw hat, Usopp-sama!
You have me the quite trustful air for
a subordinate of Okappiki.
Try you to say to me that you
deal with us all alone?
The calm one… Oyabun soon will arrive.
Three…
Two…
One!
I' L was necessary to expect it,
Onami is always also specific.
Oyabun with the Straw hat, you to play!
This kid is Okappiki?!
I hold more! This city has surely much
to offer so that it makes me marrer as much!
Be really noisy for you, large red nose.
I do not know why came to you in this city…
but this place does not belong to you.
Frankly…
To destroy the houses of the others in full day.
It is you who ace done that.
Save to me the details.
I will close the eyes for this time
if you return on your premise calmly.
WHO HAS A LARGE RED NOSE?!
Species of dumb!
You me insults and me I should listen to you wisely!?
Then?
Oh that yes, your presence causes
problems with everyone.
Problems?
Who said that I caused problems?
Does somebody find that I cause him problems?
Shit, nobody.
Were owner, you maltreated, Isn't it?
These good people included/understood my
virility and beat a retreat.
A jutte does not have anything to make here.
I saw it!
I will testify some!
It struck the owner and took all the money!
Oyabun, capture it, I request from you.
What?
Tiny tanuki.
Come-there!
Hey…
How it did that?
I know anything of it.
Don't dumb, you want to suffer, not truth?
The farm!
They is even more painful to keep silence!
As you will want, I thus go
to make of you a bag in tanuki!
I AM A REINDEER!!
Dumb!
Oyabun?
OI! LARGE CONK!
, Bends down you!
Dumb! It is what this leg?!
Ah that? I ate the fruit Gomu Gomu,
I am a man-rubber.
A man-rubber?
The fruit Gomu Gomu?
Then you also, you are a user of a fruit of the demon!?
Bite!
That hurt.
TRY you ME TO RIDICULE OR WHAT?!
Usopp!
It left!
I hold you!
Captured!
Beautiful performance as usual.
Well, direction the police station!
I will listen to there what you have to say, then remains calm.
Rubber of shit…
Richie!
It is what that?
It is what?
A bomb!
Shit! It was right a smoke producer.
The dumb!
He disappeared! Money too!
Its men are also flee!
I wonder how it has demolishes its bonds.
Does Peuimporte, what one make now?
They are easily escaped, with the money!
Eh well, one can nothing there.
Well, one will end well up finding them.
Why if be slackened to you?
Did Ah, then this doctor testify?
You are rather courageous.
I could drive out this guy with the large conk thanks to you.
Thank you.
How I have fact was natural!
I do not want your gratitude, malicious!
Then, Onami, offers to him food for…
How Ca, “Then”?
Who will pay?
Oh! I did not do that for…
Would not be timid.
Oyabun does that because he likes you.
Enchanted.
Ouais, magic!
Well, I will leave one moment.
Oh, and where that?
Small businesses.
Burst, rubber band of shit!
Advances more quickly!
Ah! It is opposing!
What?
What did it occur?
The guy!
That made a long time!
Let us defer the greetings to later.
I want to hear the reason of this situation.
Lord, I do not ask large for thing…
But, made that many rich person customers us
bring much money, as at the beginning.
If not, it will be the bankruptcy.
It is true, then not jokes, that will not help me.
I count on you, Seigneur.
I feel much better!
He, children!
What v…
What do you say?
I have just received Yabumi.
He is written. “If you want to re-examine Onami,
come towards the bed from the river, but only Oyabun. “
It uses really a cruel method.
Yes, the problem it is that they have an hostage.
Do not worry you, I have a plan.
A plan?
Go, Usopp! Allons-y!
Oyabun, addition.
Put it on my ardoi…
Not…
Shit! It gave me wire with retordre.
Does Yabumi, have reaches its target?
Of course.
It was supposed to come only,
but good, it just brought its flunkey.
I am not a flunkey!
You are really loose to take an hostage!
Hostage?
Do not make the idiot! Return to us Onami!
One will return it to you in good state…
But!
Before that,
Some of our knowledge
would like to test their capacities against you.
You company to them, isn't this will hold?
Come by there!
Oyabun…
He the guy, come!
The killer with naked hands, Gedatsu.
The epeist with the six sabers, Hachi!
These bastards called reinforcements.
Ah, I forgot…
My subordinates are rather hard
and always do not listen to me…
In fact, they are of the guy rather unverifiable…
“Baggy”… “Kuma-chan”!
Then you are that which opposed the Clown?
Unforgivable!
The largest sword-man, Hachi-sama with the six sabers,
will send to you in the other world.
Who is tallest, you said?
Really? It is what this brothel?
Oyabun, is better to draw now…
Imbecile!
The jutte will be able to never compete with six sabers.
Hein?! Ten against six? I am losing!?
Which idiot.
Yosh!
But, Oyabun!
HEY! YOU FORGOT THAT I' L HAS an HOSTAGE THERE!?
Onami is well…
Apparently…
Not, you cannot…
It leaves from where that one!
Usopp!
Usopp!!
Why?
He you! What you have just made?!
Why do you draw up you still there?
How I could make such an error.
You cannot see like that!
It was so fast, I did not even can see it.
Indeed, the name of this attack is the Jet Punch.
It is impossible for you to see it.
The only disadvantage,
it is that one can the utiser only once.
Say something, dumb!
Be to you idiot or what!?
How oses you to ridicule me?
You ridicule yourself all alone!
The farm! Eat that!
Hein?
You already have not just struck with this arm?
Oh not!
They is all of the cretins.
He! Small elastic merdeux!
You ace nothing in the brain or what?!
There is always an hostage here, then would be less expeditious!
Be too noisy for you.
I go you botter the bottom.
Moreover, Onami is not any more one hostage.
Hein?
Sanji-kun!
BUT You ES WHICH YOU?!
It did not return, I
asked what occurred.
You really made a large connery there…
I do not know who you are but I admire your courage.
The guy!
You are the only one who remain, conk of shit.
You ace quite known as “of shit”?
You soon will regret having done that.
Are Onami-san, you wounded?
What makes you marrer?
Insane steps of me.
I am always the head of the household.
Your adversary is there.
Surprised?
I am also a user of fruit of the demon.
I can separate my own body with my suitability…
The man Bara Bara!
And now, man-rubber.
I know which is your weak point.
They is the blades, not truth?
Completely.
Do not say to him so easily!
Prepare.
I will make you suffer.
Here me is, Straw hat!
Come.
Your lower part had far too openings.
Dumb.
It is the body part of a man
who should always remain intact.
That does not concern a taker of hostages!
As promised, I will boot you the bottom!
Baggy!
It is all that you merits.
Oh, it steals super good.
I imagine that it will remain
quiet one good moment after that.
Hey! Are Usopp, you well?
Come, Onami-san, I will detach you.
Thank you, Sanji-kun.
Then…
thus Oyabun overcame the Family Clown.
I did not expect from it less Oyabun.
You fought Usopp well even
while having been so seriously wounded.
Hein? Oh yes, of course!
I remember to be myself beaten against hundred as of theirs.
HUNDRED! INCREDIBLE!
And all that before the breakfast!
BEFORE EATING?! ENORMOUS!!
But they nevertheless took all the money, not?
Ah, it is not so serious.
Why?
To tell you the truth, the money which they took…
it was forgery!
What?!
It is true…
There are no badly people who have one
natural talent to locate it.
Oyabun remembered the face of the counterfeiter.
It was acted in fact of the owner of the bureau de change.
It called the police station right afterwards.
Surprising, it made its job.
Eh well, it is the kind of anybody who
fact its job when that becomes necessary.
It has interest, if not it would not be
that a dying glouton of hunger.
It is true.
No the doubt.
One would speak about me in my back?
It is hard the celebrity.
Give up.
You cannot escape to us.
You are an invaluable source of revenue.
We will not have any evil
if you are to us well nicely.
Do not touch me!
Small plague!
Does not underestimate us!
But be to you which you?
What you insane here?
I have something to say to you.
There are not time to listen to your sermons.
Unless you do not want to play the heroes?
To save people, it is the job of God or Buddha.
That does not interest me
Nevertheless, do I can take part in the business?
Eaten, nor not drunk, since three days.
I will not tear off any more rewards
if I continue like that.
Get stuffed, old bonze merdic!
Oups, sorry…
My hand slipped.
Dumb!
Oï, Usopp. I want to make the night round well…
but aumoins that one takes puffs out front.
I am hungry.
Species of…
A baston.
Bastard!
He is hefty man!
In a flash…
Oh not, the Straw hat!
We break!
Shit!
You pays nothing to await… dumb!
Which waste of time.
Hein? It seems to me to have already seen them before.
Are Oï, you well?
What do you have?
Oh but you are wounded!
He, wait!
One can know what you did here?
You will have to follow us to the station.
What did I make?
I saw you!
It is you who wounded it!
Quiet remainder!
It is not him, Usopp.
Its wound is that of a katana.
With such a talent, it would not have
need to escape like that.
Goodbye, Oyabun with the Straw hat.
Ouais, goodbye.
How does it know which I am?
He, where do you go?
Are He, sure for you that goes?
Oyabun!
It is a girl!
The wound is closed again now,
there is to worry no more.
She was very tired in any case.
Let us give him the drug, and let it rest.
That will go. She will go better tomorrow.
Well, so much better.
I brought back the futon of Onami-san too.
Thank you. Pose it here.
Of agreement.
Then, how does that occur?
Apparently all is well.
She was to be very tired.
She sleeps deeply.
She is beautiful like an angel.
I feel that it is the destiny which wanted this meeting.
It is true that it is beautiful.
But I still do not include/understand
why it tried to flee.
I suspect that it is because of…
An old bonze merdic and very extremely…
It is what one says to you.
One was stopped by
a bonze with the monstrous force.
THAT I HAD INCLUDED/UNDERSTOOD!
Do not speak to me with half deadened!
How dare you to return the empty handeds?!
Bandage rotted pumpkin maggots!
You know how much it is worth this girl?
Afflicted!
Owner!
There is an little idea of the place where this girl is.
The Straw hat?
Yosh.
Bring to me this bonze here.
One cannot let pass an occasion
similar to earn money.
Included/understood?!
Then it is called Vivi?
Yes.
But although it gave us his name,
she did not want anything to say of other.
Its state is stable, however.
I see. If it is well, it is essence.
Oh! Onami! To eat, eat!
Me too!
Welcome!
Oyabun with the Straw hat and Doctor to the blue nose.
Hein? What do you make equipped like that?
I work here from today.
THE VIVI-CHAN, YOU ES BEST
TOO MUCH NICE…
I could not refuse his assistance after all that.
You are well, now?
Yes.
Thanks to the doctor salary
with the blue nose, I feel better.
Keep silent yourself! I like at all
that me am launched flowers, malicious!
Malicious.
I see. Such an amount of better.
Vivi, can you serve the tea, please.
Yes.
He, it is by there, Vivi.
I wanted to really go from the good side but…
To serve the tea…
It is hard…
You never served the tea?
In fact… it is the first time of my life.
Hein?
I am there almost… I am there almost…
THAT BURNS!!!
Die… Afflicted!
You do not have anything, Vivi-chan?
WORRY RATHER FOR US!!
Well, well…
What would say you to eat one
delicious meal to forget that?
Sanji-kun, hurries.
Yes, Mellorine!
Will that go?
In a way or another… This time…
That with the good air!
That still saw!
You are well, Vivi-chan?
I am delighted that Vivi want to help us…
but I am afraid for the future.
He, of the tea please!
Yes, Ca comes!
Vivi-chan, here too!
By here…
On this side…
Afflicted to have made you wait.
He Ben, that filled of a blow.
Welcome.
The rumor concerning Vivi was spread in the village.
A rumor concerning Vivi?
Thank you!
Yes. How what there was a splendid waitress!
Thanks to what, the trade is prosperous. Vivi is brilliant!
I am occupied, occupied.
Vivi-chan! One will tenpura soba!
Here too!
Yes!
Vivi is too nice.
Onami-chan also is nice.
But she likes too the money.
Vivi-chan is the best, after all.
From now on, I will trail the every day in Kazaguruma.
Me too.
Stop that, band of manures.
MATER Vivi-chan like that with length of time…
Customers of shit!
Customers of shit, you ace known as?
MT MOUTH!
IF IT SE STILL MAKES RELUQUER
BY YOUR PERVERSE GLANCES…
THE BEAUTY OF VIVI-CHAN
WILL BE SOILED FOREVER!
I AI NOT NEED FOR YOUR MONEY!
INSANE THE CAMP!
Sanji-san!
Wait! What you make the customers?!
Why you feed this chaos, Oyabun?!
Return to Kazaguruma of front.
Maintaining these insects crasseux
are not ready to return.
You can finally slacken, Vivi-chwan.
WITHOUT CUSTOMER, THE BUSINESSES SE WILL DETERIORATE!
Hidokuruma is of return in Kazaguruma.
[Hidokuruma:Bad furtune]
I am afflicted, Onami-san.
I was not very useful to you.
Do not worry you for that. It is not your fault, Vivi.
Ouais, ouais! Do not worry you!
Oh, it is not well.
I forgot an important promise. I go there.
Ah yes, Vivi. You can come, too.
When they are the promises of Oyabun,
it is always to have fun.
You ace of the temps libre in any event.
That will go here, you can take a pause.
To have fun? But where?
Ben… you will see it by yourself!
Heat in front!
I finally found it.
Frankly, which annoying girl.
Its force is monstrous but…
its appetite is even more!
Our provisions…
Aa… I fix.
Then… You wanted to speak to me?
Look at me, Vivi, I will fish large there.
Then am not afraid.
That is well, now.
Do not make any you.
Y has any means that Oyabin makes a large catch.
Oyabin is large a bouzu, after all.
Be hard for you…
Look at me well.
Bouzu?
That which does not manage to take
only one fish is called bouzu.
That bites!
You ace makes a large catch, that it is clear!
Is Oyabun, it the first time that dead?
Good blood, it is too odd.
Vivi, tests, you.
You believe that I would arrive there?
Do the fish eat really these small beasts?
Hein? You ace ever seen of vers de terre?
It would be said that Vivi do not know large thing.
It is stupider than us!
You know, I also put yourself the question on this subject…
But it is not a reason to shout it, you others.
But the soft foods were not like that, with the castle.
With the castle?
Not…
Then… How does one make use of it?
You explain me?
It is terrible! Terrible!
It is absurd!
Why would Vivi-chan be on an research opinion?
It was distributed to the seat of the government.
This document is used to seek discreetly
a person which one is unaware of the identity and his localization.
I could not make like
so of nothing was not in this connection.
I think that it is about one
spy come from another country…
or a member of a higher authority.
Why?
Species of dumb!
To treat Vivi-chan of criminal!
But… Vivi, which is really?
Goodbye, Oyabin!
With the next one!
Also return, Vivi! Promise it!
Yes! So long everyone!
Be careful!
Yo! Be to you the bonze of the other time!
I do not test any resentment towards you.
but I must return this favor.
Do not take it personally.
What do you tell?
You us because step badly of troubles
the last time, Straw hat.
It is not gratitude but…
can you accept this modest gift of end of the year?
A aller simple for the Sanzu river!
Ah, it is Baggy.
If you want to treat with me, come to see me directly.
Would not be so shameless.
We are interested only in the invaluable woman, over there.
Invaluable woman? Hein?
If you wish to face me, it will be necessary
initially it to beat, rubber of shit!
It is like that, Oyabun with the Straw hat.
It is odd. What do you await ego?
Fight!
He, a technique with three saber… Interesting.
Owner!
Hein
Oï! Oyabun with the Straw hat,
it was what this punch merdic?
Well then take that!
Oï! Where you aim? I am there!
Ah! Bastard!
Oï! Fight elsewhere!
It is the moment…
Vien Richie!
Afflicted, my hand slipped.
Liar!
Dumb! You misled us!
Afflicted, my hand still slipped.
Hum…
Thank you very much.
It is not the first, but
second time that you save me the life.
Small rubber merdeux!
Now, I am really in anger!
I will explode this false bonze
and all others with him!
What? When it has…
Die!
Hein?
It IS WHAT THAT?!!
It is very hot, very.
They is not good.
The owner is an anvil.
One must save it.
Thank you very much.
It will be very for today.
What has it just occurred, there?
OYABUN!!
Vivi!
There here! Vivi!
Hein? What arrives to you?
He, Oyabun! It is a liar!
Look at this research opinion!
It is what? It is Vivi, not?
It is what this history?
It does not matter what it is, I was sure!
I was sure…
Vivi isn't malicious, hein?
Said?
Malicious?
HEY!
Of course that not!
There is nothing special… on this subject…
He, you!
Who do you believe that this person is?
It is the princess of Jipangu! The Vivi-sama princess!
SLACKEN IT IMMEDIATELY!
Princess?
Grandfather…
That… Vivi… Be to you a princess?
Incredible! A true princess!
Yes.
YOU DO NOT INCLUDE/UNDERSTAND OR WHAT!? SLACKEN it!!
There, it is sure, are to you a princess!
SUPERVISE YOUR WORDS! YOUNG PERSON INSOLATE!
Stop grandfather.
But, Vivi-sama…
Afflicted friends.
I never lived apart from the castle,
then I wanted to see the life of outside.
Good blood, why not have andé with somebody of
to accompany you, rather than to start all this bazaar?
But, grandfather did not listen
never and refused all the time.
Obviously.
What would you have made if something were arrives?
It is for that the Family Clown in
had after Vivi. They wanted to hold to ransom it.
It is true qu it exists full people without scruple!
Afflicted, grandfather.
But… But…
I am glad to have met to you.
It was amusing.
I did not know many things,
but Oyabun with the Straw hat
and the others learned to me so much…
Everyone was very nice.
This is why, I wish to make
this country a much better place!
But please, do not start again more.
If you too often remade that,
I would not make old bone.
I include/understand.
I will not leave any more the castle without permission.
Thank you with all.
It was a short visit, but I will not forget
never time that I passed with you!
Vivi-tan…
The attitude of Vivi-sama improved.
Yes.
The last events did not make
that to encourage its ambitions.
They is rather good to know.
Yes…
Princess Vivi, return quickly, I request from you.
I have some more than enough…
The adviser seems to have concern.
Yes! I touched it!
Wow! Impressing!
Be gifted for you!
Really?
Vivi-chan! I believed never again to re-examine you!
It was not supposed not to leave the castle any more?
Without permission, not.
She said that they there authorized it, therefore they are good.
I imagine that must be hard
for the adviser, in this moment.
Yosh!
Oyabun!
It is interdict to use the techniques Gomu Gomu!
Oups!
Of agreement…
Which din…
It is still them.
I can sleep even more quietly.
Oyabun!
It is terrible! Terrible!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
MUGIWARA-TEAM