Determination of Coby and Helmeppo!
Pride of father of the Garp vice-admiral
Aahh! Here they are!
The million inhabitants of Little Garden
wishing me welcome,
me the Usopp-Sama captain!
Scented breeze of the girls carrying their impetuous kisses!
“Honestly, I know that I am only one man among others.
But you can only fall in love with me, small.
It will not be my fault if one embraces oneself… “
Be to you idiot or what?
Does Ca mean what this “idiot”, Zoro?
The farm!
You cannot be quieter?
Good blood…
Forgiveness! Forgiveness! We said?
I said in short that even if there are no islands in the corner,
the coral reefs are rather important, therefore there is always a risk to break the hull.
I include/understand.
Thank you.
I will keep that in memory.
Of nothing.
Ah! Ca feels good!
Afflicted to have made you wait.
The dessert of today:tart with pears.
You level Misses.
Ouahou! Ca with the delicious air!
Your place is over there!
'silvering…
Where is Luffy?
Oh, I asked him to bring back water so that I can take a shower.
It must be with the récolteuse water machine.
Ah, it is thus for that which it is so calm.
Or perhaps not…
Eh well, I was afraid!
This thing is dangerous!
What? What did it occur?
How did you break that?
I just tried to make so that the water harvest is done more quickly.
The belt broke.
Is Ouais, it odd not?
It is because of your stupid force.
Good blood…
Can it be repaired?
Yes, one must stop and find spare parts.
In other words, I will not request anything any more from this type.
Usopp?
Can you use the other récolteuse water machine for me to bring some?
Of course!
Salt plague of Nami!
Why you do not do it yourself?
I felt food.
And you bastard, you have no feel responsibilities!
I said that I was sorry.
In losing one it is not large thing…
Nami-San, looks at!
Oh, the deliveryman of newspapers.
You two close it!!
Shit, cursed Nami…
But why the newspaper of the morning always arrives during the pause of midday?
Nothing there can. One sails on Grand Line, I recall you.
We should be grateful to have already information.
You are right on this point.
Did you find an article interesting?
Not, not!
Not really…
What?
Ca! Look at that Zoro!
What is there?
It is right a photograph of Navy.
Yes, but the guy on the photograph is not no matter who.
It is Coby!
Ouais!
Do Coby you say? It is the friend with whom you travelled front?
Well, what that known as?
Let us see seeing…
“The cruiser of the Garp vice-admiral arrived at the General headquarter of the Navy.
This photo was taken after their descent of Mountain Reverse.
The Garp vice-admiral posted his usual confidence in him.
But some young Navy seemed terrified. “
Here!
Then Coby succeeded in reaching Grand Line!
To start with the General headquarter of the Navy on Large Line,
it is not badly.
Of course, a Coby day will be the mayor of the Navy.
Pas le mayor, cretin!
An Officer recommended.
A Naval officer!
Yes, it is what I wanted to say.
Ouais, it must really give itself evil, him too!
Navy!
2000 pumps! Start!
100 crossings of cord!
200 turns!
All those which will not finish in the hour will have 100 turns of penalty!
Drive of fencing!
Do not release absolutely anything!
Does that go?
It is thus that the General headquarter of the Navy?
Well, they will not find us here.
Rest a little there please.
Ouais…. Afflicted…
He Coby.
What is there?
Don't you think only that we are not ready for this place?
You saw these guy over there, presently.
We are not far but we cannot do it yet.
There is an order in all that, you know.
We should return after us to be, at least, trained a little bit…
Yes, it is that! Let us do that!
Even if we leave, nobody…
Wait a little!
With what do think you, Helmeppo-San?
You were not to exceed your father?
Eh well yes… but…
If I were to make all the tricks here, I would die about it.
You do not wish it?
If you chose to do it…
I will become the Lord of the Pirates!
If you chose to become that…
It is the way which I chose. And for that…
And even if you were to die by beating you, isn't this because you had chosen it?
To beat me? It is not exaggerated a little?
You must fight!
Together with me.
Therefore, please, speaks again never again to flee.
“To flee” do you say?
You two!
You were not trying to stab me in the back?
Bandage little runts!
There is full with guy which would be glad to take your place.
If you want to escape, dispatch you and run.
Wait please!
We do not have any intention to flee!
Our determination brought us here.
Order to us to do anything and will do we it,
Garp vice-admiral!
You known as that you are ready with all to endure?
It is well what you said?
Your determination brought you here.
It is what you said?
Yes!
Then stop paresser here and turn over to work!
I let to you continue to supervise them.
Well!
What? The General headquarter of the Navy?
Yes, as the rumors say it,
the Garp vice-admiral is a little impulsive.
But, it, isn't this is nevertheless extraordinary?
Yes, it is what one says.
Therefore, it must have great waitings with regard to these deux-là.
Asshole! Asshole! Asshole! Asshole!
How did you can let them leave without anything to say?
Asshole! Asshole! Asshole! Asshole! Couill…
Rika… wants to still play with them.
I wanted to still speak to them…
I wanted to have a good meal of my hands to them.
I had even learned how to cook and
I did not even can say to them goodbye…
Euh, I…
Why were they to leave?
I include/understand! Forgive me!
Rika, forgives him.
They are well.
One day they will return,
as splendid commissioned Officers.
But really…
Will one become Marine by doing all that?
This old dog could do to us that for his hobby just.
A hobby?
Yes. To tire the jeunes gens must be the hobby of this old dog.
It is rather impulsive, therefore you do not believe that it is possible?
Your mouths, stupid volatile!
'is silvering, it fast this old croûton?
It is the Garp vice-admiral.
Did He, you hear?
They call it “Garp the terrible one! ”,
because everyone is afraid of him.
Eh well, its fists make more badly than those of Alvida…
Ca does not have anything to see!
Can you stop all these silly things?
Particularly when we are of guard…
I am always punished because of you.
Do not say that.
It is the “responsibility for the regiment”.
The responsibility for the regiment…
We, isn't this is friendly?
You say that only when that arranges you…
If you think it, why don't you work more seriously?
They is good, I will do it!
Not, finally, I from go away!
I want to return to my old lifestyle.
It about that, isn't this does not have there to speak now?
It is not similar to only become famous while being an elected Officer.
It is that!
What?
I cannot flee!
I should not slacken myself!
Therefore, it is possible only one to turn over to my old lifestyle:
by climbing the levels towards glory!
You do not believe?
What do you want to say by “You do not believe?” ?
Ca will not be also easy, you know.
We must do it gradually.
If you want that is easy for you…
What do you make?
Ca will not be used for nothing to wait there like a zatsuyou.
I will involve myself!
Oh not, not yet!
You cannot do that.
We are both exhausted by the work of this afternoon.
Go, will sleep!
I decided.
I will become famous and turn over to my old lifestyle.
I even will exceed my father.
Ca will occur like that!
Yes but…
Your body will not support it!
It is impossible! Impossible!
Impossible! Impossible!
If you insist, you will finish by you killing!
If I chose this way,
even if I must die about it, it is what I chose.
Isn't this?
I already decided.
To die would be easier.
If it is what I want to do, then I must do it!
I will also go far I can!
With more, Coby!
Wait please!
What is there, Coby?
What do I have says?
I swore that I will again not say anything any more pitiful.
You are right.
That does not depend on what one can or not to achieve, but of what one wants.
I have just decided.
Perhaps I do not have the same motivation as you but…
let us use this frame of mind together!
Ca suits me, small bastard!
Therefore, that will be a contest to know which will arrive there the first.
I hoped that you were going to say that.
But I prefer you to say it directly, I will not lose.
Ouais if you want.
I go there! With more!
He, does not leave me behind!
What do I have some to make?
You are not my friend or anything.
Who is concerned with what can arrive to you?
What is it supposed to mean?
You did not stop contradicting you!
1…
2…
1… 2…
1…
Here thus the 30 million Berrys for Luffy to the straw hat?
We must carry out a horrible pirate like him as fast as possible.
Completely.
Luffy-San on a required list…
Does Ca seem strange, not?
Cretin, the pirates are pirates.
If they get caught, they are carried out.
It is like that it goes.
I know it!
But you cannot classify it also easily.
Luffy-San is my friend, you know!
Sink cretin!
No Marine is the friend of a pirate!
Repeat never again that or you will be transfered Navy!
I know it already!
I will not tell it everywhere.
You have interest!
Leek!
Garp vice-admiral!!
I heard that you say something of interesting.
Can you speak to me about it?
It is which your friend?
Attention it is necessary to divide!
I you it redemande.
Summers you friends of Luffy to the straw hat?
I do not know for Helmeppo-San,
but for me, yes!
Even if we took different ways, he said to me that we would be always friendly!
You must probably know this,
but the Navy cannot let people like you proclaim such things.
Fortunately for you, I am the only one with being well-informed.
Do you want to be Navy?
Wait please!
I am perhaps the friend of Luffy-San but Helmeppo-San forever…
I am it! I am it!
And it is for that I am there!
Helmeppo-San?
Idiot, I believe that you should have asked it to me front.
It is the responsibility for the regiment!
The responsibility for the regiment.
And you Coby?
You do not want?
I want it!
Then stop jacasser and attack me!
Not yet!
Yes!
Insufficient!
Not yet…
We did not die yet.
Then you want to die at this point?
Now that we chose to become Navy,
if we die while testing, it is because we will have wanted it.
We will not give up now!
I am somebody who will become a Naval officer!
A Naval officer?
It is the funniest thing which I heard of the day!
Here, I am known for many things.
All people have something to say on my subject.
Since I brought you here, I made you work hard.
Today, I checked your true motivations.
Our true motivations?
Physically, I can see how much it was difficult for you.
But your mental is still too weak.
I checked your real motivations to see what hid behind.
Then, one was how?
I would recommend to you for your courage but
you are not yet ready to arrive there!
Forget the forts or the weak ones, you are not even that!
From now, you will involve yourselves even hard.
You prepare!
I will pass on “your friend”…
But mention its name never again.
Cherish right its memory.
Yes! Thank you very much, Garp vice-admiral!
Well! Allons-y!
Towards Little Garden…
Ouais…