Return the gold which you stole
in Papi Head of Diamond!
Gold?
You want to say that of the old Cricket?
GOOD-BYE, STRAW HAT!
WHAT THERE IS?!
OR YOU GO, STRAW HAT?!
Where?
In the sky!
Let us sail in the skies!
The rise of Knock-Up Stream
But what it manufactures?!
It is already the morning! The morning!
Forty six minutes of
delay on the agreed schedule!
One goes louper the current!
The weight of gold must
surely to slow down it!
It is too stupid to include
this factor in its calculations!
Not in fact… I believe that it
did not calculate anything of the whole.
You ace 100% reason.
Perhaps that it is
fact of beating downtown…
By this Bellamy?
If it were made beat I kill it
myself, even if it returns per hour!
It is what your problem at the end?
OHEEEE!
Here it is!
Super, it is of return!
I succeeded!
Hurry, Luffy!
It is necessary that the anchor is weighed!
Look at that!
It is a hercules!
I wasted a time
insane to find it!
A BEETLE KABUTO?!
ANY CA FOR CA?!
Ouah, it is terrible!
The Vogue-Merry, models flying!
IT FLIES!
OUAIP!
They did that for us!
Good in short.
I have like small
apprehension when I see that.
Ouais, me too.
Is necessary to say that a pigeon,
that flies better than a chicken.
It is not what I wanted to say!
Cretin!
Ok! Let us test this boat!
You are ready, the guys?!
Embark immediately
! You are not in advance.
Unless you prefer to let pass
your chance to go on the celestial island?
Simpleton.
Of agreement! Thank you for the boat!
It is them whom it is necessary to thank.
Thank you, the guy!
I give you my Hercules!
Really?!
Be too sympathetic for you!
You ES REALLY a NICE BLOKE!
Go, magne
to embark on your ship!
One will miss it!
One passes at the head! You
have that to follow us!
Quickly, Luffy!
Ouais!
The Gold City forever existed only
in the head of Norland, the liar.
You should make you with the idea that
the dreams are never carried out!
ALLIED FORCES SARUYAMA!
OUAIS!
You may find it beneficial to ensure!
No matter what it arrives,
you give to bottom for them!
OUAIS!
Go! It left!
One goes there, the guy!
OK!
Yes, Nami-san!
Small!
It is the hour of separations.
Ouais!
A thing is sure and certain.
Never nobody succeeded in proving that
the celestial island and the Gold City did not exist.
Ouais!
Ca can appear incredible,
some will make fun of you…
But one types oneself some!
Because it is that the adventure!
The adventure…
Exactly!
Thank you… for gold.
And made blunder of
not to fall from the sky!
With more, Papi!
Thank you for all, Cricket-san!
Owner! I am CERTAIN
how the Gold City exists!
Papi, is spared!
Interfere yourself your onions!
It is the morning!
Then? You see something?
Still not of ground in sight!
They really go
on the celestial island?
Ouais, it is what he said.
It will not be part of pleasure
to follow them until over there.
Then it is necessary that they are wedged front!
Luffy with the Straw hat.
A premium of 100 Million Berrys.
Listen! It is 7:00!
One should reach our
destination in the neighborhoods of 11:00!
According to what the Owner said…
The place where Knock-Up spouts out
Stream is different each time!
One must thus arrive over there in advance
to be able to locate the places exact!
Look at, look at!
One is a little with flock…
HE! YOU Me LISTENINGS OR NOT?!
Look at, Regardez, Regardez,
it recovered straight!
Eh Ben, what a funny of bird!
It cannot really look at
elsewhere that towards the South!
A compass would be said!
It is funny!
What did he say?
“I will turn the head in another
direction only for you emmerder! “
I put to you with the challenge!
It points North!
It does not support to be turned
elsewhere than towards the South.
HE, THE GUY!
STOP IRRITATING the BIG BOSS!
They is good, they are good!
It is right which my heart beats
chamade when they are unaware of me!
Ben what? What did one make?
Let us go, that is used for nothing of
to stress with any end of fields!
Let us remain Zen!
You can recall me because
which one is with flock?
It is not wrong!
Four will not be held
hours while stressing!
It is true.
Go, the guy, ahead
all, but with the cool one!
Ouaaiiiiis!           Ouaaiiiiis!
What a good weather!
Are Z' sure that goes?
It is what that?
Sky…
… is black!
Boss! Ca fears!
That there
it has?!
Darkness is in the train
to fall to South-west!
They are impérionimbus!
Ah ouais?! What time is it?
10:00!
It much earlier than is envisaged!
Ca fears…
Shoujou, you can do it?!
Outangs plungers, explore the funds!
Locate the current!
Then it is that a impérionimbus…
What?! What occurs?!
The impérionimbus arrive
more quickly than envisaged!
And one does not have yet
located the current!
Detected echo!
Enormous marine current with 12:00!
Gigantic creature detected with
09:00! Surely a monstre marin!
Vagueness with counter-current
detected with 10:00!
It is perhaps a swirl!
IT IS HELD!
All boats! Cape with 10:00!
It is there that the explosion will occur!
Locate the swirl
and do not give up!
What…?!
The waves are of
more in more violent!
ONE WILL CAPSIZE!
The EXPLOSION DOES NOT GO
TO DELAY! HANG you!
THE EXPLOSION?!
Madam Navigatrice!
What says the Log Poses?
It points right towards this cloud!
Is the celestial island just above?
The wind blows in the same direction.
The impérionimbus is directly thorough
towards the center of the swirl!
Hein, what a swirl?!
Where that?
It would be said that this time
it is the good one, my brother!
Ouais, apparently one will not be
disappointed by the extent of the explosion!
One will arrive there?!
Ouais, of course!
Hein?
One takes you along on
running of the swirl!
And then? What must one make?!
Follow the current!
You bring closer as much as possible to
center swirl and do not give up!
This enormous swirl?!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
I had never met
of the guy as insane as you.
One wants to go on the celestial island, papi!
Gold was… stolen!
I would be of return
before the lever du jour.
With more, Papi!
To speak about the dreams…
ONE SE WILL MAKE ABSORB!!!
It could have said that it
was necessary to return INSIDE!
Of made you not, Nami-san,
Robin-chan! I will protect you!
I never saw one
swirl of this size!
STOP! STOP CA!
HALF-TURN!
I WANT TO MAKE HALF-TURN!
Do not dream, Usopp!
It is too late.
Y' has of them one which is believed already up there…
CELESTIAL ISLAND, HERE US ARE!!
Go, the guy!
It is with you to play now!
Ouais, thank you for us
to have carried out up to now!
WAIT!
MADE ME NOT THIS BLOW IT!
I AI TOO FUNK!
I WANT TO RETURN, BROTHEL!
ONE WILL BURST!
NOBODY HAD SPEAKS to Me
Of a GIANT SWIRL!
It IS SWINDLES! SWINDLES!
AHH! IT MAKES ANY BLACK!
THE SWIRL US
ASPIRE MORE AND MORE!
One will be aspired, Luffy!
It is not yet too late!
You include/understand, hein?!
This swirl can all kill us!
This celestial island is not
how one dream in a dream!
A dream in a dream?
I see…
It rightly, Luffy!
I do not believe in being
able in any event!
An island which is only one
dreams in a dream?
I cannot let pass one
formidable adventure like that one!
Ca…
Ca amuses it…
He! While you
waste your time with râler…
Hein?
What still?
One arrives at the center of the swirl.
Quickly, Nami-san,
tighten yourself against me!
ONE FALLS!
Hein? It is finished?
How?
What did it occur?
This giant swirl…
What occurs?
Not…
It is not finished!
The center of the swirl has
touched the ocean floor.
It is not true…
STOOOP!
He, Zoro!
Look at!
You are held!
Luffy with the Straw hat!
It is the type of Mock Town!
Who that?
I come for the premium from 100 Million!
Go!
He, which they is these
? Friends with them?
No idea!
Why does it make so dark here?
My premium?
About which 100 Million you speak?
Then, do not be to you with the current…
Your head is put at price
to 100 Million Berrys!
And Zoro, the Hunter of Pirates!
You are worth 60 Million Berrys!
It is true!
There are new posters.
Zoro, you ace a premium now!
Hein?!
He, wait!
And me then?!
I have some too?
Heu… not.
Look at well!
Not.
I see.
It is because of
events of Alabasta…
But 100 Million…
100 Million!
Hear you that? I am worth 100 Million!
I am disappointed a little of my 60 Million!
Y' DOES NOT HAVE WHAT SE TO DELIGHT, YOU TWO!
He, the guy!
Remain concentrates!
Here…
Knock-Up Stream!
HOLD YOU READY!
What?
You stud or
take refuge in the cabins!
The OCEAN WILL EXPLODE!!
MADE BLUNDER!
THE BOAT WILL CAPSIZE!
HOLD GOOD!
DO NOT PASS OVER EDGE!!
The CELESTIAL ISLAND AWAIT YOU!
C-C' is what this is delirious?!
The boat sails in vertical
on the surface of the marine current!
It is brilliant!
HOW CAN YOU SAY CA?!
Wind…
Go! On the way towards the sky!
SINK, MERRY!
Wait a little! I fear
how it either not so simple!
Q - What
you want to say?!
That there
does it have?
You ace forgotten something in bottom?
The hull starts with
to detach from surface!
This train, one will be done
to eject before being crushed!
C-C' is quite pretty all that, but…
Q - what one
must make?!
It is already hardly if one
manage to remain studded!
It is what that?!
A monstre marin!
That which the swirl had absorbed!
Look at!
One is likely to join it
in step a long time!
He, Ho, perhaps well, but…
it is the blast of the explosion
who propelled us!
One can more nothing make!
Then it is really a disaster!
Y' HAS DEBRITS WHICH
WE FALL ABOVE!
VICTIMS OF KNOCK-UP STREAM!
One is lost!
One will fall, to be crushed
on the ocean and to die!
Set the sails, now!
It is a current sailor.
Not a simple water column!
It is a current ascending sailor!
And the breath which propelled us comes from a mixture of vapor and heat!
An ascending airstream!
If sea and wind are
part, I can sail!
Who it is the navigatrice of the crew?
It IS NAMI-SAN!
He, louts!
Made what Nami-san known as!
OK!
That somebody takes the bar,
the wind comes from starboard!
Align the boat on the current!
YES, CHIEF!!
Oh not!
One falls apart of surface!
One falls! Nami, one falls!
Do something, Nami!
One will arrive there!
ONE FLIES AWAY!!
BRILLIANT!
ONE FLOATS IN THE AIRS!
I dream or what?!
And here!
NAMI-SAN, YOU ES MARVELLOUS!
AND I LOVE YOU!!
Go! Sail beyond
imperceptible dream!
GO AHEAD!!
For little which one remains aligned
on the current with this wind…
one will go as high as it will be wanted!
He, Nami!
Does one go
to reach the celestial island?!
If it exists, it must
to find other side of this cloud!
Above the clouds…
I wonder what
we wait over there!
ONE ENTERS the IMPERIONIMBUS!
Let us gather all our dreams,
We leave to
search for our destinies…
Let us leave the compass,
it would delay us,
Let yourself pack,
and take the bar!
Even an old chart with the treasure…
is not any more one legend if
you prove his veracity!
Let us forget simply our own concern,
let us remain in symbiosis
ones others…
and let us not think of it any more!
Let us gather all our dreams,
We leave to
search for our destinies…
The pocket filled with parts,
And do you want to be my friend?
We are, us
sums… of the voyage!