To have fortune, fame and
power,
the king of pirates
rules the whole world!
Before he was beheaded, Gold Roger said:
"Send everybody out to sea."
"Do you want my fortune?
"I can give it all to you.
"But you have to search
the whole world for it!"
All the men chasing dreams
along the "Grand Line".
It means the time has come,
the time for all pirates!
Original Manga:
Eiichiro Oda
(published in Shonen Jump)
Going to search for our desires
(Based on the "Shonen Jump"
Manga by Eiichiro Oda)
Compasses only cause delays
Filled with excitement,
I take the helm
If we can prove the
dusty old treasure map
Then it's not a legend anymore!
It's alright if our personal problems
Get on someone else's nerves
Because we think about them too much
Gathering up all of our dreams
And going to search for our desires
A coin in the pocket,
We are!
You are nothing more than
a filthy pirate's son.
How dare you say I am low...
I am sorry for you, Usopp.
You must hate his guts.
You must hate you irresponsible
and selfish father
who values money
more than you!
Stop saying bad things
about my father!
...Then I will be able
to inherit the money.
Hey you!
Don't kill Kaya!
(Episode 11)
"Revealing the Conspiracy!
The Pirate Caretaker, Captain Kuro"
(Episode 11)
"Inbou o Abake!
Kaizoku Shitsuji Captain Kuro"
(Based on manga
ch.26: "Captain Kuro's Plan",
ch.27: "Information Based",
and ch.28: "Half Moon Night")
The captain's late.
So is Luffy.
He was very frustrated.
Whenever he's in a bad mood,
he goes to the beach.
Captain!
What's this?
Luffy's not with him.
Captain!
Whoa!
Where's Luffy?
Wasn't he with you
at the beach?
Is he still angry about
what the butler said
about his father?
Search me.
I don't think so!
Did you see his face?
Something must've
happened at the beach!
He's pale as a ghost!
Something ain't right!
Hey!
How can I get to the beach?
I smell trouble!
Something going on
at the beach!
Time for Usopp's pirates
to take action!
I know!
How do I get there?
Everybody listen!
The pirates are coming!
They're coming
tomorrow morning!
Run for your lives!
Everyone!
What are you waiting for?
Hey Usopp!
That's enough!
That's it for today!
No, no!
It's the truth this time!
That's what you always say!
If you were so honest
like Klahadore,
we would believe you!
Nobody will believe him.
Let's do it tomorrow morning, Django.
Attack when the day breaks.
Bastard!
Now I know why they ignored me!
He knows no one believes me!
Here it is...
The special glasses you ordered
from the optician in the next town.
I brought them for you.
It's perfect!
Thanks so much for your help.
It is a present, isn't it?
Yes.
Tomorrow is the 3rd anniversary
of Klahadore coming to our house.
He takes a good care of me.
- Klahadore must be glad.
- He is.
Everyone, believe me!
The pirates are coming
tomorrow morning!
If we'd taken what
he said seriously...
...we would have
escaped a hundred times!
Trust me!
Run away!
You will get yourselves killed!
It's true!
You have nowhere
to run this time!
Bastards!
Run!
Don't let him escape!
Here it is.
The captain always comes
here to calm down.
It's kind of cozy here.
The straw-hat man is not here.
It's very dangerous!
Be careful, Nami.
Hey, look!
What?
I found the straw-hat man!
He's upside-down!
Luffy, what's wrong?
- He fell down.
- And died!
No wonder the Captain
behaved like that!
Quiet!
That jerk.
Good morning!
Usopp?
I thought you're not
coming anymore.
Get out now, Kaya!
Or you will be killed!
What's wrong?
You've been cheated!
That butler is actually a pirate!
Wait a second, is this a joke?
It is not!
I heard him myself!
Klahadore infiltrated
your house for your wealth.
He acted like a butler
the last three years.
What he wanted was your wealth.
What are you talking about, Usopp?
He says his pirate crew
will be here tomorrow morning!
He's a wicked guy!
Run away immediately!
What you just said
was too frightening...
...but you shouldn't have
lied about that.
This is not your style.
No, it's true!
True!
It's really true!
What?
Miss Kaya is going to be killed?
The village will be under attack!
Is it true?
That's what he says.
But why are you are sleeping here?
I don't know myself!
I was standing over the cliff.
Why am I here?
No wonder he's so nasty!
So that's why the captain ran off
with a grim face!
Isn't that good to have heard about it?
We can run away safe.
The enemies are stupid!
Right!
Then we better go now!
Yes, go pack your belongings!
And hurry!
Oh no!
What's wrong?
Go buy something to eat
before the butcher runs away!
That's not the problem.
Usopp?
What's your adventure story today?
Today...
Yes!
I'll tell you what happened
when I was 5 years old.
I fought with a goldfish
that lived in south seas.
Goldfish?
You were battling with a goldfish?
Yes!
It was so big,
even your aquarium
isn't big enough for it!
First of all,
its poop was really huge.
I thought it was land and I
even moored my ship to it!
It looked fake.
Sounds fake, right?
But it was real.
Then I started a
fire to dry my clothes.
Big mistake.
Why?
The fish was almost frightened to death.
The fire was burning the fish.
How did it do?
It had no choice, I guess.
Because it was almost burned
and became a grilled goldfish!
I...
I meant to like...
The lie you made...
Why didn't you say so?
No!
I don't intend to take
revenge on Klahadore.
Why?
Why do you say so?
Kaya, I...
Miss!
What happened?
Run as fast as you can, Kaya!
Don't do that, Usopp!
Release her!
You must trust me!
Flee this village now...
...before the butler returns!
Stop it!
Let's go!
You'll see it tomorrow!
Hurry!
Please do as I say!
That's awful!
Take your hands off Miss Kaya!
Leave him alone!
Catch him!
He's kidnapping Miss Kaya!
How come...
no one trusts me?
Usopp.
Miss, are you okay?
Crew, thanks for your help.
It's been 3 years
since the last time we met.
When this plan is
successfully accomplished...
I'll give gifts for everyone
as a tribute.
Tomorrow morning,
we destroy the village!
Long live the Captain!
Who are you?
I am Usopp.
I'm a brave sea warrior.
They told me
that you're not feeling well.
Let me tell you some stories
and pluck up your courage.
Leave me alone!
Or I'll yell for help!
I know it's not my business.
It happened when I was 3...
I saw a whale lying down
and I tried to help him.
Whale?
Yep, a gigantic whale!
It seemed to have a sore throat.
I walked inside its mouth,
but I was mistaken for food!
Let's do it tomorrow morning, Django.
Attack when the day breaks.
Captain!
Hi guys!
Hi!
You're still alive!
Still alive?
Yes, I just got up!
He was in a deep sleep.
Don't worry about him, Captain,
we already know!
Tell everyone
about the pirates!
Tell everyone?
That's awful!
That's what you always say!
If you were so honest
like Klahadore,
we would believe you!
I'm lying again!
I hate that butler,
so I portrayed him as a pirate!
The straw-hat man
was in cahoots with the captain!
What's up?
Captain, I don't like
what you did.
Me either.
>> Me too.
Even if the butler was so nasty,
the Captain should never
make up stories about anyone.
I used to respect the captain.
- Captain, I was wrong about you.
- So was I!
Let's go home.
It's about time for dinner.
What are we having today?
There.
That oughta do it.
Why did you do it?
Because I am a liar.
No one would ever believe me.
I was too naive.
But still, that was the truth.
The pirates are coming, aren't they?
Yes, they are coming.
But everyone thought
that I was lying.
They thought that
tomorrow's gonna be
another peaceful day.
So I'd like to fight with the pirates!
Make the whole thing a lie!
That's what I'm supposed to do!
I got shot in the arm!
I got chased by a broom!
But this is my village!
I love it so much!
I want to protect everyone!
You are such a hypocrite.
You sent your friends home
so that you could come alone.
Don't forget, The treasures belong to me!
Okay, we are in!
You're willing to join me?
Why?
How big is the enemy's crew?
You look scared.
No, I'm not!
I don't care how many do they have!
Because I'm the brave Captain Usopp!
This is for real!
Our enemy is Kuro's Pirates!
So what?
You got a problem with that?
Do you? Do you?
We are not laughing at you.
We just think you're good.
I just feel sympathy,
though I'll risk my life to help you!
You'll... do this for me?