Help me...
Don't you dare make my navigator cry!
( Pinweel )
GOMU GOMU NO KAZAGURUMA!
Whoa! What the?
Those who have the powers of the
Devil's Fruit are dead weights!
But in this situation, even a normal
person would sink, wouldn't they?
He can't be... into the sea!?
GOMU GOMU NO PISTOL!
You bastard!
This is bad...no strength to move!
LUFFY DROWNING!
ZORO VS OCTOPUS HATCHAN!
What do you think? Interesting game, isn't it?
We'll see how long that rubberman can last.
Or will you guys die before he does?
This is terrible, Johnny!
Luffy-aniki's stuck underwater!
In the water, he can't do anything to save himself!
I'll beat this jerk's ass real quick,
Then I'll save you, Luffy!
TAKO HACHI BLACK!
My hair! You bastard!
I'm gonna...
l mean, it's only hair, it'll grow back.
Roronoa Zoro, you can never beat me!
Because l have six hands.
lsn't this cool? lsn't it wonderful?
You octopus bastard!
Tako-san-ren-shin-ken-shira-ha-dori!
Ow! That hurt!
l don't have time to play around with you!
This isn't good...
He's..?
Getting distracted by him will bring your death!
The fish fighting against the cook!?
We're running out of time...
Quit struggling! This is pointless!
Tako Hachi..... Number... 9.
What's with you? Get your ass down here!
Nyu~
You freakin' octopus...
That octopus bastard, he's just wasting time!
If we go in the water now, we'll get
dragged down to the bottom!!
But if we wait, Luffy-aniki is gonna die!
We've got to think of something!
Wait a minute!
You guys are severely wounded. If you go
into the water, what good can you do?
You'll never make it.
l'll go save that rubber boy.
You...you're going?
His survival is the key to win this fight.
I know it.
I'll go with you!
Me too!
I'm going!
No!
We can't go in a crowd, the mermen will notice.
There's no reason to endanger their fight.
Gen-san!
This is the only way we can do it.
I can handle it.
Are you alright with that?
Forgive us... thank you!
We're counting on you! Please hurry!
Wait!
Gen-san, l'm going too.
But Nojiko, your hurts...
They're fighting for my little sister!
Gen-san!
Okay. Come on.
Hurry!
Right!
I'm sorry... If onIy we had more strength...
We'II entrust Aniki to you.
You freakin' fish bastard!
Roronoa Zoro, can l ask you one thing?
I've heard that you fight with three swords,
why do you only have one now?
One is just fine! You're still gonna lose!
Hey, shut up! I haven't gotten serious yet!
Truth is human swordsmen don't
stand a chance against me.
lt'll surprise you! Astound you! Shock you!
Shit...
The pain's kicking in again, at the worst time...
Fever's getting worse, too...
I thought I could just waIk it off...
Nyu?
Huh?
Shit! l knew it. You haven't recovered from...
The wound that Hawk-eyes gave you..!
Aniki!
What's this? Pretending to be sick
is a good strategy, very good!
But I won't fall for that!
Roronoa Zoro! Let me show you my true skill!
Behold, my real skill! Six-sword fighting style!
Hey! Don't fall over!
Don't insult me!
Aniki!
I knew it! He's been enduring it all this time!
You're right!
Those were wounds that would keep a normal person
from walking for half a year
if they didn't kill him first!!
What did you say?
I knew it was strange that he could
fight with such a straight face!!
Stupid, stupid bastard...
Didn't l tell you to pay attention?
l'm a 40th Level Merman Karate Master!
Huh? What was that?
Did someone just fly through here?
Oh, Aniki?
Cook-aniki!
Cook-aniki!!
lt's over now, Arlong-san.
What should we do with Roronoa Zoro?
Toss his ass into the sea.
How pathetic...
How boring...
Nyu?
lt's over?
But they really did make a mess around here...
That's no big deal.
lt's alright as long as Arlong Park still stands.
You're right.
You bastard! Roronoa Zoro!
He was scared to death before
l got to show my skill!
I would've been so famous if
you had fallen by my blades!
Well, it doesn't matter.
Humans still can't compete against me
and my wonderful, amazing six-sword
style! You can't touch me!
That's enough, Hachi.
I understand how you feel,
but if you get serious, it might get dangerous.
You want to destroy Arlong Park?
Huh? Huh? Oh yeah, l'm sorry.
l just forgot myself for a minute there...
It's fine, forget it.
Six-swords style, huh?
You're full of crap.
Aniki!
Roronoa Zoro!
Let me just make one thing very clear, Octopus.
There is someone that l must meet again.
And until that day...
Not even Death himself can take my life away!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Shit! How fast can this long-nose run?
His speed and stamina are incredible... Chu~
If I can distract even one of Arlong's guys...
It should help Luffy and the others out!
What agreat idea, Usopp-sama!
You're so dependable and loyal, aren't
you? But thats a gift, isn't it?
Huh? He's not following me anymore?
Damn, that's too bad!
Looks like l left him in my dust...
He may look like a fish in water,
but he's just a turtle on land!
Heehee... Turtle..!
Yeah, yeah!! Turtle, turtle!
If you really think you can catch me, try, try!
I'll dust your ass again, you lazy, lazy turtle, yeeeah!
Wouldn't that be you?
The one who's being lazy, I mean.
Wait!
He's onIy been drowned for a whiIe.
If we can get him back to the surface,
we can resuscitate him.
Shit! This cement is too hard.
I can't swing very weII underwater...
Gen-san, we have to hurry!
No use. It's too hard to break.
We couId reaIIy use an air canister,
There's no way we can take the
bIock up to the surface...
That's it!
He's still alive, that guy!
Aniki! Cook-aniki!
That fish bastard's punch is Level 40?
Then the shitty old man's kicks I always
took must've been Level 400.
What's with you, Roronoa Zoro?
Why do you keep pushing yourself to go on?
I don't think you can defeat me
and my six swords as you are.
I think anyone in the world would say the same...
Shut up, it's none of your business...
This isn't good... Aniki's condition...
The fever's probably making him lose consciousness.
He's delirious.
If that wound opens again, he'll die without a doubt.
But he doesn't have time to think about that now!
Right! If there's anyone who knows that, it's Aniki!
l'll show you...
my San-tou-ryu...
Nyu?
Yosaku, Johnny! Lend me your swords!
Of course, Aniki!
Catch!
Shit... I'm Iosing it.
How many more minutes can I hang on?
Aniki, here they come!
Don't you want to use them?
Hah! Now you'll see the barrier that two-handed
humans will never surpass.
Roku-tou-ryu!
Aniki, watch out!
Tako Ashi Kiken!
Aniki!!
SAN-TOU-RYU...
TOUROU HAGASHI!
(Bleeding the Wolf!)
NYU~ !!
Got him!
The six swords didn't touch him! Aniki's awesome!
That takes such concentration...
and persistence as well!
How could this be?
I'm reaIly mad now! I'm going to kill you!
Just think about it normally, would you?
You cannot match six swords when
you can only carry three yourself.
Don't you get it!?
Normally? That's a major miscalculation.
What burdens you?
After you become strong, what do you wish to find?
I will... I will become stronger together with her!
'Til my name is heard even in the Heavens!
I'll become stronger!
'Til I become the strongest in the
world, the King of Swordsmen!
Three swords...
Six swords...
Numbers don't matter!
I may only have three swords, but yours
wiII NEVER be as heavy as mine!!
The weight, is it?
Now I understand.
Your swords are heavier? Eh?
But don't think that'll help,
each of my swords weighs 300kg, you know!
They're much heavier and more powerful
than any of your swords, you moron!
It's useless talking to an idiot...
Roku-tou-ryu, Tako Tsubo no Kamae!
Shin Shun!
Takoage!
Shit!
TAIKAI!
That's dirty! Aiming for his wound!
Watch out!
Aniki!!
Aniki's gonna be killed!
You won't hit the ground alive.
Roku-tou-ryu, Ougi!
Roku-tou no WA-RU-TSU!
Touch these for second and you're mincemeat!!
You don't have a chance!
Aniki!
The pain...!
That jerk, he spun with me in the air
and did somersaults on my swords!
Then he cut my hands like some kind of circus trick!
Now I'm REALLY PISSED, and
I'm going to destroy you!
Aniki...
he's in so much pain...
That probably opened his wound again.
Ah... if only I could suffer in his place!
A wound that'd make an ordinary
man unconscious...
l won't lose to it.
Roku-tou-ryu! Tako Tsubo no Kamae!
This is the end!
A wound that would kill an ordinary person...
I won't lose to it!
Shin Shun!
To face one who is extraordinary, Hawk Eyes...
l can't allow myself to be ordinary!
TATSUMAKI!!
Hachi!
How?
San-tou-ryu...
How could..?
Octopus jerk...
Now do you understand...
How much heavier my swords are?
You satisfied?
Enough tears.
Enough talk.
lt's time to make up my mind!
l've got to go!
They're all fighting.!
I'm sorry, Octopus, but I'm not impressed.
I have to hurry and rescue Luffy.
Aniki, look out!
You fiend! How could you do that to Hachi?!
Bastard!
Yeah, you thought you'd gotten
rid of me that easily, eh?
Hm? I didn't think there was anyone
who could stand up to my punch,
not in all of East Blue.
Oh, I bet you'll find plenty who could.
Especially in a certain sea restaurant.
You've been fooled.
Aniki, don't move!
Hey, stop!
In your condition, your ass is as good
as dead if you go underwater.
Shut the hell up!
He's almost done for!
He can't wait for your fight to finish!
Yeah, I know about that.
I know there's no time left.
That's why I'm stopping you.
You're the one who should shut the hell up!
So you don't complain about me doing THIS!
Interesting! He wants to challenge
a merman in the water?
I've never met a bigger fool!
You dumbass!
An underwater battle is just what they want!
That's... l'm pretty sure he's the
head of Cocoyashi Village...
His neck's stretched out...
I'm sorry... this is all we can do to help.
This way, if we can at least get your head
out of the water, we can resuscitate you.
Come on, breathe, it's not too late yet!
Come on, l can't hold on much longer!
They couldn't move the stone,
so they moved his head.
They need me to break the stone to get him free.
Then that old man can take care of it from there.
Gyojin Karate, Wan Tou Giri!
This is getting interesting...
What do you humans intend to do next?
Come back to life...
Please, hurry!
He's so stubborn!!