The Voice of Vivi is lost!
A hero with ground!
Who are you?
The Tsumegeri guards.
These contusions!
They drank the water which destroys the life!
They drank prohibited water!
They have nothing any more but a few minutes to live!
If you decided to die,
I, isn't this does not even need to fight you?
Inhuman…
I cannot think of a better example of stupidity.
Thus you also…
… you want to die…
… for the others?
Wait!
Kohza-San…
The battle is finished!
Calm your anger and deposit your weapons!
The royal army does not wish to fight longer!
Really, Kohza-San?
Yes!
The war is…
KOHZA!!!
Kohza!!!
An astonishing city will be built…
… one will make this country richer!
Certainly…
Tit do not fight…
… army rebels!
Kohza!
Kohza-San!
My God!
Kohza!
THEY HAVE CAR ON KOHZA-SAN!
KILL them!
OUAIS!
Works baroque!
Dumb!
Why you drawn ace on Kohza!?
Army rebels…
Listen…
What?
Sand starts to blow!
Army rebels!
They draw us above!
These cowards!!!
From which does this swirl of sand come!?
I see more anything!
Bandage cowards!
Stop drawing with the aveuglette!
But what occurs, brothel?
Nothing of such as panic.
Us, Works Baroque, naps infiltrated on the two sides.
Not!
Hey! Hold good.
You invite that “to return the weapons”?
They raised the drapeau blanc to tighten us a trap!
Then it is as that which the royal army fights?
Bandage dirty cowards!
I beg you!
You stop all!
Do not fight!
Listen to me!
Have-stop…
Army rebels…!
This battle is…
Will Ca go?
Answer the shootings, royal army!
Stop!
Stop, please…
Please…
Stop…
You fought well, my expensive…
But…
Your voice will not reach anybody.
Then it is thus that?
Course, Vivi!
Flee this monster!
Not!
You created this plugging sand cloud.
But…
But if I can prevent this bomb from exploding in 15 minutes,
I can still save some lives!
“If I make Ci, I will stop the rebellion.”
“If I do that, I will stop the rebellion.”
Open the eyes, Princesse.
Your puffing idealism disgusts me.
Those which can speak about ideals, they are those enough powerful to reach them.
And of done you not part!
I of insane, if that disgusts you!
I will not give up my ideal!
You will be able to never include/understand!
I am the Princess of this country!
I will never lower the arms!
You lack charm.
I will never give up!
I…
… will save this country.
Vivi!
More than 15 minutes before the bomb explodes.
The reinforcements of the army rebels still gather per hour when one speaks.
And, just as your cruel destiny, they go right in the middle of the disaster.
If you had been able to inform the soldiers for the bomb,
even in a general panic, you could have saved of them thousands, even tens of thousands.
Made not that!
Please, not…!
Crocodile!
Your desperate attempts to save everyone failed!
Consequently from what your loved people will be destroyed!
Beginning with the end,
you did everything me to laugh!
All, as far as you are, in this country!
You have spy my organization during 2 years.
Good job!
It is me! You do not recognize me?
It is comprehensible…
I lost a little weight.
But, at the end, you did not stop anything.
“I will stop the rebellion.”
“I will save the kingdom.”
All that your stupid idealism did…
it is to increase the number of victims!
I say it once again to you:
you cannot save this country.
Good voyage, Princess.
Impossible…
Crocodile!
Luffy-San…
Straw hat!?
One succeeded!
Luffy-San!
Pell!
It remains little of time before a bomb explodes on the place…
Everyone will die!
Nobody hears me…
If that continues, this country goes…
Do not worry you!
You very well are heard.
I say to you… that my wounds are quite worse!
Oh keep silent yourself. Be to you a man, then stops feeling sorry for you!
My leg is wounded.
I cannot hold upright!
Oh, I will disappear…
Liar!!!
Made attention with you, Luffy-Kun.
I ate tons of meat.
I feel full with energy!
I…
… will not lose once again.
How it could survive moving sands with its wounds…
LUFFY ALIVE EAST!!!
Tony-Kun!
Qu qu Quoiiii?
Luffy!?
Vivi is there too!!
You see!? I had said to you that it would be left there!
I never doubted him!
I see!
One would not have believed, considering your head.
Usopp-San, Sanji-San!
What did it occur, Vivi-Chan?
You are wounded?
Usopp!
Nami-San, Mr. Bushido…
You all are in life!!
Who asked you to manufacture a toy to make turns of magic??
I KNEW THAT YOU COULD HOLD UPRIGHT, BROTHEL!
NAMI-SWAN!
M- but, there are techniques of combat, also…
One will speak again about it when all that is finished!
Vivi?
What occurs here?
Why sand whirls everywhere?
, Salts you bastard!
How did you can let Nami-San be wounded?
I will kill you!
It is well!
Chopper, grants to me a favor.
Bury my dead-man in the wild, vast and untamed extents.
Its wounds mortals were suddenly fatal to him!
Afflicted, you all.
I… lost against him.
This is why…
I will not reperdrai!
You undertake the remainder!
Go, releases from there.
If you cannot beat it…
THEN WHICH WILL BE ABLE IT, CRETIN?
I will finish some with that.
All this history!
OUAIS!
You all…
I still have friends here…
DUMB!!!
It does not matter the number of engagements,
you will be never able to reach me!
Or perhaps do you still want to finish impaled?
Who is this!?
It…!?
Marunoko = Circular saw
It struck Crocodile!
Upright!
It is the water of Yuba, widespread on your hand, which showed me…
… that you cannot change into sand when are wet to you.
You ace fear of water.
It is for that you stolen ace the rain.
Now I will burst you the head.
Thus let us start.