Whoo-hoo!
What a huge town!
Lots of pirates stock up at this town before
heading out to the Grand Line.
You can get pretty much whatever you want here!
Alright! For my upcoming great adventure,
I'm gonna need to get some cool stuff.
I'll bet there's lots of good food to check out here.
And lots of good women!
There's something I wanna buy too.
Oh? And how would you do that?
You're totally broke, aren't you?
Okay! I'm gonna check out the execution platform!
I want to see it! The place where
the Pirate King died!!
Hey, hey! We haven't decided on
a place to meet back up yet!
Man... he's hopeless.
The Pirate King was born here, and he died here tool
He probably even walked down this very street!
YAHOO!
THE TOWN OF BEGINNING AND THE END
ARRIVAL AT LOGUETOWN
How's this?
Oh! It looks wonderful on you miss!
This?
OH! Elegant, miss!
Elemental, miss!
And this?
An elegy!
Will you be purchasing all of them today?
Nope, none of them.
I'm looking for something more casual.
Please come again soon!
Oh...! A tasty aperitif...
OH!! A lovely two-item dish!
This town is just full of delicious foods to sample!
Andyou don't even know which
to try first, you sily dog, you!
l think I just found the MAIN DISH!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Too cool! This is crazy!
This place is full of cool stuff!
Welcome, sir!
All of the items you see on display...
...were used by pirates who sailed the Grand Line!
These are valuable, special items, of course.
You mean... these are all things they used
in their adventures on the Grand Line?
We aim to cater to the needs
of true warriors of the sea.
We are so glad to have your business!
So how about it?
This is a gun that was actually used by Gold Roger!
WHAT!? It was Gold Roger's?
Yes!
Whoa-ho-ho!
Sir! What do you think?
Show me more stuff, please!
With pleasure!
Captain Smoker! There's an alert!
We've received notification from
Marine Headquarters...
That Monkey D. Luffy and his band of
pirates are headed towards Loguetown!
He's the East Blue pirate with a reward
on his head for $30,000,000!
30 million, huh?
Want me to congratulate him or something?
He is the one who defeated Don
Krieg and the Merman Arlong!
Shut the hell up!
Damn your yelling... you broke it.
Forgive me.
Well, forget it. I have my own way of doing things.
I work at my own pace. You know?
Y-Yes sir.
So, you were saying?
Sir
It seems there are a band of pirates
headed for the city today... Sir.
What are you getting all worked up for?
Since I've been at this post,
has there ever been a pirate that's been able
to get out of this city once they've entered?
Well, no...
Then don't get all nervous.
I'll take care of it, at my own pace.
Yes...
Reporting sir!
Pirates have been sighted at the harbor!
Please come to confirm the situation!
It's got to be the Luffy Pirates, sir!
There weren't any others mentioned in the bulletin!
30 million, huh?
That's something I'd like to see.
Huh?
Just thinking out loud. Forget it.
Don't you need this?
Captain, please request backup.
Don't need it.
But! The supposed strength of the enemy...
Shut the hell up.
Don't tell me how to do things!
I'm very sorry sir!
Whatever, where's Tashigi?
Oh... actually, she's been out since this morning.
She missed the morning drills.
That ditzy girl... Where'd she go off to now?
Yay! Three scoop ice cream!
Hey, hey! Careful you don't fall when you run!
C-captain Smoker!
My ice cream...
I'm so sorry! My kid...
I'm so sorry! I'm sorry! Sorry! Sorry!! SORRY!!
Sorry, kid.
Looks like my pants ate your ice cream.
Here, go buy yourself five scoops.
Let's go.
Aye.
Th-thank you so much!
Thank you.
Clean the place out, m'hearties! Leave
not a bloomin' penny thar!
For ye see, that these provisions be necessities,
for Gary-sama of the Crescent Moon
to become the Pirate King!
So make sure ye get it all!
Oi...
Huh?
Which one's the boss?
Who the hell are you?
You the bastard known as Monkey D. Luffy?
Let's see how tough you are,
since you're stupid enough...
...to show that ugly face in my town.
What? You've gotta be kidding me!
Get him, lads!
Captain Smoker?
Yeah! You know, he's one of the top
soldiers from Marine Headquarters.
This town used to be full of pirates
heading for the Grand Line.
But since the Captain was stationed here,
every pirate who comes into the
city ends up in the slammer.
He's not normal. They say he's a monster.
They even say he has the power
of the Devil's Fruit, you know.
The Devil's Fruit?
A job well done, Captain!
You finished off the Luffy Pirates in record time!
Are you blind, or just stupid?
How could these losers be Luffy's?
If these pansies are worth 30 million,
then it's the end of the world.
T-Then what about Luffy?
He'll show himself soon enough.
And then the fun will start.
Huh?
How did I end up back at the harbor? How?
HEY!
Is that another one of those idiots?
I don't think so...
What luck! Can you tell me how to
get to the execution platform?
The execution platform?
Yeah, I think I'm lost...
I've never seen your face around before.
Yeah! I just came here today.
Man what a big city!
It's totally different from Fuusha Village.
Why are you looking for the gallows?
I want to see it.
The place where the Pirate King died!
You don't know?
Whatever.
Wait.
Look where the smoke points.
Ooh! Over there?
Thanks!
Shit! So much!
They're too damn expensive!
You need a loan?
That's fine!
But you'll need to pay me back 3
times over with interest, okay?
I can't borrow any more money from that woman.
But one sword isn't enough for Grand Line.
- So, you ain't with that monster today?
What do I do?
Excuse me, you're being rude!
Huh?
Shut up!
Thanks to him, our boss is locked up in jail!
Have you not given up?
No way!
You chicken or something?
We're going to send you back to him in pieces!
I understand.
I will have to fight with you.
'That so, baby?
Don't make me laugh!
What the hell can a little woman like you do?
Take this!
Whoa, she won!
That was so cool, lady!
Guess she can't handle her own strength!
My glasses...
Glasses...
Hey. Looking for these?
I-I'm sorry!
Thank you so much.
My glasses!
I-I-It was an accident...!
Those are expensive, you know!
Why would you do such a cruel thing?
But I didn't mean to...!
Please replace them!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Man, I'm beat...
I was trying to get to the execution platform,
but this doesn't look like the right way at all.
Oh well, I'm bound to run into it eventually.
Lets see, which way...
Gold Roger?
Old man, are you the owner?
The sign outside says ''Gold Roger''.
Is that the name of this place?
Get out.
This isn't a place for kids.
And we're closed right now.
Out of business?
We're not out of business! It's just after hours!
Now get out!
I was just curious about the name...
I'm lost.
I wanted to go see the execution platform.
Can you tell me how to get there?
What's that thing on the table?
It's a skull! It's huge!
This is the skull of a man known as the ''Killer Giant.''
A man who killed hundreds of pirates.
He was a devil.
But Gold Roger fought and killed him.
Gold Roger did?
It's a famous tale!
He was a big, rough guy, with a big sword!
The battle was decided pretty quickly.
This gash is what killed him.
But he was really something.
His last words were..
''Roger. No one can touch you.''
''I praise you as the eternal pirate.''
Awesome! Cool!
King, of the Eric Pirates...
The famous gunner Silver-Silver...
All were very dangerous men.
Yet before Roger, they were like scared little babies.
Wanna hear more?
Yeah!
Nowadays youngsters don't usually
take an interest in this stuff.
I don't care, just tell me more!
Pesky kid!
Gold Roger...
Back then...
No, still today...
He's the only pirate who truly didn't
fear the dangers of the Grand Line.
Because you see, the area known as the Grand Line,
is a place where ships disappear
and are never seen again.
Navigation is said to be impossible.
Because people are so scared of it,
they seldom come close to that cursed ocean.
Old man. I want some more rum.
The whole bottle.
You seem to be enjoying yourself, Roger.
Yeah, that's for sure.
Because after this, I'm taking off for
a little stroll through the Grand Line.
I'm so excited. I can't help myself.
Hey! Are you really headed for that cursed ocean?
Why not? You saying I can't?
Well, not really, just...
I won't stop you, but please, don't go there.
They say it's a place no one ever returns from!
That's exactly why I want to go.
So, some more rum please, another
bottle would be good.
Saying that, he cleared out all the booze in the bar...
and set off the next morning, as though
there was nothing to fear.
Later on, when I heard he had
conquered the Grand Line,
I was so surprised, I even forgot my age for a bit!
But now, everyone has passed on.
Roger was executed at the gallows
here in town twenty years ago.
And from that day, everyone's been going around
with the audacity to call themselves pirates.
They even call this ''The Great Pirate Age.''
But it's all just a bunch of rubbish...
Cowards.
Less and less people are daring
to sail the Grand Line.
And so, that is the reason this
place will be closed down.
I'm... going to the Grand Line.
Huh?
He was cool, huh? Gold Roger.
Pirates should try to be like him.
That's why I went out to sea...
...to go to the Grand Line and find One Piece.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
That's a crazy thing to say!
How could you say that, here in this place?
What? But I'm just telling the truth.
Kid, after having a customer like you,
Don't do that for me.
It's decided. There's nothing you
can do to change my mind.
It's been a long time since I had a customer.
Drink's on the house.
I don't drink.
Is that so? Then how about this?
Kanpai to him, to the Eternal Pirate King.
To the Eternal Pirate King!
So it's you, huh?
The usual greeting, eh?
Not a nice way to treat an old customer.
You ruined my business.
I don't feel like joking around with you.
You shouldn't think of me as
someone who betrayed you.
It's not my fault this is the business you're in.
The pirates today are all weaklings.
That's the real problem.
A customer, huh? That's pretty unusual.
I'd like some rum.
We don't serve your kind here.
That's discrimination, you know.
Today is a special day.
Isn't it?
That's the stuff.
What happened on that day, even
now, is so clear in my mind.
Roger, in his last moments.
This is Main Street.
Wonder if Gold Roger walked along this street...
That's right.
It was a hot, muggy day just like today.
On his way to the execution platform,
even though his hands were bound,
he carried himself with pride.
Wealth, Fame, Power.
The Man who had Everything
in this World... Gold Roger.
Walking towards his death...
He held himself high, like a proud warrior.
Inherited Will,
The Destiny of the Age,
The Dreams of its People.
As long as people continue to pursue
the meaning of Freedom,
These things will never cease!
Have you any last words?
Can you take this off?
It's, chafing me.
I cannot do that!
Why would I run away now?
Hmm. That's a little saddening..
Well, go ahead and finish it.
HEY! PIRATE KING!
What did you do with your treasure?
It's somewhere on the Grand Line, isn't it?
You have it, don't you?
The greatest treasure in the world!?
Please, Keep your mouth!
Your one special treasure?
ONE PIECE!
My treasure?
All right! That's enough!
If you want it, I'll let you have it.
Go look for it.
I left all of it at that place!
EXECUTE!!
That was the beginning of everything.
Hey!
This is the new wanted listing.
Post this somewhere visible.
C-Captain Smoker, sir! Excuse me!
Huh?
Uhh...
That Straw Hat...
He's Monkey D. Luffy!
There it is...
This is the place where the Pirate King was executed.
The place where the greatest
pirate who ever lived... died.
The place of the beginning.