Tears of victorious Brogy!
The verdict of Elbaf
It is the signal.
It is quite today excited.
Where do you go?
Your wounds of the last meeting are not…
And then?
My adversary is in the same state.
There is no excuse to have in a combat without mercy.
It would be a blow to lose the face!
He! Wait, Ossan!
Where you go?
Do not move, Dorry-San!
You rest!
If you made too many efforts, you will die!
I am the Dorry Warrior.
And I will make in kind
that this combat does not tarnish the honor of Elbaf!
It is not true…
Ouahou! It manages to raise this enormous rock!
Luffy-San!
He! What you insane, Ossan?
Remove this rock of me!
He! Ossan! He!!
Nothing will stop to me now.
It is perhaps an old history which goes back to one century.
But once the combat started,
it should be finished.
And to give up it is
to give up being a warrior!
And if I am not any more one warrior,
I am nothing any more.
Afflicted to have suspected to you.
God of the War
Elbaf gave its verdict!
I lost his favors.
It is all.
Your God? To gain or lose its favors?
Ca has nothing to do with that!
If your God asked you to die, you would do it?
Your combat was sabotaged!
And a combat faked it is not any more one equitable duel!
You know that I am right!
Keep silent yourself!
How a man who lived only 10 or 20 years
can it include/understand the divine intentions of Elbaf?
I have anything of it to do that!
He! Release me of down there!
He, Ossan!
Giant-ossan!
He! Ossan!
Return, head of mule!
I will not let myself leave like that!
Put it at the carpet, Maître Brogy!
Courage!
No the problem, Usopp!
It will bite dust this time!
Ouais! Find it,
Warrior of Elbaf!
Ahead and fight!
You are the best!
You are incredible!
You are strongest!
You are tall!
You are very tall!
You are gigantic!!
They take this ridiculous combat with the serious one.
Do not say that it is ridiculous, shit!
Brogy is a proud warrior of the seas!
I want to become like him!
How can you say similar tricks?
It does not matter, turn over to the boat.
Which pitches to wait one year so that the Log is reloaded.
We must turn over to the boat and think together of a plan.
Not so quickly! Wait a little!
I am not size to face dinosaurs!
Moreover, it is impossible for us to cross this jungle alive!
What is it of your speech of proud warrior?
I spoke only about my intentions.
I want to become a man of honor!
Good, I do not have the choice.
Luffy and Vivi must be with other Géant.
It will be necessary for us to go until them.
Listen, Nami…
Even if a day comes where I must all lose,
even if I find myself taken in a combat with died on a deserted island,
it will be with pride that I will be able to shout:
“I am Usopp, the warlike valiant knight of the seas!!”
It is that, it is that…
Then hurries to become a proud warrior on whom I will be able to count.
Euh… ouais!
Dorry! Did my old man, you appreciate this glassful of beer?
Ouais.
It was divine.
You exaggerate a little there!
In guard!
What arrives to you, Dorry?
You lack guarantor!
Not, I am the same one as usually!
CA CANNOT SE PASS LIKE CA!
He!
Me which thought of having found a warrior valorous…
Luffy-San…
Why is it made of it as much for a Giant that he hardly knows?
It does not resemble these sanguinary pirates whose head is put at price…
It is which? Who wasted the duel of the Giants?
With the fact…
Where is Karu?
Oh! But it this would not be empoté of bird which is always with the Princess?
Ouais.
Not a gesture.
It is a pleasant chance to find you here.
There is something which one would like that you make.
Indeed.
Zut… I am lost.
I remember to have seen this tree.
It was not “on the left of the tree with lianas”?
It is Nami!
You at the right moments.
I am released a little there.
I do not know any more where to go…
But with do the fact, what you make here?
What you ace?
A DINOSAUR!!
Dino!
YOU RUN TOO QUICKLY!!
This imbecile…
Luffy!
Fortunately!
Why be to you here?
Nami?
Nami!
Oh shit.
NAMI!!
Luffy!
LUFFY!!
They is dreadful!
Nami was puffed out by a dinosaur!!
REALLY?
One ran together through the jungle to escape a dinosaur,
when suddenly, it disappeared!!
What did I make?
I let it be made kill!!
Wait…
You calm!
The guy!
You said well that it had disappeared suddenly…
Then you did not check that it was made really devour, not truth?
GOOD BLOOD!
HOW I WOULD HAVE PU TO CHECK
Whereas I HAD DIED OF JITTER!
IF It IS NOT a DINOSAUR,
It IS ANOTHER WILD BEAST!
WHAT DOES CA CHANGE?
I am not sure, but…
Baroque Works perhaps followed us on this island.
And among you two, Nami-San was the only one of aiming.
Is Baroque Works here on this island?
But then…
Why I am not aimed too?
It is surely because you are not on the list of Works Baroque.
I see!
And it is similar for this beer,
it was reserved to us.
The beer?
It is what this beer history?
Brogy gave our beer to Dorry.
But when Dorry drank it, the beer exploded in its stomach.
WHAT?
Did the beer explode in its stomach?
And it left to the combat under these conditions?
I tried to stop it.
But it posed this foutu rock on me!
Not possible…
Here is a century that they
fight of all their force with equal footings!!
This battle must be the most honourable battle in the world!
Ouais…
How do they dare to intervene in their combat??
What arrives to you?
They continue to fight.
This Dorry Ogre blue tougher than is envisaged.
I should perhaps give a small nudge in the right direction.
It was
a long century of combat.
God of the War, Elbaf,
its verdict gave.
I lost his favors.
It is all.
Luffy!
Luffy-San!
It IS WHICH?
SHOW you!!
Mr. 3, I believe to have heard something.
How it is funny! It is perhaps the cry of overcome which resounds in the jungle!
73 thousand…
467 engagements…
466 ties
and 1 victory!
It is the victory which makes you cry joy?
Like I envy you to be a unicellular being.
Lastly, I address my sincere congratulations nevertheless to you.
Tears of joy…
You could not include/understand.
And initially which are you?
I am Mr. 3, sorry to present to me under my code name.
I am a simple sculptor.
And here my assistant, a realistic painter, GoldenWeek Miss.
And to finish, you are now under my control.
What is it?
Well, Luffy!
I do not know whom did that,
but I will make him his festival!
I come too.
Ouais! They is cool which you come too!
I am reassured more.
It will not be necessary!
They was thus you!
It is returned to you.
One does not need any more now.
Karu!
Why…
It is which these deux-là?
They were in the last city where stopover was made!
How did you dare?
Karu does not have anything to see in all that!
You are right. This bird does not have absolutely anything to see in all that.
But, one was wary of this man to the straw hat.
Then we thought that if one fesait to shout this bird,
you would come to his help in the jungle.
But this thing was more coriace that envisaged.
Go. Call your mistress.
Only an only great cry.
And one will let you leave.
It is like that?
One will make you shout!
Call the Princess.
You would do better…
TO CALL IT NOW!
Open your nozzle, cursed duck!
But now that we are here,
and that Straw hat is in the incapacity to move,
we do not need thus more this bird.
Karu…
Which stupid bird.
You…
Then it was you who put the bomb in our beer!
Hein?
Oh, ouais.
It is which that one?
It was on the list?
Not, but it forms apparently part of the band.
Let us eliminate it too.
It is you who sabotaged the duel of the Giants!
I go you botter the buttocks!
It is me which will eliminate you!
Oh? You want to face us, Miss Wednesday?
You think of being serious vis-a-vis two agents like us?
Take that!
They were had!
Wahou! What a explosion!
Poor small urchin…
Usopp!!
You calm!
It is not worthwhile to excite itself like that,
we will not kill you immediately.
One follows just the orders of Mr. 3.
Mr. 3?
Doru = the last part of “Kanudoru” (candle)
The man who ate the Fruit Doru Doru.
It is on this island?
Indeed.
It can create wax starting from its body
and to control it with its desire. A human candle.
A human candle?