To believe in the dream of our companions!
Battle with the taupinière 4th Avenue
The hopes of the desperate people are being destroyed by a sand cloud.
Some seek hope, and others try to keep a glimmer of hope.
Their ideas were mislaid, and in confusion, the curtain of the history was closed on a tragedy.
Seriously wounded, Karu took Vivi on its back.
Dodging the attacks of Mr. 2,
they run through the battle which makes rage between the rebels and the royal army,
and move directly towards the palate of Alubarna.
But Karu is touched by a stray bullet, and fall to ground.
Mr. 2 approaches quickly…
but the squadron of the Super-Mallards and Sanji come to the rescue!
During this time, with the South-eastern door,
Chopper and Usopp started the combat against Miss Merry Christmas and Mr. 4.
It is over there?
When it succeeded in escaping?
This form…
Oh, I see, Zoan.
I knew that it was not human normal!
You are well, Usopp?
Thank you…
You saved me the life.
And then?
That will not change the fact that we have the advantage.
Allons-y, Mr. 4!
Allons-y!
One goes there!
Go!
Molasse species!
Mola…!
Mol-! Mol-!
They turn over under ground!
Usopp, remember that if you stop moving, you died.
I know.
If we stop moving, they can canarder with their bend us!
Ca arrives!
If I get rid of you…!
I hold you!
Wouldn't the play be also funny without beater, maintaining they are good?
CHOPPER!
I had forgotten that I could do that.
Dirtiness of old crone!
Species of…!
Shit…
If they continue to hide in these holes of moles,
even if I use Rumble Ball, I will not stop running to them afterwards.
Euh?
What?
Where it disappeared?
This long nose!
It rightly. Usopp left!
I have something to say to you to both!
You did beautiful work by digging all these tunnels!
Beautiful job!
But there is a large fault in your strategy.
Where are you?
Where you are!?
Wait…
It is that! There is full, of these goods small tunnels!
And you them guy…
do not be the only ones with being able to use them.
Dumb!
He was in one of the tunnels!
Mr. 4!
One…
A hammer of 5 tons!?
Where this guy acquired the capacity to use a trick like that!?
5 tons…
Q- Who devil are you?
I sailed on the seas of the world…
destroying all the enemies being on my way.
I could not count the number of ships which I ran.
People fear me and call me…
the Prince of the Destruction.
Remember my name well.
CAPTAIN USOPP!
Super! Incredible!
Impressing!
Extra!
Oh, thank you!
Super!
But…
Thank you, baby!
Thank you, goodbye!
But…
I…
I will sign autographs later.
I always thought that you were weak until now!
He.
Mr. 4 was…!
He does not move?
Did I really hurt him?
B- Well. In isn't all the cases, it is my chance?
It is your turn, the penguin!
Prepare to taste the 5 tons of my hammer!
She escaped…
Where are you, penguin!?
I am a mole, cretin degenerated!
!
Stop… moving…!
Ba! Ba species!
If that cannot touch me…
… then this trick is useless!
Let to me say a thing…
I am sure that you listened to the agents of Works Baroque which underwent a defeat vis-a-vis us.
And that which all overcame them…
… it was me!
Q- What!?
And moreover…
I have 8.000 disciples!
REALLY!?
5 tons!
Whoa! Impressing!
Whoa!
5 tons!
Impressing!
Whoa!
5 tons!
Impress-!
O---W---W---W--- !
It has badly that now?!
But it was struck by a hammer of 5 tons!
It is a monster!
It does not even have a bump…
Not even a scratch after having taken a hammer of 5 tons on the head?
Paperboard!?
Was He, it a forgery!?
Of course how it was a forgery!
How you would like that I raise 5 tons!?
I give up already after 5 kilos!
It is a portable foldable model…
… I did it with two stoves and a stick!
What? You are foutu of me!?
I will not retain any more my blows, henceforth!
It is turned over in the taupinière…
Pay attention to the holes!
Q- What will it make, this time?
Where you are, collapsing?!
Where devil are you!?
To pay attention to the holes?
How you can be pathetic!
The ground is like a swimming pool for me!
A swimming pool?
In it is able…
Usopp!
Mr. 4, Lasso.
You two, take care of this Man-Reindeer.
Make him the blow of the 400 balls!
They are not good.
We will not be able to hold vis-a-vis such attacks!
I must try my chance, and all to bet over the three next minutes…
I must find a means of overcoming them!
Kohza…
Where… you are?
Do you include/understand?
A country, it is people.
Father…
Isn't the rebellion can still be stopped?
Vivi-Chan?
All that you want, it is that nobody dies in this combat.
Is it a joke?
People die.
Stop speaking like that!
If you are the only hope to stop the rebellion…
… then you must remain in life at all costs.
And now, no matter what it arrives to us, that will not have any importance!
The guy, leave in front!
We will await you Alubarna!
Ouais!
It is this kingdom of no importance…
… which will die.
I will stop that!
What imports what I must do!
Chopper?
Chopper.
It is not the moment to worry for someone else!
Where?
Hadn't I said you that I was not going from now on any more to retain my blows?
Ba species…!
I will strike you as much as I will want it.
And then I will let you dry in the desert!
I arrive!
There are rules which prohibit to strike a man here!
Thus keep silent yourself, Ba species!
Yes! There are walls over there in the ruins!
If we continue at this speed, then when one arrives over there…
it will crash to pieces the head on the buried part of the wall!
Come there…
Come there!
Crash to pieces yourself the head!
Usopp?
Usopp…
I will not have soon enough any more of time!
Rumble Ball will make effect only during two more minutes!
All will go well for Usopp!
He will not die like that!
Now, I must find their weakness!
If not it is finished by it us!
It is true.
It is Usopp which said it to me!
Now…
I must do what I have to do!
I think that this penguin was crushed!
Too much naze!
I said that I was a mole!
Help me!
Go!
Stop!
They is dangerous!
If you go also quickly…
in a place like that…!
Look in front! A wall!
A wall in front!
Don't you see the wall?
DECREE!
I see!
I see your weakness!
Now!
USOPP!
Usopp, can you rise?
Usopp!?
Huh?
The taupinière! Moved away from the holes!
You will not need to say it to me second once!
Quickly!
What did they envisage?
Q- What?
The weakness of the taupinière…
… it is that all the tunnels are connected.
Oh?
Wow.
They are in life?
They is bad.
I already used half of the effects of Rumble Ball!
Not…
What?
Not more! Not more, or I will die!
Usopp!
Insane Es you? One is likely no to gain!
These monsters are still in life after all that!
Do not do that! You will not be able to escape to them while fleeing!
USOPP!
You should listen to your friend!
This pretty small explosion really irritated me!
You do not have any chance to escape to me also easily after that!
USOPP!
The captain is weak, then it is not a surprise if its crew is weak also.
Captain?
What arrived at Luffy?
Luffy with the straw hat was already killed.
The Boss is occupied.
The rebellion left and started without him.
Eh well, its adversary was quite simply too weak.
Did Luffy… die?
Do not say anything!!