Ah! She's laughing.
They raised the price again?
Don't you think that's a little too high? Why you...
Next time the price is raised, I won't buy it, hear?
Geez, it's just a newspaper!
But if you get it all the time, it adds up!
Well, you don't have to save up to buy
your village from Arlong anymore...
So why keep worrying about money?
Dummy! That's exactly why!
I don't have that obligation anymore,
so from now on, it's all for myself!
I can't go around being some kind
of cheapskate pirate, can I?
Hey, keep it down!
I'm in the middle of formulating my
''Hissatsu Tabasco-Boshi'' here!
With this, if I shoot it into the enemy's eyes...
What? Come on, just one?
Never!
This is Nami-san's tangerine grove.
I won't allow you to lay a finger on it!
NAMI-SAN! THE SECURITY GUARD
OF LOVE IS ON DUTY!
Thank you, Sanji-kun.
She uses him like a tool, that dork Sanji.
What the hell? It's just one little tangerine!
Stingy Sanji.
I SAID NO!
Oh well, whatever. I'm in a good mood.
The world's in such chaos right now.
There was another coup-de-tat in Villa.
Hm? A flyer?
BOUNTY! STRAW-HAT
LUFFY BECOMES WORLD FAMOUS!
So, it seems to me, that what
you are saying is that they...
won't be defeated by simply
dispatching a military force.
Correct.
Since their formation,
and subsequent defeat of Captain Axe-Hand Morgan,
they have been quite active.
Clown Buggy, 15 million.
Pirate Fleet Leader Don Krieg, 17 million.
And Mermen Pirate Leader ''Saw
Nosed Arlong'' 20 million.
Keeping in mind that the average
bounty in East Blue is 3 million...
These are big-league pirates that
are worth over 10 million.
And he's taken them all out.
The initial price on his head will be $.30,000,000,
which is a record figure,
but a reasonable one.
It would be wisest to take care of them quickly.
To pluck this seed of evil before it takes root.
Absolutley.
Anyone who wants to run, do it now!
For there is no room for weakness,
here in this fortress of peace during the Pirate Age!
It is not a crime for civilians to be weak.
We are the heart of Justice!
If there is deadly evil upon the seas,
we, the Marines will exterminate it!
In the name of ABSOLUTE JUSTICE!
Oujousama!
Kaya-oujousama!
What's the matter, Meri?
Please, look!
Usopp-san!
That back profile...
is definitely Usopp-san!
It does seem to be, yes...
Hey, you look a lot healthier today, Kaya.
What story should I tell you today?
Usopp-san is pursuing his dream...
I'm studying to become a doctor,
so that I can help people.
My dream and Usopp-san's dream...
The day when they'll meet again
and become one will arrive someday.
I'm sure of it.
At last...
At last!
Luffy-san is moving on with his dream!
I'm Luffy!
The man who's gonna become the Pirate King!
See yaa!
But...
The next time we meet, we may be enemies!
CAPTAIN!!
The one who's gonna become the Pirate King is ME!
Seems like there's a lot of stupid dreams around.
I'll go for my own sake.
Hey! Old man...
You ever heard of All Blue?
For all this time...
I owe you a hell of a lot!
Check it out, we're WANTED!
Wanted... Dead or Alive...
$30,000,000?
$30,000,000 YEAH!
Check it out!
Even my back is famous now!
Damn, I've got it goin, on...
They don't have my picture,
yet they have Long-nose's?
Oi- where, where? I don't see you.
Seeeee?
It's just the back of your head.
It doesn't count.
Hey now don't be jealous!
Someday you could get one too,
and be famous like me, even
if you aren't the captain.
Really?
Well, if you work hard...
All right crew! We're goin, to the GRAND LINE!
YAAAY!
You guys...
Once again you really don't understand
the seriousness of this situation!
Don't you see this means they're
coming for our heads?
After this...
I don't think we'll be able to lounge
about in East Blue anymore.
30 000 000 $
With a huge bounty like that even the
top Marines will be Iooking for us
And tough bounty hunters after the money.
From now on, we'II be in a whoIe new Ieague.
Let's Go! Let's Go! To The Grand Line!
Let's Go! Go! Go! Go! To The Grand Line!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Crap.
Cheap wine tastes like shit.
How I miss the days when I used to sample
fine vintages, with lovely ladies...
One bad waiter ruined my whole life!
I was demoted from my high position of Captain,
Captain Fullbody!
What? You're so noisy.
Um. it's the new wanted list.
Yeah, whatever. Put it there.
Not like it'd have anything to do with us, anyway.
That face... I've seen that face somewhere before.
I've never seen that pirate flag before.
I am Boat Captain ''Iron Fist'' Fullbody!
l am Boat Captain ''Iron Fist'' Fullbody!
Who is your Captain?
I'm Luffy!
I'm Usopp!
The flag was made just a couple of days ago!
Oh yeah, I remember that time.
Yes! He's given me a chance to
escape this boring, lousy post!
That kid will be so easy to catch!
I'll use him to get my position back!
ALL HANDS!
MEN, WE'RE SETTING OFF!
Settin' off, um, where to?
Um... er...
Well, they should be near the sea restaurant...
OOH! Restaurant!?
Oh Boy! Yummy!
Whoo-hoo!
No! I...
It's him!
Full stop! Hard to starboard, 180 !!
Are those pirates?
Using a scrapped military boat?
How wasteful, the Marines are.
Just throwing them away as scrap...
WE ARE NOT SCRAP!
Are you idiot's blind?
How could you forget Fullbody the ''Iron Fist''?
Ah! It's that Marine ossan!
Are you in trouble? Do you need us to save you?
Stop kidding around!
Destiny has placed you into my hands.
MONKEY D. LUFFY!
You are under arrest!
Cool! My picture looks good!
And the back of my head looks good, too!
DEAD OR ALIVE.
Dead or Alive.
LOAD CANNON!
They're so noisy!
What's going on?
What're they doing? Attacking us?
They're aiming right at us...
This is not goood!
Alright! Lemme at 'em, I'll bounce it right back!
Luffy, I'll handle it.
Right, right. You stand back.
W-w-why? Why?
Don't get involved.
Hey, this way, this way...
Sink them.
Woooo, Awesome!!
No way, that's crazy!
What? It's been so frickin' noisy out there...
You shouldn't bug people trying to take a nap.
How many shots can you stand!?
Fire!
Er... not good.
Not good?
See? The cannon had a crack in it.
Yeah, that's definitely not good.
Listen, you brats!
Do not look down upon an
Ex-Captain of the Marines!
We'll defeat you in close combat.
Let's go, men!
I'll have your head!
GOMU GOMU NO...
How dare you interrupt a cook
in the middle of his work.
You frickin' jerk.
We're not serving soup today.
You wanna lick the deck?
Why is that waiter here!?
Huh? It's over already?
Hmph. He's all talk.
That guy's still a jackass.
You guys are so noisy!
Can't I get some peace and quiet to read?
NAMI-SAAAN!
THE FOOD IS READY!
Really? I'm starved!
Really? l'm starved!
Food! Food! Foo-food! Food!
Huh?
What the hell's that?
Lemme see.
Hawk-eyes! What are you doing here?
Shut up.
I have no business with you.
Where are your superiors?
Camping on an island such as this...
He's much too casual.
Boooss!!
Hawk-eyes!
Yo, Hawk-eyes.
Long time no see.
I'm not feeling too good right now.
You come for a match?
I have no interest in challenging...
a one-armed man like yourself.
However, I came across some interesting pirates.
And it reminded me of something
you told me a long time ago.
A story about a small village,
and an amusing little kid...
No way...
So you've come, Luffy!
Well then, Hawk-eyes.
I can't let you go just like that.
So, Hawk-eyes!
C'mon, drink up! Drink, drink!
We're gonna party today!
You seem to have already done so.
Don't mind me. This is a time to celebrate!
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
CHUG! CHUG! CHUG!
I like it! PARTY! PARTY!
But, boss!
You just said you had a hangover
from drinkin' too much!!
Idiot, Don't ruin this good pleasure
Don't you think it is rather early?
Don't worry about it!
Let's get WASTED!
Hey, did you hear? There's a price on Luffy's head!
Whoo! Way to go!
Hah, this village might get known
for producing an infamous pirate.
Not bad!!
YOU FOOLS!
Stop all this racket!
S-Sonchou!
What's to be happy about a villain
coming from our town?!
A toast!
Yeah!
Geez...
Everyone's getting into it.
Look, Sonchou-san.
Luffy looks so happy.
A pirate is a pirate.
I'm gonna be a pirate!
But, that's his dream.
Are you worried?
A dream?
Or fate?
We're getting very close to the Grand Line.
The only way to get there, is to
go through 'Reverse Mountain'.
That's a pain in the ass.
Can't we just go straight there, from the sea?
Nope.
According to the old man's stories,
it's the only way to get into the Grand Line.
Why's that?
It's extremely dangerous.
That's why I asked! Why?
I don't know any more than that!
The reason is...
OK! I got it.
Let's go head-on through the front!
Are you even listening to me!?
Because, won't it be more interesting?
It'll definitely be more exciting that way!
Argh...
Trying to explain things to you is driving me insane!
But what's most important is,
we should stop at an island and buy some meat.
Meat, meat!
On this island, there is a famous city.
Loguetown.
Loguetown?
Are they famous for their meat?
It's also called, ''The Town of
the Beginning and the End.''
Or so I've heard.
It's the place where the Pirate
King, Gold Roger, was born.
And also the place where he was executed.
The city where the Pirate King died...
Wanna go?
Yeah. I want to see it.
The man who owned One Piece.
The man who had everything in the world.
The place where he was born and died...