You knew at the end of the ocean,
there was a fabulous treasure?
That which will find it will become
the Lord of the Pirates.
Es you as excited as me?
There are incredible adventures
who await nothing any more but us!
Then, uncle fortress?
I had left to lend hands
strong with my companions.
We are the elite of Navarone!
We will show them our
relentless direction of the capture!
Shit! Shit!
Here unit 88.
The special plan captures
is operational.
We will put the hands on
pirates of straw hat.
Remain nevertheless on your guards.
What goes one,
Nami?
Where one goes?
We will follow Doctor Kobato.
Smash the barricade!
going Merry is recovered!
Be sure for you that it is by there Ussop?
They is good, I am sure and certain,
it is this way which it is necessary to take.
Here, here, it is here!
One takes on the right, it is
over there how Merry is moored!
However that appears too much
beautiful to be true…
Y' has a trick which bell.
Well! It is necessary to recover
the boat as fast as possible!
It is incredible!
It is surely one of theirs
units of tireurs d'élites.
They do not have nowhere or outward journey!
You put out of cheek!
It is so sudden!
Gomu Gomu No
Fire!
Fuusen!
What you insane?!
Heavy artillery, in position!
Shit, of the bazookas.
Fire!
Shit.
They is forgeries?
Is whore, it what that?
My eyes burn me.
I saw a trick which dazzled me!
They are teargas grenades.
Regiment of infantry in your turn!
Kill them!
Dumbs!
I am well!
Did Oh, you use them?
I have a pair for you.
Ok!
Tatsumaki!!
I am not like the other moron who
spends its days to run the underskirts.
Hein?
Gomu Gomu No
Gatling Gun!
No
Mushi!
Too much easy!
Hold, where passed Sanji and Zoro?
It is you who massacred them!!!
Ah, sorry…
Large idiot!
Whore…
He, the green alga what
you told presently?
It is not the moment of you chamailler!
Fire!
Whore, I am not able to leave me from there.
Luffy!
More one gesture!
the least gesture can
you to cost the life.
the commander of the G8 base us
asked to capture you alive.
But if you oppose resistance to us, I could not be guaranteeing of anything.
H-He, Luffy.
We does not leave in the shit!
I test, but I do not leave myself there…
And I do not know why,
but I empty myself my forces.
Kairoseki?
How?
Exactly!
This net at especially conceived summer
for the holders of fruits of the demon.
Then, Straw hat?
Te revoilà finally.
What do you make?
They is dangereous because of here!
Pas la pains to excite you.
[Note] Pinch:Bad posture
Whore…
Impossible to count them,
why are they so numerous?
You would make better return to you.
You cannot beat a retreat.
Arm!
Fact of shitting, it should be fought.
Go ahead!
What does it occur here?
Hein? It is…
Ah… Afflicted. I will die…
Ussop!
Who wounded you also seriously?
They are the soldiers of the Navy?!
Bandage dumbs!!!
Not, not, not.
Hein? Kobato?
Euh, My-Major…
What you made?!!
What it you
takes suddenly?
One took to us as an hostage!!
With the help!!!
They forced us to follow them!!!
Kobato-san?
The species of giant cuddly toy
fact also part of the pirates!
Wait, what
you tell at the end?
It is what this circus?
- But which is this young young lady?
- I took to you as an hostage?
I know anything of it.
I include/understand there nothing any more.
As long as they retain them as an hostage,
it is be likely to draw to them above.
Dumbs! You are really
pirates, bandages cowards!
It is the man who was
infiltrated in the infirmary.
It was thus true, it did not have
nothing known as with his/her companions.
Exactly!
I make party indeed of
the crew of Straw hat,
I am that which one
call “the Rough one”!
If you made not only I you
, I say will crush you until the last!!
And then initially, that you make
still on my way?
I see.
It is very interesting.
And how that jumps!
If not I break the neck with his 2 wives.
It will do it without hesitating!
It is much more damaged than
us when it is with work…
A true dispenser of justice cannot leave
two women to die under its eyes.
Chopper, blunder, or you make
will finish in the same shit as me.
Firm your large mouth!
It will kill us!!
Please, made
what he says to you!
Not!
Not, not and not!
How much time I would have
you to repeat it?!
It is food for
a thousand of people.
One will be able to never leave oneself there if
you made not good job!
Too much slow!
All but not the ladle.
What thus? You have a problem?
First of all…
It will be necessary to put your pride on side if you want that I come you to assistance.
Well, come prepare
ingredients here!
Said, Jessica-san in
fact not a little too…
She has still evil to believe that the other cook was in fact one of the pirates.
And then these two others
are good that to complain.
They are goods with nothing.
I do not have you
to ask to bring back it.
Yes! All our excuses!
He, Billy, taste one
little my special sauce.
Then, they is good?
Or not…
Not it is good but…
It is that which one
concocte each time…
Yes, yes, completely.
Since I tasted
food of the other type…
I have always the impression to forget
something when I cook a dish.
It is not that they are bad, but
there is always a trick which bell…
I have evil to admit it but it is necessary well to acknowledge that the other type was rather gifted.
Doesn't whore, what go?
Jessica-sama?
Hum… What?
Euh… What does one have to do that?
It is a receipt which wrote
the other type before fleeing.
The pirate?
A receipt?
I remember it…
One minute please, it
time to write a receipt.
What do you want to make some now?
Ah… Ben… I…
Since it tried hard of
to write, one could make use of it…
Do not say stupidities!
One should not depend on a pirate!
We are the cooks
of Navarone after all!
He is the enemy of those which
we endeavor to nourish.
It remains you with
less one bit of pride?
Euhh…
It is known well that you
be exasperated but…
It is what this brothel?!
You do not even know
to peel a potato!
Euh, usually it
are the subordinates…
One forever known to make.
Listen! We are
within an army…
Here, the least apple of
ground has its importance.
Even cry them of apples
as ground are used with…
Euhhh…
You dispatch and peel them
with the greatest care!
Ouuuuuuuiiiiii!
My-major…
Make pass the order of fold.
Lower all your weapons and move back!
Break the formation!
The tireurs d'élite, lower your rifles.
Major…
There is nothing to make…
Oh, Ca with the air to go.
Such an amount of better.
Hein?
You saved me, Zoro.
Wasn't He, it the voice of Kobato-san?
You think too?
Mechanic-san.
What does it occur?
Kobato was taken as an hostage.
What?!
Really, that fears!
Ah, of made to you not.
Ca does not change only my daughter
howl or not, I have the practice…
I am rather anxious…
For these.
As you can it
to see, the way is free.
Now, release the hostages.
Brilliant, that went!
He, Chopper.
Impossible! We will not release the hostages solely that after us to be flee.
Dumb!
Your orders were
transmitted to unit 17.
Well.
Wait until it
that I give the signal.
It is not the sorrow to make some
as much! Embark on your boat!
That fine wordss…
but are they sincere?
He, hold good.
Nami, Chopper, Coil-cook!
Hein?
As soon as I enter in scene,
run towards the boat.
Luffy, you will have to lengthen tone
arm to take them along to the boat.
In are you able?
No the concern.
I see.
Major.
What imports the result, I would know
to take my responsabilities.
Which dishonor it would be for the soldiers of G8 if we let them escape.
Ah, I am sorry.
What? Does not frighten us any more like Ca
Idiot! It came to save you!
Zut! Nami-san!
Find a means of going to the boat!
Allons-y, Capitaine.
No the district! Stop them!
It thus had well an idea
behind the head, this underhand old man.
Ca fears.
Go ahead!
He, the guy! He is
great time to embark!
Are they still in life?
Maintaining it is with us two, Zoro.
What?!!
Do not let them slip by!
Draw to them above immediately!
But they took the hostage with them…
Draw nevertheless!!
Played well, Merry!
Always the same one! You thus do not go
to never stop making weak tricks?!
You believe that one is in
rubber like you?!
Good, the guy. One goes there, one goes there!
It is that, the boat
pirate about which he spoke.
He is in the train of
to sail quietly.
Why we do not have
the authorization to attack it?
They took hostages on their board.
They removed a nurse.
These pirates are
really without scruples.
Is Ah, it?
It is it which gives the orders?
It is really anything!
The ship is it ready?!
One does our better.
Father?
Ah, Kobato.
It would seem that you learned
many things today.
Is it you who
their boat launched?
Do what you will want.
You will appear in front
a cour martiale.
No father in the world can allow himself to leave his daughter adored to suffer.
Kobato-san did not fear anything…
and since
battle was committed…
You did not count nevertheless
not to give up the nurse?!
It is incredible which a major can do abstraction of the life of others.
You still have many things
to learn from the commander Jonathon.
Major, precisely in connection with the hostage.
Somebody informed us that it belonged to the crew of Straw hat.
How?
Please wait,
Madam the inspector.
Where do you count go?
I do not have accounts to return to you.
We, we have things to say to you.
Oh, eh well you will say
with your commander that…
I spent a pleasant moment here.
Te insane step of us!
It seems well that my
disguise became useless.
Why longes you the coast?
Ca could be fatal if one
was made attack in the center.
At least from here, one will have
that a side to be supervised.
Oh, where are we?
Ah, be finally awaked to you.
What do I make on Merry?
It is a long story!
I see. Nami had been made pass
for an hostage. It was a super idea.
Obviously!
One recognizes well your
talents of arnaqueuse.
Who could well give
the boat with water?
It is surely the old man
who bump with the mechanics.
From where you know it?
It does not matter.
~ I am dazzled by the beauty of
Nami-san in its held of nurse ~
In spite of the fact that one is escaped…
I am anxious because
there is no chart.
One would have had better
to prepare before leaving.
Which band of idiots.
Oh! Robin-chwan!
Coooooooool ~!
Lieutenant Shepard
was thus an intruder.
We are afflicted, it east flees.
It is not your fault.
I always had evil
with the pretty girls.
However, they are only six.
There is of them thus one of which
the identity remains unknown.
Yes, they is good for that…
One has just learned presently…
Yes?
After investigation with the infirmary…
That there was no disappearance
of nurse to date.
It is the plan of the fortress.
I thought that one could
to use to escape to us.
There is only Robin who includes/understands me!
Fortunately how you are there, Onee-sama!
O-Oui…
We are attacked!!
There is still an hostage. They are foutent some?
It does not matter, I imagine that they
discovered our subterfuge.
The other ships catch up with us!!
They do not have any hostage.
Pursue the crew
of Straw hat.
I repeat it, charge all
guns with the firing!
Is this the exit of this fortress?
Ussop, prepares the gun.
Chopper, retain my instructions well.
Received.
If it is the single exit…
One must find a means of passing.
However it is odd…
I have the impression that there is more
ramifications actually that on the plan…
and then positioning
port is false.
Why thus?
Something does not turn out badly.
Then anything else to announce?
Eh well so much better if there is nothing.
Continue like that, I count on you.
I inform you that…
the pirates are all
close relations of the door.
They are échecs et mats.
What a damage!
You are still so young,
Straw hat.
How?! There is no more
no boulet de canon?
Yes, all reserves of
powder were emptied too.
In there reflective, that appears obvious.
They were seized by the Navy.
What will one make? One
will not be able to pass through the door.
One will have that to sink straight.
Ca will go if one manages to take
the control of the ascencor.
Easier to say than to make!
Do not make any you!
I have an good idea.
Anéantissont our enemies pirates!
Fire!
Gomu Gomu No Fuusen!
One succeeded!
I see, it is not badly.
Nice, Luffy!
Good, now…
“Boulets de canon and
did the powder disappear "?
Nami?
Is Oh, what there?
One was made have…
Our spoils DISAPPEARED!!!
But where they have
been able to pass, these pirates?
Impossible,
how did they can escape?
They will not flee.
If there is not any more gold, that
is used for nothing to flee!
A pirate who leaves his spoils
behind him is a shame!
Half turn!!
Soon in One part:
The boat pirates with missing!
2nd attack on the fortress.