He Chopper. Did you find plantes médicinales?
I found much of it. This island is filled with rare plants.
There is a thing which disturbs me since one moment…
Which is this strange line?
Can it is true, what that be well?
It would seem that a cyclist passed by there.
We found a zone cleared.
A tanuki?
[Tanuki:left raccoon]
I am a reindeer! Look at my horns!
You are well, Chopper?!
Who it is this guy?
Doesn't something go, Luffy?
Who are you?
Who you are?!
It is which this giant?
Who is this man?
Robin!
The admiral of the marine base, Ao Kiji!
The threat of a great power!
To be able to disturb Robin like that…
Who is it?
It is a navy.
The admiral of the marine base, Ao Kiji.
Admiral?!
Admiral? A so high rank?!
There exist only three men who have the title of Admiral
(the red dog)
(the blue pheasant)
(the yellow monkey)
Only the admiral commander-in-chief, Sengoku, can give them orders.
He is one of the three plus great powers of the government!
How is what a guy like does to him here?!
You did not find pirates more famous than us?! See elsewhere if not…
Alalala?
C… It is what?
A novel method of dredger! Hello.
How is what you insane, jerk?!
Pay attention so that you say!
He, of calm the guy.
Did you listen to what I said?
I said only that I trotted myself. You do not ignite.
Summers you… this… good…
“It”?
“Good”?
I forgot… It is not serious.
Your sentences do not have any direction!
It is which him? He, Robin, be sure for you that you were not mistaken in guy?!
It is impossible that he is admiral of navy!
He He, does not judge people by their appearance.
My currency of navy is “a lazy justice”.
THERE IS ALREADY REMARK!
In any event… good…
Ah, forgive me.
(Yokkorasho is said when a thing is tiring to make)
Then, why did you sleep upright?
To make short… I by no means intend to capture you, are without fear.
I just came to confirm the position of Nico Robin after the incidents of Arabasta.
As envisaged, it is with you.
It is really lazy.
It is at least equipped like an admiral.
I will announce only this to the general headquarters.
Because by adding the settings at price, the total reward increases.
100 million more….
60 million more…
79 million, that made…
I know anything of it… I lose myself in my accounts…
Remade calculation…
GOMU GOMU NO…
He wait! Wait, Luffy!
Stop! Stop!
Come here! It is what your problem…?
What good is it to attack it?!
- It is one of most powerful the navy!
I of insane!
We will let it capture Robin?! Species of bastard!
Aiaa… As I already said, I will not do anything.
I go you botter the bottom!
Stop that, Luffy!
Wait!
It is a navy? So only they had said it earlier…
Who are these people?
He, did not fear.
Wasn't this island, uninhabited?
Not.
They are probably the passengers of the shipwreck who failed themselves on this island.
I had echoes of a report/ratio mentioning these shipwrecked men in the surroundings.
How are they, Chopper?
They underwent wounds but their days are not in danger.
They will be left there if they follow my regulations.
But they have not eaten anything for six days. They are very weakened.
Sanji-kun and Ussop went to seek to eat presently.
He! One is there!
They were really hungry.
Do not eat so quickly.
still let us have we much food.
- Yes, we have much of it
Why do you eat?
Although this island is uninhabited, it is not difficult to find food.
Ca was not to be easy if you did not have any experience.
You were lucky sacrament to survive a shipwreck on Grand Line.
We are the only survivors having been able to reach this island.
What did it occur?
We were of return of a culinary visit to Pucchi, the Greedy City.
Then the boat was struck by an enormous frog which swam the crawl and broke.
A frog which swam the crawl?!
Don't the frogs, usually swim the pitch-stirrer?
Ca must be brilliant! I want to see that!
You are sure?
It is true!
[Yokozuna which is the name of frog means in Japanese:Sumo champion]
Yokozuna?
We then fought for finally reaching this uninhabited island.
We had awaited our rescue for one month…
But whereas we thought that somebody arrived, we did not believe our eyes of them.
It rolled to bicycle on the ocean.
Could He He, how a bicycle…?
Ah, it was me.
Arrived then a pirate boat.
It was us.
Then you “this”, isn't this is?
Good… Hum… It…
Express yourself clearly! Clearly!
It is true! I forgot! He, stops you saying conneries!
L… Luffy! Wait, wait!
Calm yourself!
Not, but…
As I already said, I did just one strolls.
What, one strolls?! Then does not remain there! Break!
It is not reasonable.
At all events, Luffy wants some…
Ok, I go there.
I return, but before that…
You all… Prepare you to leave…
By chance, I know an inhabited island not far from here.
It is preferable that you are neat over there.
He! You! Do not listen to it! It is a navy!
Where is the problem?
It is true, the navy are the nice ones
and we, isn't this is the malicious ones?
Do not laugh!
Will it help them?
Does it have a boat initially?
There was no boat in the neighborhoods, except ours.
Without boat, nor log book…
How will they join this close island?
Ah, all is ok.
You are not at all convincing.
It is possible…
Thanks to the capacities of this man.
Here, it is ready.
We sufficiently responsible it for food and water for ten people.
It is not in your practices to make the things with half.
Yes, it is our strong point! You surely realized some.
It is honest after all.
What will you make? Do you hope them to trail, them and the loading, with the stroke?
As if I of it were able.
You move away a little.
It is what?
A monster! Probably the Master of the places!
That?! He! Run away yourself!
Pay to!
GOMU GOMU NO…
OLD ICE
A fruit of the demon?
The sea is… cold.
Here capacity of an Admiral of the marine.
Ca should last one week, I think.
You can walk prudently in this direction.
You will reach the inhabited island within four days.
The weather will be cold. You equip with warm clothing.
Do I dream?
The sea became solid!
We can now cross the sea! We can leave this island!
Admiral-san! Thank you!
It is a miracle! It is a true miracle.
Here, we are about to leave.
Ah…
You had chance.
Made good voyage.
All the pirates are not the same ones.
How to thank you?
Not only you looked after us, but moreover, you shared your food.
Do not make any you for that.
To help your next improves your destiny, you know.
Made attention that the children do not catch cold.
Food will be preserved as much as the weather will be so cold.
Thank you very much!
I will not forget your gesture.
Pirate with the straw hat!
Goodbye! Take care of you!
It is brilliant, brilliant.
The weather is cold, very cold…
It is the winter here.
I can make iceskate!
Excel, Chopper!
A winter island, that then!
What is there?
Stop!
I am cold, I am cold!
I am frozen.
What is there?
How would I say…? You are exactly like your grandfather.
Monkey D. Luffy.
I became insane…
Or am I right?
Grandfather?
The grandfather of Luffy?
What doesn't go Luffy? You perspire.
Not… This. it is nothing… really… good…
A long ago, your grandfather me because much of problems.
I came here for Nico Robin and…
In order to know you.
Perhaps I would have…
To kill you immediately…
The government yet really does not know which you are, but…
By studying your last respective, one realizes danger which you represent.
Although you are little, this gathering of gangsters…
Is tedious.
First setting at price on your crew…
Until your death warrant here…
Your progress was amazing.
Up to now, you were confronted only with criminals, but…
That made to you more dangerous.
Why you say that of a blow?! Presently, you said that you were there to only confirm.
With the result that your crew is regarded as dangerous now…
It is you… Nico Robin.
He you! You tracked Robin! I go you botter the bottom!
Its setting at price does not reveal only its force…
It also represents the threat which it inflicts with the government.
This is why…
Although you were only eight years old, you gained a setting at price of 79 million.
You made certainly well comprise you a such child.
You betrayed your partners…
And be been useful to you of them like toys.
To survive in a medium of shadies…
Was single only to serve your own interests.
Which blow schemes you in this new team?
He, you!
All that you say tends to irritate me!
What reproaches you in Robin-chan?!
- Stops, Sanji!
I do not have anything in particular to reproach him.
If I do not have any maintaining contact with it…
It is because it slipped to me between the fingers once.
It is an old history.
You will realize there also, a day or the other.
When you have to make with a suspect woman…
The time of the regrets is already far.
And for you to prove it…
All organizations that Nico Robin could infiltrate…
All were destroyed…
Excluded it.
This is not…
Nico Robin?
You, you stop that! The past does not have any more importance!
If the past were not forgotten…
How could we travel with a kind of hunter of pirates and a kind of robber?!
“A kind” was not necessary!
It is not the past, but the present which imports me!
Now, Robin is an invaluable companion!
Do not speak like that about our companions!
I see.
You became very popular in this crew.
What tests you to render comprehensible me?!
If you wish to capture me, then do it!
TREINTA FLEUR
Robin, stops!
Alalala!
In would I have said too much?
Which disappointment… I over-estimated you, I believed you more intelligent.
Clutch
It was crashed to pieces in thousand pieces, it died!
NR. Not! It is impossible!
H.hé! We, everyone save!
To make a so cruel thing…
ICE SABER
I did not intend to kill you, but…
SLICE SHOT!
YOSHAAA!
Blasted cook, you put yourself at it, you too?
What did you believe?
GOMU GOMU NO…
GUN!
It is frozen!
They are frozen!
All three, in only one attack?!
Ca becomes serious! If one does not deal with them…
They will catch engelures, the fabrics will not resist!
What do you make, Ussop?
Quickly help them!
It is not the desire which I miss, but…
My body cannot move any more. I am frozen, me too!
You lie! You are frightened too much to move!
- Ahhh! Luffy!
- Sanji! Zoro!
Robin, runs away himself!
Your companions are very courageous…
But you remained the same one, Nico Robin!
You are mistaken! I am not any more…
Robin! Pay to!
Run away yourself!
I am…
Robin-chan!
Robiiiin!
IT IS NOT FINISHED!!