An island without doctor?
Venture in an island without name!
Island in sight!
An island?
He said 'island in sight "!
We arrived on an island!
He, Nami! It is not brilliant?
He said that he found an island!
Soon you will be better!
It is an island!
An island! An island!
An island! An island!!
Will check!
It is an island!
Such an amount of snow!
What a joy!
You do not approach, pirates!
He! Here are people…
But… I have a bad presentiment.
You them pirate!
You will leave this water good once for all!
At once!
We came to find a doctor!
We have a very sick girl on board!
One will not let oneself have!
Dirty pirates!
They really hate us!
And one has just arrived…
Close it!
They drew!
You will regret that!
Sanji-San, wait!
Vivi!!
Bandage dumbs!!!
Out of cheek!!!
Wait please!
You should not fight with them!
I am well!
Ca just scratched me the arm!
If you wish it, we will not accost here!
But, please, bring to us a doctor!
Our companion suffers from a grave disease!
Help it if it vout likes! I beg you!
Vivi…
You are a catastrophe as Capitaine, Luffy!
To always act without reflecting résoud not all!
If you fight against them,
what will it occur of Nami-San?
Forgive me.
I was wrong.
Please, call a doctor!
Please, save my companion!
I will lead you to the village!
Follow me!
You see? They included/understood.
Ouais… Be really strong for you, you!
I should warn you.
Our country has one doctor, a witch.
A witch?
What does that want to say?
This country is really odd…
With is the fact, which the name of this country?
This country does not have a name yet.
A country without name?
This kind of thing exists?
A bear!!!
Everyone, made it dead!!
It is a bear hiker.
It is not dangerous.
Greet it just as the mountain dwellers do it.
Well! Ca is better!
Now, I can finally begin my intensive super drive!
I have enough the usual musculation of it,
and to remain sitted to supervise the boat is tedious.
Thus now, it is time to go to swim in cool water to release the spirit!
Here is our village, Big Horn!
There are strange animals which walk in the corner.
What you could wait of a snow-covered country!
Nami-San, we reached civilization!
A village!
Eh well, thank you for your assistance.
All those which are not guard can turn over to work.
But, you will leave yourselves there all alone, Dalton-San?
They are pirates…
I do not believe that they want us evil.
Call that the intuition.
Trust me!
Dalton-San…
What does one make?
If Dalton-San says it…
Well, they do not need our assistance.
Ca must be true.
Yes.
Well, Dalton-San, one leaves them to you!
Keep an eye on them, Dalton-San!
Call us if something occurs.
I suppose that they are not the armed forces of your country.
They are civilians.
You can come at home.
He! Look at! Luffy!
Another bear hiker!!
Still?
Oh, Dalton-San!
Hello!
I heard that pirates were there.
Does that go?
Yes, all is under control!
There is no reason to worry.
Oh, Dalton-Kun, I impatiently await the elections in 2 days.
Everyone says that he will vote for you!
You… would not owe you!
Not somebody like me!
I have made too many sins!
Use the bed over there, please.
I will heat the part.
Forgive me not to be myself presented, my name is Dalton.
I am the Captain of the guard of this island.
Want excuse our hostile reception!
Do I can ask you something?
I believe to have already seen you some share before.
I think that it is your imagination!
More important, can you say some to us more on this “witch”?
A little earlier, the temperature of Nami-San reached the 42°C!
42°C?
Its fever has increased regularly for 3 days.
If it increases further, it will die!
Yes…
Moreover, one does not know the cause of the disease, nor how to treat it.
It is not serious! There is a doctor here!
Where is your “witch”?
The witch?
You see the mountains behind the pane?
Yes, these whores the large ones…
Mr. Hyper snowball!!
Shiroa, the monster of snows!!
I will ridge you, band of morons!!
These mountains are rock Drum.
You can see a castle at the top of largest, the central mountain!
A castle?
It is a castle without king.
Ah… good and heat!
Yes, I see it.
Is there something in this castle?
The woman whom one names witch, the only doctor of the country,
Dr. Kureha lives in this castle.
What?
Why did it decide to go to live over there?
Well, in this case, call it!
It is an urgency!
Even if we want it, we do not have any means of contacting it.
And it is supposed to be a doctor?
What is it that this kind of doctor?
There is not to doubt its medical competences, but
it is a rather strange old woman.
She lives since almost 140 years.
140? And it is still alive?
Eh well, some say that she likes Umeboshi.
Umeboshi = Prune which lengthens the life
But what does it occur when somebody is wounded or sick?
It goes down from the mountain when it wants.
She seeks patients, looks after them,
and takes what she wants in their house in compensation before setting out again.
An old robber would be said.
He He! A pirate would be said!
But how made an old woman to go down from this mountain?
It is right a rumor but…
Several eyewitnesses report to have seen it the nights of full moon
to take a sledge and to go down by the sky.
Therefore it is called witch.
They also said that a strange creature came with it. A creature like one forever considering.
I knew it! I knew that there was one of them!
An abominable man of snows!!
I knew that there would be one of them!!
A witch with an abominable man of snows!
Oh, please, made that they are not met!
She is perhaps our only doctor.
But, this old woman does not want relations with us.
All that we can make is to wait the next day when it will go down.
Oh not!
Make shit! There are not time to remain here sitted and to wait.
During this time, Nami-San…
He, Nami!
Nami!
You hear me?
He, what you insane brothel?
Oh, you are awaked!!
Listen, you can see a doctor only if we climb a mountain.
Therefore, we will climb!
You are insane?
What do you want that Nami-San makes?
They is good! I will carry it!
Ca will do nothing but worsen its state!
What? More quickly she will see a doctor, more quickly she will be better. Not?
It is true but not like that!!
Look at how much these slopes are high and stiff!
I can do it.
Perhaps that you can but that will cause too much stress with Nami-San!
But even if I release it, there will be snow in lower part of us!
Even a person in good health would die if it fell from this mountain!!
Moreover, its temperature is of 6°C higher than the normal!
You do not include/understand it?
I must… better hurry be…
quickly by regard for Vivi…
Take care of me, Capitaine!!
Worry you!! Let make me!!
I knew it! When the Captain says something, its navigator goes in his direction!
Do you know under which condition you are, Nami-San?
Will that go?
This voyage will take several hours…
Ossan!
Give me meat!!
Meat!!
Meat?
Well! I go there too!!
Listen well, Luffy.
If you climb and that you tombs would be this only once, Nami will die!
Ah? Even once?
Wait! Do not move a moment.
I must attach that very tight!
I think that you are ready.
I will await you here.
I would do nothing but slow down you if I came.
Similar!
Of agreement!
Ok, Nami!! Cling well!
If you are really serious, I will not stop you.
But please, tackle the slope opposed to this one.
Lapahns do not live by the way over there.
It is a wild rabbit species.
If you must meet a group of it, you would die.
Rabbits? but we are in a hurry.
Ca will go!
Not?
Yes, I will strike them!
To strike?
Impossible!
You run to your death!!
Ca will go!!
Allons-y Sanji,
before Nami does not die!
Do not tell such doubtful jokes!! Salt bastard!!
Will that really go for them?
Eh well, not to worry for these 2 guy, but…
The true problem is to know if Nami-San will hold long enough.
I hope that they will arrive there healthy and safe.
Doesn't something go you two?
You should return! It is rather cold outside.
Ca goes! I prefer to remain outside.
Me too!
I see!
In this case, I will remain there too.
A long time ago, had we…
doctors…
But they left all.
They was very good doctors.
In truth, they could take the best possible care.
Then why?
This country, even less than one year ago, was devastated
by a crew of pirates.
All country?
This explains why you were so nervous when we arrived.
Exactly.
The citizens are not yet ready to hear the “pirate” word.
You must excuse their behavior.
It was a crew of pirates of 5 members only.
Their Captain was done called Black Barbe,
and with its capacity by far higher than ours, it devastated the whole country.
A simple crew of 5…
It is impossible!
Black beard…
However, some affirmed that it was well for the country.
How the plundering of a country can be beneficial?
Yes! Who could say a similar thing?
Thank you.
But it was true because until this moment,
the monarchy of this kingdom caused the loss of the people.
The old name of this country was the Kingdom of Drum.
And our king was… Wapol.
They was worst conceivable kings.
Yes! This man… I remember it!
Wapol?
The weather is increasingly cold, not?
The wind redoubles.
Buffoon! Why do you run the naked legs?
I have badly only by looking at you.
Eh well, it is right my Polisuu.
It is what a “Polisuu”?
It is your “Policy”!
Word game!
Policy = Insurance
Yes, it is that!!
Do Oh, you know what?
People, in the covered with snow countries, never sleep!
Ah? How is that done?
Because if they fell asleep, they would die.
Would not be stupid! Ca does not arrive at anybody!
It is true! Somebody said it a long time ago to me.
It was Usopp?
Not! I heard it with the bar of my village!
Then why there was a bed in the house of this Dalton?
Ah… yes!
Eh well, it is for when it will die.
Yes, you ace reason! Softened cranium!
Oh, listening that!
The women of the snow-covered countries have all the soft skin.
Why?
It is not obvious?
When the weather is really cold, you must put cream. How that!
It is for that their skin becomes soft.
A soft skin, if white that it is almost transparent.
Here how are the women of the snow-covered countries!
Do Hein, how they become white?
Eh well…
Of course because of this rain of ceaseless snow which fades on their skin.
Hein, you are really stupid! You know it that?
I do not want to hear that of your share!!
Moreover,
you start to make me shit!!
It is what its problem?
Nami-San!!
Hold good still a little!!
One will take you along in the doctor!
Snow is deep by here…
He! Luffy!
Course more gently, do you want?
You will hustle Nami-San!
What is it that?
They are large and white…
Ca must be ours polaires!
It is sure!!
You two…
You know Wapol?
Eh well, one “does not know it” not really.
But it was the name of the pirate who attacked our boat.
I fought it with force.
Now that I think of it, it said something in connection with the Kingdom of Drum.
Yes.
It rightly.
I remember it perfectly.
When I was child, I accompanied my father
with the council of the Kings.
I saw it over there.
The council of the Kings?
Who are you with the Juste?
Not, finally, I…
At all events, we met Wapol!
It was yesterday, on the way towards here.
Yesterday? You are sure?
But now, what does that mean?
He said that he was pirate, not King.
He uses piracy like a temporary camouflage.
Wapol derives on the oceans,
while trying to return on this island.
Then, people on his ship were to be
those which were driven out because they could not resist to the pirates of Black Beard who attacked your island.
To resist?
Not!
At the time,
the forces of Wapol did not even try to fight!
From the moment when it carried out the power of these pirates,
it immediately gave up the country!
Wapol was the first to be fled on the oceans and to escape!
It is what caused the fall of the country in despair.
This like that is that one…
Is this as that a King must act?
As they is dreadful…
A King who gives up his people…
Vivi…
Like you known as.
But now, the tyranny of Wapol is finished.
The remaining citizens linked themselves to rebuild their country.
Now, the thing that we fear more is the return of Wapol.
The return of monarchy.
With the people if little protected, we must avoid that,
with an aim of rebuilding a country of peace.
It jumped!
It is insane!
How can they move thus?
They are gorillas or what?
Not, they are ours polaires!
They are rabbits!!!
But you have just asked whether they were gorillas.
These things must be Lapahns about which Dalton spoke!
But… Why are they so numerous?
Wapol-Sama!
What is there, Chess?
Did you find the ship of Straw hat?
Not, Wapol-Sama.
We finally arrived at the house.
What?
I have wondered for how much months we derive?
It is our fatherland, the island of Drum!!
Really?