Nami?
One was made have….
Our spoils DISAPPEARED!
2nd attack on the fortress
The pirate boat disappeared!
What?
They will escape!
Catch up with them!
But Major….
This zone conceals
rocks emerged from everywhere.
It is very riqué to continue the continuation
as long as the fog did not rise.
Yes I know it!
Ahead!
But…
You know what it will occur
if one lets them slip by?!
One will be overpowered sarcastic remarks and will be underestimated
by the other bases of the Navy!
It would be a terrible affront!
You want to say…. that
fortress of Navarone could…
Exactly!
Our reputation will be tarnished.
They will treat us dead losses which
are not rotten to even capture a fly.
They will start again the polemic to know
so yes or not, they will have to crush us.
Then!
You could support that as
sailor of the Fortress of Navarone?!
To in no case!
With all the ships!
Changement de vitess!
And plunge in the thick fog!
It is the ocean!
One will be able to leave if one
continue straight!
One does not leave!
Change course!
Made half-turn!
Immediately!
It is necessary to turn over to the fortress!
Soldiers of the Navy us
concealed all our gold!
What you say?!
Is Ouais, but reasonable?
Nami… one came very close to death for
to succeed in arriving up to now.
Yes it is reasonable, it is all
what there is of more reasonable!
That would not have any direction of
to leave from here without our gold!
When the money is in
play, that does not laugh any more.
Nami-san is so beautiful when
it is in this state!
But looks at!
A so large breach was made!
That would be damage of
not to thread there, nan?
We are pirates,
not true, Luffy?
Ouais.
You do not think that they is ashamed for
pirates to leave a treasure behind them?
Ah, I see.
Well, it is decided then!
Made half-turn!
Change the direction of the rudder!
Cape towards the fortress!
Yes, well included/understood.
Ouais! All that Nami-san orders!
Bar with starboard!
Go!
He, the guy!
You shake what?!
Made not anything!
It is well, it is well.
Continue like that!
Make sound the bells!
Make still sound them!
The fog reduces the visibility.
Let us avoid the collision!
It occurs what?
Keep silent yourself Luffy!
Hein?
A wind small bell?
It is a bell of alarm which allows
to announce its position to his/her comrades.
That fears!
The waves come from face.
Here! Nami-san, that
presents itself well, hein?
At all! With port side immediately!
Hein?
Trajectory is changed!
If one continues it is
the assured collision!
It is for the interest
of Nami-san… Go!
One will be made strike!
I failed to be reduced in crumbs without
to have been able to see the glare of our gold!
I wonder what it occurs in top.
Still?
This time, small bells
wind mills are more numerous!
They come very from opposite.
A ship, two…
Not, there are several
ships in approach!
It is what this brothel!
Nami-san!
One transfers with port side or starboard?
With port side all!!
It is necessary at all costs
to leave this fog!
What it occurs, good blood?!
One types oneself some, trust
Nami-san and all will occur well!
It is the best navigatrice in the world.
It is time, one will strike!
Lord the Almighty…
One has escaped it beautiful.
Let us continue straight!
One should not waste time.
That becomes urgent to leave
of this awkward fog.
One will be made locate!
Ouais, exact!
If one leaves this smoke, one
will become the game of a shooting!
Our bodies put in parts…
will sink in the sea!
Then one will throw oneself to water!
Miss Navigatrice.
I consulted file.
Formerly this fortress
was populated even.
And it appears that several ships
of war were used there.
He, Robin! You do not believe that the moment is badly
chosen to tell us an old history?!
They are ships of reserve.
They are certainly in
ruins per hour that it is.
This is why there is much of
unused docks in bay.
Unused docks….
I see!!
Robin, it is a good pipe, that!
The guy!
One will hide Merry in
this unused dock!
Hein? But it is where?!
You have only with
to follow my instructions.
Qu-Quoi…?!
Call the guards!
Question to see them whether the ship of
Straw hat crossed the gate!
O-Oui!
Call to the guards.
Here the vessel of Drake.
The ship of the band of
Did straw hat pass?
How?!
Apparently no ship
the gate did not cross.
How?!
Where you disappeared,
dirtinesses of pirates…
It could be that…
you slipped by beyond the horizon…
while the artillerists were
plunged in the fog?
Humm…
All my excuses!
We lost sight of the fact the pirates
whereas we had reached the ocean.
They volitilized
how by magic!
Ah, in the final analysis…
Well, you made good job.
For the moment, return at the base.
We will establish
a new strategy.
There is no reason
that they leave from here.
As long as their dream resides
in this fortress.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
GOMU-GOMU-NO-FANSUB
Let leave to me!
Or I will carry felt sorry for near the court
martial for offense towards a superior!
You hear that?
The cour martiale!
Will have you that to do it
when you can it.
You! Slacken this person!
All our excuses, Lieutenant!
I warned you!
I am the special inspector
envoy by the HQ of the Navy.
The Lieutenant of frigate, Shepard!
Hum… The band of Straw hat
some share by there must be.
I want well to take them
in hunting still a little.
I will wait until they
leave their burrow.
These pirates of Straw hat
we gave wire to retordre.
Research will show after it
delicious meal which will give again us forces.
It is what that?
It is different from it
that one ate this morning.
Ouais, I never ate a meal
like that of this morning until now…
He, cooks!!
Spin us of good
puff out like this morning!
Slip by of good food us!
Jessica-san!
All the soldiers complain about the meal.
Slip by of good food us!
Finally… Leave us
to use this receipt!
Slip by of good food us!
My friends,
where thus the honor passed
cooks of Navarone?
Jessica-san!
This cook was perhaps a pirate.
Only, it concocté dishes for
soldiers returning of their mission the empty belly.
It is a cook of exception!
It is true.
Its kitchen had the virtue
to give energy!
An incommensurable number soldiers
are them also fallen under the charm.
Please,
reconsider your words.
Please.
Please, Jessica-san.
PLEASE!
I do not want to lose vis-a-vis him.
We will prepare ourselves the goods
dishes which give people full with energy.
But today, let us put
our self-esteem on side…
and let us borrow its receipt
that it left us.
It is true that when it
found in this kitchen,
he was not a pirate
but a cook out-par!
And the priority of a cook is
to be able to satisfy its customers!
Jessica-san!
You dispatch!
Made not await the customers!
Ouais!
Then Nami… One will do what there?
It is not yet too late…
One can move towards the gate
to leave to reach the ocean.
Ouais, soldiers from here
do not make the things with half.
Even if one wants gold, one
risk our skin, what!
Do Luffy, you think what of it?
I want gold but I have the flagstone!
Sanji, prepares puffs out it!
I will throw an eye on
ingredients and to see what I can do.
But our reserves are empty!
While excavating as it is necessary,
something well will be found.
You want to really flee
by giving up gold here?
Ouais, ouais.
Ah ah, what a damage!
The division of this treasure would be
equitable, it is obvious!
Normal, considering the enormous quantity of gold!
Our life would be so much more
comfortable with each one our share…
Ouah! The same share each one!
Naturally.
I awaited it!! I go
to buy a bronze statue to me!
Really? I could
to buy books to me?
Last medical books!
I would like to study the last techniques
medical appeared that I am still unaware of!
A new pan, a news frying pan,
ustensils and an effective rat-trap…
It me will remain about it more than one should not any.
I could drink as much as I want.
Then?
Oui-Oui!
Initially, 80% represent
my hidden economies.
Wait a little!
I joke!
Obviously how it is a joke!
Who would have economies
also colossal?!
Major the part of this gold
will use to repair the boat.
The boat? You want to speak about Merry?
Exact! It is our Going all the same
Merry which took us along up to now.
Now that I think there…
it is true that one embarked from my village
native in East Blue and badly not sailed with…
It dates a little but.
I undertook personally
design of this ship…
and of the assembly with
to start from my plan…
until the placement of the veils.
I present Going Merry to you!
Hurry to go up.
One is friendly, not truth?
Ca-captain…
It is me, the Captain!
Do not say anything!
This ship transported things so much,
it east impresses memories….
I decided to leave our island.
Good… I from go away.
I go there.
One crossed the Mountain Reverse
and travelled on Large Line…
thanks to him.
Incredible…
The backward flow of water
point towards the top.
It left!
One entered the clouds!
I see it!
It is thus that, more
large sea in the world.
Large Line!
One Piece is
some share with far!
GO!!!
Then, one went
in the Celestial islands…
Who is the navigatrice of this boat?
It is you, Nami-san!
m 262.703 B 267.711.265 715.269.709 B 270.706.273 702.275.698 B 277.696.277 695.283.686 B 287.680.290 675.291.673 B 298.663.304 655.311.647 L 322.635 L 344.614 B 357.599.366 588.372.580 B 377.571.380 560.380.549 B 380.537.374 526.363.518 B 352.508.338 504.322.504 B 312.504.304 505.297.509 B 289.514.283 518.279
523 B 277.527.276 530.274.534 L 269.547 B 264.538.261 530.257.523 B 248.511.234 504.214.504 B 198.504.185 508.174.518 B 161.526.157 536.157.549 B 157.559.159 569.165.580 B 170.588.180 600.192.614 B 207.628.220 641.227.647 L 235.658 B 239.663.243 667.245.673 L 254.686 L 259.695 B 260.697.261 702.263.703 L 262.703
He, band of idiots, made
what Nami-san orders!
Ouais!
ONE FLIES!!
Brilliant! This boat flies!
Nami-san, you are superb!
m 262.703 B 267.711.265 715.269.709 B 270.706.273 702.275.698 B 277.696.277 695.283.686 B 287.680.290 675.291.673 B 298.663.304 655.311.647 L 322.635 L 344.614 B 357.599.366 588.372.580 B 377.571.380 560.380.549 B 380.537.374 526.363.518 B 352.508.338 504.322.504 B 312.504.304 505.297.509 B 289.514.283 518.279
523 B 277.527.276 530.274.534 L 269.547 B 264.538.261 530.257.523 B 248.511.234 504.214.504 B 198.504.185 508.174.518 B 161.526.157 536.157.549 B 157.559.159 569.165.580 B 170.588.180 600.192.614 B 207.628.220 641.227.647 L 235.658 B 239.663.243 667.245.673 L 254.686 L 259.695 B 260.697.261 702.263.703 L 262.703
J-I I
love you!!!
Me… I already protected it
ship with the danger of my life!
Not! Stop!
Please, stops!
All but not the boat!
Shit!
Then there was this unknown
who repaired us the ship….
I It AI SEEN FOR TRUTH!!
It is insane with all that it
boxed, it held good!
It held out until now,
but it in ruins, isn't this falls?
I am of agreement.
It is the great patching up
of Going Merry!
I am therefore!
Well, I do not know yet with
how much will rise the total expenditure…
One will have to reserve the division
equitable until the resumption of the treasure.
Us were plundered
majority of our food,
but what was with
the interior of the refrigerator was intact.
Eh well, go ahead.
Indeed, do-it-yourself of amateur of Usopp
will not allow us to go well far.
I said it to you! I am gunner
and not naval engineer!
But the old Mechanic-san
had also advised me…
that it would have to be done
to repair for good.
The ideal would be to take it along
on a shipyard…
so that a true engineer
naval can occupy itself some.
There thus exist people more
qualified that you in repair, Usopp.
From time to time it is better that a pro
takes care some, if not one could regret it!
Ouaip! It is decided!
One will seek a naval engineer
to become our companion.
One will live still full with adventures.
Ouais.
Its aptitude will be essential.
Ouais, ouais.
Merry, it is our house with all.
It is our life!
One will go in the search of an engineer
who will take care of the ship!
It starts again…
It is so rare when it
express yourself on essential things.
It is important! It is what one will do!
Then, it is decided!
Ouais, that would be well
to find somebody.
And also a musician!
Not, drops.
It is quite beautiful
to give objectives,
but you had not forgotten
the condition sine-qua not?
Which?
One must recover our gold!
Indeed.
Still should it be known where
our gold is stored…
Probably in a trunk.
It well is known, that.
It is precisely because one does not know
the place of the trunk which one breaks the head!
Do not excite you.
Here perhaps?
It is only one presumption…
But if gold is dissimulated
in the fortress,
it is surely in
the part best kept.
That does not astonish me by you, Robin-chan!
It is true! This place
with the air to lend itself to it!
Ok, everyone! One goes
over there and our gold is recovered!
But one will leave Going Merry here?
It would be likely to be discovered.
If you want to hide a tree,
hide it in the forest!
If you want to hide a ship,
hide it among all the ships!
Of agreement, it is right that….
It is not a ship only one
can dissimulate so easily…
Formerly, this dock was an old building site
naval where and repaired the boats were manufactured.
When we moved here, I have
between outline several intact materials.
I see! I have just had an idea!
Here what one will do….
I would need your assistance to all!
Ouais!!
Then?
With that, there will not be any more blood
of ink to be been done for Merry!
To disguise our Going Merry in the ship
Navy, what a brilliant idea!
I wonder whether one will pass sufficiently
unperceived under this getup merdic.
While looking under several different angles,
I see only a navire de guerre Navy!
Yes.
It is serious…?
Well! It is time
to recover our gold!
The guy, our mission
will begin at midnight crushes!
Of agreement?
Ouais!!
But why one
does not start now?
Ben, it is obvious, one
more fishing will have the night.
Ah ok!! It is for
environment, I see!
I see.
Euh… That does not have anything to see!
Going merry is now in safety but
, you wait there will not go there like that!
Good blood, to move in group,
it is too much risky!
Listen well, I go you
to reveal my special plan.
Soon in One Part:
Not there, it is me!
Plans of the resumption of gold
and of the recovery of Waver!
I will become valorous
warrior of the seas!
You too?
and of the recovery of Waver!
Plans of the resumption of gold