The plan of Eneru God
come to a end.
Luffy comes to defy Eneru,
but it falls from the Arch.
What is there? You managed
to survive all this time.
Forget these lower imbeciles.
There is a future which you wish, not?
A future which I do wish?
Yes, I have one of them.
But, if I were to leave
with you, I would be alone.
The truth, it is that there is a multitude
of thing which I want to make or to have.
But if I must give up these people
and outward journey with you to have them…
Then I do not want anything!
I of insane who you would be a god.
If you installations would not be this
that a finger on Nami-san,
I would become it
Demon of the Blue Sea!
NAMI-SWAAAN!
mezameta futari
Two Reveillees People!
The Face of the Love Ignites!!
moeru koi No kyuushyutsuzen SEN
If you do not wish to remain on board this vessel, then you have only one possible destination.
It is a forthcoming life.
It is impossible for
me to overcome this type.
However, I do not want
not to remain on this boat!
My heart…
no regret has.
Well, following that, you include/understand well that you will not be able to leave this healthy and safe arch.
Or then, you by chance would count on
two mice which was introduced on board?
I… I want to go down!
To this pace, one will go so high
that one will not be able to go down any more, Sanji!
Moreover, God must
to find on this arch.
One already started to climb
the arch! It is necessary to go until the end!
But how
you will be caught there, Sanji?!
This boat is so large that it could
to have well there hundreds of enemies on board!
One will not be able to even unload.
It is not all. One does what
if God and the Priests are there?
He, you ace jitter or what?!
However, you ace of the effective tools.
You can fight well not?!
It is not for that
I invented them!
At all events, now we know
that our enemy uses his Mantra.
It is not the sorrow to move back.
One already had to be made locate
by the enemy since one moment.
They know that one is there?
How one makes now?
Useless to worry some!
When one is inside, one
separate and one goes on the bridge.
Nami-san
find over there!
Q-what? Good Ah, one separates?!
Be insane for you?!
One does not even know how much
they are in it!
They is too dangerous, two people alone will not be enough to overcome them, then why…
Imbecile!
If one does not separate, one
will be beaten both.
How that? You say that to
less will one of us die?
One minute… by chance waits…
do not only say to me…
it is to save Nami.
Listen to me, Usopp.
If is to save Nami-san,
it is not serious if you sacrifice yourself.
I WILL KILL YOU, DUMB!
Go, one goes there!
Await to me Nami-san!
Our discussion was not finished!
Nami-swan!
He wait! Await me, Sanji! He!
Wait! Sanji-kun!
It would be said that they are beautiful
and come well to save you.
They are really ridiculous.
Who thus? With Luffy share,
nobody is in a position to move.
Moreover, how they are
gone up on board boat?
Even if the helps arrive,
nobody will be saved.
And then, I do not have
need to await them.
I must count on the chance… I
can only jump out of the boat.
If not, I am sure
to 100% to die here.
I face the lightning…
There is a means
to overcome it?
What is it that?
In fact the machines do all.
Not need for machinists
or of hommes de main, hein?
, That I do not like shit.
There is nobody here!
But in a so large boat…
why machines
function of themselves?
How this boat can fly away?
I had never seen that!
The simple fact of going up
on this boat frightens me.
It is strange!
What can feed it well?
There is a risk
what does the boat fall?
Moreover, even if one finds Nami on
bridge, one will not be able to be left there afterwards.
How one is
to make, brothel?
Sky…
darkens more and more.
It for soon
to begin the destruction.
And unfortunately…
the Gold Bell must be
just above us.
Assemble all on the boats
! Do not remain here!
Quickly on the White Sea! It
does not have there time to lose!
What a sinister boat!
It is really the end of this country!
To evacuate the village? But Chief…
What are warriors made?
They are not yet
incomes Upper-Yard!
Useless to await them.
Why that?
What do you say?
The warriors are not any more of the children.
They can only manage.
Believe in them.
Eneru will make disappear this country.
Ca is not any doubt.
Just like it destroyed
its native land, Bilka.
It tries to destroy
this one also.
Go, will run to your boats!
Our priority is to save
life of the villagers here present!
Any thing has an end.
Wiper, that is enough.
You made any possible tone!
You come from the Blue Sea?
Ouais, one comes from in bottom.
You live here?
All occurs in
the forest in front of me…
But I cannot see it.
I can only wait.
You all…
Return healthy and safe!
Bird-horse-chan
!
Afflicted! You protected me!
Aisa?
Aisa!
AISA!
Luffy?
You are alive?
Where are you?
By here!
Here!
Aisa!
Aisa!!
He!
I helps!
Here! Here! Here!
How you made ace
to fall like that?!
Good!
Shit! I do not arrive at
to remove this gold testicle!
[Note:kintama = testicle/testicle of gold]
Do not speak about testicle!
In any event, it is necessary to return
at the place where was Robin!
One cannot let make Eneru.
I included/understood!
Do not believe only that
will be enough to stop me!
I will follow your boat!
I know where it goes!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
Very interesting, young girl.
I succeeded…
It crowned weapons there in
blue Sea, so that I see.
THUNDERBALL
They is very clever to create
a current to deviate the lightning.
That implies solids
weather knowledge.
But… that is not enough.
You seem to have already understood that if I increase the power, that will not function!
Isn't this?
I have another thing to make.
Disappear!!
I cannot dodge it.
It is you which will disappear!!
[Note:explosive ball mortal]
Die…
Afflicted.
Usopp!
Then it was you!
One met on the boat.
Is Euh… where Sanji?
Sanji-kun? It is him there too?
Good Ah, it did not arrive yet?!
I see.
Hello.
Hééé!!
Do I have to flee?
Would Usopp the hefty man flee?
You ES GOD AND THEN?!
Usopp!
Nami!
Yes?
What can I make?
Save me!
Cretin!
But came to you to save me or not?!
Ben…
I am not any more very sure.
THEN WHAT YOU INSANE?!
He well…
He well what?! SAVE ME, BROTHEL!!
To save you?
But finally, it is God see?
Oh, you ace reason!
With the Nami fact, this hat…
Yes, it is that of Luffy.
It was there very with
the hour but it fell.
But he did not die. He will leave himself there.
The arch flies away.
One cannot count on
Luffy to save us!
Exact!
Will be necessary to manage!
I do not want to die today!
Included/understood!
He!
Remain beside this electric tube!
It is perhaps the system of the boat!
It will not be able to launch
powerful attacks above!
Usopp! Look by-there!
Waver!
Our only chance
it is to jump with!
To jump?! From this height, one goes…
Not.
In the middle of the forest, it
there a zone of ilonimbus has!
If one can reach it, one will be saved!
I see!
Shit!
I will try to distract God!
Prepare!
Ok!
Take that, God!
usopp
[Note:Spell = Magic spell]
“You were inserted a needle
between the nail and the flesh! “
Aah!
The simple fact of thinking that of it hurt!
Idiot! Stop yourself the ears
if not you could die!
“You cut yourself the finger with a sheet
of paper right on the articulation. “
“You have five mouth ulcers
purulent on the gum!! “
Usopp!
In any event, I must all prepare!
If one wants to escape,
it is our only chance!
Usopp…
It is the right direction!
The ilonimbus are just
under this bean stem!
They is good! I am ready…
USOPP!!
Even if you just seek to flee,
it will not be easy with me.
Do you want nevertheless to test?
You cheeks with a hide-and-seek
mortal with God!
Usopp! Take my hand!
Your hand!
Even now,
do not hope to be saved!
Usopp!
You bar!
EL
Sanji-kun!
Start, Nami!
THOR
Await Usopp!
Why accelerate you?!
And Sanji-kun?!
It is necessary to flee!
You do not want nevertheless
to waste the sacrifice of a man?!
They finally jumped!
They did not include/understand yet with
what a not I am powerful?!
They are always also vulnerable.
He, God!
I have something to say to you!
But before that…
Thank you.
I sought fire
to light my cig.
Another thing?
Ouais.
Prepare with chialer.
What?
The Arch…
Prepare with chialer.
You… do not only say to me…
Dumb!
What you have
fact in the boat?!