Be content for you?
The doctor considered as a witch
Please, save my companion!
Please, call a doctor!!
Forgive me not to be myself presented.
I am called Dalton.
I am the captain of the guard of this island.
The only doctor lives as a hermit in this castle at the top of the mountain.
Why is it necessary that she lives so high?
Take care of me, Capitaine.
I was sure. As soon as the captain says something, the navigator follows.
Yosh, allons-y!
Before Nami dies!
Do not say similar things!
It is of Lapahns that?
Wapol-Sama!
What?
We finally arrived on our premises!
It is our terre natale, the island of Drum!
Nami?
Nami-San?
Soon… In Arabasta…
All is well, rendors.
Do not occupy you of nothing for the moment.
Even if its own life is in danger…
Nami-San, hold good still a little.
It is necessary that one reaches this rotten castle where this doctor saw.
Bar you, rabbits of shit!
They arrive!
Ouais!
Listen, Luffy!
No matter what it arrives, does not attack them.
Why?
Idiot. If you put yourself to attack them or if you are caught a blow,
it is Nami-San which will be directly touched!
And she will die.
COM-included/understood! I will not fight with them!
But then, that do I have to make?
For the moment, avoids them!
Dodge, dodging, dodging and course!
But does not move back!
It is too difficult!
Shit! This snow prevents me from striking of all my forces!
They all arrive at the same time!
Sink in wood!
I cover you!
On the left all! Direction the mountain!
Included/understood.
It is necessary that one finds a means of sowing them!
If one must all do them, one until fell the night from there. Exactly it with what one can expect with animals of snows.
It is without hope!
Imbecile! I said to you not to attack them!!
Leave the-me!
Afflicted…
I do not joke!
Sanji! There is a way up there!
Well! Continuous!
Why does devil you ace do that?
Continue to run until in top!
Ca becomes really dangerous up there.
Made that Nami-San is healthy and safe.
But… which are you thus?
Who we are?
To travel until Large Line with for crew
6 people without doctor…
Ca appears rather absurd.
We are pirates.
It for that you pointed your weapons on us, isn't this is?
Although that is a small crew, As long as the courageous warrior of the sea Usopp-Sama is one as of their, they will never fail!
Oh?
However, we need a doctor.
We thought of meeting one of them on this island
who would become one of our companions, but…
But which could have thought that your only doctor
is a witch living in a castle?
Which strange combination.
You are certainly not the kind of pirates
which we expected.
Dalton-San!
Dalton-San.
Oh, happy to re-examine you.
You Doctor Kureha, isn't this seeks?
Yes, it is exact.
However, the patient is already…
It is said that it has just gone down
at the close village Cocoaweed.
What did you say?
They come from louper!!
Couldn't He, landlord, you make it conceal?
This kid cries so extremely that I cannot any more support it.
Oh, I am really sorry.
He, Tamachibi, which does arrive to you?
You have some share badly?
I cannot help you as long as you cry.
You annoy the customers.
Tamachibi, speaks!
I will throw you outside, if you do not stop!
The witch?
The witch…
I am afraid…
And it is still with him…  This alarming monster…
Go! Stop that!
Oya, oya. This child has really an ungrateful father.
When a newborn ceases crying,
that means that its body is sick.
Remain behind, Chopper.
Excuse me.
You are content, small snotty-nosed kid?
Dr. Kureha!
The secrecy of my youth?
Not, it was not asked!
I do not manage to believe that it is really 140 years old!
I am always 139 years old!
Do I have to look after it?
To look after which? My son is not at all sick!
You are doctor?
Good, allons-y Chopper.
Wait, please!
Forgive me.
It is an error of my share.
I heard yesterday that the doctor was to come, but
I thought that it would spend several days to go down.
It is not your fault.
The problem it is the superhuman force of Luffy and Sanji!
We would be probably unable of
to follow in top of this mountain.
If the witch is at the village of Cocoaweed, it is necessary to ask him to turn over to its castle immediately!
Yes, you are right.
We do not have an other choice.
Forgive me…
Because this country is without doctor…
Not, not, there is no reason to be excused, Dalton-San.
It is true!
We dispatch!
My hand… I have badly…
Is your hand, it well that?
Whereas do say you that?
My leg!!!
Hold, looks at, you ace more badly with the hand!
What do you believe to make?
be content for you?
Content?
Well. Now remains quiet.
He!
Do not shout, I just touched his leg slightly.
But it was a very strong noise…
It has badly with the hands and the legs.
It does not have a fever.
But its leg swells because of a purulent ignition.
The stage is already quite advanced.
It has a bacteriological infection of the bones.
Chopper, will seek me antibiotics.
D-doctor… My son is…
The treatment sufficiently early of this disease is the key of survival.
You do not worry. It will be left there,
whereas it should have died.
To die?
I will make some incisions,
then would be courageous my boy.
Won't He, you anaesthetize it?
Here your anesthesia.
Made not that!
The drugs make effect well.
There will not be need for treatment additional.
Bandage to him the legs well while it rests.
Once you will have arranged it, keep it cold. Included/understood?
In compensation…
I am with court of bag-dustbin and toilet paper.
I will take all the food you have here.
And…
I want 50% of the receipts of the capital of this pub.
Chopper, brings all to the sledge.
, You Have-await are not serious?
Half of my capital?
Does not leave it you berner, landlord!
It will strip you!
Ouais, it is sure!
What does she want to say by “should have died”?
If that is the newborn made that to cry!
You misuse your statute of doctor!
Ouais, ouais!
Do not benefit from weak people, old witch!
Slept, Chopper!
They are right dirty snotty-nosed kid which râlent.
Grandmother…
I feel much better.
Thank you!
Oya! It would be said that I had a good tip.
I will drop to 49%.
I will pay.
Thank you.
Oh… Kid.
This wellbeing…
Does not forget it!
Yes!
The weather is so cold!!
My body engourdit as if I were on ice!
But I did not finish any yet.
Once my completely emptied spirit, fire will be refreshed,
and the ice will be heated!
He Karu! Go down too!
This drive will make only good with your weak body.
He, there is full of fish down there.
I think that I will go back there.
They continue to arrive?
Not.
Yosha! I suppose that they were sown!
Incredible!
What do they make?
They are irritated because they are hungry?
Not…
Wait.
And shit! They go…
You… Now say to us who you are.
It is sure, you do not act like a normal villager.
In fact, when you speak, I feel a soldier.
I was… with the service of the former King.
I was the subordinate of Wapol.
Since the reign of the last king, I was useful as a captain of the guard of this country.
But when the king died,
his/her Wapol son succeeded to him the throne.
And the country changed.
Oh yes! I have just thought of a new brilliant law!
Exile all the doctors of the country!
To exile?
Doctors?
Exactly.
Gather the 20 best doctors and make my personal specialists.
I will call them the “Isshi-20”.
The “Isshi-20”?
Yes, the “Isshi-20”.
All the other doctors will have to be exiled!
You are brilliant, Wapol-Sama!
What a marvellous idea!
But if one does that, which will deal with the patients?
And what do their diseases have to see with me?
Whoever wants to see a doctor owes prosterner in front of me!
There will be nobody any more in this country to be opposed to me!
I am… a genius!
Therefore, whoever falls ill will have to conclude
a market with Wapol to see Isshi-20?
And the price to pay to receive a medical care was enormous.
It is the same thing as to control by taking the inhabitants in hôtage!
It is not a government!
It is a crime.
Yes, without any doubt.
Shit! I made some too much and I swam too far!
Where am I? Where is the boat?
Name of god, there is so much snow here which I have no idea where I am!
Oh! Saved!
He, grandmother, that would disturb you of me
to lead to the city nearest?
But why devil you have the belly with the air
by a similar cold? Insane old woman…
You should pay attention so that you known as.
I am always a young person, too young hundred-thirty year!
Allons-y, Chopper. There are not time to lose with odd people.
He, wait!
What does not go in this rotten old woman skin?
I am cold!
Shit, I will have problems if I remain here.
I suppose that a muscular drive should heat me.
Me revoilà! I am finally of return in my country!
The kingdom of Drum!
Therefore, they set up a patrol of monitoring.
With what devil did think by drawing us above?
Oh, what a seen for my sensitive eyes, the island of Drum!
Unchanged, majestic, Natural Mother!
Is Chess, the castle healthy and except?
Yes.
It is in the same state that losque we left, Wapol-Sama.
Then, direction the castle!
Let us turn over to my castle!
I have some to be a pirate enough!
I become again King!
Ahead, Robson!
He, Robson! Stop sleeping and advances!
Go, hurries and advances!
Wapol-Sama, I have bad news!
What still?
The pirates of yesterday moored their boat with the bank!
What?
This dirty small… What Straw hat
and do its crew make in my kingdom?
Even if they said not to know where it was, they are there!
Release me!
Do they have the least idea of what arrived to me afterwards?
Now, go over there and kill them!
But precisely the boat is completely empty!
What?
One does not know where they are!
You want to be made carry out?
I am really sorry Wapol-Sama.
Please excuse this good with nothing!
Chess. Kuromarimo.
We explored the neighborhoods of the ship in the search of prints.
We think that they went in Bighorn.
I see. You are geniuses.
Well, we will start by announcing the return of monarchy by a blow of gun to Bighorn!
What you known as?
It already left the village?
One comes from the louper?
What a binding!
She cured my infection.
You seek Doctor Dalton-San?
We have an urgency with a patient.
You know where it went?
Somebody said that Doctor Kureha moved towards Gyasta.
Gyasta?
Where is it?
While crossing by Bighorn, it is opposite.
One still crossed?
Ice-skating is very popular by here.
It does not matter!
I did not ask anything!
The calm one, Usopp-San!
Nevertheless, us should leave.
Now that one arrived up to now, one does not have time to lose.
Ouais, you are right.
Dalton-San?
You were there…
You were not judicious to make the guet today?
What arrives to you? What did it occur?
All the other guards… were killed.
What?
Of only one blow this boat arrived of the ocean and…
They killed everyone!
Who are they?
Calm yourself and say to me who did that to you!
Dalton-San, please, save us!
With our force we cannot…
What does it occur?
It is him?
It is Wapol!
Wapol is of return!
What has it just said?
Is Wapol of return?
Dalton-San!
I will put an end to all that!
I do not intend to play the part of justice here…
You and me guilty sums of the same crime!
You will not go further, Wapol!
They really will do it… these rabbits of shit!
It is not true…
He Sanji. What is there?
What occurs?
He. Course, Luffy.
To run? In which direction?
Anywhere, also far you can!
They will cause an avalanche!