Luffy is entirely encircled!
The secret plan of the Admiral Nelson
Oh… One is outside! Outside!
That they immediately are continued!
Still a thing, Major! Erik-San also returned and it goes up in this moment on the boat.
They try to catch up with us!
The Merry Vogue can sail more quickly, but…
Will He, what one make arrived at the Gunkan island once?
Worry you!
How that?
As long as one finds the nest of the dragons in first
and what one gives Ryuji on feet, it is essence, not?
It will not be easy.
The small fish entered our nets!
How all the ships are put in range!
Akuyoku Formation!
Oh not… One is taken with the trap!
One will board their ships,
their foutre a beating and to break these chains.
It is the only solution.
It is not a so bad idea.
Well! Ahead!
One arrives!
Marvellous! What a splendid spectacle!
Especially do not stop the attacks only one second!
Yes!
But…
My invaluable due must remain intact!
Yes, Admiral!
Sennenryu which I sought during so a long time
is finally with my range.
And the elixir of youth of Ryukotsu will be soon with me!
Report!
The flagship announces that the plan is a success!
They will continue the attacks on their side!
It would be said that our mission is finished.
If that continues, they will fall right into the hands from Nelson Royale.
Wait, Major!
What still?
Prepare to me a boat with
three men to row.
A boat?
For what to make?
If not your masts will be destroyed.
You are insane!
You will enter the circle?
Make, it is to it all!
Apis! They is dangereous because of here,
go down in the hold!
I cannot leave Ryuji alone!
He, wait! Return!
He, they is dangerous, return here!
I cannot help you if you tombs.
Ryuji!
Hold good still a little, Ok?
One will bring you to the nest of the dragons, Ok?
Ah… which courage.
I have the tears with the eyes of them.
Very well! After having reduced these boats in parts, one will bring you to the nest of the dragons!
One touched us by behind!
He, Sanji! One is touched!
Sanji!
One died! One will run!
The farm! They missed us!
Ah? Really?
Yes!
Ah, saved… Which is the imbecile
who made me this stupid joke?
It is you!
They is good! They is good!
Ahead!
He! A boulet de canon arrives by here!
I can nothing make of other,
you ace that with you to occupy some!
Well, I will test that!
Incredible!
This immonde small freluquet, how he dares
to touch one of my men-of-war?
What do you wait?
Deploy the gun of massive destruction!
Yes!
You will not be able to escape!
You will be with me!!
Prepare you to draw with the gun from massive destruction!
The pirate vessel is out of cheek!
Loan to make fire!
It is what that?
If one is touched by this trick, one will finish in crumbs!
Worry you! I will reforward it once again!
Do not say conneries!
One must change course!
Quickly, will move the back!
Dispatches you
Eye for eye! I will show you what I am able!
Here it is done!
Take that!
Fire!
Made fire!
What did it occur?
The enemy gun drew on ours!
What do you have says?
You dispatch and help me to raise me!
Yes!
Then you liked?
It is what arrives when
Usopp-Sama becomes serious!
It was certainly bowl.
Yes, surely.
What? I can remake it when I want! Look at me!
Wahou! What a shooting!
Usopp, they was super!
All will be well.
Worry you! Remember, you must protect Apis!
With which you speak?
In Ryuji.
It is our chance now.
Cut the chains and clear us an exit
as long as they are surprised.
Yes, Nami-San.
Luffy!
Let make me!
Ok!
Ryuji!
Await me here!
Me v' there party!
Afflicted, Zoro!
You…
I want a total return of the situation!
Yes!
Three pirates approached the man-of-war
with starboard nearest.
Hein? How is this possible?
Steel chains!
You can cut them?
There is not only I donot can cross.
Well. Go ahead!
It would be said that they all are here.
I would like to take the part of right-hand side.
As you want.
I let to you do the housework.
Ok!
To have reversed the Admiral Nelson,
we will not let all to you break.
Yes! Yes! Go ahead! Go ahead!
It is brilliant!
Cut them!
Cut to them all!
Shit!
How you of the pirates of shoddy goods dare you to cut my barrier?
Capture them at all costs or
I will put all at once to you with irons!!
They arrive!
Incredible!
They are really strong…
There remains only one chain!
I will operate the boat!
Yes chief!
Not! Not! That somebody stops them!
Oh Erik! Played well!
Maintaining Sennenryu is with me!
Hein? Which fun…
It is you the fag who ate the Okama fruit.
Not “Okama” but the fruit Kama Kama!
Okama = Fag | Kama = a scythe
Gamine! You must leave me this Sennenryu now!
Not question! I will never give you Ryuji!
The farm and leaves the-us!
Not!
You know that I can use my Kamaitachi
to cut out you as much as I wish it.
Stop!
If you touch this child,
I will never forgive it to you!
It is true, Usopp-Sama will not let to you do that!
Bandage the innocent ones.
The Kamaitachi last missed its express target.
Stop me once again and the next one will make fly.
I will reduce your boat of pieces.
What is there?
It is still him.
Hein? It does what?
Quickly! Fasten the raft with the boat!
It would be said that it took Apis as an hostage to steal the dragon.
It is not well that!
Wait! If you try to strike it,
it will kill Apis and the others!
I see! I include/understand!
Then, I will strike it!
You me listenings at least?
Maintaining Sennenryu is with me,
especially, do not want me.
Salt bastard! Return to us Apis!
Erik, excel work!
Now, the-I pays!
I do not think!
I believe that I will keep it for me.
What do you tell?
I only obeyed you to profit
information network of the Navy.
Traitor!
One is in the same ship, not true?
You only engaged me for your interest.
I gave you a colossal sum!
You gave me it is a true little argent de poche.
But I am not obliged to respect the orders of a large Morse like you.
A Morse? A Morse???
With Ryukotsu of this Sennenryu,
I will become invincible!
You will pay it to me… You will pay it to me!
Kill this traitor!
Fire! Fire!!
They draw again…
Avoid these boulets de canon!
If you want to live, I suggest you rowing!
Stop!
I ask you not to maltreat Ryuji never again!
Ryuji anything did you!
Quiet remainder!
One must as fast as possible bring back Ryuji to the nest of the dragons!
Please, stop!
What you made? Release me!
Put back me immediately!
Stupid gamine! You are my hostage,
and your Sennenryu belongs to me from now on.
I will never give Ryuji to a monster such as you!
Never I will give up it!
That is enough, small plague!
Still a word and I reduce to you in parts.
That is enough!!
This gamine bit me well!
He! Return!
Return immediately!!
Shit!!!!
Ryuji! Test that! They is good!
He, Ryuji, eat!
And you will be better, Ok?
Oh it is so nice!
That suits you well, Ryuji!
Make conceal it!
Ahhh!! My ears!!
Ryuji howls with death.
Ryuji!
You can move! I am so content!
I am so content!
Hein?
It is not true?
What is this…
… what it manufactures?
It is that! Go, Ryuji! You can fly!
It succeeded! Ryuji flies!
Not question!
I want this dragon for me!
I will not let this Sennenryu escape!
Fire! Cut down it!!
Stop!!
Ryuji, flies!
Fly out of reach guns.
Fly!
It is that! You dispatch, cut down it!
That is enough!!
Flee before they réattaquent, Ryuji!
What do you wait?
Open fire!
Yes!
We must descend it!
Ryuji! Not by there!
With what he does think?
He moves by here!
Quickly! Cut down it!!
It arrives! Fire! Fire!!
Ryuji!!
Ryuji, holds good!
He! About what you do speak?
You should not think of dying.
Yes. I know.
I will take care of Apis,
and I will bring you to the nest of the dragons.
Then fight!
Ryuji!!!!!!!