So tough...
"I'm Luffy! The man who will become the Pirate King!"
"Ore wa Luffy! Kaizoku-ou ni naru Otoko da!"
(Based on Manga ch.2: "They
Call Him Straw-Hat Luffy")
Don't worry about it...
The whirlpool won't do
any damage to this ship.
Miss!
Can I dance with you?
Not again!
You missed!
You said you missed?
Eh? Huh?
It's so heavy...
It's got wine inside! I guess...
We got it!
There is a ship behind us!
With a pirate mark on it!
It's a pirate ship!
Enemy coming!
Captain! A pirate ship!
What?
Stay calm, everybody!
Stay calm! Follow your orders!
Attack!
Koby!
Yes!
Who is the most beautiful
person on the sea?
The captain of the ship...
it's you, Miss Alvida!
Good answer...
Thank you.
Miss Alvida! We got a
good quarry this time.
That's right...
Let's board!
Aye!
I'll show those busters how good I am!
For I'm Iron-Mace Alvida!
Koby! What are you doing?
I'm scared...
You dare to disobey my order?
Please don't hurt me...
Then go! Right away!
It hurts...
Fear me!
We won't kill you,
but you must turn over
everything valuable!
We'll throw anyone to
the sea who try to resist!
Hello there...
Seems like no one's here.
That's good...
What a big barrel...
Who are you? I've never seen you before!
Hey kid!
Slacking off again, are you?
No, no! I'm trying to move it!
Okay! Let's make it lighter!
Yes! I'm thirsty!
How can we do that?
If Miss Alvida finds
out, she will kill us!
You can keep your mouth shut...
...can you, Koby?
I... I... yes!
It's really heavy.
I can't wait!
Shut up! I'll open it now!
Yeah!
Nice nap!
What the...
Who are you?
We ask the same question!
He'll catch cold sleeping there.
It's your fault!
Don't you know we're pirates?
We act this way! Well?
I'm hungry! Got any food?
Listen to me!
You runt!
Go to hell!
What're you doing?
Who are you?
Me?
I'm Monkey D. Luffy, at you service!
What? What happened?
What's the matter with him?
Run! Quickly!
If they find you here, you'll die!
But I'm hungry.
You're in mortal danger!
They got a gang on the deck!
Oh yeah?
Come with me.
Not there!
That hurts!
Oh!
Food! Food!
It's great!
The most dangerous place
might be the most safest.
What should I eat first?
That box! Yes! That's right!
Looks good!
I'm Koby! You're Luffy, aren't you?
You're good! How did you do it?
This is good!
Isn't this a pirate ship?
No, it isn't.
This ship was hijacked by Miss Alvida.
So what?
Is there a boat on this ship?
I think so.
My boat got swallowed up.
Oh? That whirlpool? You survived it?
Yes! I was shocked, If
you can believe that!
Are you a companion of those pirates?
It's the most miserable
day of my life...
I was on my way fishing,
taking a boat offshore...
Huh?
And somehow, I boarded a pirate ship!
The next year,
They didn't kill me
they kept me as a slave.
You're not only stupid,
you're also an idiot!
Don't say it like that.
Why didn't you run away?
It's impossible! No way!
If I were caught, what will happen?
I'm so afraid to think of that!
You're a wuss!
You make me sick!
Hey! Don't just stand there!
Move all of those before
the navy gets here!
Or you can have the
taste of my Iron Mace!
A good haul! so much
fortune on this ship!
Don't fool around! beware
of Miss Alvida's Iron Mace!
It would be painful!
Nobody can take that!
Miss Alvida!
Yes?
Something came up!
What do you mean?
The barrel...
There is a monster!
What did you say?
Not you! We mean there
is a monster in the barrel!
Maybe a bounty hunter!
What?
I think you're right...
I wish I have the courage
to drift in a barrel.
I would like to do something.
By the way...
Luffy, why are you traveling?
I want to be the King of Pirates!
Oh!
The King of Pirates? Yeah!
Is it true?
Of course!
Luffy, are you a pirate too?
Yes!
How about your companion?
No one! I'm trying to find someone.
The King of Pirates...
...has control of the whole world!
It also means a treasure
of fortune, fame and power!
The lucky person with the "One Piece"!
Oh! "Oh"? What "oh"?
All the pirates are
looking for that treasure!
That's my goal, too!
No way! No way! Absolutely No way!
How can it be possible for
you to stand on the top?
No way! No way!
Why did you do that?
I wanted to do it, no reason!
Forget it; I'm used to it.
I don't care if it's possible or not...
I want to be the King of Pirates.
I've made up my mind
If I should fight 'till
I die! It doesn't matter!
Ok! I'm full! I should
try to find a boat.
Can I have a boat if I sack them?
Hope they're not so stingy!
I never thought of it that way...
I can do it too!
With the courage If I should die...
What are you talking about?
Can I join the navy too?
Navy?
That's right! To catch some bad guys!
The dream I had since I
was a kid! Can I do it?
How should I know?
Yes!I should try it!
Being a slave like this,
it's better to run away!
Catching Miss Alvida!
No! I want to catch her...
Who do you want to catch with him?
Tell me! Koby!
He isn't the "bounty
hunter", I think! "Zoro"!
"Zoro"?
Koby!
Who is the most beautiful
person on the sea?
Of course! That is..
Who is the ugly and old fat woman?
Ugly and old? What is he talking about?
Damn you!
Let's go!
Damn it!
Oh, there!
Attack someone from
behind, that's dirty!
Kick around with many, that's dirty!
Get a load of this!
GOMU GOMU NO!
ROCKET!
What?
Luffy! What are you?
Me? I'm the rubber man!
Rubber man? What's that?
You've eaten the "devil
fruit", haven't you?
That's right! I've
eaten the Rubber Fruit!
You did?
I heard that before...
I never thought that
"devil fruit" really exists.
You got a good hand
wanna gain the prize?
I'm a pirate!
Pirate?
You? All by yourself?
Yes! I'm alone for now...
I'll have a companion sooner or later...
...at least 10, I guess!
Is it true? You're a pirate too?
A competitor of mine, eh?
Luffy! Run away now!
Huh?
Didn't you see the size of her mace?
The most powerful one on the sea!
I've made up my mind to
be the King of Pirates.
If I should fight 'till
I die! It doesn't matter!
What do you call me?
The most.. ugly, old fat woman!
What did you just say?
I want to join the navy!
Then, I'll catch bad guys!
Don't you know what
you're talking about?
Yes I do! I want to do it!
I want to join the navy! Join the navy!
Then I'll catch you!
You've just dug your grave!
I'm not sorry! I'm not!
You heard me! I'm fighting for my dream!
Nicely put, Koby!
It's no use.
What?
I'm a rubber man!
GOMU GOMU NO!
PISTOLET!
The sky is so blue...
Hey! Aye!
Give Koby a boat...
...he wants to join the navy!
Let him go right away!
Aye aye!
Luffy-san!
That is... the navy!
And it's the right time! Go ahead now!
I'm a pirate! It's
better to slip away now!
Knock it off!
It's not my day! It would
be unlucky if I was caught!
We got away finally.
Yeah! That's fun!
Hey, Luffy...
Yeah?
To find the"One Piece"...
You must go through the "Grand Line"...
They called it "The Pirate's Graveyard".
Right! So I must find a good man...
Who's that guy? The bounty hunter?
You mean"Zoro"?
I heard that he was caught by the navy.
What? That bad?
It's not like that!
He is truly a devil!
Why do you ask?
If he is so good, I want
him to be my companion!
Huh? You're thinking
the wrong way again!
Maybe he is a good man...
Bad guys would be caught!
No way! no way! Absolutely no way!
Why did you do that?
I wanted to do it, no reason!