Kohza, the warrior rebels!
The made promise with vivi!
With the kingdom of the Oases.
Three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
In a howl of sadness, this desiccated ground sinks from now on in an enormous wave of agitation.
Having left the green city of Erumalu, Luffy and its crew…
… move towards the oasis of Yuba, where the rebels are.
He, stops that!
Look at all that you reversed!
It is really waste.
One will not make a cheese of it!
Ace gave us an entirely full barrel.
You thus do not have any direction of reserve?!
You are lagging behind since the beginning.
He also will drink a little water.
I kept of it side for when Nami-San says,
“Ah, I die of thirst…! ”, and at this moment…
I will have it at disposal for him to give some immediately!
NAMI-SAN! VIVI-CHAN!
You want a little water?
Imbecile! It is me which will drink!
Not, that will go.
Give the-me!
Moron!
Release me!
Give!
You reverse all!
Why I cannot have some a little?
There is so much!
Species of jerk! What you insane, Luffy?!
Good blood, what do you believe that you make, there?
You want to drink a blow?
It is what your problem?!
Drop! It is not right for these young ladies!
Thank you. But that goes.
What takes to you?!
Be to you a dumb, Luffy!
You already drank some!
Dumb, you are all wasting!
Say, Vivi?
You would like to say some to me more well on the rebellious army?
Yes, you have reason, it is better than I learn some to you more on them.
RELEASE me!
It was 11 years ago…
Vivi. You…
… will be a large Princess!
Our village…
Our village suffers from the dryness.
Why are not you not come to save it?!
The climate is a thing that only God controls.
I am perhaps the King, but there is not only I can make against the forces of nature.
But my father said to me that the King could all achieve!
I can just make my better with the means which are given to me.
Your size!
The father of this boy penetrated in the palate.
What a audacity!
Your Majesty, it is with me to assume stupidities of my son!
I am ready to humbly accept any punishment which you will consider necessary!
I beg you!
I do not manage to believe only this… idiotic!
This imbecile…
This imbecile!
You Toto, isn't this is called?
Yes!
Until new order, the country will provide for the needs for the villagers touched by the dryness.
You will remain here, in Alubarna to think of your future.
What a kindness!
I thank you!
Thank you with you!!
But whore?!
You do not include/understand at all what the villagers can feel!
Remain there, Kohza!
Return immediately!
Louse.
Yes!
It is a good boy.
He spoke about what the villagers felt!
It was for their although it came here.
What do you have, pleurnichard?
Do Tain' what you want me small?
Small?
Cobra-Sama.
What is there, Igaram?
Can I say a word…
I am afraid that there are not enough means in the budget of the country to provide the needs of all these villagers.
IMBECILE!
Then take in our own funds!
No matter what we can make, one will arrive there!
Included/understood. As you will want.
It is terrible!
Your Majesty!
Vivi-Sama is…!
I fought.
But I lost.
VIVI!
VIVI-SAMA!
This species of small snotty-nosed kid!
How did he dare to make such a thing with the Princess of our nation!?
I will give him a lesson!
Wait, wait! Igaram!
I will give him a good lesson!
I am really sorry!
Let give me my life as an excuse!
STOP THIS DIN, BANDAGES SIMPLETONS!
Imbeciles! It is not that a brawl of children!
Hello and welcome!
Welcome! Welcome!
They is cheap! It is not expensive!
They is really good! Go, come to buy!
There is a brawl!
Welcome!
You dispatch!
Do not retain yourself because it is the Princess!
She looks us top!
Put to him a beating!
VIVI-CHAN! VAS-YYYY!
He you two!
Our leader, it is Kohza!
If I gain, I will become your leader.
I will not lose vis-a-vis somebody like you, small!
I was always the leader of this clan!
I arrive!
Listen, all!
From today, Vivi are the assistant manager of the Sandy one!
Objections?
NONE!
Look at, Igaram.
Vivi was made friends.
Yes.
If this girl is led one day to direct Arabasta,
it is the most important thing for it.
Louse-Ojisan, Obasan! Hello!
Where is the leader?
He, hello you.
If you seek Kohza, it already left.
It is surely at the usual place.
From agreement, I go there!
Oh, Vivi-Chan!
What do you make for the lunch?
I will eat with you! With presently!
It is really a strange country.
The Princess of all the kingdom comes in a poor farm like ours.
It is sign which peace reigns.
Igaram-San, would you like to join us for the lunch?
Not, not, that will go.
I have onigiri prepared with me.
Excuse me!
Co Cobra-Sama!
Good blood but what…?!
Your Majesty!
You still followed me?!
M- But…
I worry for Vivi-Chan…
Return immediately! You want that my concerns are double?!
HOW?!
There is not “how” which counts!
It was a good country.
Yes.
He! Coward water!
Not question!
But…
… much things did without.
He you, small.
You go some share?
You want company?
Sandy! With the attack!
YES!
Who are these kids?!
One did not deal with them or what?!
Leader… Everyone…
Vivi! Run away yourself!
It is with you that they want some!
Hurry to flee, Vivi!
They will kill you!
But… Leader…!
One will not kill it.
One just will kidnap it to ask for a ransom, you see?
Shit!
Go, come without resisting, Princesse Vivi…
You believe that I will leave it to you?
The Sandy ones will protect it until death!
YES!
Wow? What is it?
It is what this trick?
It is what?
IT IS ENORMOUS!
Super!
He, tells me the remainder of the history!
Of agreement. The leader, Kohza, were a boy with enormously of bravery.
But it is this great bravery which worried me.
You believe that I will leave it to you?
The Sandy ones will protect it until death!
You were really not on your guards.
There was another guy?!
Shit, it flees!
It moves straight towards the ruins.
One will catch up with it.
Do not let them pass!
YES!
Species of large dumbs!
But what that means?!
He!
What arrived to you?
Who did that to you?
There are brigands who are after Vivi!
HOW?
A brigand with a knife!
They went to the ruins!
Kohza was put at their continuation…!
What?
Princess!
Where do you hide?
Where are you Princesse?
Good blood but where is it hiding place?
Let us find it and this time let us not let it escape.
Princess Vivi, you show!
Oh, then it is there that you were hidden.
Render to me service while delivering to you without resisting.
WAIT!
Leader!
You do not have anything, Vivi?
Shit, that hurt!
Do not mistake the Sandy ones, brigand!
You may find it beneficial to release from our village!
He, kid.
Close it and delivers to me the Princess.
You should not attract you the anger of an adult.
A knife!
Course, leader!
It is not your wood end which will frighten me!
The Sandy ones will protect it until death!
Leader please, stops!
You really want in découdre, hein?
Leader!
He, how did you dare tabasser Aniki of the kind?
Aniki is employed here in the direction of “brother”.
It was not really a thing to be made!
They are taken both?
Now, come by there.
TAKE THAT!
Stunned poor wretches!
Dad!
Igaram!
Vivi-Sama! Es you wounded?
Bastard, that you made with my daughter?!
Species of refuse!
Insolate!
Insolate…!
It would seem that these guy also form part of their band.
Insolate!
Chaka!
Pell!
What you made there?
“What you made there?”
It is what one would like to know.
Why the king is out of the Palate and that one finds it fighting kind by here?
Please abstain from this kind of heroic behavior.
Igaram!
Kohza is…
Yes, we must bring it to a doctor!
As well as the members of Sandy who are in a dirty state!
Chaka! Pell! Carry assistance to them!
Yes!
Such a courageous child…
What doesn't go, Vivi?
How long still will you cry?
But…
I had if fear.
Eh well me too.
It had a knife.
That is not that…
It is because the Leader said that it would protect me until death…
The Sandy ones will protect it until death!
Say never again that you will die… Leader…
More than anything else, the prospect to lose a friend really frightened him.
Vivi is still a child, but it is the Princess.
Kohza.
Today, you achieved a noble task.
I would like to express my gratitude and to say to you thank you.
Vivi is my friend.
Therefore I did it.
I see.
I am in a hurry to see you taking again the torch with Arabasta in the next years.
Es you attached to this country?
Yes.
It is here that I was born.
Eh well me too.
I am…
I am a little anxious.
Why thus?
The leader of a country must make at the same time difficult and severe decisions.
In this respect, Princess Vivi is too nice.
Igaram.
Yes?
All is well.
Arabasta goes better thus.
I will remain on the throne until death separates me.
Yuba?
Yes, it is that!
Your father spoke about it with mine.
Louse-Ojisan?
He entrusted the direction of this uninhabited oasis, Yuba to us, to develop it and transform it downtown!
Many merchants and travellers forward each day there.
It is the center of activities of Western Arabasta!
If we build a city there, will you imagine a little which be the joy of people?
Isn't this brilliant?
And my old father accepted the function of representative of the people!
Do leader, you leave too?
Of course that yes!
Even if my old father asked me to remain here.
I know very well that to build a city will not be an easy task, but I will arrive there!
I will build a new town of my own hands!
Yuba is the kind of city which the country needs!
I count on you, Toto.
Yes, your Majesty.
I will build you a splendid city.
Eh well, I say to you with soon, Vivi-Chan.
One will not be re-examined before a short period of time.
When the city takes form, thus come to visit us!
It is of agreement! Louse-Ojisan!
We will build a splendid city which will help the country to thrive!
ON THE WAY!
Later, Vivi. You…
… will be a large Princess!
Yes!
Kohza! How can you be also arrogant?!
Kohza rightly.
Yuba surely will help the country to thrive.
In fact, your friend Kohza was a guy well.
But is there an unspecified relationship with the rebellious army?
Yes.
You see…
We move towards Yuba, the place where is installed the rebellious army.
And the name of their leader is…
Kohza.
You want to say that…?
It is the same boy that about which I spoke to you.
NAMI-SAN!
Nami-San, would you like to taste some a little?
This shrimp of the desert is really good!
That is not a shrimp! It is a scorpion!
I cannot about it any more, I ate too much!
I CANNOT BELIEVE IT! YOU STOP MAKING THE IDIOTS?!
One advances, now!
What puts it as much in bad temper?
Who knows…