Rebellious army VS the royal army!
The battle will be in Alubarna!
With the kingdom of the Oases.
Three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
In a howl of sadness, this desiccated ground sinks from now on in an enormous wave of agitation.
Separated from Vivi and its crew, Luffy faced all alone Crocodile.
But overcome by its phenomenal power, it sank in sands of Arabasta.
Although it was saved of accuracy by Miss All Sunday,
the wound mortal inflicted in Luffy makes that its re-establishment seems improbable.
During this time, Vivi and the others carry on their road towards Alubarna.
While crossing the vast one extended from the country, they were helped by certain single creatures of Arabasta…
… and advance more and more towards their final destination.
Vivi and his/her friends must try to prevent the battle.
But the rebellious, strong army of its 2.000.000 men, is almost with the doors of Alubarna!
The Sand glass of the Destiny counts the last seconds before the end.
Meat…
Hey, you!
Does Ca go?
Meat…
Meat!
Meat?
About what you do speak?
Hold out!
Wait. I take you along in a doctor.
This dumb of Crocodile…
I will make him pay.
To say as many conneries of Vivi and Ossan…!
It will pay it to me!
But which are you thus with the Juste?
Meat!
I see it!
It is still far, but I can see Alubarna!
Kohza, we will be there in less than 30 minutes!
Well!
CLOSE ALUBARNA EAST!
BE READY WITH THE COMBAT!
OUAIS!
Chaka-Sama!
The Rebellious Army was seen with approximately 15 kms in the south!
Very soon, 2.000.000 of rebels will start to attack the Southern Door!
Is!
West!
South!
South-east!
South-west!
Defend each door until the end!
DO NOT LET THEM PUT ONLY ONE FOOT IN THIS CITY!
YES!
Alubarna - Western Door
He, He! Look at over there!
I can see the rebellious army!
They are so numerous!
The Princess must be insane to think of being able to stop them!
But this insane…
… really will come?
Will it really come?
Or not to come?
Or is it coming?
It is too ambiguous!
He, He, He, He, He, He!
Should Ca be good? They is good?
They really come!?
This Princess and these pirates!
With this pace, the Army Rebels will be the first here!
They do not want to stop this battle any more!?
There are strong chances that they do not arrive in time.
They enormously wasted time with Rainbase, after all.
What, are you serious!?
But if the rebellion starts before they arrive there?
What will we make?
We will not do anything.
Once the started combat, even the Princess will not be able to do anything.
All that one must do is to kill those which one orders to us to kill.
It is so complicated to include/understand for you, queer?
What would you say to taste my Kenpo!?
Thus stop, you two.
Ah!
My hip!
My sciatica!
R--E--G--has--R--D--E--Z I--L--S.A. --R--R--I--v--E--N--T…
Mr.4, massage!
WHAT!?
Why you it known as step more early, weak!
Super Mallards!
Super Mallards?
What do you see, Miss Merry Christmas?
Aren't they too numerous?
I count six of them.
After the elimination of Straw hat,
there should remain only 4 about it.
You are mistaken, Miss Merry Christmas.
You did not listen to the speech of the Boss?
This Mr. Prince is with them.
If they are two moreover, the account is good.
What imports how much there is moreover,
we must just eliminate Vivi.
Why tergiversate?
Mr. 1.
“We must just eliminate Vivi”?
Eh well…
WHY DON'T YOU SAY ME WHICH IS VIVI!?
They carry all the same coats!
And these birds are fastest of Arabasta.
The squadron of the Super Mallards!
Bandage rats…!
Which of you is Vivi!?
It IS TOO AMBIGUOUS!
FIRE, Mr. 4!
Attention, you draw aside!
They dodged it!
These birds are fast!
Two of them passed to the South!
They divide!
I bet that they go to the Southern door!
It is there that the army rebels moves.
One of them must be Vivi.
THESE TWO ARE IT FOR ME!
Allons-y, Mr.4!
Mr. 1, y' has two of them which flees by there!
One of them can be Vivi!
They project to enter by the Western door.
These bastard…
Allons-y!
One…
Two!
Good! We direct towards the South-western Door!
On the five doors of Alubarna, three of them can be crossed by the West.
They try to enter the city separately.
It does not matter! We will eliminate them inside!
You will not escape to me!
He. Somebody assembles the steps!
The enemy!?
Not, wait!
It is the squadron of the Super Mallards!
Let pass them!
I will not leave you…
… to enfuiiir you!
I am so happy that you followed me up to now!
How?
Stop! Stop!
One can say that you are malignant!
Yes. I am Princess Vivi…
What you…
D-say?
It is me true the Vivi.
I think that one can stop there!
One had fun, my expensive.
Now…
It is time to show our truths faces!
DAMAGE, PERDUUUU!
WHAT!?
Thank you with all…
I must hurry.
The rebellious army is almost on us!
Allons-y, Karu!
Vivi and Kohza…
… do not have to meet.
A CAMEL!?
And you?
D-DESOLE!
Go ahead Zoro, smashes them!
YOU WANT TO CLOSE IT WELL!?
Stop them and I will forget your debt!
Which disappointment…
ONE IS ALREADY FREE!
One has any forgery.
Your rebellion will not take place today.
What do you have says!?
I will stop them!
I must stop them here,
or all our efforts will have been vain!
Fix the guns correctly!
Do not let them roll stupidly!
During the bombardment, do not break the formation!
Made attention with your boulets de canon!
This grondement is unreal.
We face a mad enemy of more than 2.000.000 men.
It is normal that the ground trembles with their arrival.
Do not flanchez!
They is good, Karu.
You can go there.
They will not notice us even if they trample us.
Please, Leader…
Listen to what I have to say to you…
ALL UNITS!
WE WILL ENTER BY DOOR CUS!
THEN ALL THE OTHER DOORS WILL FALL FROM THE INTERIOR!
WITH THE ATTACK!
YES!
STOP YOU, REBELLIOUS!
THIS BATTLE EAST A BLOW GOES UP!
PLEASE, LISTEN TO WHAT I AI HAVE TO SAY to YOU!!
REBELS, STOP VO…
He!
You did not see a person by there!?
A person!?
It is not the moment to be delirious!
Especially that they started to draw us above!
What?
They cannot any more see me, now!
How the Royal army can make a similar idiocy!?
SPECIES Of MORON!
I AI NOT DO NOT GIVE the ORDER TO DRAW!
Do not act without one giving you the order of it!
J I excuse myself.
By inadvertency… my hand slipped.
You do not stop, advance!
It is right a sand cloud!
NOT, STOP, PLEASE, STOP!!
For the good of our country, we will détrônerons the King!
Leader!
LEADER!!
What do you have, Kohza?
Not, it is nothing.
Was this my imagination?
Leader…
Listen well!
It is our final combat!
YES!
Wait! Listen to me!
LEADER!
They approach!
Prepare you to make fire!
LET US RELEASE ALUBARNA!
Karu…
You protected me…
Excuse me…
One did all that one could…
But the rebellion started…
Forgive me…
But… I will stop them!
I will still test, as much once than it will be necessary!
I cannot have done all that in vain!
On this boat… it is what I learned!
I will never lower the arms!
Vivi!
You were thus there!
Usopp-San!
You can arrive still there!
Quickly, goes up!
Yes!
But, Karu…
This bird can nothing any more make!
If one does not hurry, the rebellion will gain ground!
Come quickly!
This… bird…?
Allons-y, Karu!
What arrives to you?
Hurry and goes up!
Usopp-San.
Prove it.
What?
You doubts of me?
Look at!
NOT!
Usopp.
He, Usopp!
Matsuge, upright!
Ah, Sanji.
Hello.
Ah, my combat against this type?
The part of the plan where it had to be deceived was successful perfectly.
But then…
Ca lasted two seconds.
One second for each one of us.
Could to you have better done!
But are Sanji, why you here?
Your Mallard invited me to come to save you the round loaves!
Oh.
At all events…
Mr. 2 was made the trunk.
Yes.
Shit…
Listen, the transformations of this bastard of pervert are perfect.
He could become any among us to be caught some to Vivi.
If you have most slightest doubt small on one among us,
remove your binding and show this mark.
If they cannot, they are impostors.
Ca does not resemble itself to think of such intelligent tricks like this double mark.
Ca must mean that you are this bastard of pervert!
I WILL CUT YOU OUT OF DISCS!
Ah not, it is Zoro.
Ouf… it is Zoro.
You… are not Usopp-San…
Well…
I wonder how you uncovered me.
I thought that it was perfect.
Zéro-Chan said to me that you carry all same white binding on your arms…
They is bad…
Vivi-Chan is in danger!