Those which fly through the vast sky!
The 1000 year old alarm clock of legend!
It arrives!
Fire! Fire!!
Ryuji!!!
Ryuji, hold good!
Ryuji!!!!!!!
Cling!
You must turn over to the nest of the dragons!
Fight!
Ryuji…
Ryuji is…
Wretched bastard!
They is not good…
Ouais, it can swim more.
Which fun.
To so abruptly charge me like that.
Admiral!
Sennenryu is running!
No panic.
It will be captured before it runs.
Use the harpoon to bring back it to edge!
Target Sennenryu!
Perfect. Draw when it is ready!
Yes!
What?
What you made?
You do not have any idea on what you are, small snotty-nosed kid.
The only thing that I want they are the bones of Sennenryu.
When I would have this Ryukotsu,
I would obtain the eternal life!
Salt bastard!!!!!!!
Ryuji is not a thing!
It is our friend!
We sailed together!
It is a expensive friend in our eyes!
It is what this connery?
If it is the case, why you do not run with your friend?
How oses you to attack me?
Kill this little runt!
But, if one does that Sennenryu…
And then?
Even if its bones are reduced in parts,
I will be able to always collect them!
Yes!
Target the surface of the ocean!
Is that enough?
Would not be if defaitist!
Our goal yet was not achieved!
One will go to the nest of the dragons!
Stop saying that you cannot about it any more!
You know that I am right!
You do not have to worry for Apis!
Now, you must think of you.
Detach me!
I must be with Ryuji!
It is what that?
I must save Ryuji!
Let Luffy deal with Ryuji!
Not, not, not!
I want to go there! I want to go there! I want to go there!
It will save it! You will see!
The ocean starts to tremble!
What is it?
What does it occur?
What?
Ryuji…
Really?
You want to say?
What still?
One does not know! There is no underwater volcano known in this zone!
One of fout!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
I included/understood!
You have also important friends at your sides!
Ryuji!
Why he howls thus?
He calls them…
Who that?
Sennenryu disseminated throughout the world.
Time came!
It is what he says.
Did time come?
Does that want to say what?
Is He, He, it what over there?
SEN… Sennenryu,
the sky is filled by it!
I bet that they are the friends of Ryuji!
Ouais!
Incredible!
But from where they leave?
It is…
of Ryukotsu!
A whole mountain of Ryukotsu for me all alone!
Made fire!
Cut down them!
Impossible!
The guns cannot draw so high!
Ryuji!
Yes, I included/understood.
I will say it to Apis of your share.
Let use your neck to me!
What? What did it make?
What occurred?
It killed the Admiral!!!!
These guy of the Navy quickly give up once their chief with ground.
And these drafts did not even take care on him.
Let us drop us too.
They turn in round?
Why?
He, hurries!
Ouais!
Ahh, chains!
Stop cretin!
One will return oneself inside!
Wahou! They was cool!
Nami-San! I am of return!
Keep silent yourself and goes up!
Where is Luffy?
That it is owl!
Yo!
Y' does not have a yo which holds!!
A little softer when you would be landed!
You will break the boat!!
Ryuji!
An earthquake?
Still?
Ryuji…
My promise with Ryuji…
I will not be able to hold it.
I will not be able to bring it to the nest of the dragons.
The wish of Ryuji was carried out.
Sennenryu call…
You can hear them?
Hein? It is what?
There are as many earthquakes why?
This one is strongest!
He, looks at!
The ocean is withdrawn!
Then it is that!
What do you want to say, Nami-San?
How said it the fresco, the nest of the dragons is here!
The name “Sennenryu” does not refer to their lifetime.
That means that they come on this island once every 1000 years!
Sennenryu are migrating!
The herd did not appear here by chance!
“Lost Island” is the perfect name for that.
It makes surface only once every 1000 years.
It is normal that nobody remembers this emergence!
And now, in this moment,
the nest of the dragons will appear!
Incredible!
It could be that it is…
Yes.
It is the nest of the dragons which Ryuji wanted to re-examine.
Then it is…
He! He, Apis!
Apis!
But where it like that runs?
It is Ryuji.
Ryuji is over there.
Ryuji!
Ryuji!!
It is by sheer coincidence,
but the place where Ryuji fell is the nest of the dragons.
I wonder whether it knows that it can rest in peace.
Worry you!
Before running, he said that its wish was carried out.
Then it is that the nest of the dragons.
There are many rocks bizarroïdes.
I wonder
if it is of Ryukotsu.
Look at this rock over there.
One would say a dragon, you do not believe?
He well yes…
Why these rocks are carved like dragons?
Because during these 1000 years,
they were under the ocean.
Their bodies were calcified.
I see.
You included/understood a word of what she said?
Not, nothing the whole!
When the elephants die,
they go in a place called “cemetery of the elephants”, you see?
It is perhaps what is this place,
a cemetery of dragons.
A cemetery of dragons…
Not! It is not true!
Ryuji said to me that if it turned over to the nest of the dragons, it would be much better!
That cannot be a cemetery!!
Apis…
Ryuji was stray Sennenryu.
Luffy?
During 1000 years, it was all alone.
But, then it became friendly with Apis.
Apart from the 1000 years that he lived,
it was the time spent with you that he cherished more in the world.
Luffy.
You can include/understand what the dragons say?
About.
Do not tell conneries.
But, I know what he said!
Liar.
Ryuji, liar…
It is a nest of dragons.
The nest of the dragons was found,
then opens the eyes!
Speak to me!
You will be better!
Ryuji did not lie.
He said that Sennenryu was to turn over to the nest of the dragons every 1000 years
to reappear.
Ryuji would be…
Look at over there!
A Sennenryu baby!
Then you see, Apis…
This place is not only one cemetery of dragons.
It is also… a place which connects them to a new life.
Thank you, everyone.
When Ryuji said
“Bring back for me to the nest dragons”,
I believe that I included/understood
the kind of place that was to be,
and why Ryuji wanted to return there at all costs.
Apis…
It is an incredible place.
I include/understand why our ancestors built these temples now.
Thank you, Luffy.
Now, let us turn over to the village!
I bet that the villagers must worry!
Ouais!
Very well!
Let us turn over on the boat and leave this island!
He! I have the flagstone!
Sanji, prepares to us something of good!
Very well.
With meat!
Me of vegetables and a large dish of beans!
As if I had ever heard that front.
But this place is incredible!
Then they all are of Sennenryu?
Yes one would say well.
Too much hard for Ryukotsu.
If they become all like that,
that must be right a fairy tale.
Then the elixir of youth, you believe…
A dream among so much of others.
With all this coral which recovers them,
it is impossible to make an elixir.
I suppose that you are right.
These guy of the Navy wasted just their time.
Bandage cretins!
I do not die so easily!
I must really thank you.
But, not yet.
Of Sennenryu!
With them I will be able to have as much of Ryukotsu than I want!
Release.
Erik, looks at!
A whole herd of Sennenryu!
I will pay you more!
Let us make another market!
With alive Sennenryu,
we can extract the elixir!
Out of my way!!!!