Ambush!
Bliking and Wapol Blik
Everyone, come quickly!
What is there, Vivi?
Nami-San has…
an high fever!
I have a request to formulate.
I realize that it is very be likely for you to take along me on your boat, but…
In this moment, my country runs towards a tragic destiny.
At all events, I want that one hurries!
I cannot let any more pass from times.
The boat must continue at maximum speed towards Arabasta!
Of course.
One, isn't this promised?
Therefore, now, quickly let us find an island with a doctor!
We must look after Nami-San as quickly as possible.
Then, one sinks towards Arabasta.
It of this boat, isn't this is the maximum speed?
Of course! It cannot go more quickly!
It must see a doctor immediately.
This rate/rhythm, Nami-San goes…
He!
You see a doctor?
How if it could see a doctor, cretin!
He!
The guy…
You believe that people can hold upright on the ocean?
You want to know if one can hold upright on the ocean?
Do Zoro, about what you speak?
Then, it is what that?
What?
What do you want to say?
'Silvering, cold fact today.
It is very cold today.
Yes, cold. Very cold.
Really cold today.
You believe it, you too?
Made immersion!
Yes!
What is it that? A water melon?
Why does all tremble like that?
Hold the rudder good!
If something arrives at Nami-San, you, the idiots outside, you died!
This thing would be…
a boat?
Ah shit!
C-C' is a pirate boat!
Terrible!
There are not time for that.
You are surprised?
Here is my giant boat of underwater ambush:Bliking!
Vivi-Chan, supervises what occurs here!
Yes!
He! What occurs?
Good, you will answer me?
Us were attacked.
Here.
Good, it is what I thought…
with the first glance.
You, the poor wretches, you are pirates?
You are right a band of nazes.
It would be said that you are four.
Whatever the way of considering it,
it is too little to make a crew of pirates.
It is what its problem?
It puffs out a knife!
I have badly only by looking at it!
Good… I already asked it.
We move towards the Kingdom of Drum.
Would you have by chance Eternal Pose or a Log Poses on you?
I do not have any.
I never heard the name of the place about which you speak.
Ouais! It is true?
Now release.
One is in a hurry.
We do not have time to lose with you.
Ah, do not put your lives in danger of the kind.
If you do not have any, it is not serious.
However, I will take your richnesses and your boat.
But before I…
I have a small hollow.
What does it make?
Do not eat our boat!
Quiet remainder, you!
Wapol-Sama benefits from its meal!
This small unconscious! Kill it!
Fire!
One should have started by doing that.
Can Oh, I the shooter now?
Stop! One can discuss all that!
They engaged the battle all alone.
Cretins! They are in a hurry to die!
Shots?
Karu, supervises Nami-San.
I return immediately.
Please, do not enter in a so impolite way!
That mouth.
Wa… Wapol-Sama! They are…
You continuous to puff out?
This boat is not so bad.
He, you!
Cretin! You are not size vis-a-vis Wapol-Sama!
You will be eaten alive by the power of the fruit Baku Baku!
Luffy!
What?
Ah Vivi-Chan! How is Nami-San?
This guy it is chewing-gum.
Wapol-Sama?
He, one must hurry!
They released Wapol-Sama as if it were a headstock!
What does one have to make? Wapol-Sama is an anvil in water!
We must recover Wapol-Sama before it runs!
If we will not save it,
it will sink!
You point out that well!
We will return to make you pay!
Remember us!
Remember well!
Please!
Remember us well!
What was it to the Juste?
They called it Wapol or something like that.
Who is concerned with his name? Forget it.
It is right ton imagination, idiot.
Not what to worry.
This man…
Where I already saw it…
Several days before…
Colonel Smoker. Colonel Smoker.
We have just intercepted an interesting transmission.
What?
What a splendid Hitatsura!
Hitatsura = Effect of flame obtained by differently forging the edge and the fort of the blade.
One of Mono Ryouwaza…
Mono Ryouwaza = Less than 50 parts of extraordinary talent.
Kashuu.
Kashuu = Country of the flowers.
Tashigi! He, Tashigi!
I did not expect from it less Large Line.
To so early meet so beautiful Meitou…
Tashigi! He!
Summers you deaf, obsessed katana?
Yes!
What is there, Colonel Smoker?
Do you want coffee?
I do not want any!
Climb here and listen to that!!
It is…
Den Den Mushi with black cable!
Listen well.
We intercepted a conversation between two men.
With your permission, Sergeant Major, I will pass by again it to you.
Yes, made.
Mr. 0…
Princess Vivi and these pirates of Hat…
Straw hat…
Pirates of Straw hat?
Yes, mission accomplished…
… To establish communication… Will receive orders when…
It is all…
There were too many interferences to decipher some more.
Even with the interferences,
we succeeded in isolating 4 key words from the discussion between these two men:
“Princess Vivi”,
“Straw hat”,
“Orders”,
and…
“Mr. 0”.
Mr. 0?
Could that be a code name?
If it is the case, it could be in relation to this mysterious type which we captured in Runes the other day.
This man is called itself Mr. 11.
Yes, it is true.
Probably an criminal organization whose members have names with figures like code names.
And these members carry out “orders”…
Something like that?
Mr. 0? An criminal organization?
Jamis heard that.
Do not tell me such conneries.
If it is true, it was what the orders in your pocket?
I knew that I should have burned the orders!
Ca… Humm…
Ca?
There was nothing in your pocket, buffoon.
Princess Vivi.
If I remember well, it is the name of the princess of the kingdom of Arabasta.
Its current location is unknown.
But isn't the kingdom of Arabasta under the threat of a coup d'etat?
Would it be possible that this secret organization and the pirates of Straw hat are implied in this chaos?
I do not know.
But for the moment, it is the only evidence which we have on the position of Straw hat.
Therefore, from now…
Yes.
Contact the general headquarter and find to us Eternal Pose!
Yes!
Let us go on a small journey
with the kingdom of sand, Arabasta.
I bet that it is really hungry…
And if she ate 100 meat rations?
If she eats meat, she will go better in one nothing time!
Make a pause.
Go, mouse!
She does not smile!
Not small…
Perhaps that if one throws water on it or a trick of the kind,
its fever will fall.
MORON!!
Thin, it makes already night, Vivi-Chan.
Yes, you are right.
We should drop anchor some share.
Without the assistance of Nami-San, we will not be able to sail of night.
It is sure.
Oh yes!
You want them really my autographs?
Known as step…
Whore, it makes really cold.
Tomorrow evening, that will be the full moon…
I am cold! Shit, I fell asleep.
You are morning, Usopp!
I cannot remain now sitted.
In a similar situation,
it is necessary to move as quickly as possible.
Yes.
It is true.
Nami, looks at me! Look at!
It is really odd…
She does not smile at all…
Go, Nami! Make me a smile!
What is there, Luffy?
Meat.
Remove that! They is alarming!
Thank you!
While passing…
You noticed like it makes cold these last days?
Ouais, it is sure.
The temperature has been just stabilized.
Ca must be because of the instability of this place.
This ocean, Large Line.
Now, it is not perhaps any more the case.
That wants to surely say that we are close to an island.
Sanji-San, looks at the horizon with attention.
Vivi-Chan…
There is a winter island close to here.
I am sure.
A winter island.
In meteorology, the islands of Large Line are classified according to 4 types:
estival island,
spring island,
autumnal island,
and winter island.
And each one of these types has one season which is clean for him.
Therefore, it goes basiquement like that:
while crossing Large Line, you have, at least,
summer of an estival island at the winter of a winter island,
to endure 16 different seasons.
Of course, there are still unknown islands whose climate is not classified yet.
I include/understand. And moreover, there are so much islands close from/to each other…
The sea which separates them cannot maintain a climate stable.
Exact.
Therefore when the climate becomes stable,
it is the sign which an island is not far.
It rightly…
I see it!
Here is the island!
An island!
He, an island! We arrive on an island!
He, Nami! They is not super?
We arrive on an island!
You will go better soon!
It is an island!
An island!
Island… Island!
Thus will see it.
I…
It is an island!!
White! It is very white!
I bet that it is snow! A snow-covered island!
He, Luffy!
I should not say that to you but one will not run to the adventure this time.
We are there to find a doctor!
Once one will have examined Nami-San, one will leave immediately!
He! He, Luffy!
Snow they is so cool…
It is so white…
Useless, he does not listen.
Wait a little, the place is sure?
If there is snow, there could be monsters of snows or tricks like that!
It is not even known if the island is inhabited or not. It is our bigger problem, not?
Oh not! One should not go on this island!!
Snow… I like snow because it is so white…
I believe that I will prepare our arrival.
So much of snow… I am so happy!!
This place is different.
Look at these mountains.
With the fact, Luffy, you ace not cold while carrying these clothes?
The temperature is of -10°C!
With this temperature, the bears prepare to hibernate!
I am cold!
Be always also slow for you!
It is a chute d'eau created by the snow melt.
I think that one can place the boat some share by here.
Well. Somebody must go to seek a doctor.
Lastly, one must initially find people.
I go there!
Me too!
Yosh! Go ahead!
More one step, pirates!
He, there are people.
But… they do not seem delighted by see us.
Pirates.
We are with the regret to ask you to leave this shore…
Immediately!
We are here to find a doctor!
We have a sick person on board!
You think that your tricks will go on us?
Pirate poor wretches!
it is our island!
We will not let a group pirate pose the foot here and invade us!
Now, go up your anchor and leave!
Otherwise, we will destroy your ship!
They really hate us.
And one has just met.
Close it!
They drew!
You will regret that!!
Bastard!
Sanji-San, stops!
Vivi!!