Battle of Titans!
The Giants Dorry and Brogy
Eh well?
I am sorry.
You could repeat?
I asked to you whether you have gnôle.
We must have some a little…
Oh! You have some?
We drank some very little lately, one especially uses it for the kitchen.
But if you want some, you can all take!
A dino…
A dinosaur.
I AM the MOST POWERFUL WARRIOR Of ELBAF!
BROGY!
Now, I have what to eat.
You regard as my guests.
He…
Make the dead…
no matter what it does.
But it is not a bear.
Be sure for you that will function?
What a seen splendid!
It is the ideal place to eat my snack.
But be unconscious for you my word?
Then y' has really volcanos by here.
And it there capable enormous cracks over there!
They is dangerous!
Go down from there immediately!
Even if there with the flexible air, that remains always a dinosaur!
They is good, worries you!
I want to see the large cracks over there!
It is surely a strange place!
The place, one of fout!
Then go down from there!
He, sorry to disturb you,
but could you lead me over there?
He, even if you do not include/understand a word of what I say,
go, please takes along me.
Over there! At this place!
Not there…
Over there!
DO NOT MAKE CA!
Oh, sorry… I was right…
It IS Of HELL!
Luffy-San! They is dangerous!
Now, go down from there immediately!
He, these dinos is larger!
I bet that I will see better up there!
About what you do speak?
As I thought it.
I can still better see the cracks from here.
Pay attention!
Vivi! You should test! It is owl!
The sight is much better here!
It was made puff out very believed!
Where am I?
I observed you!
You played with the long necks in full jungle.
What a sharp small human!
Here well a long time that I had not had any more of guest.
Be gigantic for you!
Be human for you?
You requests if I am human?
I am the most powerful warrior of Elbaf, Dorry!
It is a Giant.
I never saw some…
Only heard stories which spoke about it…
I am Luffy.
A pirate!
A pirate? It is brilliant!
Karu, awakes!
Let us leave from here before it is too late!
Do Ah, you see these people over there?
It is Vivi and Karu.
Said “hello” the guy!
Luffy-San, why do you have says that?
He the guy, let to me show you where I live.
It is appetizing!
For how long will one have to do it dead?
I knew it. This trick does not function on the Giants.
It was surely my imagination.
Good blood, why you shouted ace?
It left all alone.
You ace considering all these skeletons over there?
I know, I know. But…
Early or late, he will eat us too.
Do not say that!
But…
One cannot wait until he eats us!
Mm, mm, succulent, this meat of dinosaur!
Roast in the flames of fire and lends to being absorbed!
Succulent…
this meat of dinosaur!
One has finally…
succeeded in escaping to us…
At least one will not finish in the stomach of the Giant.
But…
To be digested by a Tiger with the Teeth of Saber, it is not better either!
Finally, all that one does is to change stomach.
It does not matter what one does, our destiny is sealed.
One made our better,
one must just accept our fate.
He, the guy, you are finally awaked.
The meat is ready.
Let us take your gnôle and eat!
Well, let us eat!
The meat of dinosaur is very good!
I lost the appetite.
You do not obstruct! Eat!
One does not want to eat some…
But they is however good, the meat of dinosaur!
First of all, it lets to us eat the meat of dinosaur,
what returns more dodus to us…
And then he will eat us.
Yes, it is what make the Giants.
One is too young…
Perhaps that he prefers the tender meat.
Oh which taste…
They is really good.
Perhaps that if we are able to deprive to us of food until the Log reloads,
we will be able to remain in life.
But how long is it necessary so that the Log is reloaded?
The meat feels so good, that I will not be able to control myself any more very a long time.
Brogy-San, do I can ask you a small question?
Go ahead small, I listen to you.
How long is it necessary so that the Log is reloaded on this island?
One year.
Not…
It is impossible, one will not be able to be deprived of food during one year…
I… will be unable to control me.
Then you put at ease!
They is super good, Giant-Ossan!
This small bento of pirate was not bad either.
With share which it was a little small!
Of course!
It was a special menu prepared by my cook!
If you had said that it was dégueux, I would have you boot the buttocks.
Boot my buttocks?
What a joker, this p' tit man!
One would say of the old pals together.
With do the fact, Ossan, why you only live here?
You ace not of village?
Ouais, I have a village.
Elbaf, the village of the warriors.
Some share on Large Line…
But there are laws in my village.
Laws?
For example,
to regulate a conflict, the opponents must leave the village
and to accept the judgment of our Elbaf God.
Elbaf always grants its divine protection to the Juste.
And only one warrior out of alive spring.
Your Elbaf God?
Eh well, I began a quarrel.
And for this day, this island has been used to us as arena to my adversary and me,
until the right terrace the other.
But that made 100 years and y' still does not have a winner!
You have fought for 100 years?
Be astonished to you? Y' does not have what,
one saw 3 times longer than you, the small men.
Even if you live 3 times longer,
a 100 year old combat,
that does not have any more any direction!
Why do you continue to beat you?
You could die about it.
With that, I will beat Zoro.
The winner of this challenge is that which will bring back the most meat,
and it will be me!
That which will bring back the most tons of meat will gain.
I will gain!
Zoro?
Sanji?
I AI GAIN!                             I AI GAIN!
You LOST ACE!
Look at!
Mine is larger!
What?
The challenge was of knowing which would bring back the most tons of meat!
Apparently, I paid more, therefore I gained!
What counts it is how much one can draw some in kitchen.
With this heap of bone,
you can only draw 5 grams from meat!
This trick has nerves so much, that it is inedible!
I can nothing there, I had to face this poor small beast.
But the next one will be so large that it will nail you the nozzle.
Ah yes? Eh well mine will be so large
how it will not be the sorrow to compare!
Very well.
The next volcanic eruption will be the signal of end.
One will have to bring back our preys to the Vogue-Merry with this signal.
Ouais. Ca suits me.
It is a SACREE eruption!
It is the hour to go there.
It is what that?
An volcanic eruption.
Its glance changed…
I am afflicted,
but I must leave.
Hein? To leave?
Ouais.
It has been the signal of our engagements for 100 years.
A combat?
Against which?
For which reason?
Reason?
I forgot it!
I remember more when one decided
that the volcanic eruption would be the signal of our engagements.
But…
Why have you hated yourselves at this point for 100 years?
Which is the reason initially?
Ca is enough.
Ca does not have anything to see.
Exactly.
It is a question of honor!
REASON?
A LONG TIME AGO THAT I It AI OUBLIEE!
What is there?
Incredible.
They are gigantic!
He. Out of my way, large lizard.
Let to me take care some.
Oh, Mr. 5.
You have a famous capacity.
To also quickly build a hiding-place in full jungle…
But as you know it, it is always our mission.
One made a point of specifying it.
There will be no more blunders.
Blunders?
Not, I do not believe.
You are quite simply the inefficient ones, Mr. 5, Miss Valentine.
It is useless to take this air.
Throw an eye with this research opinion.
I must really thank you
to have given the opportunity to me to come on this island.
The Blue Ogre Dorry and the Red Ogre Brogy of the Giant Pirate Warriors.
I heard legends on them.
Is this research opinion old one hundred years, not truth?
Yes, but they are always alive here, on this island.
This time, they were worth 00,000,000 chacun.
A them two, that made aneo BT} 200,000,000.
s72} B   200,000,000 of reward?
But they are Giants!
A professional assassin uses the trick to achieve his misdeeds.
You will have only to follow my orders to the letter.
With a little ingeniousness,
one can cut down mountains.