While wanting to prevent Luffy
and Nami to reach the Arch,
Eneru releases its powerful Mamaragan.
Ca will not go, Eneru!
THIS GROUND SE WILL NEVER SUBJECT!!
Luffy approaches the Arch…
Return the Gold Bell!!
Now disappear
with this ashamed island!
RAIGOU
Gomu Gomu No Hanabi
Ougon Botan
RELEASE THE SKY!
MAKE IT SOUND, STRAW HAT!
RELIGHT THE FLAME OF SHANDORA!
And after having reached
the arch Maxim, Luffy…
complete finally its combat with Eneru.
With more!
I will sound you at the same time!
Gomu Gomu No…
Ougon Files
LET them HEAR It!
The war ends!
The dream resounds proudly with far
Can you hear it?
Papi Head of diamond! Large monkeys!
GOLD ISCED…
IS THE TOP!
C cretin succeeded!
As it is beautiful.
What a pretty sound!
What does that?
What is it?
I always knew that this day would come.
It is thus the bell
that Norland heard.
Suu…
This is…
the sound of the song of Vearth?
Does God… exist?
It is an exceptional miracle.
After 400 years of silence,
I had lost any hope
that it resounds again.
Large Karugara Warrior…
Can you hear it?
The Flame of Shandora resounds!
That it occurs
on our island?
Which is this sound?
This would be…
the legendary sound?
Can you it hear, Montblanc Norland?
We made you wait.
I hope that your descendant…
can hear it.
You also, you like to hear
this bell to sound?
Is owner,…?
Yes, it is that.
There is only one bell in the world that
one can hear of also far!
Does Ca feel the adventure, hein?
It is in the sky!
My heart is beating wildly!
These monsters which appear
with the impérionimbus…
There is a theory on them.
When human is held in
sky at a very high distance…
and that a light illuminates it,
a silhouette is projected
far behind him on the fog.
And it thus resembles
with a giant monster!
These monsters are thus in fact
people who live in the sky?!
How it is made that one was not with
current how of people lived in the sky?!
Ouais. It is a theory
tedious and forgotten…
But it would be said that it is true!
We hear the sound
large Gold Bell.
The Gold City exists in the sky!
Norland, my ancestor…
was not a liar!
And it is what is in the train of me
to prove this kid, since the sky!
He, kid.
Thank you.
[Note:On the Tee-shirt we can read
the kanji “Saru” which means “monkey”]
Owner?
That there
does it have?
You feel badly?
I am content that they are well!
I was so anxious!
Look at! Over there!
It is the arch of God!
And God!
He runs!
Eneru God and his arch…
run.
The sound of the Bell…
is the pride and the glory of
lost city. The Flame of Shandora.
The song of the island has
announced the end of the war.
Sounding after 400 years…
the bell of their promise.
The voyage from this floating island
and deadened was long…
But it always preserved
its distances memories.
Once, of the men entrusted
a message with this bell.
A sound reaching them
the most distant seas…
carrying its proud words.
And now?
It sounded.
Ouaip.
You believe that Papi and them
did monkeys hear it?
Ouais, I am sure.
We are there!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
You, the strapping man there!
Hang this cord here!
Aisa, were you worries?
Here your treasure!
I do not want any!
Laki!
Others…
They are well.
Do not speak.
Y' has somebody by there.
I am alive?
Not, you need a treatment.
I can wait.
It needs some more than me.
Look at if you can help it.
He almost died.
It is true!
Its bones are broken!
They is not good!
Isn't He, it a warrior?
Him nothing is owed.
Ouais, I do not include/understand
not very well me either,
but it fought
with such a eagerness.
Hein? It is what that?
Sympathy?
I do not know.
Excuse me…
Is what it goes of
to leave, Tanuki-chan?
I am a reindeer!
Look at, I have drink!
Do not worry you. I go
to ensure me that it remains in life.
Thank you!
Pierre, will put back you with
blue sailors.
Pierre, quickly. Bring back them
families of the soldiers here.
Thus finally, the Bell
of Gold and the gilded arch of Eneru…
Ouais, they are
fallen both.
It is judicious being the City of Gold,
but with final it a name is right.
Our voyage without a round continuous.
I prefer to carry some
Dials rather than gold.
Once returned on the Sea
Blue, one will be able to find some more.
But you believe that Nami-san is well?
And where is Conis-chan?
You think that we can make confidence with the inhabitants of the Blue Sea for Wiper?
All will be well.
Aisa with the air to like them.
We should be dispatched!
If the enemy awakes,
all will have been done in vain!
Enlist all those which can move!
It is necessary to give up them
Priests with the Drifting Cloud.
Ok!
You of ace finished with him?
Yes, it needs rest now.
HEEEEE!!!!
Luffy?!
Nami-swan!
Conis-chwan!
Luffy!
You all!
Which joy of you
to re-examine healthy and safe.
I was so anxious,
but I could not…
Conis-chan, you worried for me…
Not, cretin.
Is He, they provisions?
Where did you find them?
In the forest.
The reserve of the Priests was discovered!
Y' in has still full!
But how you made
to go down from up there?
Gomu Gomu No Fuusen!
Besides, Conis, where is your father?
He well, in fact, it protected me…
And Eneru…
You want to say…
Conis-chan…
Conis-san…
Conis…
ONE SPEAKS ABOUT YOU!
Afflicted I am in life!
Father!
You were on the White Sea?
Yes, when I began again
conscience, I was in bottom.
Now, people who went
in Cloud End to go down from the cloud…
use of Milky Dials for
to turn over on the Sea of Opal.
But, they cannot turn over any more
on Angel Island which does not exist any more.
They come by here, towards Upper Yard.
Thank you very much, God!
This title does not belong to me any more.
I am sorry to have left you
in this horrible place during six years.
Please forgive me.
We lost our
hearth, Angel Island.
And Shandia lost them
village hidden in the clouds.
Is the war really finished?
Holy guard of
God disappeared, but…
Chief, tear a 400 year old
can it heal also easily?
Pfiou, I am gavé!
It is already the night.
Loans to be turned over to the boat?
Nami! About what you speak?!
What?
Once on the boat, I will be able to make a good gross nap in my hot bed!
Usopp, you ace heard it
what it has just said?
Ouais, I do not believe my ears of them!
If it does not include/understand, it one is missed as a pirate and anybody!
To include/understand what?!
It is what that?!
I return…
in the place legitimates of God!
In the sky, nothing will block
my field of view.
You all were harmful.
You will not have it!
It only belongs only to me!
Air ground, without limits!
Now, ahead, Maxim!
Direction my Divine kingdom
who illuminates the night…
Infinite ground, Fairy Vearth!
Where am I?
You are in the ruins of Shandora.
Gan Fall!
You should not move!
You are one living of the sky!
You must rest.
Chief!
We were captured
by the inhabitants of the sky?!
There can be no distinction
between the victims of a war.
But the Gold Belfry! Our
to have is always to protect it.
What it is?!
This is the beat
of a drum of war?!
There is fire with the ruins!
Abrupt step, Wiper.
Reflected before acting.
It does not matter which heroic pretexts justified a war in the past,
we live here now,
and the sky is our fatherland.
And this fatherland does not reject anybody.
But, right in front of my eyes…
Yes, you should see that by yourself.
For people gathered here…
the war is the thing
more unthinkable which is!
It is the festival!