GOMU GOMU NO...
What's that for?
One week, please!
Are you mocking me?
If you'd just remove the bug,
then it wouId've been edible.
then it would've been edible.
It took me three days and nights to make that soup.
I'm a customer!
A customer who paid you money!
You think money...
will fill your stomach?
What?
I said...
Will money fill your stomach?!
AN UNEXPECTED GUEST!
SANJI'S FOOD AND GIN'S GRACE
Man, I can't hold it any longer...
Courtesy!
That's love!
Only love makes a restaurant.
The customers are Gods!
Service, service and more service!
And the very foundation of service
is a heartfelt greeting.
Welcome, mere bastard.
Please, enjoy yourself.
No entry for the poor.
Here's 10,000 beli!
Keep the change!
Okay!
Ah... I feel much better.
Now, back to work...
Oh! WeIcome, mere bastard.
Service, service and more service!
Custo...
A customer!!
You're at it again, Sanji?
What're you doing to our customer?
Isn't that a marine lieutenant?
Gotta problem, you crappy cook?
Don't talk to me that way!
A crappy cook like you has
no right to call me crappy!
To a restaurant, customers are everything!
Beating up our valuable customers,
what're you thinking?
Customer or not, it's no different.
This guy not only ruined our dishes,
he also insulted its chef!
That's why I thought I should teach him a lesson.
What kind of restaurant is this?
Do you treat all your customers this way?
How does it even stay in business?
I'll destroy it!
I'lI destroy your precious little restaurant.
I'll contact my superiors right now!
I guess that means I can't let
you leave this place alive.
Stop it, Assistant Head Chef!
Let go of me!
He started it!
Stop it! Stop fighting, Sanji!
Just who do you think you are?! Huh?!
What is it this time?
What happened?
Man, that surprised me!
O-Owner? What's going on?
Damn it, see what you did?!
You broke my ceiling!
It's all your fault, boy!
You broke it yourself, old man!
What are you doing, Boss?!
Leave him and help us stop Sanji here!
Hey, Sanji!
Were you fighting in my restaurant
again, you ingrate?
Shut up, old fart!
What?! Who do you think you're talking to?!
You wanna destroy my restaurant?!
You insolent boy!
You're another one!
Get the hell outta here!
What's wrong with this restaurant?
Even the owner's gone nuts!
Just looking at them...
They're just like... just like a pirate gang.
You got that?!
The customers are Gods!
Only the ones who can stand your cooking.
Patty, Sanji! If you wanna fight, don't
go doing it in front of our customers!
Are these people really chefs?
L-Lieutenant!
Lieutenant Fullbody!
We've got a problem!
This restaurant sure is lively.
The Pirate Krieg's man has escaped!
What?!
We thought he could've given us a lead on Krieg....
We've already lost seven of our men.
That's ridiculous!
When we got him three days ago,
he was about to starve to death!
And we haven't fed him yet, have we?
The d-dreaded Don Krieg Pirates?!
Isn't he supposedly the most powerful
pirate of the East BIue?
I'm reaIly sor...
Another customer has arrived.
He'd better not cause anymore
trouble in my restaurant.
A pirate, eh?
I don't care what it is..
Bring me some food.
This is a restaurant, isn't it?
Welcome, mere bastard.
I'll only say it once more, so listen up.
Bring me some food.
He's gonna kill that cook!
I'm sorry Sir, but we'll be expecting
you to pay for a meal here.
Do you have enough money?
Is a bullet okay?
So I take it that you don't have any money.
What?!
Why that Patty bastard broke one of my chairs!
Wow, what power!
If you can't pay up, you can't eat.
Way to go, Mr. Cook!
That pirate's nothing. Take him out, Patty-san!
Oh, your stomach's growling there, you filthy pirate.
That was a fart.
You jerk, hurry and get me something to eat.
You're no customer, so get the hell outta here!!!
I can't take it anymore..!
I don't want anything to do
with this kind of restaurant!
I-I'll never come here again!
Alright, everybody!
Please, continue with your meal.
Please get lost.
Damn him...
How dare he...
I wouldn't normally let anyone
get away with that crap...
Hey, you're starving, aren't you?
S-shut up..
I'm the least bit hungry.
Eat it.
Shut up! Go away!
This is worse.
I won't accept charity.
Take it away!
Don't be so tough, just eat it already.
To me, any hungry person's a customer.
I... I can't pay for it.
The vast ocean can be very cruel.
It's awful to not have any food or water.
Just awful...
I understand starving people more than anyone.
I don't care if you wanna die with dignity.
But if you eat up, you'd be able to look
forward to a new tomorrow, won't you?
But if you eat up' you'd be able to Iook
This is so delicious.
So delicious. It's too delicious!
I thought I was gonna die.
I thought I was a goner.
Yummy, so delicious.
I've never had such a good meal in my whole Iife.
You like it, eh?
Well now, I've found my cook!
Hey, aren't you lucky?
If he hadn't given you something to eat,
It'd be all over for you by now.
Hey, Mr. Cook, care to join us?
You'll be the chef on our pirate ship!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
You're a pirate?
Yup!
Then why did you attack this restaurant?
That was an accident!
We were just defending ourselves.
The hell does that mean?
Anyways, you'd better not do
anything else to this place.
The head chef here was once a
chef on a notorious pirate ship.
Heh? So that old man was a pirate?
For that old fart,
this restaurant is worth more than any treasure.
And those cooks who came after his
fame were once fierce pirates.
Well, the pirates in these parts
often come to this place.
Yeah, this place never seems to have a duIl moment.
It's not bad. I'm used to it.
Recently, most of the people only come
to watch the cooks and pirates brawl.
But thanks to that, it scares away
alI of the part-time waiters.
Oh, that explains it.
No wonder he wants me to
work here for a whole year.
Hey, join us!
I refuse.
I have my reasons why I must remain here.
No! I refuse!
A-About what?
I refuse your refusal.
You're a good cook, so come
with me and be a pirate!
Hey now, you Iisten to me!
So, what's the reason?
I don't need to tell you!
Eh? Didn't you say you wanted me to listen to you?
I meant that you must accept my decision!
You'd better watch out or I'll gut you
like a fish, you straw hat bastard!
What did you say?!
Don't you dare insult my hat unless
you're picking a fight, you bastard!
Sorry to interrupt, but...
What is it?!
I'm part of the Krieg Pirates crew. The name's Gin.
So, you're a pirate too, eh?
What's your goal?
I'm looking for One Piece!
I'm headed for the Grand Line.
You're still looking for a cook...
Your crew must be quite smalI.
Yeah. We've got five, counting him.
Why the hell are you counting me in?!
You look like a decent guy, so let
me give you a piece of advice.
You'd better not go to the Grand Line.
You're still young.
There's no need to rush.
The Grand Line is only a small part
of the world's vast oceans.
If you wanna be a pirate, there are
many Iess intimidating places.
Oh, I see.
So, do you know anything about the Grand Line?
Nope, I don't know anything about it...
Nothing, nothing at all.
That's why it's so scary.
Are you really one of the dreaded Krieg's men?
I didn't think he'd hire such chickens.
Krieg?
Table 3's fried rice is ready!
You take it! There's no waiter.
You sure we'll be okay, Patty?
The guy you punched in the restaurant a while ago...
Isn't he one of Krieg's men?
Yeah, at least that's what I heard.
Don't forget his captain, Don Krieg.
He's supposedIy the greatest pirate in the world!
Yup, that's true.
He has a total of 50 pirate ships under his helm.
He's a monster.
So what?
He's got more than 5000 people
under his command.
What if that guy...
tells Don Krieg what had happened here just now...
It'd be Iike an elephant stepping on an ant.
It'd be like an elephant stepping on an ant.
He'd blow this restaurant to smithereens.
So you mean, I should've let him eat for free?
That'd be unfair to the other guests.
That'd bring disgrace on the Baratie name!
And it'd also bring shame to alI us ''warrior chefs''!
And it'd also bring shame to all us ''warrior chefs''!
How many pirates do you think
we've beaten up 'til now?
If you're so scared, then you're better off quitting!
What did ye say?
Your attitude's the reason why
we lost all of our waiters!
Patty!
It's all your fault we're so understaffed!
Well, they were all cowards.
We didn't need 'em anyway.
Come on! Let's get it on!
Kick his ass. Fight!
Hey, you morons!
Get back to work!
Right away, Owner!
Later then.
I'm still going to the Grand Line.
Yeah, do what you want.
We're strangers, so I've got no right stopping you.
I just thought that I should warn you.
Oh, and Sanji-san...
Thank you very much.
You saved my life.
The fried rice was the best!
Can I come again?
Anytime!
Hey there, waiter boy!
Ah! It's the old man!
So here you are!
Get going, Gin.
I'm sorry.
You're gonna get in trouble
for letting me eat for free.
Whatever.
They don't have any proof now, do they?
Don't get caught again, Gin!
Thank you, Sanji-san.
I won't forget this...
Sanji! Waiter boy!
Get back to work, right now!
Table 3's ready!
I'm Luffy!
As of today, I'lI be your new waiter!
Nice to meet ya!
Isn't table 6's dessert ready yet?
Who's in charge of it?
Wasn't it you?!
I'm busy as it is!
Yeah, 'coz you didn't pay any attention!
What did ye say? You wanna fight?
If you're just sitting around,
GO WASH THE DISHES!!!
Where is that Sanji bastard?
He's out there entertaining the guests.
Again?!
It pisses me off that he's the assistant head chef.
What can we do about it?
He's been here longer than anybody else.
Do you know why Sanji stays, even though
he doesn't get along with the boss?
'Coz he wants to be the Head Chef?
So, you knew.
Hey, waiter boy!
How many dishes have you broken?!
Sorry, I forgot to count.
That's not how you apologize for breakin 'em!
Forget about the dishes, go clean up over there!
Yosh! Leave it to me!
Don't go eating that!
That's the main course!
Come on now, don't worry about it.
H-HOT!!!
HOT HOT HOT!!!
Get out of the kitchen!!
Listen up, you go serve the customers.
Go ask what they want.
Can you handle that?
It's so hard to do all these odd jobs.
I guess this is what Coby felt like, eh?
Hey there, waiter!
Hey! It's you guys!
Hey, I heard that you've gotta work here for a year!
Can I redraw the pirate flag?
What's all this?!
You all stuff yourselves with such
great food while I'm not around?!
That hurts!
Not really, it's our free will.
Take that.
But I've gotta admit, the food here's great.
I feel kinda sorry for you.
You drink it!
Why'd you do that?
You, too! What were you trying to pull?
My stomach's aching!
Man, they're noisy...
Are those idiots his crew?
Pour it yourself.
O' Mother Ocean!
Thank you for arranging this encounter today!
Oh, my love!
Go on, laugh at me.
I, who can't bear torture.
As long as I'm with you, it matters
not if I'm a pirate or a devil...
My heart's ready as can be!
But, this is horrible!
There's such a great obstacle between us!
The obstacle is me, right?
Sanji.
The old fart!
This is just great.
Why don't you just run off and
be a pirate just like them.
We don't need you here anymore!
I see.
So that cook saved your life.
And you were able to return.
Isn't that so, Gin?
Yes, Capt'...
But...
I never would've thought that this
would happen to our ship.
Don Krieg!
What now?
Let me lead the way, to the
Floating Restaurant Baratie.