The prediction of Eneru
will achieve itself in one hour.
Now, there remain 25 people.
Seis Fleur
Stop!!
No matter what you say, it is too late.
Ca hurts…
After its victory over Yama,
Robin discovers Shandora,
Cité d'Or, in the middle of the ruins.
Moreover, it does one
unexpected discovery.
This would be…
After having explored so many places, it remains
still of Ponéglyphes which I did not find.
If it is the case, then the Large one
Belfry enters the four furnace bridges…
perhaps tell the True History…
It is perhaps Rio Ponéglyphe.
Chance of survival:0%!!
Chopper VS Ohm the Priest
I am there almost.
If I am the first to find gold,
everyone will be surprised.
Still ruins…
What bell, here?
The ground is slightly tilted.
I initially will leave from there.
Gold, gold.
Slept.
Slept, Holy.
Holy, lying.
I over-estimated myself!
I should have turned back!
I am foutu!!
You are the third which passes
in the corner, today.
Who are you?
Whore, this scatterbrain
is more naive than ever.
It is you who put ace one
scraped in Gedatsu, isn't this?
He speaks about the guy about presently.
Oh, not. Do not make any you.
The world goes better without this cretin.
You are not agreement?
It is what?
What do I have…?
Pas la pains to be afraid.
This dog it is Holy, my adored doggie.
It will not bite you.
But, this man is
unconscious and covered with blood!
Holy was indeed drawn up.
It dead person without reason.
It is me which cut out this man.
It is horrible!
Who you are?!
Who are you?
I am called Ohm.
In any case, keep silent yourself!
Ca returns to me sad… to see with which
not the human ones are fragile.
You frighten me… I must flee…
I do not like that of the whole…
Of knowing that their life
is so transitory…
Why people want
to always fight?!
How that?
They are born merry…
Seek the joy…
And instead of that,
they die in the combat!
They never would thus have had
to undertake anything!
People are unable
to overcome their nature.
It is so sad.
But there exists a means of saving them!
Everyone should die!
Why you say tricks
horrible like that?!
I do not believe in it!
Why did you come here?
I am just there for
to find a little gold and…
When that one seeks some
thing, to fight is inevitable.
I will save you.
To save me?
It is true?
While mourrant, you will not have anything any more
to make and more nothing to seek.
It does not intend to save me!!
Why?
Why everyone is…
carbonized?
It is as if they had
summer struck by the lightning.
Kamakiri?!
Kamakiri!
Laki?
Yes, it is me!
Leave!
Leave, Laki!
But, Kamakiri…
Wiper is… on the way
for the Sanctuary of God.
Eneru is not over there.
You can still stop it.
Stop Wiper!
Of agreement! About agreement, does not speak any more!
Nobody can overcome it…
I am the lightning.
It is invincible!
It is what people fear such one
god since mists of time, the lightning.
He is the reincarnation of God!
I will stop Wiper.
Wait here.
I leave the bag of Aisa at your sides.
Take care until my return.
Nobody can overcome it…
It is invincible!
Kamakiri is very strong,
but its will was broken.
Goro Goro is one of more
powerful Fruits of the Demon of the Logia type.
[Note:Goro Goro =
detonation of the lightning]
And Eneru has its capacity?!
I must stop them!
It already seems me to have seen that… not?
Perhaps well…
Or perhaps not…
If, it seems to me.
It is right a resemblance?
You insane of me, cretin?!
What?
It is your problem if you
am to me to eat gratos.
Here what arrives when one sticks to me.
Still want you?
Cretin! He!
Moron! Y' has anything to puff out inside!
Coward!
But where you go like that?!
This place is really odd.
Exit… Exit… Exit, where are you?
Exit!
Here!
A bottom of bag!
After all this way? It is not right!
Wait, perhaps…
And if it were a secret door?
I see.
Perhaps that if I pass to
through, I could continue.
Gomu Gomu No…
BAZOOKA!
Hein?
Ca did not even move.
Qu… What occurs?!
I sowed it. Thank you my God.
It is a Priest, him too?
There is full with hiding-places by here.
I must leave from here and
to find Luffy and others.
A epeist would have been said.
If I am held remotely and
remain hidden, I could flee.
He has me preceded sacrament.
This dead loss flees then
that I try to save it.
That shows its attachment with
life… a primary reaction.
However…
It is possible no to survive
with the Truth of the Pain.
The chance of survival is of 0%.
Ordalie of Iron!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
Another voice disappeared!
Aisa?
I cannot remain here!
I will find Laki!
Remain there!
He, do not make the idiot!
Brothel!
I said to you to remain there!
And why?
Release me!
Release me!!
It is not your problem!
It is not my problem, but I cannot
to let a child like you be made kill!
I am warlike!
Ouais, I ouais included/understood.
You are small warlike.
You do not impress me
with your black look.
Excuse me… You leave yourself there?
They is good, that goes.
He, stops agitating you!
Go up!
He, stops! NOT!
Let leave to me!
I must help them!
RELEASE me!
Calm yourself immediately
or I put on a snap to you!
And does not cry!
We already lost two
members of our crew.
I will not let myself leave!
Now, hurries to go up.
Oh shit!
He Ben, I flippé!
It is what this cave?
Initially this funny of tremor of
ground and then a torrent of océonimbus.
I failed to drown me!
Filth!
Open!
THIS TRICK ENORMOUS EAST!
Whore!
Where is the exit?!
Gok19} driven  Go  driven  No
Ga  tling Gun !
Nami-san!
You move towards the forest!
What can we make?
They entered the forest.
Brothel.
Be to you coriace!
What?
Who is this?
Something…
Something approaches!
Goes by there! By there!
It is the Master of the Skies!
Was this Aisa?
One is… in the forest!
He, poses to me!
You hear me, dumb?
Cretin of bird. Pose to me
or I cut you the wings.
It is what?
L IT PYTHON!
He! Take height
or one will be made puff out!
Hurry! He!
It still follows us!
This snake with the furious air.
The Sanctuary of God is
at the top of Giant Jack.
Eneru will be over there.
I will put a term…
at these 400 absurd years of history!
It arrives.
Wiper, while still climbing
the stem of bean…
you will reach the Sanctuary of God.
Who gave you the permission to go there?
Ohm!
There is no more reason of
to go up to the Sanctuary of God.
Gan Fall!
What you insane there?
You would have the intention of
to recover your divine throne?
At all.
I am here to achieve my duty.
I return very right
sanctuary of God.
A tragedy… it has
completely destroyed summer.
Of course, there was not
no trace of Eneru.
It is a way of saying that more
nothing up there is useful for him.
These six dreadful years of
hard labor touch at their end.
I came here for
to present my good-byes to you.
What you mijotez
every both, Ohm?!
You say that Eneru is not
with the Sanctuary of God?
One of the companions of Straw hat?
Ca hurts!
I will butt it this sparrow!
You?
One would say…
old ruins.
And well, it one is crowned band
the hard ones to cook that we have there.
He, bring gold!
He well, which sadness.
None among you will escape
in my Ordalie of Iron.
If one of you is put in
through my road, I kill it!
You will say to me where
find Eneru and my holy guard.
It is what this connery of cave?!
He well, gentlemen, you have
all air to have to make.
But to achieve your goal,
you will have initially to survive!