Good-bye the island of Drum!
I take the sea!
Goes now…
My wire idiot.
Splendid!
Yes!
Which color.
He… Will that go for Chopper?
It needs to be alone for the moment.
It starts to include/understand what is “to follow its destiny”.
It forever left this island of all its life.
And from now on, it leaves it behind him.
I am my way.
Doctor, Doctorine.
It finally will be able to start.
My… ventures!
I adore it! I adore it!
The moon is shown and the cherry tree flowers!
Chopper!
He, Chopper!
Imbecile, how long you will remain there sitted to daydream?!
Wood.
Eh, come to sing with me!
Go, tries to put these rods in your nose!
Ah, what a beautiful cherry tree!
It is not funny if one does not sing!
I frightened you?
Now you are the companion of one crowned band of kids.
Sing! Sing!
A companion?
It is the best!
Yes, they do not have the least direction of the responsibilities, but they are your companions now.
You will have to learn how to know them, of agreement?
Karu! Why you went in this cold river?!
Ha ha, it probably had to slip and fall inside.
The moron!
Keep silent yourself, Mr. Bushido!
He said that named Zoro went to swim in the river.
And when he saw that he did not return, he was afraid that something arrived,
then it jumped in water to go to help it and it is there that it has cold.
It was thus of your fault!
Do Tony-Kun, you include/understand what Karu known as?
Yes, at the base I am an animal.
Thus I can communicate with other animals.
You can speak with the animals?
It is brilliant, Chopper!
In addition to your medical capacities, you also have this faculty!
Idiot!
I do not like that one compliments me like that!
Small stupid!
However, it with the rather content air.
With do the fact, Nami, what you understand by “medical capacities”?
Chopper is a doctor.
It is Dr. Kureha who taught all to him that it knew of medicine.
It is a doctor of first order!
WHAT?!
Chopper, be to you doctor?!
Super!
You pleasant!
Imbecile! And why did you invite Chopper to join us?
Seven levels of transformation.
It is a super reindeer.
Food of help.
Oh not!
I was so in a hurry to leave that I forgot to take my case of care!
Good Ah? But then it is what this trick?
My backpack!
It was on the sledge.
How?
What do you want to say by there?
It is not you who ace prepared your business for the voyage?
At the end of the day…
She pertinently knew what there was at the bottom of your heart.
It is really a marvellous person.
Ah! Droppings of nose in the airs!
Yes.
Go! Take that!
Do not stop you!
He, Chopper!
Also, tests you!
You me master keys rods?
Frankly!
They make any really only at their head!
Sanji!
Divide it in two! 'silvering release me!
Well, Chopper!
Chopper?
Thus test, salts cook!
DO NOT MAKE CA!
WELL!
He, morons!
LET US CLINK GLASSES!
What you said ace, jerk?!
You ace of course, I have known as salts cook to you!
I would like to introduce our new companion to you…
Sanji, of the meat!
… Tony Tony Chopper!
You know…
As a ship's doctor, the responsibilities for Chopper will be…
YOU LISTEN TO Me, BAND Of IDIOTS!?
He the morons, I try to speak!
Whore, will you stop beating you?
You know…
He you, the oaf!?
Go shit! Let finish to me!
It is really the very first time that I have fun as much!
They is cool!
With our new companion! Health!
GO!
HEALTH!
Eh well, I suppose that it was time for him to leave the island.
This reindeer has good heart and it has the capacities of a very eminent doctor.
Hiluluk gave its life so that the cherry trees flower.
It is perhaps the reason for which this inexperienced reindeer decided to take the sea.
He… became a man.
He will become a good ship's doctor.
Eh well? What do you hope to make now?
I…
I owe expier the faults which I made as a Commander of the guard of Wapol.
I should leave and entrust the good walk of the country to the people.
It is what I intended to do.
And… you always have the intention of it?
Not.
I realized that while leaving, I would not make amend.
The collapse of the old kingdom will be able to leave room to the awakening of a new nation.
If I remain, I will be able to then make in kind help with the construction of a nation.
I believe that in this way, I will be able to repair my faults.
Hmm, always a kid.
Your heart is always attached to this country.
A heart attached to its country…
A long time ago, a ten year old young girl showed me what it was.
Mariejoie, Holy Land
Bah… Still a world council…
Ca still will be an useless and tedious meeting.
Yes, probably.
Is the Kingdom of Drum on the right track?
The rupture enters the King and the people nothing but do increase more and more.
Oh!
It is the King of the Kingdom of Arabasta!
Nefertari Cobra-Sama…
It is the wise one and benevolent King d' Arabasta.
Dragon, the revolutionist.
The ideologies of this man are dangerous!
From here five or six years, it inevitably will represent a serious threat with the World Government.
Which fabric of conneries.
That does not relate to of anything my kingdom.
I will not waste my time with this “revolutionist” and his political opinions badly inspired.
If you want to capture it, band of morons, that will be without me!
WAPOL!
Species of large oaf egocentric person!
Why you believe that this top takes place?!
Give a your opinion more with the serious one.
Nefertari Cobra!
Bah! This meeting was really the worst of all.
It is. !
It is the girl of this snotty-nosed kid of Cobra!
Oups! My hand slipped!
WAPOL-SAMA!
Vivi-Sama!
Excuse me!
Hold, would not be this the Princess of Arabasta?
Ca must be hard to be the girl of such an unimportant King!
Salt dog! What takes to you?!
Stopstop please, Igaram!
I am well!
It is with me to excuse me.
I am sorry to have hustled to you.
Which extraordinary child…
With the presence of all the kings brought together in this same place,
even a small incident as this one could start a war.
Was it contained with full knowledge of the facts?
It is however so young…
Salt small morveuse!
Allons-y, Dalton!
Afflicted.
Ca hurts…!
You were very strong, Vivi-Sama.
The Princess who is attached to her country…
For this day, it has remained the same one.
It became somebody of good.
Dalton-Kun.
Our hearts also are always attached to this country.
Say to us what we must do…
in the interest of this new country.
Hiluluk.
This country will be able to reappear.
Just like did it your sons, Chopper.
DALTON-SAN!
It is horrible!
I have just remembered an important thing!
What thus?
Look by yourself!
It is him!
The pirate with the straw hat which eliminated Wapol!
Ca is not any doubt!
A reward of 30.000.000 Berry…?
For its head?
Ca with the air to be a truth hard to cook.
Where did you find?
I forgot to speak to you about it when it arrived, but…
Approximately a week ago, in the town of Robelle,
this strange traveller arrived of nowhere.
Oddly this day, it did not snow at all…
We did not have really any idea from where devil it could come!
Always it is that he said being to the continuation of Black Beard, the same pirate who put at bag our country.
But when it was said to him that there were no more pirates here for a long time…
In this case, I have another question.
You would not have seen a pirate wearing a straw hat in trimmings, by chance?
When I said to him that not, it gave us this poster and added:
If it comes in the corner…
If it comes…?
Say to him that I will await it during ten days with Arabasta.
I let to you undertake some.
He, wait a little!
Which is your name?
Ah yes.
It is true, I were going to forget.
I am called Ace.
When it passes, say the-him and it will include/understand.
OHE! THAT SOMEBODY CATCHES THIS GUY!
He left without paying the addition!
DO NOT FORGET ESPECIALLY!
He will await it during ten days with Arabasta?
Dr. Kureha.
What is there?
You have the air thoughtful.
Do you know Gol D. Roger?
“D”?
You want to speak about Gold Roger?
Thus it is called, now.
It would be said that…
… my small reindeer left with hard to cook.
Then it is always present…
Will of D…
It is really brilliant!
The ocean is immense!
Obviously!
To leave to the adventure on an immense ocean, it is that the life of a pirate!
I see!
To be a pirate, it is really exceptional!
He! It is what that?
It is a gull!
How a gull can be also imposing?
He, the gull!
IT ARRIVES!
What had I said?
It is well a gull.
There is not the question!
Because of you, it sinks right on us, now!
Wow! An great adventure!
Wait, where passed Luffy?
CAUTION!
You will be made puff out!
With the assistance!
Luffy will be made puff out!
It is not the moment to play charts!
Did he ask of the assistance?
Not.
Then all is well.
Leave it démerder.
But…
Wow…
He, Sanji!
I found us meat.
What you made, the guy?
You roupillez or what?
It IS OF MT FAULT, CRETIN!
How hope you to refund me?!
I had a good hand for once!
Oh I see. Afflicted!
Wow, super.
One finally will be able to have a true meal.
Does Ca eat that?
Is Eh, what there, Chopper?
Eh well…
I find…
That to be a pirate it is…
They is super!
You said it, they are super!
He, you!
One soon will accost in Arabasta.
There are not time to have fun.
You dispatch.
Ouais, one arrives.
Said, it is what Arabasta?
It is the country which the father of Vivi directs.
A démoniaque guy called Crocodile tries to reverse his capacity.
And Crocodile is one of the 7 Shichibukai.
Shichibukai?
They are pirates with the pay of the World Government.
A pirate with the pay of the Government?
Yes, they are really very powerful!
They furrow the seas to eliminate from other pirates.
This is why controlling them give them capacity in exchange of their services.
Crocodile, hein?
I am in a hurry to meet it!
Crocodile is regarded as a hero with Arabasta.
It protects the cities against any pirate raid.
But it is right a cover.
In the shade, it prepares a coup d'etat in Arabasta.
He wants to seize the throne of Arabasta.
But nobody is with the current…
Nor people…
Nor even my father…
Well!
One needs just botter the bottom of this Crocodile, not true?
Yes. If we manage to stop his coup d'etat, then we will be able to put an end to Baroque Works.
Works baroque…
It is true, you do not know them either, hein?
Eh well, I do not know any much more.
The system of Works Baroque is too complex.
In fact, their system is rather simple.
At the top, there are the Boss, Crocodile.
Alias “Mr. 0”.
Then, there are thirteen “Agents” which are directly under its orders.
There are twelve men and an animal.
They are associated with a female agent which comes complémenter their capacities.
Mr. 1 and Doublefinger Miss.
Mr. 2 is the only agent not having a binomial.
Is Mr. 3 the man candle whom we met in Little Garden, it is that?
Yes, it is associated with Miss Goldenweek.
Ah, this child.
Mr. 4 is associated with Miss Merry Christmas.
To tell the truth, I do not have many information on these deux-là.
And then, there is Mr. 5, the man with droppings of nose.
Droppings of nose?
Ouais, its droppings of nose are true bombs.
In fact, all the body of Mr. 5 is a weapon.
And Valentine Miss has the capacities of the Fruit Kilo Kilo.
It is this woman who can change her weight at will?
All the Agents to Mr. 5 are called “the Agents Officers”.
They have all of the capacities of a Fruit of the Demon.
They act only when one mission is of extreme importance.
And then, that goes from Mr. 6 to Mr. 13.
Their work consists in directing the employees who collect funds for the organization with the doors of Large Line.
Now that I think of it, I met a strange otter and a chicken.
You must surely speak about Mr. 13 and Friday Miss.
They are executors.
They deal with all those which missed with their duties.
Moreover, the “Agents Officers” have under their called subordinated orders 200 “Billions”.
And the “Agents Borders” as for them subordinated 1.800 under their orders called “Million”.
Here what is the underground criminal organization “Works Baroque”.
Then if I make the made account, 1.800 and 200 that…
Ca makes 2.000 people?!
2.000?!
Well! I know now.
It is necessary just that I boot the bottom of this Crocodile, not true?
You ace really nothing measuring rod with the situation, hein?
If the intention of Works Baroque is to seize the capacity of Arabasta…
Then the remainder of the Agents Officers must all be…
… gathered in Arabasta.
Yes.
It is simple! I just will burst this Crocodile…
It is good now, one included/understood.
Ah?
One, Two.
THREE!
THREE!!
Please, forgive me!
Mr. 2, Good Clay-Sama!
Stop of you foutre of me!
With which believe you to be addressed?!
I am Bon Clay-Sama, the Agent Officer of Works Baroque which can put an end to the tears of the children.
And you, you are a vulgar navigator!
Yes!
Points out to me which were the orders of Zero-Chan?
To intercept Mr. 3 on the direct way between Arabasta and Little Garden, and to remove it!
Oh, then you see, when you want.
In is direct way, there “direct”, not?
Thus we came directly from Arabasta in Little Garden, not true?
Then why we did not cross Mr. 3
on the road between Arabasta and Little Garden?!
Does that want to say that you let spin the boat of Mr. 3?!
Not… It is impossible…
Then you want to insinuate that it is entirely my fault?
Not, Mr. 2…!
Then it closes!
In any event, one cannot fail in this mission “Of removing especially Mr. 3” at such an important time!
The failure cannot be tolerated. If we fail, Mr. 1 and his binomial will be sent to remove me!
YOU INCLUDED/UNDERSTOOD?!
If you do not want to die, then you may find it beneficial with me to find it!
Mr. 3…
HOW THE SWANDA PUTS FULL CAPE ON ARABASTA AND AHEAD ALL!
It IS INCLUDED/UNDERSTOOD?!
And do not let pass only one boat!
YES!
Mr. 2, Good Clay-Sama!
What?
Do pirates pose problems in the Kingdom?
They thus do not know that they are on my grounds?
Who knows? Sir Crocodile.
A country right in the middle of a civil war is being a target of choice for a pirate.
You leave?
Yes, I must achieve my duty, after all.
Which kindness of heart you have there.
It is very natural.
Shichibukai are pirates who carry out other pirates.
They are the heroes of the people.