The candle of the devil!
Tears of regret and
tears of anger
He! What you insane, Ossan?
Remove this rock of me!
You at the right moments.
But with do the fact, what you make here?
What is there, Nami?
There is someone else
on this island!
It IS WHICH?
You…
Mr. 3.
Forgive me to use my code name.
I am only one humble sculptor.
And here my assistant, a realistic painter,
Miss Week Golden delicious.
Mr. 3? The man who ate the fruit Doru Doru…
It can create wax starting from its body and control it according to its desire. A human candle.
I… will never forgive you!!!
Dumb.
What do you make?
Hum… what I do do?
Eh well, before the end of the day,
you will become my very new artistic great project.
Calm yourself maintaining.
Did you think honestly that you could escape Baroque Works?
And especially with a man whose head is worth 30.000.000 of Berrys.
I am really happy of being able to make you pay what you did to me in Whiskey Peak.
The pirates should not line their nose in this kind of delicate situations.
We already caught your friend the fencer and the girl.
You had Zoro?
Then… you will be made slice.
You still speak?
Perhaps should I burst you then the face with small a kick bomb…
You believe that will hurt me?
I will péterai you the buttocks.
What a madness!
Luffy-San!!
Goes in hell!
Tsss, moron!
Luffy-San!
Allons-y, Miss Valentine!
Usopp-San!
Karu!
Salt bastard!
Oh, stop! Stop!
Once my Candle Jacket is solidified, it is almost as solid as of steel.
The unlimited force of a giant
is nothing once it was contained.
We use our heads,
thus we do not have to be obliged to face you face to face.
Leave the victory to your head.
The red ogre Brogy.
Do not look at me thus.
I died of fear.
Isn't Ca makes good?
This length, very long duel was finally completed.
You with honor during one century, isn't this fought?
Isn't the taste of the victory exceptional?
Although…
this time there was an outside assistance.
Amn't I right?
Dumb!
Not possible?
But at the end, there is a true victory!!
You did not know?
Your heads were put at price:
200.000.000 Berrys for you two.
And it is always valid.
Dumb!
I feel as if I had discovered a hidden treasure.
Then it was that your plan.
Mr. 3!
We brought
the traitor of our organization.
You were slow.
I wait since one moment.
Your methods are contemptible, Mr. 3!
To think that you placed a bomb in the alcohol of Dorry-San!
What?
Alcohol?
Alcohol… that I did give him?
Dorry!
After so a long time, this drink was exceptional!
Ouais.
It had a divine taste.
It is what you wanted to say?
Dorry!
Therefore, the young girl discovered my small round.
It is nothing, it cannot nothing make to stop to me now.
Mr. 5?
Bring to me the fencer and the girl.
I start!
Tokudaï Candle Set = Méga Service with Candle
Then it is thus that the capacity of Mr. 3…
What does it make?
Here they are.
It is disappointing
to think that I was overcome by this crew of lower row.
It is if embarrassing!
I am ashamed of myself!
It arrived only because you are weak.
Hein? What do you say?
Nothing.
Dispatch you to place them on Candle Set.
Set?
What is it that?
Nami-San!
Mr. Bushido!
Vivi!
You were not with Luffy?
Yes… but…
You speak about Straw hat?
I completed it.
It was an easy work.
You?
Welcome everyone
in my Service Set!
Then here what does that resemble?
To be a candle on a cake.
It is what this trick which turns up there?
I cannot move my legs.
Why would it have let us move?
It is our enemy, you know.
Tsss, too hard!
And in this position, I cannot use my force.
Something falls.
Benefit from the taste of my Candle Service!
The wax which falls on your heads
will transform you into wax statues.
There is something that even my artistic talents cannot create:
the perfect human statue.
Just like its name indicates it,
you will become wax statues containing of the hearts.
For the glory of my art,
you will die.
But of course!
Why should one be your “art”?
Brogy-San!
You do not rest like that!
Made something or you will become also a statue of wax!
'silvering, they are really cowards…
Ca is not used for nothing to require of him.
It simply realized
that without to have noticed the wounds of its adversary,
it killed Dorry, the friend with whom it fought during the 100 last years,
of its own hands!
And this idiot has even versed tears of joy for this victory!
Or perhaps did you deplore the loss of your friend?
Now, nothing can any more it help, morons!
I knew.
I knew that something did not go.
At the moment when we began our combat,
I knew that Dorry hid something.
Humm, you known as whom you had noticed?
What a lying!
If it were the case, why to have continued the battle?
I saw at which point you fought ardently.
I did not see an ounce of sympathy!
How a kid who does not include/understand the direction of the word “Duel”
could it include/understand the reason of my tears?
How could you know?
A warrior dissimulates his wounds and continues to fight,
how do you dare to insult it?
How can you test sympathy
for a warrior who wishes a duel?
And now, I include/understand how that occurred.
And now that I know,
I will finish my own hands of them
how thanks for my best friend, Dorry!
Brogy-San!
What a irrascible monster!
Usopp…
Can you… forgive them?
Never.
I will never forgive them.
You also… you are in anger?
Yosh, let us smash them!
One goes them botter the bottom!
Brogy-San!
What a cretin!
It would be said that I underestimated it.
Even me, I could not await me the power of a giant.
It would be said that I will have to calm it myself.
Doru Doru Tekase Arts = Wax Shackles
And in here still!
And maintaining the blow final!
That catches!
Now you will not be able
to move definitively more!
What a cruel torture!
Now, more quickly, my Candle Service!
Change them into wax statues!
Ca burns me the chest.
The wax vapor penetrates the lungs…
If that continues, I will transform myself into wax statue of the interior!
Yes! Yes!
Show me all the pain that you test!
A pathetic face of pain and anguish
is the kind of art which I prefer!
Harden with these desperate faces!
It is what this form of art,
species of degenerated with the tied braid?
How do you dare to do that in Brogy-San?
You will collect what you deserve!
You hear me?
Braillez as long as you want!
100 years…
Day after day…
Fights after combat…
We fought with the original honor of Elbaf, the village of the warriors.
And now…
Why should that finish like that?
Oh God of the War, Elbaf!
Is this the judgment which you gave?
Elbaf!
Why did you let do that?
Why won't I die in the combat?
What a superb expression!
Exquisite!
This pitiful, failing expression is the supreme form of art!
Elbaf!!
Oh not! I cannot move my hands any more!
I do not want to die like that!
One can nothing make?
My body hardens already!
What can one make?
Can Zoro, what one make?
He Ossan.
You isn't can always move?
Me also, I can still move.
Would Ca say to you to butt these guys with me?
Zoro, what…
You do not go…
If.
To cut your own legs?
Stop joking!
I do not laugh.
It is the only means of leaving from here.
You decide what?
Our decision?
It is without hope.
Even if one manages to go down, we are recaptured immediately!
What do you know of it if we do not test?
We will die here in any event.
Why not do it in a dirty way and while fighting a little?
One will not burst so easily in front of this useless waste!
Not?
About what does speak he?
He is insane?
It is bluff!
You will be able to never do that.
It is right pride!
Which bold kid…
I believed that I had lost
my reason to beat me.
With such a spirit, how do I can refuse?
You talk cock there?
You are serious?
How will you fight without your legs?
I do not know.
But,
I intend to gain.
What does it have this type?
It cracked!
How this kind of anybody can exist?
But I have the impression to have already seen these eyes-there before…
Princess Vivi.
Did you decide not to die?
With… Wait…
I will fight too!
Vivi!
Yosh! I included/understood!
Allons-y kid!
Do not even test!
What do you think of being able to make?
I go you botter the bottom!
What?
Allons-y, Usopp!
Ouais!
The bird!
Luffy!
Usopp!
Karu!
Brogy Master!
We are here to avenge your sorrow!
Usopp…
Satisfy you to smash these guy
until they are full with holes and make steal them!
Ouais! It is what I intended to do!
They destroyed the duel of Ossan!
It is you?
The most required man of East Blue?
The Navy seems to have lowered its criteria.
Ouahou! You ace an odd head!
It is not your problem!
It is one 3! One 3 ignited!
Your mouth!
Before that, Luffy, destroy this pillar!
One soon will become human wax statues!
What? You have troubles?
Not it is nothing!
What? Wait!
Your legs…
Oh, I cut them only to half.
How is that it nothing?
In any case, Luffy…
Does Ca say to you to destroy this pillar initially?
I will leave them afterwards to you.
Included/understood well!
I do not think.
Whatever this thing,
let us destroy that in first!
Yosh!
I included/understood.
I am a different man today!
You, good blood dispatch!
One hardens!