ZEFF AND SANJI'S DREAM.
THE SEA OF DREAMS, ALL BLUE.
Gin!
Regardless of how great a man he was before,
now he's just an ordinary chef.
Blasting his head off is no problem now.
You want to save this man, don't you, Sanji san?
So just heed my word and get off this ship.
I don't wanna have to kill you!
Leave this ship?
Not a chance!
You look pathetic, old fart.
In that state, you can't order the
cooks around to fight, can you?
I don't want to hear all this
crap from a small eggplant.
Who are you calling puny, asshole!
Stop treating me like a kid!
That damned Sanji!
He's not gonna abandon the owner, is he?
Gin, aim that pistol at me.
Are you a moron? You'll get killed!
Maybe.
Sanji-san... Why?
If you're so eager to die, let me do the honors.
I owe you one for my nose.
Don't you dare move now.
If you don't want to get your boss's head blasted.
Ultimate Killing Technique...
Pearl Present!
Sanji!
Why didn't you dodge that?
If I did that, he'd pull the trigger!
Why are you doing all this?
If you'd just abandon this restaurant,
everyone will be saved!
It's that simple!
This restaurant is that old man's treasure.
I'm the one who took everything from that old fart.
His power.
And his dreams.
That's why, now...
I don't want that old fart to lose anything, anymore!
Sanji, watch out!
Pearl Cross!!!
Sanji!
All Blue?
Yeah! the legendary sea!
It's out there somewhere.
I'm sure of it!
Are you a fool or something?
Of course that legend exists.
True.
As cooks of the sea,
even we'd like to see that sea, at least once.
Yeah!
I will definitely find that sea one day!
You'll find it eh, Sanji?
First of all, do you know where All Blue is?
Of course I know!
Don't think i'm dumb!
East Blue, West Blue, North Blue, South Blue.
East It's the sea in which fish from all these seas swim in.
That's the All Blue for ye!
For a cook of the sea, it's an unattainable paradise!
It's my dream.
No kidding, 'coz you can get any ingredient of the world in that sea.
That's what our cooking skills were meant for!
Yeah!
There are some that'd sacrifice their lives to find that sea.
Too bad it doesn't exist.
It can't possibly exist, a marvelous sea like All Blue.
If you stop and think about it, you'll get it.
Only cooks that daydream all the time think of that nonsense.
Well! now! That should be enough of this foolish talk.
Go get the dishes, Sanji.
Man, what a waste!
There's so many leftovers.
They didn't even touch this plate, even though I put in a lot of effort into it.
Customers these days sure don't have appetite.
Everyone oughtta stop eating those leftovers!
I just got rid of some that was spoiled.
It's that kind of attitude that makes you only half normal human size.
Don't forget that we're cooks of the sea.
You can never tell what'll happen on the sea.
You don't want to be caught off guard.
Say, how about some of this for ye?
No way!
Everyone! Calm down!
Please calm down!
Pirates!
Pirates?
That ship...
They're pirates!
It's Red Leg Zeff's ship!
Has he returned from the Grand Line?
Are you this pirate ship's captain, Red Leg Zeff..?
What are your intentions?
Everyone!
The loot... grab it all!
Shit! I can't just let them kill me!
I can't get killed by these goons!
What's with this kid?
Hey, brat. That thing's dangerous, so don't go swinging that around.
See? I'm bleeding.
This is really life threatening!
Shut the hell up!
You think I can just let myself be killed by the likes you?!
Sanji!
This looks bad! Don't annoy them!
A kid that wants to die so badly, just kill him off already.
Like I'm going to die!
If I'm gonna get killed by you, I'll just kill you first!
Sanji!
Good one Captain!
No mercy whatsover!
Like I can die...
I...
I have to get to All Blue someday.
''All Blue'', he said?
What a stupid dream!
Captain, tell him.
Such a thing doesn't exist, even in the Grand Line.
That idiot! He's still going on about that!
In a place like this...
In a place like this, I can't just get myself killed by these pirates.
Captain, let's get outta here!
There's a strom approching, and it's even bigger than last time!
Very well! You lot put the treasure you've looted onto that ship.
We're leaving.
Sanji!
Captain!
Damn kid!
Why all the trouble for just one brat?
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
So you came to eh, small fry?
You're something else.
Pirat...
There's no way you could move!
Whose kick do you think you took earlier?
Where's the ship?
Who know...
In that kind of storm, wouldn't be surprised if you got destroyed.
We are the only ones who made it here.
There's no vegetation or animals on this rocky island.
You might think of catching fish,
but if you go down once, there's no return.
Dying like rats, makes you wanna cry, doesn't it?
It's all your fault anyway!
I'm gonna kill you!
Stop barking.
All we can do is wait 'til help arrives.
Otherwise you'll use up all your energy and simply turn into a skeleton.
A skeleton?
Me?
That sack over there is your share.
If you eat like you normally would, it should last you five days.
So use your head on how you go about it.
Good thing we're both cooks, eh?
Wait!
Is that your share?
Isn't that a bit too big? three times at least!
But of course.
I am a full-size adult, my stomach's much bigger.
Be grateful that I spared you any.
Don't expect me to feel sorry for you.
You old fart!
You wait on the other side.
When you see a ship, let me know immediately.
Until then, we shouldn't contact each other.
Because we can't afford to waste any energy.
And keep praying.
Why that old fart!
If a ship comes, like I'd go tell him!
I'm all set.
I have enough food for five days.
Within these five days, one or two ships have gotta come by.
But there is still a chance that one won't come.
So, maybe I should divide this into 20-day portions?
If I give 20 days, a ship is bound to come!
I'm all good!
I'll definitely be saved!
Piece of cake!
None today, eh..?
It's alright, they'll come in a two or three days!
I don't want to die.
The last loaf of bread.
Better take it in well.
Man, what a wastel
There's so many leftovers.
Everyone oughtta stop eating those leftoversl
I just got rid of some that was spoiled.
Say, how about some of this for ye?
No way!
No way! No wayI
My last bit of bread!
That old fart...
wonder ifhe's dead...?
He's still alive!
Moreover, his ration... there's so much of it left!
There's still much food left!
No matter what, I have to get my hands on it!
It's his entire fault to begin with!
I want to live on!
Why are you here, small eggplant?
Perhaps you saw a ship?
I came to take your food!
If you're gonna kill me, then go ahead and try.
Without anything to eat, I'd die anyway.
To save so much for your own self...!
I thought we were not to contact each other until one of us saw a ship?
What's this? It's all mere treasure?
Having money but nothing to eat.
Funny story, don't you think?
Hey. This sack's just full of treasure.
What's this nonsense?
What's going on here?
What's about food?
Didn't you eat anything until now?
Hey, say something!
What happened to that leg of yours?
It was then...
Wasn't it just a dream?
To have you saving me...
The food you handed me, was that all of it?
Precisely.
Without that leg, you can no longer be a pirate, now can you?
Guess you're right.
Why?
You didn't have to!
I don't remember asking you to treat me so kindly!
Why?
WHY?!
You... You have the same dream as I do.
All Blue?
But, even your crew said that such a thing doesn't exist.
But it does!
When the times comes, travel to the Grand Line!
All Blue is definitely there!
I certainly can't be a pirate anymore.
So this time, you go there and find it.
Hey! Old man, don't die!
Don't just lecture then die out on me!
This sea...
I wonder how many people have cursed the vastness of this sea and died.
Up until now, whenever I've been in a drawn out starvation dilemma,
I'd think to myself,
''Wouldn't it be nice if there was a restaurant somewhere on this vast sea?''
Restaurant?
Yeah.
If I manage to escape this hitch, I'd bet everything into building my own restaurant.
Yosh! I'll help you out, so don't die on me!
For a weak small eggplant like you, that'd be impossible!
I'll get stronger!
So... don't die!
Hey!!!
Help us!
The old man!
Help this old fart!
Hey!!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Heeeey!!!
That old fart!
He gave up his leg so that I could live.
I too...
If I don't place my life on the line as well,
I won't be able to repay that old fart!
Why... why are you standing up, Sanji-san?
Even if I can make this restaurant
last for just one moment longer.
That bastard... is he trying to get killed?
Damn kid!
Yet another refined speech.
But now, this restaurant will be out of business.
From now on, it will be a pirate ship!
Idiot! Stop it!
Don't you dare hit it!
What's that guy thinking?
GOMU GOMU NO...
AXE!