He!
Ground here…
It is ground.
Oh, it is true. The celestial island east
manufactured starting from îlonimbus.
Then, why this
is island different?
I believe that is really worth
the sorrow to explore this place.
Your chances of survival in
the Lost Forest are of 10%.
Ordalie of the Bubbles!
Come now, if you made not quickly, your boat will be inserted very far in the Lost Forest!
H-He, it is necessary to catch up with it
boat or one will lose sight of the fact it!
I will give a lesson to the large heap!
Pay attention!
This type has odd capacities!
I will return as soon as
I will have the boat!
Ok!
GOMU GOMU NO…
GUN!!
MUCHI! [Muchi = Whip]
And still!
Shit! I cannot see it from here.
Make attention, Luffy!
These Priests are not ordinary!
It is necessary to find the boat and
to release from here as quickly as possible!
The danger of Ordalie of the Bubbles!
Fights died in the Drill Lost
Take your time for you
to release! Have fun!
Where are the two different ones now?
Nobody must escape.
In here one.
He!
You can see it, Usopp?!
I see it!
Say me moreover it!
It is right in front of you!
Climb on the second
tree after that one!
This branch will allow you
to reach the boat!
Ca rolls!
Here it is!
What goes it
to make?
Release!
ATTENTION, SANJI!
A bubble sinks right on you!
What?!
But what it fout, Luffy?!
Attacks Surprised Bubble!
Usopp!!
It IS ME WHOM IT AIMED?!!!
It will explode…
Ca wants to say what “Pon”?!
Failures, hein?
CRETIN!!!
SPECIES Of DUMB!
GOMU GOMU NO GATLING GUN!!!
DECREE, LUFFY!
Do not touch only one of these bubbles!
What?
What!? What?!
MEEERDE! It IS TOO LATE!
Pay to!
They rebound in all the directions!
What a band of clowns!
Lances!
A crab!
Four at the same time!
Hein?
Still failures?
Not, one would not say…
It is well that?!
What?
You want that I sing with you?
Ok, then be not astonished!
Me am called the Singing Pirate.
Well.
I did not sing yet!
HEAT!
HEAT - HEAT - HEAT
- HEAT - HEAT…!!!
HEAT!
WATER!!!
WATER - OF
WATER - WATER!
HEAT! HEAT
- HEAT!
HEAT - HEAT
HEAT - HEAT -
HEAT - HEAT!
THE RIVER!!!
AIIIIIIE!!!!!!
I passed to through!
Luffy!
Do not fall into this river!
It surely does not have basic!
Of accuracy!
LARGE WEAK!!
usopp hammer!
[Note:Wagomu = elastic]
Oh yes! Ca gives me an idea!
It is the moment to test
the small last!
Would not have you an idea, Usopp?!
Of course that if!
Me am called the Large Inventive Pirate!
You will discover my
all new weapon!
ussop has
It is what this trick?
Oh, admires that!
Here it is!
It is on the river just opposite.
I can arrive there!
Set Up!
What does it make?
Perfect. Here is a way
direct towards the Small Corbel.
If it still moves away in
forest, it will be out of reach.
I am not entitled to the error!
It is not a bad idea!
But pay attention to the bubbles!
I am already with the current.
Call me the King of the Jungle!
I go there!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
I go there!
Good!
It IS PARTIIIT!
Super! Perfect trajectory!
Now, goes up on
boat and cut the engine!
That there
it has?!
Go up quickly on the boat!
Not, it is…!
On this subject…!
I forgot…
The cord is fixed at my belt,
I cannot take down it!
Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit!
Still a little! I can the attrap…
Yo, Usopp!
You ace air you to burst, you too!
'Is necessary that I speak to you, both.
Included/understood?
I will pass sponge on your stupid things.
But you will listen to me henceforth.
Excavated, décholé. (Yes, sorry.)
Boi auchi. (Me too.)
Let us forget the boat for the moment.
With us three, we owe it
to put K.O in only one blow.
I insane that it is one
Priest or anything.
If we attack together, it us
an opening will leave inevitably.
To put K.O to me. ?
Where did it pass?
Impact!
SANJI!!
The life is only suffering.
And now, more than two.
Thank you.
He, you did not see some
thing to move over there?
Not really.
Don't He, you have anything considering, Robin?
Not, I do not have anything considering.
It was probably one
monkey or a trick like that.
A monkey?
Perhaps…
Good, must we check
on the other side of bank?
Not! And if one were still done
to attack by sharks?!
Whore, but is it what your problem?
I cannot reach it…
But I promised in Zoro
to try to repair the boat…
Go! I must better do my.
I hope that they do not see me.
Gently…
I have it!
I can repair the boat now!
The whistle!
You will have only with
to blow extremely in it.
I will descend from the Paradise itself
to fly to your help.
In normal weather, I make pay my
interventions 5 Million Extols…
But exceptionally, I you
fact gift of a whistle.
Wait!
Tell us at least your name!
I am the Knight of the Sky, Gan Fall!
And here my companion, Pierre!
That the chance is with
you, courageous hearts!
How one will make to go up, then?
I know! I will call it
grandfather and to ask him!
ATT…
Have-HAVE-HAVE-HAve-await,
Luffy, stop!
It is only to require
of the assistance in the event of urgency!
And if the odd guy with
its mask was repointait?!
Listen to me!
I decided that I
will keep the whistle on me.
An objection?
Yes.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
How can you say that!?
I am a fragile little girl!
You?
I am the only one to whom it must return!
I want to call it…
Not question, Luffy! You want just
to blow in this foutu whistle!
Remain apart from that!
I want to call it
grandfather! He is cool!
Give it to me!
I am weakest!
Anything! It is me,
weakest of all!
Stop your conneries! Everyone
How I KNOW am weakest!
Not, I am weakest!
You ever noticed how much
I was magnificiently can with the combat?!
They need little of it to fight…
Very well, here it
that we will make.
In the middle of the boat.
I hang it on the mast. In the event of
danger, no matter who will be able to use it.
It is equitable like that.
Ok.
Of agreement.
Oh, and another thing.
None you has it
right to blow inside.
Bah, I want to call the grandfather…
Use it and I dispatch you with the other
boils of the world of a kick to the bottom!
Ok, one will remember it.
B-good.
I prefer to keep it on me.
Now, if I am in danger, it
Knight of the Sky will come to my help.
But… the whistle is
my last recourse.
PERFECT!
I will better do my
to occupy me of the boat!
It is what?
How?
You are the only sacrifice for
which I moved?
Stone slabs?
While continuing in this direction,
perhaps other indices will be found.
He, you do not have anything
heard at the moment?
If. Do not move any more.
YOU WILL STOP YOUR CONNERIES?!!
It is not your day of chance, hein?
Remain on your guards.
Thank you…
Usopp!