Zenny lives on the island of the goat
There is a pirate boat
on the mountain!
Follow them!!! Do not let them flee!!!
I was unaware of at which point these pirates were dangerous.
But look at how they escape.
Sergeant!
One will capture the crew of the “Straw hat”.
I cross which one will be able them to have.
Hey! …
If nothing is done they will catch up with us!
I am hungry!
Me also…
Does the navy thus release never taken?
You did not can anything catch?
It is not a question of being able to catch something or not, but one moves too quickly.
This rate/rhythm, we will be dehydrated or died of hunger.
Robin-chan,
Your tea of the afternoon.
And in no-claims bonus delicious milfoils.
Thank you, Cooker-san.
[Cooker-san:Cook]
I want me too.
Where you hid that, brothel!!!
Hey! Remove your dirty legs from there, cretins.
I want me too!
How can you have fun in this situation.
It is not the moment to laugh!!
Nami! I cross which one will have to more worry about this that navy.
You would make better take the bar!
You ace not to say that to me.
Still fog?
Perhaps will be able we to use this fog in our favor and to mislead the navy.
But… These currents are too fast…
And of many rocks are submerged.
At this place, the sea represents an imminent danger to the fleet.
One cannot advance any more!
We are likely to pass there.
Keep silent yourself!
We continued them all this way up to now! We are close!
Sergeant, we must…
We withdraw ourselves. Let us make half-turn.
But we received direct orders of the Moore captain…
… imperatively to capture and eliminate the crew from the “Straw hat”!
Keep silent yourself, species of idiot!
The Captain is not charges some here.
But am months I there, measuring rod?
Yes, Mister!
Right in front of at any speed!!
Draw the principal sail on the left!!
We exceeded the fog.
Ohh!! An island! I see an island!
Perhaps that there is something to puff out!
Six people and an animal!
You do not have any chance, doubles of pirates.
You will see what I reserve to you!
Perhaps isn't this inhabited?
A goat?
Vian…!!!
Meat, meat, meat…
Viaaaaaaande
Stop immediately!
Even if you are hungry, you cannot eat this poor small goat!
It would be said that the friends of your pretty small goat
we surrounded.
It is a trap!
It led us in a trap!
I cross which one does not have the choice.
Does not kill them, Zoro!
They are not also bad.
I can ensure it to you.
CAT ko20} SHI
This goat deviated the trajectory.
Wait! One is not here to eat you.
I swear it to you!
But, why did you lead us in this trap?
Eh? Did somebody order to you to do it!?
Who?
Stop!
Idiot! Draw from there!
They is dangerous…
Arrêteeeeeeeeez!!!!!!!
M… Monster!!!
A strange grandfather fell from the tree.
Is Chopper, him it guy who asked the goats to attack us?
Good?
They say that it is him…
He probably believed that one was going to attack it…
Do not fear anything. We need simply a little water and food.
I cannot believe the words of a pirate!
Let to me say to you that there is no treasure on this island! I am mown.
You do not have the air of a guy who has much money in any case.
Dirty pirates!!
I remain a man despite everything!
You can boil me and burn me if you want!
Is Oh, it true?
I am the cook.
To boil and burn it are what I can do best.
Wait! Wait.
I joked!
Devils! Traitors! Assassins!
He disappeared.
This capricious grandfather is really timorous…
Oh not! Its heart stopped!
Zoro!
Demon!
What a horror!
Marimo!
Meeeh!…
Wait! I do not have…!
I am doctor.
Show us the house of the old man.
I believed that I was going to die.
Is never necessary to lower its guard vis-a-vis pirates.
Keep silent yourself!
You disappeared all alone.
Did Ossan, your heart stop because to you stays frightened?
On Large Line, one is not with the shelter of the surprises.
How are you managed to survive with such a fragile heart.
Ouai, It is true!
Lastly, what a relief!!
You do not have anything low register.
Which relief??
Following this incident, which is entirely of your fault.
I must rest a little after having come very close to death.
I will be able neither to cut wood, nor to extract from water.
It is a great failure for me!
You must compensate me for at least 50 million berrys!
Aren't you over-estimating?
Ca should not exceed that.
It is too severe. Even if I am generous, that must at least do that.
After deduction of the expenses of medical intervention of Chopper, that must do that.
These jeunes gens misuses a poor old man like vultures…
They are tyrants!
How if they planned to kill me!
One does not try to tyrannize you…
I want to live a long life…
Do not cry please!
They is good, Ossan. One will help you to cut wood and to extract from water…
Mugiwara-nii-chan, you include/understand me!
Ca solves the problem.
This insane old man seems to hate the pirates.
Perhaps he has his reasons.
The goats say that it is the only human being on this island.
It has failed here, and lives with them for 20 years.
20 years? One already met somebody of similar.
Where is what you go, Zoro?
I will seek food.
I doubt that this old rascal wants to divide something with us.
Ok!! Do not forget especially to bring back meat!
Do not force me has to strike you…
Let us see seeing!!
Move back a little behind. The young people nowadays do not appreciate art to cut out wood.
And they do not pigent anything with cleaning.
Remake to me that!
After you will give to eat with the goats. And do not forget to repair my hat.
Ah, I am burst.
Stop trailing and come to make me massages.
I must all say to you to you the young people.
You cause me too many problems.
And now…
Still!?
Shit!! It is by where north?
It is where the south?
What?
It is…
Finally of return…
You did not finish any yet with that?
This old man does not stop giving us his drudgeries has to make.
I am exhausted.
Ehh, I am hungry!
A pirate boat?
It was in rather bad condition, but y' had a flag pirates above.
Who built it?
Ca must be this old rascal.
And why would it have builds a pirate boat?
Who is concerned with it?
Can be that one discovered something of interesting.
Let us throw a glance there…
At the top of this mountain, not?
Allons-y !
Hey, not the sorrow to run.
Wait, that takes much time to go there!
It was right!
Brothel, It is really very close if one goes straight.
Ca appears unfinished.
Like a ghost ship on the mountain.
Robin, does not say similar things.
It is what?
Do not eat me, I am still too young person!
They are only fireflies!
He used trees as timber.
But it would be said that it stopped suddenly.
Is this really this insane old man who built that?
I believe that it is not here.
What is what is not here, Nami?
The treasure!
Treasury?
My instinct says to me that this old man is really…
A former pirate who tries to hide something!
Pirate?
I bet that it made shipwreck and failed only on this island.
And to escape from this island it started to build this boat.
But a former pirate hating the pirates?
Ca does not have any direction, see!
It is simply a camouflage, as that one will not seek his hidden treasure.
I found it equivocal as soon as I threw a glance on what it had.
Remember these valuable articles in the hut of the old man.
According to me it was a very beautiful collection.
Oh Nami-san, it was brilliant!
You laugh. This old very timid man cannot be a pirate.
He east can be old famous pirate,
In any event, look at this boat!
There is no way open in front of…
And behind, there is only one cliff impossible to climb.
If were to escape, why build it at the top of a mountain?
Why, Nami?
Why, Nami-san.
Ben…!!
Why did you withdraw yourselves?
Dangerous sea?
Is what you believe that you can make reign the justice of the Navy by being afraid of something like that?
All my excuses.
I thought simply that these pirates would also find this area dangerous for navigation.
Our game is not yet escaped.
Smoker and the Squadron of the Black Lance of Hina failed their mission of eliminating the pirates from the “Straw hat”.
But I will crush them my own hands.
Captain, I do not think that one can have them also easily.
Organize a team of attack immediately!
Locate and eliminate the crew from the “Straw hat”.
Yes Mister!
Excuse to me captain…
Allons-y Caporal…
Yes, Mister.
Why didn't you inform the captain in connection with the island?
You saw it?
Yes, among this water, I saw an unexplored island of my own eyes.
Doesn't the captain owe the knowledge, included/understood?
Why?
The Straw hat east can be on this island!
I will tell you a small secrecy.
On Arabasta, which was this person who stopped Crocodile?
Dear Sir, it was the Smoker captain!
A large hero in the Navy!
I cross although it deserves a medal.
But it was right a cover.
But, which will be able of…?
Apparently, it was Straw hat.
If one faces types like them, we will never have enough men.
But…
Hey, does not take always also seriously what your superiors say.
If one tries to face them of face, they will have us in a wink.
But in this moment, there is a thing for which I need your assistance, Caporal.
My assistance?
Hey, let us foutons the camps of this island.
If one remains here, this idiot will make us work for him for eternity.
Above all, I said…
Luffy!
I am hungry!
It is not sufficient to hold me upright!
What, y' has some more!
Very well, let us join the boat.
You ace very eaten when we turned you the back
Ah Chopper! One turns over to the boat.
I will remain with the old man.
I cannot drop my patient.
He goes well now.
You will never finish any if you feel sorry for him.
It is finished soon.
What?
Finished?
Its heart did not stop simply because it was frightened.
It is sick.
Finished? You want to say…
I am sure, it has less than three days to live.
What?
Three days?
I slept well.
Ca feels good!!
Hello Ojii-chan.
Your breakfast awaits you.
It is what all that?
Sanji is a large cook!
They is delicious!
The goats showed us some places where one could fish and collect food.
Now, go ahead and tastes!
I warn you, Nami.
I will not give you a round for that!
Do not worry you for that.
Incredible!! It is difficult to believe.
I had intended to say:“Be wary of the pirates who become suddenly friendly”.
There must be poison inside.
Species of impolite idiot.
To deal with doesn't the old people have anything strange, not?
Good, if you do not want any, I eat it!
, I wait eat it, I eat it!
Be to you which, you?
Are Jii-San, you well?
Does not frighten it!
Afflicted.
Thus you ate a fruit of demon.
It delicious, that is done well a long time that I had not eaten anything of also good!
Ojii-chan, has there T it another thing which we can make for you.
Thus you will not leave anything unfinished.
Firm your mouth cretin!
If you like my kitchen, I will prepare you dishes when you want.
Really? Thank you!
Ouiii, they is very good…
They is so good!
What does not go, Ossan!
It is not possible.
Already?
Not!!
Hey, does not give up now!
They is really good!
I was so surprised that had been wedged in my throat!
What, food was simply wedged in your throat?
Do not frighten us thus any more.
I knew that it was a little too early.
Too much early why?
C….it is nothing!!
He wanted to say that you eat too quickly.
But, you can take mine!
Mine too!
Also take that…
It is true?
Thank you!! Thank you!!
All is quite good…
This appetite… that points out Luffy to me!!
Will he really die in three days?
I found, Sergent.
According to this report/ratio, 20 years ago…
… a man on board a pirate boat disappeared in this water!
Now I remember, its name was Zenny or something like that.
Zenny?
It had not completely disappeared!
It was there with its large treasure.
If it made shipwreck on this island…
… It should be ready to pass the weapon on the left.
But the treasures never die.
Hey, You eat too much!
I have just started…
You are too cool, Ossan…
www.rival-spirits.com
http://www.zento.fr
www.saiyajin-team.com
www.kyubi-wolf.net
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/rival-spirits
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/zento
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/saiyajin
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/Kyubi-Wolf
CYB3RFR34K-ISO