On Upper Yard, ground of God,
the play of Survival beats full sound.
With the service of Eneru God, the Priest Ohm.
The Warrior Shandia, Wiper.
The Knight of the Sky, Gan Fall.
And Zoro.
Each one fights to survive, one
incredible battle is launched!
What a cretin!
Aisa!
You were distracted and you
lowered your guard. Idiots.
Forget the others!
There is nothing any more with
to make to save them.
The Ultimate Test of Ordalie of Iron!
The Combat has Mort of the White Barbed wire!!
Played well, Ohm-sama!
In this moment in the ruins
higher, 4 Soldiers are.
And these deux-là does not have
not known as their last mot.
What makes 4 Shandia and
an inhabitant of the Blue Sea.
More the python and Holy.
What makes a total of
10 men and 2 animals.
According to the prediction of God, it
will remain soon that 5 survivors.
Now, let us take again the combat.
I will finish some with you.
Ohm, species of dumb!
To attack Wiper by behind…!
Oh? This man, who is nothing vis-a-vis
Is God, so important in your eyes?
Wiper is our reason to live!
It showed us
true pride of Shandia!
We are here for
to recover our terre natale!
Poor wretches such as Eneru cannot
not to include/understand the pain of Shandia!
Even if I included/understood, you
would gain any sympathy of my share.
To be frank…
You waste your time!
Burst, Ohm!
You will not échaaapperas me!
We are ready for the final attack.
Holy, it is the moment!
Sink, Holy!
What does it make?
Whore. How a dog
can it run like that?
I do not like that!
Here come the Ultimate one
Test of Ordalie of Iron!
The Combat with Died of the White Barbed wire!!
You did not need
to build this cage.
I will not flee.
Species of imbecile!
Say rather than you
can escape more!
The cage is tiiiissée
white barbed wire!
And then?
Then…
Ca makes very badly when one rubs there.
How I leave from here once
I will have cut out you out of discs?
Worry about that once
that you will have cut out us.
There remain 8 men and 2 animals.
I must initially deal with this python.
Nami is inside…
And…
Knight of the Sky!!
this man who saved Chopper, too.
Wiper!
When we were children,
you taught me a thing.
Our Shandia ancestors
lived in the Blue Sea,
in the large capital
holy of Shandora.
The Large Karugara Warrior
our ground protected.
But, 400 years ago…
Knock-up Stream propelled
Shandora, thus creating the celestial island.
It will never be able
to turn over in the Blue Sea.
What was to be to them unbearable.
However…
However, inhabitants
celestial island…
regarded as their ground
crowned and concealed it to us!
Our ancestors were driven out
of their terre natale.
They could never turn over
in the holy capital.
They did not can even touch
ground of their village!
And during these 400 years,
Shandia underwent humiliation!
Upper Yard is with us!
We will recover it!
It is our terre natale!
Pride of our ancestors!
Once us in
will have finished with Eneru,
it will not be any more the sorrow of
to make concern for a bag of Vearth.
We will turn over to Shandia,
our home, 400 years before!
That those which are not yet ready
to risk their lives remain here.
I would not be upset with them.
He, Wiper.
Loans? We always were it.
Summers you ready to give up those which
will fall on the battle field?
That those which will span theirs
brothers fallen to the combat…
and which will continue, follow me.
Today, I…
will take the head of Eneru!
Wiper!
WIPER!
God thank you, I find you!
Laki?!
Wiper!
Listen to me!
What?! What you insane there?!
I came to repeat you
what Kamakiri said!
Nobody can beat it…
Escaped, Wiper!
Cease the combat!
Eneru is… in the forest.
He, Laki!
Eneru is what people fear more than
all since mists of time, the incarnate lightning.
Remain with the variation!
MOVE AWAY FROM HERE!
You cannot overcome it!
HE, STOPS!
Wiper?
You called me?
Eneru…
Does not approach you it, Eneru!
Does not touch it!
It gave up the combat!
HE!
LAKI!
Laki! Does not attack it!!
ESCAPE!
Bandage idiooots!
You will not survive if
you worry about the others!
It is invincible!
It is what people fear more than
all since mists of time, the lightning.
Reincarnation of God!
I hold you, Wiper!
Species of idiot!
Flee!
Eneru…!
Hein?
Did Ca do anything to him?
Then I will give him another of them!
You are even more
ignoramus that I thought it,
Wiper, the Shandia Warrior.
Whether it is a woman or a warrior,
I do not make distinctions enters
the sheep which are opposed to me.
With a little chance, she will survive.
This was… God?
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
And well. This woman was insane.
Even petrified fear,
it attacked God.
It was its punishment.
I have a last thing with
to make before breaking me from here.
PYTHON!
You ace a trick in
the stomach which I need!
Release from my way!
Holy! Stir up yourself!
Eisen
[Note:eisen = iron (in
German) & whip = whip]
CENTER!
Now, there are 6
men and 2 animals.
Super.
Nobody with the wounded air.
Which is this place?
We are in the stomach of the snake.
One was made swallow.
Ah, I see.
This stomach with the rather long air.
Are He, Aisa, you well?
Wiper, I am sorry!
Hein?
Which is this place?
Interior of the stomach of the snake.
You had not noticed?
Do not be quite malignant for you.
The snake?!
Good, let us leave quickly from here
before being digested.
I hope that Waver is in good state.
But, why are not you
not on the boat?
This thing continued us
then we had to flee.
My faith, that does not disturb me.
Is this young girl Shandia?
Oh not! God!
I will eliminate you!
He! Now, stops with that.
Besides, you believe that we would have
to bore the wall of its stomach?
DO NOT BE STUPID!
What it would arrive to us
if it were put at régurgiter?!
You want to die?!
Reflect a little!
O-Oh… I joked just.
It is what your problem?
Odd knight, you
be really odd!
Whore.
I am curious to see
the head of somebody…
of enough stupid to attack
this thing of the interior.
This noise…
Noises of step.
But which that can be well?
Who goes there?
Nami!
Odd Papi!
You…
Luffy!
What you made…
in this mysterious cave?
Wait, until you make here?
I lost myself!
I do not manage to believe in it.
The snake also swallowed Luffy.
I hope that the others are well.
Hein? I arrived there all alone.
Hein?! The snake?!
Exact.
It is for that you are there.
Oh, I see.
Ca was to be terrifying.
You were done
to eat by the snake?
As… I… said…
YOU TOO!
ONE IS ALL IN the STOMACH OF the SNAKE!
Do not draw me the nose! My nose!
The head of Usopp!
Who is this cretin?
I have shame to acknowledge it, but
it is the captain of our boat.
Oh, then you are the captain.
I believe that it is the end of the world.
Ouais, it is the impression which it gives.
Do not be very malignant for you if you ace not
noticed that you had been made swallow.
Then, it is the stomach of the python?!
I was made eat, me too?!
It is what I tests
to render comprehensible you.
Your clothes are also in
train being made digest.
He, you are right!
He, it is necessary to find
the bottom of this thing!
Its bottom…
It is like that you intend to leave?!
One was made eat, then one does not have
that to leave at the same time as the excrement.
NOT!
Rather to make me digest!
Nami makes fear.
Women of the Blue Sea
are really violent.
At all events, it
snake is of bad mood,
Then one was made eat.
Before it recovers
in anger, we must…
It is of bad mood?
Ouais.
It had the very sick air
and pain twisted.
Why it was sick?
OH NOT!
You… made grabuge
since you are in it?
Ouais, I tested
to break the wall to leave!
Then it was you.
And all these efforts gave me hunger.
You have anything to eat?
What is there?
You…
CRETIN!!
You shout like an imbecile.
Make as you want!
Be not made digest
before I arrive, Aisa!
Now, I go
to open by tearing it!
Dumb!
Hold good still a little, Nami…
And… heu… Odd knight!
Just time to put
a beating with this guy.
Now, it is time to finish some.