What's that?
Yahoo!
Are you ok?
I am fine!
They all come here to see
what I have achieved.
The new members of
Usopp's pirate crew.
We are not.
I need you to do me a favor.
A favor? Me?
Yes! We need a big ship...
- Hey you!
What are you doing here?
Klahadore.
What is the meaning of this?
How can you break in like this?
Who are you?
(Episode 10)
"The World's Strongest Weirdo!
Django the Hypnotist"
(Episode 10)
"Shijou Saikyou no Hen na Yatsu!
Saiminjutsushi Django"
(Based on manga
ch.24: "The Lie Rejector",
ch.25: "Lies" and
ch.26: "Captain Kuro's Plan")
Uh...
Pardon me, Klahadore...
These people are...
- Be quiet.
I will let you know later.
Please leave now.
Or do you have business here?
We want a ship.
I can't help you.
Usopp!
Damn!
We heard about you a lot.
You are quite famous here.
Really?
They said you had been
to different countries.
Very impressive for your age.
You can call me
"Captain Usopp".
That's my nickname.
Captain.
I heard about your father too.
What?
Klahadore, stop it.
You are nothing more than
a filthy pirate's son.
So I am not surprised
of whatever you do.
But you stay away from
Mistress Kaya!
How dare you say I am low...
You and Kaya live in
completely different worlds.
Are you here for money?
How much do you want?
You've gone too far, Klahadore!
Apologize to Usopp now!
Watch out, Kaya.
I am not going to apologize
to this savage, lady.
I am just telling the truth.
I am sorry for you, Usopp.
You must hate his guts.
You must hate you irresponsible
and selfish father --
-- who values money
more than you!
Klahadore!
Stop saying bad things
about my father!
Usopp!
Why are you so worked up?
Why not tell me some lies
about your father?
Like your father is a merchant...
...or that he's not your
real father, perhaps.
Shut up!
Captain!
Look at him.
His first instinct is violence.
He's merely an animal.
Like father, like son.
Shut up!
I'm proud that my
father as a pirate!
I am proud of his
courage on the sea!
You are right.
I love to make stories.
But I am proud of
being a pirate's son!
I am a pirate's son!
Captain.
Your pirate is a
brave fighter on the sea?
That is a deceitful way
to tell the truth.
Your behavior is iron-clad
proof of your ruffian heritage.
Lie all you want...
...but when in trouble,
your first recourse
is violence.
The most damnable thing is
to get close to Kaya
only for money.
What did you say? I am...
I am on to your scheme!
You're trash!
Just like your pirate father!
That's enough!
Stop it, Usopp!
No more violence!
Klahadore isn't a bad guy.
He just concerned about me.
He didn't mean to do that.
Leave the grounds.
And don't ever come back!
You win.
You don't need to
tell me to leave.
I won't be coming back
ever again!
Usopp.
Damn, that man!
Captain isn't that kind of person!
Yeah, you idiot!
Idiot!
Idiot!!!
Why is it your concern?
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Stupid jerk!
Get off this property at once!
It's meal time, my lady.
I don't want it.
I don't want to eat.
The chef will be upset
if he heard what you said.
He cooked really hard for you.
He made alot of healthy food for you.
Why did you say that?
Of course, I know I shouldn't
hide it from you.
I was wrong to talk to Usopp.
But you don't have
to make them leave.
May I sit down?
- Please.
It's going to be 3 years...
...since the first day
I got here.
I will never forget that day.
I got kicked off the ship
I worked on...
...because I made a
tiny mistake.
No job and no money.
I almost died on the street.
- Hey! Don't come near here!
- Get up!
This place isn't for
a person like you!
Sir? But...
I got it.
I'll let him in now.
To me, your parents
were my saviors.
You are my saviors' daughter.
I know I don't have the right...
...to tell you who you can
make friends with.
But that young man Usopp...
...can't even do well greeting.
What can we expect from him?
If anything bad happens to you,
I'll have failed you
and your father!
I went too far.
Do you hate me?
I don't hate you.
I am grateful to you.
But please don't take this wrong.
Usopp is a good man.
It doesn't matter.
- Klahadore!
I really don't know
how to make you understand!
Right -- I don't.
Hey, where is Luffy?
I don't know.
He might have gone
to find the "Captain".
I know where the Captain went!
Yeah!
The beach!
He goes there often.
Wanna see?
No thanks.
Are you missing someone?
You mean Onion?
He disappears all the time.
Then he'll come back screaming.
We're doomed!
See?
There is a man walking backwards!
There is a strange guy
walking backwards!
Liar!
- It's true!
Look!
Hey, who called me strange?
I am not strange.
You are strange.
Don't be silly.
I am just a travelling hypnotist.
Hypnotist? Cool!
Can you show us your trick?
Show us!
What?
Don't be silly.
Why should I show you my ability
to someone I don't know?
Ok. Look at the ring.
Why didn't he say so?
When I say
"One Two Django",
you will fall asleep.
Ready?
One... Two... Django!
Why are YOU sleeping too?
Hey!
Here you are!
What in the...
Can't you say "hi" normally?
What?
Anything happened?
Nothing.
That bastard!
He insulted my dad.
I hate that guy,too.
No matter what,
Yasopp is a great pirate.
Tell me!
He sticked to his dream
of becoming a pirate.
I'm really proud of my father.
That guy insulted my father
I am so proud of.
I will never forgive him.
You will never see that
lady again, will you?
I don't know.
If that butler comes and beg me,
MAYBE I'll see her.
THAT butler?
- Yes.
That butler.
That butler?
Why is he here now?
Hey, Django.
Didn't I tell you to
lay low in this village?
You were sleeping
on the street.
Don't be silly.
I'm not standing out.
And it's not strange at all.
There's a strange guy with him.
I haven't seen that man before.
Who is he?
So, is the plan all set?
Of course.
I'm ready anytime...
...to murder that
mansion's owner!
He said "murder"?
Don't use that term, Django.
Oh, sorry. Didn't mean to.
Hey, what are they talking about?
Who knows.
I was gonna ask you.
I don't want to just kill Kaya.
We have to make it
look like an accident.
Got that?
We will wait for you signal
and attack the village.
And take her life, right?
Then you will inherit her money.
Stupid!
You are so stupid!
I can't inherit her money as
an outsider.
You need a plan.
It's not that easy.
Listen, this is very imporant.
You have to hypnotize her and
make her write the will.
Make her write down:
"I will leave all my money
to Klahadore."
Then I will be able
to inherit the money.
Very naturally.
It took me three years
to earn everyone's trust.
I'll make it look like an accident
and nobody will suspect me.
That's why you were butling
for three years.
("Kuro": Japanese for
"black" or "dark".)
Three years ago when you
suddenly said you quit,
you found someone at
random to replace you.
And told them you were executed.
Now I know it's the beginning
of the whole plan.
You are worth being called a genius.
Stop calling me a genius.
I gave up the title
three years ago.
I hope to get the money without
being chased by the government.
I am a pacifist.
What kind of pacifist are you?
For your own peace, you went and
killed the girl's family.
Hold on -- her father died
from natural causes.
That wasn't expected.
So what?
That doesn't matter.
Give us a sign when you're ready.
We've been anchored offshore
for about a week.
They are thirsty for blood.
Something big happened.
You are not going to believe this.
Hey, what's up?
It sounds like an emergency.
Weren't you listening?
It's horrible!
They are serious!
That butler is Captain Kuro.
He is the smartest of all pirates.
Also the cruelest one.
I heard that he was arrested
by the navy and was executed.
I can't believe
Captain Kuro is still alive.
And became a butler.
He had it all planned.
For the last three years,
he plotted trying to get the money.
They're gonna attack the village!
And kill Kaya!
We're doomed!
Hey, don't stand up --
they'll see you!
Hey you!
Don't kill Kaya!
Who was that?
Idiot!
They saw us!
We better run and hide
or we're dead!
Well...
Isn't it Usopp?
They found me too!
Heard anything interesting?
No, no, no!
What are you talking about?
I just got here and
didn't hear a thing!
We heard everything!
There is no way to avoid this.
Hey, kid!
Look at the ring.
What?
It's a weapon!
Let's go!
When I say
"One Two Django",
you will fall asleep.
OK?
One, Two...
Django!
Hey!
Get up, Django!
You never changed.
What're doing?
You're gonna fall!
He fell on his head.
I didn't want to kill him.
From that height,
he is dead for sure.
Damn them!
He's dead!
There is one more.
Should I kill him?
No need.
Nobody will believe him.
Let's do it tomorrow morning, Django.
Attack when the day breaks.
Destroy some houses to
make it look like an accident.
And kill Miss Kaya!
Tomorrow?
You heard that, Usopp?
No matter what you heard,
no one can stop my plan.
There isn't gonna be any problems, right?
- Of course not.
My plan won't be changed.
Oh my God!
We're doomed!
Everyone in the village
will be killed!
Kaya is going to be killed!
And everyone I love!
Who are you?
I am Usopp.
I am a brave fighter.
I heard you weren't feeling well.
Let me tell you a story to cheer you up.
It's none of your business!
Please leave, or I will call for help.
Then what?
What's next?
Of course,
I fought him like a soldier.
I first used the cat stick to
take the huge cat down.
BASTARDS!
Usopp's running.
His face looks angry.
What happened?
The butler is a pirate.
He had his men attack the village.
It's good to know
that in advance.
Let's slip away, don't worry.
Hey!
- What's going on?
I have to buy some meat, or
the boss will be gone.
What are you thinking?
Next "One Piece":
"Revealing the Conspiracy!
The Pirate Caretaker, Captain Kuro"
I want to be the king of the pirates!