Then?!
They are always with our cases?!
It would be said that they gave up!
I see them nowhere!
Oh, it is a good news.
Brothel, this monstrous gun made me flipper!
But where could they hide that well?
A gun?
Do Ouais, you remember?
This enormous trick that the warriors carried!
Oh, that?
“OH, CA”?!
What does not go at home? Y' has anything funny!
It is for that they would run us afterwards!
Ouais! Do not laugh!
He, look at! It is Nami and Conis!
Oh, Nami-swan! Conis-chwan!
Is all well?
Of course!
Blue Sea finally!!
Final weaves by the emotion
What?
They fled the island?
Yes, we will never on the occasion to express our gratitude to them.
Which tragedy.
Do they know at least that we are indebted for them?
Yes.
I must admit it.
They absolutely do not have any empathy for the others.
You were right to do that, Aisa.
To keep yourself the secrecy.
Everyone made of din because of our heroes who ran away themselves.
But Luffy and the others said that it had to be said to anybody!
Their do you have says at least something, Aisa?
Ouaip! I said to them thank you.
He, Laki, guess what!
Luffy can also extend its arm far it wishes it!
Gomu Gomu No Pistol!
He, Aisa, remain quiet.
It there also of the strong warriors on the Blue Sea.
I would like to also be like that one day. Gomu Gomu!
Aisa.
Hum?
I make you just a small cut today.
You require that your hair pushes back.
I think that will suit you well.
Isn't a girl must be nice?
NICE?!!
Me?
Exactly.
You will not have to carry weapons any more.
You can live free, like any inhabitant of the celestial island.
Be really sympathetic today for you, Laki!
He, Aisa, stop moving.
Laki the sympathetic one!
Aisa!
Large Karugara Warrior.
I intended to say that the duty of Shandia had been accomplished.
And your last wish reached your friend.
The future generations will not have to pour their blood any more again.
The war is finished.
But, we will not lose our pride!
Therefore, please, continue to protect us.
I promise that the Flame of Shandora will die out never again!
I am the Knight of the Sky, a free mercenary.
This country does not require it any more.
Now, this country needs somebody to control it.
And I believe that you are that which will achieve best this task.
You are our enemies.
This city was yours in the past.
This does not have any direction.
That does not justify all.
This war taught it to us with all.
Nobody can have Vearth.
God is a support.
This country is Skypiea. This city is Shandora.
Only a man who deplored this war can link them.
This man, it is you.
Knight of the Sky, Gan Fall.
Please, accept
new the divine throne of God…
and support this deeply ravaged ground.
We also want that you returned!
Gan Fall-sama!
We are all of agreement us too!
Ouais!
Gan Fall!
God!
Please, return us!
Honestly.
Just at the moment when I thought of being able to benefit from the harvest of my pumpkin piece…
He, everyone, it is there!
Look in front!
It is Cloud End!
Ouah, lets see me!
Then, one can go down by there?
One quickly arrived.
Does Ah, one return already?
You ace reason. It is hard to think that one from goes away finally.
We will leave this white sea.
It is sure, the celestial island was fun!
But it was a little frightening too.
It seems that after having passed this door, Milky Road kills us on the Blue Sea.
You think that one will return one day on the celestial island?
Ca would be well.
Ok, everyone, I am sorry!
We cannot go further!
Take care of you!
Thank you to say to us goodbye!
Conis-chan, take care of you!
Thank everyone too for our share!
With more!
Thank you for all!
Not!
It is with us to thank you for all!
We will never forget you!
Conis, Grandfather, made attention with you!
Yes!
Now, please, your veils and you stud arrange!
Ok, let us do what he says!
One starts to accelerate!
Well, the road is with 7 kilometers height!
Grouillez you!
OUAIS!
What, what?!
“Do not leave without me!”
Ah, the Bird of the South which we accidentally brought on the celestial island.
Well, Captain!
The Log is pointed on the next island!
Ouais, they is good!
When one is in bottom, one
a new adventure will start!
The guy!
Be ready!
ONE TURNS OVER ON THE BLUE SEA!
OUAIS!
How everyone is careful during the freefall!
The freefall?
Heso!
It left!
Living White Sea, Takoballoon!
AN OCTOPUS!
Why you…
Q-Q-qu-what?
He, come to see!
It is a trick of insane!
It is what this thing?!
A balloon!
They is too cool!
We slowed down!
I… I…
thought that I was going to die.
Sound it!
Send to the heroes of this country the tinkling of the Bell!
Heso!
Luffy, return quickly!
Still return!
Thank you with you!
Return healthy and safe on the Blue Sea!
When it sometimes happens to you to throw a glance in the sky…
Although that can be a legend,
think that the country of God floats up there, of 10.000 meters above you.
If you tighten the ear,
you will hear the tinkling of a bell.
It sounds today.
It will sound still tomorrow.
This bell sounds top of the skies, coming from a floating country…
and its pride sings.
They is sympathetic!
Ouais, I adore that!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
You give up exploration?
Of course!
The Gold City was in the sky.
We will not find anything at the ocean floor.
The things are finished now.
There is no reason to remain here, apart from our pride.
Owner?
I owe you all my gratitude for all that you did.
You supported my daring dream during so many years.
That seems…
so far!
Then, the guy!
In which adventure one will launch out now?
We will follow you anywhere, Patron!
Gold!
One is rich finally!
What could one buy?
Why not a énooooorme statue of bronze?!
Imbecile!
Why you would exchange gold against bronze?!
Guns should be bought!
One will buy Ten of them! Ten guns!
Nami-san! I would like a refrigerator with a lock!
It is stupid!
I want… I want…
I want to buy books!
I would like to read books of medicine of other countries!
It IS FOR CA THAT I GO
TO BUY, DRAFT!
Await the guy!
One must initially land before being able to start to divide the treasure!
Please, buys to me books!
One did not leave the inn if I let to you buy all that you want.
Madam Navigatrice?
Where does the boat go?
Where?
The next island, of…
What is there?
It occurs what?
What occurs, Nami-san?
Fact of shitting.
One took an airstream and we deviate of our trajectory!
An airstream?
Now that I think of it, I feel a breeze.
Does Ca fear?
Of course that yes!
Now we do not know where we will land!
What does one make?
With the octopus, we cannot set the sails to control ourselves the boat.
He, does not worry you for that!
Once the sea will have been taken, one will go to the next island!
You still speak without knowing, like always.
But, wait…
A problem, Sanji-kun?
Not, it must be my imagination.
Hein? How that?
Not, nothing.
Look at over there!
He!
What, it was a dream?
BROTHEL, WHAT
DO NOT TURN OUT BADLY AT HOME?!
I WILL KILL YOU, DRAFT!
I will throw you over edge!
You made us die fear!
Moron!
Zoro! Ca gives what?!
The sun lay down for the day.
But the sight remains sympathetic.
Ouais, you ace reason!
Hein? Already the morning?
It grows dark, cretin!
Ca takes time before reaching the Blue Sea.
I still wonder until where we will derive from our main roads.
He! And if I sang you one
impassioned love song?
Buckle it!
This rate/rhythm, one will be made carry until Raftel.
Usopp, it is incredible!
It is impossible.
We have even more half of Large Line to cross before reaching Raftel.
Ah, ouais, ok…
I knew it.
Brothel, one is bored.
How long still before we land?
Turn over to lie down.
If are awaked to you, come by-there, Zoro!
It east is delirious!
Hein? Luffy?
From where can it shout well?
It was as if it were rather far.
Are Luffy, to you where?
Up there!
The guy, go up too!
It is too funny!
Shit, I knew it!
They is too cool! Too much cool!
He, do not do anything stupid, Luffy!
Our lives depend on this balloon!
They is good! They is good!
Stop, Luffy!
Go down again!
He, Luffy, stop!
Why you shout, Sanji-kun?
The octopus narrows!
This rate/rhythm, one will fall!
What?!
He, Luffy!
What doesn't go?
The octopus narrows!
What?!
Now that I look at it, it seems a little smaller.
One does what?
One is still in high-altitude!
Will it hold until one lands?
He, Luffy!
Y' has a problem! Go down!
I flippé!
Ca has right decree to rebound!
I had said it to you, the octopus narrows!
Hein? I fall again.
One falls! One falls!
Oh not! At this speed, one will be crushed on the sea!
If the sea is touched, nothing will be able to save us!
Really?! Fact of shitting…
What will you make, Usopp?
How I would know it?!
I will save the boat!
What you will make?!
Do not make the nutcase, Usopp!
usopp…
aaaaaaaaaaaa
Well, I succeeded!
Good!
[Note:Breath = Breath]
Ok, now fleet!
One slowed down!
Ouah!
One is saved?
It seems that it is the case.
You have all considering my moment of glory?
Usopp, you are incredible!
I had the jitter during one minute!
Me too.
I thought that we were lost.
WHAT?!
Usopp!
The guy, you with something hang!
Nami-san, Robin-chan, you are well?!
I was afraid!
The octopus has narrows blow very!
I think that it did not have any more air.
How it occurred?!
But, one succeeded!
Without dying!
He, thank you!
But…
Which crowned place.
After being returned here low, that seems so much far.
Almost like if we had dreamed.
It is the country of the dreams.
I wonder whether we will go back one day there.
You will go up there when you die. Or some share not far.
Zoro, are you sure that you will go to the Paradise?
Species of moron!
Well, all is calm now.
I will make coffee.
I want puff out, Sanji!
I will make some, therefore wood your coffee and patient!
Of course!
In any event…
But…
where we are?