While attempting to escape from Upper Yard,
Nami's team was confronted by God Enel, who displayed his fearsome power.
Meanwhile, the four members of the exploration team,
had become separated on their way to the ancient city.
Luffy later engaged in battle against the Shandian warrior, Wiper.
BAZOOKA!!
Nami's team then faced a new enemy!
Like hell you don't!
My name is Hotori!
My name is Kotori!
And our third brother was taken out by you guys!
And Chopper, after becoming hopelessly lost, found himself face to face with a Priest Gedatsu.
Where'd it go!?
SCARY!
ORDEAL OF SWAMP!
CHOPPER VS PRIEST GEDATSU!!
This is... a monument to the city.
Their ancestors must have erected it after the city fell.
Shandra.
That was the ancient city's name.
Year 402 of the Kaien  Calendar.
The city was at the peak of its prosperity over 1,100 years ago.
And then it fell 800 years ago.
The 100 years of history which vanished from the world without a trace...
Perhaps this island holds some knowledge,
Of the untellable history that cannot be found on the sea below.
This is a complete map of Shandra.
Perhaps i'll learn something if i go to the center of the city.
Some clue about the untellable history.
Who's there?
My, what a lovely young lady.
Are you another one of God's servants?
Servant?
Silence that mouth of yours.
I am the Chief Enforcer in God Enel's service, Yama!
And? What is it that you want, Mr. Chief Enforcer?
You will see soon enough.
Where did it go!?
A stealth technique, no doubt.
This guy's got his eyes rolled back!
Those white eyes are scary!
Gedatsu-sama! If you do not direct your eyes foward, you cannot see your enemy!
How careless!
Is this guy an idiot!?
An enemy?
I get it now!
You must be one of the Priests!
That is correct, heso.
I am the Guardian of the Sky, Gedatsu!
A Priest in the service of the almighty God Enel!
I govern the Ordeal of Swamp on Upper Yard.
Say something, you dimwit!
Gedatsu-sama! if you do not speak, the enemy cannot hear you!
How careless!
HOW CAN YOU FORGET THAT!?
I advise you to watch where you step!
Lying all around us is Swamp Cloud!
Once the swamp has seized you, will never reach solid footing again!
The survival rate is 50%!
How careless...
Swamp?
The Ordeal of Swamp!
YOU'RE SINKING!?
Fool, I am not affected by it!
SWAMP CLOUD COUNTERMEASURE!
MILKY DIAL!
Wow, Cool!
Something's blowing out of the bottom of his feet and he's using it to fly!
Wow, he looks so awesome!
Something's blowing out of his hands too...
One tanuki is hardly worth my trouble.
Eat this!
SWAMP CLOUD BURGER!
It has the density of a cloud, and the properties of a swamp!
Once touched, nothing can escape it!
Gedatsu-sama! No! You aren't supposed to aim at me...
He can't get it off!
That's right. It's a cloud.
If you try to push against it, your hand just passes right through it!
The more you struggle, the farther you get sucked in!
I've gotta save him!
There you are, tanuki!
SWAMP CLOUD BURGER!
SCARY!
If that hits me, I'm dead!
Oi! Are you okay?
Wake up!
Oi!
You've got to breathe!
Don't die!
Phew, you're alive!
You saved my life.
Allowing yourself to be saved by the enemy...
You have no dignity.
He's here!
And you dare call yourself one of God's 50 Enforcers of Skypiea?
Call it what you want!
I've had enough! I'll no longer serve you!
You will die by my Axe Dials!
Yosh, we'll team up and fight him together!
Bring it! We're not scared of you!
Very well.
JET PUNCH!
This is the extinct Jet Dial.
Ising this, I can throw an accelerated punch before my enemy even know he's been defeated!
The only downside is that it tears holes in my clothes.
This is a Priest?
If i don't get out of here as fast as i can, I'm dead!
I can't run on the clouds!
The Swamp Cloud traps are everywhere!
I have to run on the ruins and get into the forest!
Where do you think you're going, tanuki?
JET PUNCH!
RUMBLE!
JUMPING POINT!
The effect of the Rumble Ball will last for only three minutes.
That means if i don't get out of here in three minutes, I'll be killed!
So' you've eaten a Zoan-type Devil's Fruit?
Don't bother running!
JET PUNCH!
HEAVY POINT!
SWAMP CLOUD BURGER!
That again!
GUARD POINT!
Damn! You little shit!
BRAIN POINT!
SCOPE!
Weak point! He has to have a weak point!
Anything!
I'll find a chance and get out of here!
JET PUNCH!
Even with... my Guard...
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Just where do you think you are?
Don't damage these historic structures!
Rather than worrying about this rubble, you should be worrying about yourself, miss.
PUNCH MOUNTAIN!
Oh no!
You... fool!
Does this cave ever end?
No matter how far i walk, I can't find a way out.
I'm getting hungry.
But it doesn't look like there's anything to eat around here.
I wonder what Chopper and the others are up too.
If i get the chance to get out of here...
His feet.
I see his weak point.
WALK POINT!
Can i get away?
My vision's starting to blur.
He can still move?
My legs are shaking.
And... the effects of the Rumble Ball will run out soon.
That's right.
I'm not going to run away.
I'll defeat him!
Hey, dammit!
What do you think you're doing!?
SWAMP CLOUD BURGER!
I'm always the first to run away, so everyone has to protect me!
That's why they can't depend on me!
I'll raise my pirate flag here!
You have chosen an unsightly death.
The air is my territory!
Do you still not understand?
Come!
Was that it?
He took off my boot!?
Damned tanuki!
You chekky little shit!
I'm a monster!
AND I'M STRONG!
The weakest beasts roar the loudest.
JET PUNCH!
I let myself get carried away and lost control of my Mantra!
He missed!
That was close!
ARM POINT!
I'm alive!
KOKUTEI...
CROSS!
NOW I'M A PIRATE TOO!
He fell right into a patch of swamp.
That's a relief!
Don't come up again!
HE'S MOVING!
He's still alive.
How careless! Losing to a tanuki!
When carelessly sinking into a patch swamp, I must escape.
Don't come up again!
Sink! SINK!
Escape, with a Milky Dial!
Wow, he sank fast!
HOW CARELESS!
YOSH' I BEAT HIM!
Another Priest's voice disappeared.
This is bad! I have to get to the others!
Hey, what's going on?
Engine failure at a time like this!?
Come on, move! Come on!
It's my first time using it, and now i have to repair it?
I can't do that...
HELP!
PLEASE, JUST LEAVE ME ALONE!
Father, please hurry!
I know. Please hang on tight!
Conis-san, here we go!
Okay!
Now, Conis-san!
Here! Grab my hand!
My, that was certainly dangerous.
It's alright now.
You're a Shandian child, aren't you?
You don't have to be afraid.
We won't...
I'm not afraid!
I'm a warrior of Shandra!
Her name is Suu. It looks like she likes you.
Suu?
My name is Conis.
Hello. Please call me Pagaya. I'm sorry.
And what's your name?
I'm Aisa.
Hey, I'm sorry to ask after you saved me, but...
Could you take me to Upper
Yard as fast as you can?
Even as we speak, everyone's
voices are disappearing.
I'm telling the truth!
Even from this far away, I can hear their voices.
So many voices.
Actually, we're already headed to Upper yard.
We thought that we should guide the pirates from the Blue Sea out of Skypiea.
You mean the guys who were on that ship?
Yes.
They're trying to get out of the forest right now.
Do you know where their ship is?
Yeah.
Father!
Yes. I'm sorry, but please take us there.
Sure...
I finally became a pirate!
Instead of looking for everyone, I'll search for the gold!
I'll surprise the hell out of them.
That place looks suspicious to me.
Maybe... everyone's over there.