Eneru God…
is overflowed following the last
act of provocation of Sanji.
What makes it possible Usopp to help it.
During this time, Luffy…
start to climb Giant Jack for
to regulate its accounts with Eneru God.
Robin!
Does Eneru want the bell, not true?
It is at the top
is bean, it that?
With the right in the middle
happy meeting again,
having repaired the Arch
Maxim, Eneru God…
its attack begins again.
[Note:God of the thunder of
aboriginals of central Australia]
The guy, turn over to the boat!
I will seek Luffy
and I catch up with you!
Splendid!
Do not believe…
to draw you like that, Eneru!
B-brothel!
Ca fears! One must leave from here!
All will be destroyed!
Then it is there that they were.
These Shandia warriors
tedious and their hidden village.
They are originating in the Blue Sea.
They surely will appreciate that.
Now, go down in the Blue Sea!
Our village!
Ca could have been us.
If we had awaited one
little more, we would have died.
“Lend oath to Large
Karugara warrior! “
“Let us relight the flame of Shandora”
Wiper…
Your ancestor…
the Large Karugara Warrior,
had another reason to want with
any price to recover our terre natale.
Another reason?
Yes.
For Karugara, it was
what counted more.
Now listening.
The Large Karugara Warrior had a friend.
The friend of Karugara?
Yes.
400 years ago, it met
Karugara, its name was…
Montblanc Norland!
Guides by the sound of the bell! The legend
large warrior and of the explorer
He was once, he there
has very, very a long time…
Perhaps more than four centuries…
A history ever written,
but always engraved in
heart of those which heard it.
True story of the warrior
regarded as a demon…
and of the explorer
regarded as a liar.
Return on the boat!
The Demon of Shandora
is with our cases!
Quickly! Let us weigh the anchor!
Let us weigh the anchor now!
But Captain, the crew
is not yet on board…
It is an order! Weigh the anchor!
You will be eliminated!
Leave all and leave.
Dear Sir, the daily report/ratio!
Admiral, we reached our
limits of reserves in food!
We go now…
slowly…
to die at sea.
The cook disappeared.
Shit! The remainder of our food…
The Admiral fell to the sea.
It is Grand Line!
It drowned by giving up us?!
Perhaps that he preferred
a fast death with the famine.
It is ridiculous!
This man returned two
time living of this sea!
It is a great man.
Then, why it laid out its clothing and shoes like that on the bridge?!
H-He, somebody could go to see…
It is impossible!
This water is infested monsters!
It does not go up…
Admiral!
It was a coriace that one!
Here.
Euh… a cord?
Draw it!
It is what that?
Admiral, you killed
this thing under water?!
Cook it.
To remain sitted all it
time with nothing to make…
deadened my instincts.
We are taken in
a storm, Admiral!
One would say well!
I feel the boat to pitch.
“One would say well”?!
The rudder is broken!
Where is it?
The main thing! The main thing!
This, my third voyage, has
started there is more than two years.
It is a miracle which us
survived so a long time.
Did He, you hear that?
Hein? Heard what?
You speak about the lightning?
Not, rather like…
the repercussion
of a splendid bell.
A sound like that.
Priest, are you certain?
This ground was cursed!
If nothing is done, Shandia
will fall in ruins!
What do we have to make?
Can our village be saved?
Priest!
NR let us must offer we…
a girl!
On the Sacrificial Furnace bridge!
How much victims
there did it have?
More than one hundred.
How that may it be?
We never saw anything of such!
If that can save the village,
I will give my body with pleasure.
Why do you cry, mom?
I will meet God Sun.
It is an honor to be
chosen for a sacrifice.
Thank you to have raised me
all these years, mom.
MUSE!
If it is a bad dream,
let to me awake!
Make shit!
Leave!
Leave me!
Large Karugara Warrior…
Seto.
I wanted to be like you one day…
a honest warrior, fighting
to protect our ground!
I do not want to die like that!
I could kiss you, Admiral!
We took the direction that you
wanted, and of course, here is an island!
Ouais, and good news,
the storm seems to be calmed.
But, really, none
you did not hear it?
Not, nobody heard bell.
Hein?
Ouais!
You must hear things, Admiral!
Here is a quite luxuriant jungle.
I hope that one will find
beautiful specimens studied.
Admiral!
Ca must be what you
heard, Admiral!
He, that is enough!
You really believe that I would have confused the cry of this strange bird with a bell?
Have-admiral,
you have…
It is not true…
The tonality is so beautiful…
Then this island is inhabited.
H-He, Admiral! Wait!
Somebody is lengthened, there!
Oh not! Of the intruders…
He, you…
Admiral, there is something
of strange with this child!
Remain there!
Leave me!
It is a plague known under
the name of Fever of the Trees.
It was not treated.
NR we let us must leave this island!
Doctor, do we still have of Cona?
Administrate amounts with this
child and with all the crew.
It is terrible.
Even harvests are infected.
Admiral, all the village is sick!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
Take along the girl on the Furnace bridge!
God of the Sun!
God of the Rain!
God of the Forest!
God of the Earth!
In exchange of the life of this girl,
Please save our village!
It is Kashi God!
MUSE!
You do not have!
It can save our village!
Kashi God…
Which splendid form.
Please…
Please save my son!
And my father!
What?
Something fell.
What was it?
What did it occur?
Who is this?
Kashi God!
It killed God!
This ritual is finished.
You must be terrified.
All goes well now.
You do not have to die.
Kashi God!
Please forgive us!
The whole village will be cursed!
Kill them!
Offer more lives to God!
Before we undergo his anger!
Karugara! Kill it for us!
The Admiral is there really foutu!
They have really the furious air!
The Admiral does not have all his spirits!
He killed a god?!
What occurs?
We should not be implied
in the ritual ones of tribes!
Please alleviate the anger of
God, Large Warlike Karugara-sama!
I am an explorer of North Blue!
NOR Montblanc…
I insane of whom you are!
You will be eliminated!
Did you always very eliminate like that?
Including any form of progress?
I will not have a discussion with you!
You will pay for your crime!
Who is this man?
He fights equal footing with Karugara!
Now, uses it
knife and gives up your life!
What?
How oses you to cry and request for your life whereas you have the honor to save our village…
Do not feel you shame?!
It is enough!
Stop!
Have-admiral!
Our sacred duty since centuries…
was to banish all
intruders of this island!
You have committed the crime
unforgivable to kill God!
Your life alone cannot
not to refund that!
We will take your lives with
all for expier this atrocity!
Then, it is thus that?
Life? Sacrifice?
Is this that your Gods want?
This ritual insults the principles
big bosses of the past.
I will not let it remain!
For these explorers and researchers who
traverse the seas for our good with all…
it is a dishonor!
And if your Gods evaluate
your lives rightly,
this ritual is not it
méprisable for them?!
Give me time!
I will make disappear this
so-called curse!
And if I cannot,
you will do what you will want of us!
What?!
Dog! You are caught for God?!
In exchange,
if I can save this village,
you must promise more
to never practice this ritual!
It is all that you have to say?
What a nonsense!
You will die here and now!
Let test it!
What do you say?
Fate of these men
will be decided tomorrow evening.
I accept!
Then tomorrow evening…
We all will be killed!
Made confidence with the Admiral.
He, Miss.
Ca must be hard too for you.
It is a shame to be
born in this village.
Ouais, you ace well reason!
You would be enough beautiful to marry you
with an aristocrat, there from where we come.
Ca is enough!
Don't you have any tact?
This man…
You speak about the Admiral?
Montblanc Norland.
Rather a famous explorer.
It is also a senior botanist.
He traverses the unexplored islands…
in the search of new species
vegetable that he studies then.
One could probably consider it
like a hero in our country.
But it is too nice like guy!
It feels obliged to intervene
in situations like that!
But it is known that one
can count on him!
Why you do not have
let Karugara kill it?
You will have the answer tomorrow.
He said that he would save the village.
We do not lose anything to wait.
How you can
to be also patient?
To be unaware of the words of the Priest
and to trust this man…
Karugara, say something!
If I feel the least
danger to weigh on this village,
I will not wait
tomorrow evening to kill it.
I do not have the capacity
to hear the voices of the Gods.
However…
I can hear the words…
of a wise man.
It is all.
Why are you still upright?
I am cured.
Large Karugara Warrior…
What did he hear by progress?
I found one of them!
It is Cona!
It was sure that I would find some
in a so large forest.
It is an earthquake!
Ca is there! This time that is there!
It is the anger of Kashi God!
He, make leave to us!
Which disaster.
The ground of the forest is very turned over.
This island splits itself into two.
What a spectacle!
It would be said that God chose
to punish you itself!
Then it would be said that your God…
is not as powerful as you say it.
It does not even have the capacity
to kill only one man.
You fights still.
Afflicted, but could you from go away?
I do not want to see your head.
I must…
quickly to go to the village.
Amusing.
I would like to see that!
Try to release you!