These will only get in the way.
There it is...
Cat Snatch.
I'm not too familiar with one
sword techniques, but...
Let's go, Buchi!
Gotcha, Sham!
Damn... If only I had one more katana.
If I can get these katanas to Zoro...
What do you want with these katanas?
LUFFY' REVIVAL!
KAYA-OJOUSAMA'S LIFE AND DEATH CONFRONTATION
Never would thought that you guys
would be tripped up by these brats.
The Kuroneko Pirate Gang isn't what it used to be.
Eh?
Jango?!!
But...
Didn't you say...
tha these pesky kids wouIdn't be a problem?
Yes, I did.
So what?
I knew they would come and try to stop us.
But what I did not expect was...
...that you fools would all be so damn useless!
We are... use... useless?
Who's useless?
How dare you say that, Captain Kuro!
It's true that you were strong once before...
But that's a three year oId tale.
When you were fooling around in this village, we
weren't just hanging around doing nothing!
That's right!
We've pillaged countless villages and
defeated many pirates gangs.
What are you implying?
After these three years, do you...
...have enough skills left to able to win against us?!
Stop! Buchi! Sham!
You're not our captain anymore!
Sorry, but we're gonna attack you now.
When did he get behind them?!
And that weapon...
Who...
Who did you want to kill?
Turn..
around!
He's gone!
It's appeared, Stealth foot.
Stealth foot?
You guys were right.
I'm not as fast as I once was.
Although with only one katana, Zoro was having
a tough time with them, yet he easily...
That man's Stealth foot is a...
...silent movement technique.
Even if you had 50 assassins, he can kill
'em all without anyone noticing anything.
It's impossible for us to escape from his plans.
After three years, seeing that old habit
of his, makes my hair stand on ends.
To avoid the ''Cat Claws'' from scratching his own
face, he always readjusts his glasses like so.
This proves he never forgot how to fight!
I've become more humble... after staying
on this island for three years.
I'll give you five minutes.
If you don't finish them off in five minutes...
Then all of you here...
Will be killed by me!
Five minutes...
Ahh! We'll manage somehow
with those five minutes.
Ah, it's him!
If we beat him, then we'll be
able to get past this slope!
The guy who's barely able to fend off our attacks...
We'll finish him in five seconds!
I'm counting on you! Nyaban Brothers!
Zoro!
What?!
Why you! Don't go kickin' my katanas!
Where's my ''Thank you''?
Thank you.
No useless, useless...
Even if you have three of 'em...
The result's still the same!
TIGER...
You guys don't get it.
HUNTING PREY!
Four minutes to go.
Using three swords and three
sword techniques are...
totally different things.
Incredible...
Only a single strike...
He defeated the Nyaban Brothers
with a single strike?
Don't worry!
In less than five minutes, there won't be anyone left.
I'll take care of 'em all.
Three minutes to go.
That bastard... I'll kill him!
Captain...
Please hypnotize me.
Please... Captain!
He's still alive.
Guess you're a bit soft.
He's probably saved by all that fat.
Get him, Buchi!
Hypnosis again, eh?
He's gonna be more of a pain now.
He tore the ground apart in his original state.
What is he able to do after powering up?
Chance!
I have to go and wake him up!
What are you going to do this time?
What a troublesome woman.
Everyone's been fighting injured,
while he's still...
Die!
Wake up!!
Nami!!! Watch out!!
Two minutes to go.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Wake up!!
Nami!!! Watch out!!
I'll split you in two!
Duck!!
What the...?
The ring...
Wasn't it just a tool for hypnosis?
Nami! How dare you step on my face!
Ah, he's still alive?!
Was it just bad timing or a mere coincidence?
Lu... Luffy?
Luffy!
That hurts...
THAT HURTS!!!
That guy woke up!
This is bad, with this...
There's no way we can finish 'em in five minutes!
Nami, that hurt you bastard!
That wasn't me!!
That wasn't...
Nami, your shoulder's hurt?
It's nothing. I'm fine.
Anyways, I've done all I can.
I'll leave the rest to you.
This battle... we can't lose to them!
For the sake of my treasures.
I shoulda known.
Go for it!
For the sake of my treasures.
Yosha! That is your style.
One minute to go.
This is impossible!
Capt' Jango and Buchi-san wouldn't make it in time!
There's just no way we can finish
'em off in one minute!
Buchi, no time to play around!
You take care of that guy with the waistband,
and I'll take care of this weird kid.
You with the straw hat!
It's about time to kill everyone.
What? That evil caretaker's here too?
That bastard...
Didn't he fall off the cliff and die?
That's fine...
Don't even think of...
Sneaking up on me!
Kaya!!
Usopp-san, are you alright?
Kaya, what're you doing here?
I'm sorry, Usopp-san.
I know that you might never forgive
me for what I have done.
I just cannot believe that...
Ku... Kurahadol is a pirate.
That doesn't matter now!
Why did you come here?
I told you to run away!
He wants to kill you!
But, aren't you fighting?!
I did such a horrible thing to you.
Yet, you're hurt all over and still fighting.
That's why...
Kaya-ojousama...
Why... are you here?
Please stop...
Please stop this, Kurahadol!!
Meri told me everything.
Isn't that the lady of the house?
So that's the final target of our plan?
So then, now we don't have to
go to the village anymore?
We just need to kill that girl, right?
Kurahadol, I beg of you!
If you want my fortune, I'll give it all up.
So please, leave this place!
Right now!
I thank you for the offer... however...
There's one other thing that I desire.
What I desire is...
The tranquility of my soul.
Tranquilty...
Yes, all I want is tranquility.
I've spent three years to gain
the trust of all the villagers,
which made me feel unbelievably comfortable.
Therefore, I'd like to keep this sense
of tranquility with me forever.
Therefore...
Therefore I must obtain this tranquility
and your fortunes!
That means the pirates will attack this village!
Then...
You will leave a will and die!
These two terms are absolutely necessary.
N... no... he's...
Not Kurahadol.
Run!
Run because anything you say to him is useless!
Run!!
He's not Kurahadol!
He's not Kurahadol...
Kaya...
Leave... this village!
Oh, you're actually pointing a gun at me.
Leave now!
So that's how it is...
You've grown a lot these past three years,
Kaya-ojousama.
Do you still remember?
Many things have happened
in these past three years.
Since the time when you'd always lay in bed,
crying for your parents whom passed away.
It's really been quite a while.
A long time...
I still remember... the sorrowful and
joyful days we've spent together.
K... Kurahadol...
We went shopping together.
I nursed you when you had fevers.
You were so happy listening to anything I'd say.
I gave my all for you.
I have always... yes, always...
Endured it.
Yes, everything was so that...
I can kill you one day... Today!
I, formerly known as Captain Kuro,
had to keep a smile for a little girl
whose nose always sniffled.
No matter how much I hated it,
I tried hard to make you happy.
Bastard...!
Can you imagine, my humiliation of those days?
Can you imagine me, the former Captain
Kuro, doing such things?!
KURO!!
Come to think of it, you still...
You still owe me a punch in the face.
Usopp-san.
You hit me pretty hard that time.
Since you hate it so much, I'll give
you a hundred more for free!