With the Divine Sanctuary, Luffy and Nami are finally unable to reach the Arch.
It is too distant
top of bean.
What can we make?
How could one reach it?
There must be a means!
During this time, Eneru finishes
by finding the Gold Bell.
Then here.
Splendid!
Here what made the pride
large city of Shandora…
The Large Belfry!
After having found a plan,
Nami sends a message
in Usopp and the others.
Hein?
There is something of writing above.
Cut down giant bean…
towards the West.
But the ultimate attack of Eneru
is already above them.
All my objectives were achieved!
All that it remains…
it is to use this Raigou for
to destroy this country and the impérionimbus…
then to leave for Fairy Vearth.
Reject
NOW TOMB, GIANT JACK!
It is reversed!
Assemble Luffy!
Give all that you ace!
OK!
To try like that to reach me…
is of a stupidity without equal!
You will include/understand your silly thing.
MAMARAGAN
Miracle with the country of god!
Song of love heard by the angels!
Upper yard…
disaggregates.
Luffy!!
Nami!!
One would say…
that he does not only want
you it keys again!
How if that could stop me!
The ruins are discovered!
It for destroying the ground.
But Wiper is over there.
And Zoro too!
Brothel!
Ruins…
Ca will not go, Eneru!
The city will not be inclined
never in front of you!
Wiper!
The city of Shandora…
was the fatherland of one
race of proud warriors.
And this city preserved its history of all its forces, where that it is!
This fantastic capacity…
will never bend in front of you!
It does not matter the number of
forests which you will burn…
ruins which you will destroy…
THIS GROUND SE WILL NEVER SUBJECT!!
Cours Wiper!
They is too dangerous!
Wiper will die!
Let to me go there, idiot!
I still hear them
small simpletons jacasser.
Vearth…
of course!
She did not fall!
Upper Yard is always there!
Which power…
Of course!
Vearth is powerful!
Which stupidity that of
to fight for Vearth!
We made run such an amount of blood…
and lost so many lives!
Why nobody of
is seen in 400 years?!
Wiper!
Neck… will run!
The bean falls!
He, leave from there!
Go!
GO!!
STRAW HAT!
I arrive, Eneru!
They do not include/understand anything.
Return the Gold Bell!!
It is too much, mortals!
I lost patience!
It is sufficiently large.
Now disappear
with this ashamed island!
RAIGOU
Nami, thank you.
Hein?!
I promise to you that it
will not be for nothing!
Wait, Luffy!
The arch is over there!
Luffy!
Do not go in it!
Drafts and
the lightning could kill you!
What hope you to make against
this insurmountable power?
Man rubber!
Gomu Gomu No Hanabi
[Note:Hanabi = Fireworks]
[Note:Ougon botan = gold Peony]
You and your lightning!
We made all this way
to the celestial island…
and you and you arrive yourself ruins the weather!
Dirtiness of the lightning!
Q-that are thus these
electric shocks?
It is true!
Gold on its arm
conduit electricity!
And then?
I will drop it right front
that you donot can destabilize it!
It is the end!
McKinley captain!
Stop please!
It is the country of God!
Ca does not have any direction!
It does not matter!
Us, the human ones, who were create in the abyssal zone of the life and dead…
There is not only we can make!
We gave up our
country and selected of living.
We do not have nowhere where to go.
To request…
it is all that remains us.
Song of the island.
When it resounds of
new in our ears,
the war will have ended.
Let us Somme us…
all condemned?
If I had courage
to hold head in Eneru,
all would that have been saved to them?
He, Suu.
Does God really exist?
If it is the case,
would it save us?
Please, if you exist…
protect these good people, God!
Please, made a miracle!
Protect this ground…
God!
RELEASE THE SKY!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
RELEASE THE SKY!
The mass of clouds of flashes disappeared!
But what did it occur?
OOOOH!!!
Luffy!
OOOH!
Oh! Oh! OOOHH!!!
MAKE IT SOUND, STRAW HAT!
RELIGHT THE FLAME OF SHANDORA!
Go, Luffy!
Let hear it to me…
Song of the island!
You dared to destroy my Raigou!
Monkey of the Blue Sea!
With more!
I will sound you at the same time!
Mortal insolate!
200.000.000 VOLTS
[Note:Amaru = Flash of the paradise]
It is what that?
To sound what?!
The Gold Bell?!
When it sounds again,
that will mark the end of the war!
Try you to realize
this prophecy?!
I am God!
You perhaps became extremely
thanks to the gifts of the paramecia…
but you will not exceed
never the force of my logia!
Ca does not go on me!
Stop taking to you for a god!
Which god would test of all
to destroy on its passage?!
Oh?
You skilfully managed to avoid
to be impaled by seizing my three-pronged fork.
Luffy!
What will you make, man rubber?
You cannot flee nowhere!
Your own arm you
conduit towards my three-pronged fork!
And if you try to flee,
you tombs in the vacuum!
I am impressed that
you would have arrived until there,
but you will not go further!
Neither you, nor this ground!
I will form another Raigou!
It is the duty of our people!
I am so sorry!
Luffy…
The celestial island
really will be destroyed?
Thus you chose to fall!
Luffy!
Nami, moves from there!
What?!
Do not underestimate me
not, lobes of ears!
Gomu Gomu No Rocket
Gomu Gomu No…
Still this attack?
Until the Bell sounds!
This time I will impale you!
[Note:Ougon Files = gold Rafale]
Too much fast!
When you return in Jaya…
What you will think when
you will see us parties?
Wait still a little.
I you will make it hear soon!
“We are there!”
LET US RELIGHT THE FLAME OF SHANDORA!
The War of the Sky started…
400 years ago…
to see this moment to arrive.
Yes…
Crowned Earth…
will sing again.
One day, undoubtedly.
Six years ago,
on the island of Jaya on Large
Line, I saw the Gold City!
The Gold City exists!
Never nobody succeeded in proving…
that the celestial island and
Cité d'Or did not exist.
It is that the adventure!
LET them HEAR It!
Papi?
You hear it?
The Gold City is there!
Since 400 years…
the Gold City…
WAS IN THE SKY!!