Quick! Light the fuse!
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
Zoro!
Attack behind me! You are so nasty!
Big nose!
Hey, Zoro. You are hurt.
You go inside and stay there.
I am doing it my way.
What's wrong with this man?
Luffy, who is she?
She is our navigator.
Are you kidding? Who the hell are you?
Get away.
Don't bother me.
(Episode 6) "Desperate Situation!
Beast Tamer Mohji vs. Luffy!"
(Episode 6) "Zettaizetsumei!
Moujuu-tsukai Mohji VS Luffy!"
(Based on manga ch.12: "Dog", ch.13:
"Treasure" and ch.14: "Reckless")
Why are you risking your
life? You are not a pirate yet.
Those people didn't
respect me. What a joke.
They must be here to challenge me.
Here you are, Mohji.
I want Zoro's head. I am leaving.
Well, OK.
Where did this dog come from?
Oh... the dog.
Hey, Zoro. Why isn't he moving at all?
How should I know? It's
his freedom to stay still.
Is it dead?
Stop playing around!
Damn dog.
I bled too much.
Hi, navigator.
Please take this.
Thank you for saving me.
Oh. The key!
You stole this for
me? Thank you so much!
Don't take this the wrong way.
I just don't want to owe you.
Thank god.
Cough it up!
Stupid dog! It's not
your food! Spit it out!
Stupid dog, spit it out!
Spit it out, come on!
Hey!
Kids, don't take
advantage of Chou-Chou!
Chou-Chou?
Who are you, man?
I am the mayor.
Who are you guys?
Hey, you are hurt so bad.
You must be hurt by Buggy.
You have to see the doctor right away.
Where's Zoro?
I told him to see the doctor.
He said he just needed
sleep. What is he thinking?
Is this dog called Chou-Chou?
Why is he sitting here?
He is guarding the shop.
Guarding?
Yes.
Oh, it's a pet shop.
It is.
The owner was my good friend.
I am here to feed Chou-Chou for him.
For him?
Yes, he is dead.
He died of an illness.
Your saying he has been waiting
for his master to come back?
Everyone said so.
But I don't think so.
Chou-Chou is a smart dog.
He should know his owner is dead.
Then why is he still here?
It's because the shop is the
most precious thing to him.
It's the only thing left
from his most beloved owner.
So he will stay with it forever.
I tried to take him
to avoid the disaster.
But he didn't even move one step.
What? What's that sound?
It must be him! Mohji the Lion Tamer!
What tamer?
Hey, hold on.
Oh, here comes trouble.
Give me the key, please.
Oh, your pal left you? Poor
thing. It's hard to get out.
Who are you?
I am Mohji the Lion
Tamer, Buggy's First Mate.
Why are you wearing strange fur?
That's rude! Its my hair!
Then it's even more strange.
You think you are safe in the cage?
You don't seem to fear me.
There is no animal that
I can't tame in the world.
Shake hands.
You are just a little nobody.
I am not interested in your life.
Tell me where Zoro is.
No.
Go, Richie!
Great! It's open!
He is dead.
Ok, Richie. Go look for Zoro.
Kill him and I will be famous.
What is that? It's a pet shop.
Ok, finish your food and go to work.
What? The little dog
is guarding this crummy shop?
That's incredible!
But it's good to get out of the cage.
OK! Let's kick butt!
And make Nami my navigator!
Why are you still alive?
You are still alive.
Can't I be alive?
The house has been destroyed.
And you survived? Too weird.
Really?
What are you doing in this town?
Why did you mess with the pirate?
I just figured out why I am here.
I want to find the treasure
map and the right navigator.
That weird guy wants to find
Zoro. Let me check it out!
Chou-Chou, it's
our shop, just you and me.
That bag is too big for Chou-Chou.
Chou-Chou, you can't
be hurt. Let me do it.
Chou-Chou, did I tell you not
to eat the things in the shop?
Come, eat this.
Oh, you just don't
know how to be afraid.
Chou-Chou, I am sick.
I have to stay in hospital.
Don't worry, I will get well.
Before I come back,
you stay in the shop.
It's all in your hands.
It's itchy, Chou-Chou.
It's because this shop is
Chou-Chou's most precious thing.
This is left from his beloved owner.
So he wants to stay
with the shop forever.
Damn, this dog bit me.
Aren't you dead?
I am not that easy to get killed.
Then I will eat up your brain!
This damn lion doesn't know who I am.
Gomu Gomu No...
Gavel!
Richie!
What kind of monster are you?
I ate the "Rubber Fruit."
You ate the Devil Fruit,
like Captain Buggy?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to be.
No matter what you done, it
won't bring back his owner.
So I will clobber you instead!
Damn all the pirates in the world.
They took the people's love.
Hey, this pirate is still alive.
I thought you were eaten by the lion.
Since you are a pirate, I will kill you!
Before you kill others.
I will kill you first!
Don't, girl.
You think you can beat me?
Show me what you got!
Stop that! What's
the matter with you?
I only got you this box back.
He ate the rest.
He fought the lion...
for the dog.
You are really brave.
Even I didn't see it.
But I can imagine.
You cheer up, too.
You've been beaten?
I am sorry, Captain Buggy.
Mohji, you've been beaten by Zoro.
No, not Zoro. It's the guy with hat.
What? You were beaten by that kid?
Because he is...
I am really angry!
Go set the Buggy Ball. I
will bomb this town flat!
I am sorry.
I yelled at you.
Forget about it. You have your reason.
I don't want to ask too much.
I am useless.
Even Chou-Chou fought for his family.
As mayor, how can I see this town
being destroyed without doing anything?
Mayor, please calm down.
40 years ago, It's a deserted land here.
We claimed this land.
We built the farm land and the shops.
We built this town little by little.
This town is our treasure.
I won't let the pirate ruin our land!
Fire the Buggy
Ball. Blow the whole town!
Even my home is destroyed.
Hey, Zoro is sleeping inside!
Is that man dead?
Hey, Zoro! Are you alive?
Why are you so loud?
I need to sleep more.
It's amazing you are alive.
Great, you are not dead!
I won't allow this to hapen again.
I can't stand this anymore.
Those bastards from nowhere have no
right to ruin our 40 years of effort.
I am the mayor of this town.
I am protecting this town!
Wait, mayor.
We are men. We have to face the war!
Right, kid?
Yes, sir!
Don't you make it worse!
What can you do about it?
You will only get killed!
I know I might get killed.
Let's wait
and see, Buggy clown!
Mayor cried.
He did? I didn't see it.
It's showtime now.
Yeah, right.
You are still laughing.
Don't worry, I love that man.
I will never let him die.
If you say so.
Are you going, too?
You are seriously hurt!
It's just a little wound. My
reputation is much more important.
Our goal is the Grand Line.
We are going to get the map back.
Be my partner, Nami.
I don't want to be a pirate.
But we can do it together
for our own purpose.
It's ready to fire again.
Ok, fire.
Buggy the
Clown! Get out here now!
I am the mayor, Boodle.
I am here for my home town!
Let's get it over with right now!
You idiot.
You called your town "treasure"?
What a joke. Don't be stupid.
People like you will never
understand how others feel!
I am the man who will get
the treasure and rule the ocean.
All the treasure in the world is mine.
Nobody but me can, and
dare to, own the treasure.
If you love this town so much,
then be prepared to die with it!
I will fight to the death.
You are like a mouse to me.
I will never let you ruin
the town, even if I die.
Let go of me.
It's the hat kid again.
I am here to beat you up to the sky.