The Kuroneko Pirate crew isn't what it used to be...
We are useless?
Zoro!!
Thanks!
TIGER HUNTING PREY!
Wake up!!
Nami, why you!
Kurahadol, please stop this!
Run Kaya!
I gave my all for you.
I've always...
Yes' everything was so that l can
kill you one day... namely today!
Bastard...!
Since you hate getting punched so much,
I'll give you a hundred more for free!
DEFEAT KURO!
USOPP'S TEAR-FILLED DETERMINATION!
What the hell was that?!
How did he do that?
His arms simply extended!
But how could he do that?!
He really smacked Captain Kuro!
I'll leave the rest to you.
I'm gonna retrieve my treasures!
Usopp Pirate crew... reporting!
You guys!
Stop that!
Give up!
Kill him! Kill him!
You dare break the peace of this village!
Quit it!!
What are those brats doing?!
What the hell are they thinking?
Stop this.
You guys, cut it out!!
Yosh! I think he's suffered enough.
They've totally pissed Captain Kuro off now.
Those stupid brats!
Captain!
Just as we thought, Captain's fighting them!
Why didn't you tell us the truth?
Are we insiders?
No, outsiders?!
Whatever!
Anyways, you guys gotta get out of here now!
Run!
No!
We'll fight with you!
If we ran, it'd bring dishonor
to the Usopp Pirate crew!
You morons, hurry up and get outta here!
Captain!!!
Not bad...
That was a pretty good punch
you threw at me there.
You!
You possess the power of the
Devil's Fruit, don't you?!
Yeah, the rubber fruit.
I'm a rubber man!
What?! That's bad news!
Those things do exist!
No wonder he's so weird!
So, he's a rubber man.
His arms stretching out so long wasn't
just me seeing things then.
Jango!
I will take care of this kid.
Please take care of Kaya-ojousama.
She will write the will as planned...
Then kill her!
And the three ants over there...
are an eyesore!
Understood.
Stop.
I won't let you pass me.
Buchi!!
Cat Kill, STUMP!
That again?!
His power's completely different from before.
Damn.
Kaya!!
Damn...
I have no strength left...
Damn... Damn!
Damn...
Usopp Pirate crew!!!
Aye!!!
Listen to me!
We won't run away.
He's gone too far!
We'll have our revenge!
Protect Kaya!
Listen carefully...
I will now...
Give the most important mission... to you guys.
Get Kaya away from here!
Don't say you can't!
Because... protecting what we cherish most as men
is the reason why we formed this pirate crew!
Usopp-san...
This is... Captain's order.
Aye! Captain!!!
Kaya-san, hurry!
Come, this way!
This way!
What an elegant speech...
It's the same as telling them to run away.
Going into the forest is like entering my back yard!
Jango!
Oh shit, I blanked out.
Are you stupid..?
You'll never get away from me...
How's that?
You bastard!
Hurry up and get them, you idiot!
Fine!
It's useless...
I know exactly how bad Kaya-ojousama's
condition is.
She won't be able to escape Jango.
You might want to go after them...
If you can walk past this slope that is...
Buchi!
You've already lost to me once.
Didn't I tell you not to bother me anymore?!
Outta my way!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
What... what was that?
Who knows...
Jango's got them covered, maybe you
should take a look for yourself.
However...
You may be too late already.
You bastard...
You've been living under the
same roof for three years...
Don't you have any compassion for her?
None!
Like I said, Kaya is only part of my plan.
After her death, I might then thank her.
Why you...
Hopeless bastard.
I didn't plan to save him in the first place.
Usopp!!
You go and look for 'em.
Leave everything here to us.
Leave it to us!
Oh, you can still move?
Not bad...
Shut up!
I won't... let you have your way!
You dare betray the villagers and Kaya's feelings!
Do you think you can simply do as you please?!
Usopp!
Damn...
I can't move a limb.
You really amuse me.
I, betrayed them?
Are you kidding me?
Everything was planned.
This isn't like playing some pirate game, where
you'd go around pretending to be the captain!
So just stay put and don't move.
Well, even if you do manage to catch up
with Jango, you're no match for him.
You'd be much safer here.
Even if I can't...
Even if I can't, I want to protect...
I still want to protect them.
For I am the Captain of the Usopp Pirate crew.
I am a brave warrior of the sea!
I won't allow you to lay a single
finger on any of the villagers!!!
What's he up to?
What's he yelling for?
Yeah look, he's cryin'!
What's so funny?!
Luffy!
I'll take Usopp and go after the hypnotist.
Any problems?
Nope! Get goin'!
Sorry...
It would've been faster if I'd gone alone,
but without your help through the forest,
I won't be able to find them.
Hey you fools, who gave permission
to get past this slope?
That would be me!
Go! Zoro, Usopp!
One more punch!
GOMU GOMU NO...
POWER KICK!
Damn, he vanished again.
Ah well, they did get past.
Before we fight, I'd like to ask one thing.
As an outsider, why are you
getting yourself involved?
Because there's a man here whom
I don't want to see dead.
That's simple. But, is it okay?
For this will be the reason for your death!
It's fine, but I'm not gonna die!
Let me show you death!
GOMU GOMU NO...
WHIP!
PISTOL!
I'm getting bored.
You bastard!
Damn, my mouth got cut.
That straw hat guy is definitely strong but...
Th... that's Captain Kuro!
Kill him!
Captain! Banzai!
Captain Kuro!
Great, Captain Kuro!
Don't call me by that name!
You still don't get it, do you?
For this is... my plan to completely
be rid of the name, ''Captain Kuro''!
I've had enough...
The days when I had to plan everything for you
guys, whom only knew how to make a ruckus!
Enough of those government dogs who
kept chasing me for the reward!
I can't take it anymore!
Marines...
This is the third time this week.
There's nothing we can do.
We keep doing stuff that make us wanted criminals.
And we are somewhat infamous!
That's right... it's my name that attracts them to us.
That's why, I'm gonna quit being ''Captain Kuro''!
That's a weird thing to say.
It's no use.
The Marines will chase you 'til you die.
Then I will die!
It seems like I'm not cut out to be a pirate.
But you are the Captain of this ship.
Then, you be the Captain!
I've had enough of this noisy lifestyle.
I'll...
I'll kill the me in this world!
Captain Kuro!
Captain!
Capt'!
How many ships do they have?
Just one.
What should we do, Capt'?
Should we use our cannons to attack them?
Lower me a small boat.
Huh?
A small boat!
First Mate Jango, Captain Kuro is...
Yeah, I know.
But, how can he just go there all alone?
He's not turning himself in, is he?
What?
They stopped attacking.
What happened?
This is strange.
Close in.
But...
Just do what I told you!
Aye!
Hey, prepare the cannons!
I see so thats how its gonnna be...
Be ready to do battle!
Hey you!
Ye... yeah, what is it?
I'm sorry to bid you farewell so soon.
The Marines are...
All dead!
Now...
The plan shall begin.
Hey now, get a grip.
I particularly spared your life.
Shu... shut the hell up...
I will never beg!
Just kill me!
You've got guts.
Being able to spew out as much with
a crushed jaw isn't bad at all.
I'll now present to you, a nobody, a little parting gift.
You should be honored.
To get the head of the devious Kuro.
You are Captain Kuro.
You're the one who did this.
One... Two... Jango!
My name is Captain Kuro.
I killed all these people.
And you're the man who caught Captain Kuro.
Return to your base and execute this man.
One... Two... Jango!
I'm the man who caught Captain Kuro!!
There he goes again.
This is good.
As long as my imposter dies, Captain Kuro will no longer exist in this world.
And so, once today's plan succeeds,
I will have achieved my goal.
I will have money and a tranquil life.
You get it now, kid?
This plan which has taken three years will not fail!
My plan never fails!
It seems that you can do more
than just stretch yourself.
Of course, I'm well trained...
To be a pirate!
You can't take it anymore, you say?!
If you're so afraid of the fame on the sea,
then you're not qualified to be a pirate!
If you wanna compare ambitions...
Mine is much greater!!!