and of the recovery of Waver!
Plans of the resumption of gold
Good…
Go everyone, on the way!
Wait, He wait, oh!
What is there, Usopp?
Frankly, you then…
you intend to leave
like that, without reflecting?
Hein?
Like that, one will be done
to undoubtedly locate…
Seven people who
move in group,
it is not a little obvious?!
Oh now that you
say, they are not false.
Then also…
in spite of this camouflage…
Merry worries me!
It is true that there…
However it seems to me well hidden, you
believe what it will be nevertheless discovered?
Not what to worry!
This old wreck,
nobody would like the emp…
Do not speak about wreck, does not speak about wreck
!! And then the problem is not there!
Good blood…
Me I always think of
what it could arrive to us,
when comes the moment when one will be
discovered, one will run, without no doubt!
Moreover, Naaaami!
Hein? Me?
By the way, that did you make of Waver?
Ah, zut!
I hid it in
undergrowth and I forgot it.
Bin here….
Ah forgiveness, forgiveness!
Nami-san is delightful
when she forgets!
Hum… Let us leave the imbecile on side.
Listen, band of idiots…
I go now you
to entrust my strategy.
Open large your ears!
Tadam!
Ok.
Your attention, Mesdames and Sirs!
Therefore, here them
explanations of my plan.
Initially the team which undertakes gold:
There will be Luffy, Zoro, Robin and
then the Usopp-san captain.
After that, the team which recovers Waver:
There will be Nami.
But also another…
Sanji!
Ouooooooh!!
Your plan is super, Usopp!
Let us make our possible unit, hein!?
Ouais, ouais.
Which ball.
What, dumb?
Say, Usopp…
I must still keep
the all alone ship?
Do not make any you!
The camouflage of Merry is perfect,
that does not fear almost anything…
Almost?
And besides, which us
will look after the every day?
Héhé, the Super Doctor!
Argh!
Species of idiot!
I am not content
because you flatter me!
Small rascal.
Ok?
One is currently here.
The team of the Treasury will avoid the ordinary way
and to pass by shortest in direction of the treasure.
Nami, you remember
did the place where you hide Waver?
Ouais…
in a split in the east of the island.
It is necessary to cross a chain of
mountains which borders the crater.
It seems to me that it is on this side.
Hum, it is practically on the other hand.
By terrestrial way, that us
would take too much time.
He? Oh! I found!
Hein?
You have only with you to return there
of a draft with this boat.
What?
The place of return
will be here… in Going Merry!
Ouais!
Yes, what?
You are still there?
You can lay out.
“You must make sure that it will carry food
to its mouth to swallow it! “
It is what my Chief-Cock ordered to me.
Even if I were to leave this part…
a rule remains a rule!
You must eat without anything to leave.
This Jessica…!
You also, Sergeant!
Heiiiin?!
We prepared some in excess.
Hold, good appetite!
Sergeant, you hate
also broccolis?
Not, rather tomatos
and carrots…
Oh, Major!
Forgiveness, you were dining…
In this case, I
will not disturb you.
Not, not, it is exceptional.
You fall to peak!
I precisely hoped to call you.
Commander, I let escape three
time the crew of Straw hat.
I present to you my excuse!
It is not the important one, that.
Say to me rather,
did you already dine?
Euh, not.
Not well, not well! It
is not well whole!
One cannot make
war the empty belly!
And then, as a superior…
you must show
the example with your subordinates!
O-Oui.
Useless to retain you…
Eat as far as you will want!
Can you transmit to him
what they was delicious?
Included/understood well!
Species of dirty hedgehog.
I will crush you!
You still, Commander delight.
The hour came.
We need
to reorganize the troops.
This plan consists in taking the initiative
in order to bar the road to them, it is that?
Exact.
Sergeant, prevent
immediately troops.
With your orders!
This is an emergency communication
for submission to each squadron!
Supervise the neighborhoods of
the door as well as bay.
What do I have to make my regiment?
When you train the crew…
Make patrol them
around the door.
Included/understood.
You!
What a surprised!
Enchanted you
to know, Konteriano…
Finally…
the special Inspector…
the lieutenant of frigate, Sheppard.
Commander Jonathon,
it appears that the pirates of
Straw hat have escaped you.
Not, not… undoubtedly they hide
still some share in this Fortress.
Oh I see, this is why you were in the train
of dining with unconcern, what a world of peace!
Not astonishing that this imbecile
peaceful of Hariguchi beat you.
Hum, excuse me!
No the concern!
Then? You have finally
located their hiding-place?
Yes, about, I suppose
that they will return to recover gold.
Gold, do you say?
Nevertheless they became weak,
valiancy and bravery is not enough.
Lieutenant, you have
wisdom to direct them.
I could grant to you
best troops…
What a joke!
You are ready to order
best troops, isn't this?
By the way, where the soldiers are who have me
confused with the pirates of Straw hat?
With what that would be useful to you it
to be informed about it?
It is for my report/ratio, naturally.
I had given the order to apprehend
at once all doubtful people.
They did nothing but carry out it.
I am somebody of
suspect, it is that?!
Being given the circumstances….
Our opinions are divergent.
I have just recalled me of a thing
to make, I will return to see you.
Are commander, you sure?
It is a Lieutenant of the District
General, it is well too proud!
He will not take it
command of our section.
Not, it is not a question of that!
Go, it is the hour of glory for
the strongest unit of G8. (???)
????
Still idle talk….
I am serious.
Bandage the stupid ones!
He, you!
Where the Commander of the ship is
Stanberry which arrived this morning?
Yes!
In this moment it is
occupied with the infirmary.
What, with the infirmary?
What it
card-indexes over there?
The majority of its crew is wounded,
he must be with the bedside of his men.
Make come it! Immediately!
Yes!
They aim at gold and I see one place where it could keep it in this Fortress…
You will see, dirtiness of Commander!
I will undertake the pirates of Hat
Straw personally and to destroy the fortress.
I wonder whether everyone is well.
Me I… S so sad!
The moon, stars…
then only with Nami-san
ballotante on this boat!
What a formidable situation!!
It is as in a dream!
What does it occur?
I have a bad presentiment.
Sanji-kun,
could you accelerate?
Ouuuiii!
Does Pas la pain to shout, of agreement?
And rows in silence.
Ouuuiii!
R.A.S on the right, R.A.S on the left.
I am unaware of where the Navy is posted.
One should not be pointed out!
If one passed unperceived with
that, it would be a miracle…
Mr. Length-conk, one has anything
to fear for the moment.
You could not say it earlier!!
It is in the train of ronquer….
Would be a little more serious!!
It is really relaxed!
Commander!
If our troops leave the split,
the guard of the base will be weakened.
We do not have the choice,
it is very right if we can
to overcome the enemy with the sentinel.
However, we cannot leave
these young people pavaner in the fortress.
What think you of forming
new recruits?
It is not possible, that
would be too risky for them.
I knew that you would say that…
this is why I kept
the secrecy until now.
In fact, we receive
many candidatures…
who come from
members of my section.
And just like us, they
like this Fortress.
Really?
In this case, let us let express them
their patriotic passion…
and let us make pass the order
that they lend strong hand to us.
Yes! They will be charmed, undoubtedly!
Here are which is made,
but I still have another thing
to ask you, Sergeant.
Yes…
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
GOMU-GOMU-NO-FANSUB
How? It is madness!
Stanberry cannot take the sea,
it is currently in repair!
What does not want to only say
the whole of the ship is defective…
It is true…
But…
we were taken in
a storm while coming here!
Several sailors
are hardly able to move!
Captain, would be you in the train
to insinuate something…
towards me, the special inspector
envoy by the General headquarter?
Not… I do not have anything
known as of such… But…
If you included/understood,
gather all the crew!
Half will accompany me, the remainder
will await my instructions with Painpiku.
I will show with these soldiers
fortress, power of the General headquarter!
He, Zoro!
You are to us, there?
Dumb! You me drunk!
Is Robin, it still far?
One is there almost.
Ouh there!
It is really over there?
One does not have any more but to jump.
Yes, according to the route of the chart…
Then the trunk
find inside…
Exact! It is necessary for us to infiltrate
this place, it is our short cut.
It is decided! One goes there!
Ok! One sinks in a draft!
Well!
One goes there, Usopp!
Hein?
Dispatch, Usopp, magne you!
Say, one remakes it?
Do not talk cock! There will not be
not second once!
Well!
Pas de Marines in sight.
Shit!
Afflicted disturbance!
Nami-san, made attention!
Thank you.
They would be tedious if
the disorder was sown.
It is to better skirt
the coast from here,
because we do not have time
to lose unnecessarily with them.
Sanji-kun,
we dispatch!
Yes!
One is there almost!
Still an effort!
One grouille!
I found it,
it is enough to go down, it is near.
The trunk is at the end of the corridor!
Well!
Await us, treasure!
One arrived
up to now too easily,
It is equivocal.
Well!
D-of the pirates!
I you lay-aisserai step to pass!
Stop!
We do not have the intention
to destroy the fortress,
nor to try anything
the dangerous one towards you.
The farm!
I do not admit only whoever
comes to disturb peace!
Since I say to you that
we will do anything to you!
I do not believe in
words of the pirates!
To protect this fortress at the sides from
Commander is an honor for us!
In short, you would be ready to risk your life?
Obviously!!
Then, you should puff out and you
to smash even more with the drives!
It is what that?!
Impressing!
It is rather well reinforced!
It should be recognized that this place
appears ideal to contain gold!
I feel that there are other tricks
brilliant in addition to our gold!
And? What does one make?
Oh 'scuse, Zoro!
You…
I excuse myself…
It will not open by the force!
For this trunk,
one must turn these buttons…
So that the figures correspond, it is
there that the wheels in top will swivel
and the leaf will open small with
small towards the object of desire!
You seized well?
You will not go further!
They finally showed
their end of their nose.
Yes, one would say well…
I am Kurono Nezumi!
Appointment wisely, it
is not yet too late…
It is an attack with the dignity of one
pirate to withdraw itself in front of a treasure!
Good, after I count on vouuus.
He!
Cursed pirate!
They dared!
Fire!
Usopp, one entrusts the trunk to you!
Count on me!
Then Mr. Length-conk? Will that go?
It is perhaps the speciality
of Nami this kind of thing!
But with such a lock,
it is an easy work even for me!
Well!
First is engaged!
If that falls us above,
it is instantaneous death.
What! They are detached?!
It is enough that I gourre once
and it is a direct blow on cranium!
Now!
Luffy! Does not lengthen your
arm wrongly and through!
If not they you will slice them!
Ok!
And the second in fact!
Major, all supervisors
arrived on the ground…
The guard is finished.
Well!
Say to them to maintain it
statute-quo until new order.
With your orders!
More than 50 minutes…
Papaa!
Nice, Robin!
I was done encircled.
That will not finish any or
what!? They are heavy!
Usopp! It is not yet open?
It is open!!
Biiien!
All with the shelters!
Hein?
It is too funny this trunk!
What?
There is not… of gold!
You will not leave if
easily… Navarone.
All these many humiliations
sudden will be avenged.
Ouais!
All the Pirates of Straw hat will be exterminated by us, special gendarmerie of the general headquarter.
This is the last model of
portable bazooka nidel peg ladder!
Waah its tears!
Burst, Feu!
Go ahead!
He
Soon in One Part:
Catch all in only one net!
The secret plan of Jonathon.
I will become the lord of the pirates.
Catch all in only one net!