We're doomed! The pirates are coming!
Pirates are attacking the village!
Pirates! Pirates!
They are coming now!
Run for your lives!
Pirates!
(Episode 9) "Honorable
Liar? Captain Usopp"
(Episode 9) "Seigi no
Usotsuki? Captain Usopp"
(Based on manga ch.23: "The Dread Captain Usopp"
ch.24: "The Lie Rejector" and ch.25: "Lies")
We can't sail the Grand Line like this!
You are right.
I need some meat.
The only food supply is fruit.
We need some wine.
What are you talking about?
I am not talking about that.
I wanna find the Grand Line! But
it's the most dangerous place.
The most-successful pirates are
searching for the One Piece too.
Of course, they will sail the
most sturdiest ships there.
And also with a crew.
We have no crew, and
the boats' equipment...
...isn't completely safe.
We will have chefs
and musicians for sure.
Musician?
What an idiot.
There is a village a
little south of here.
If we can find a better
boat, it will be great.
And eat some meat.
They got fine wines there.
That's enough! Both of you!
The pirates are coming!
Pirates!
Everyone run!
Pirates are coming!
Pirates!
Damn them!
Pirates...
What pirates?
Just kidding!
You lying brat!
I'll teach you a lesson!
Stop right there!
Come here, you!
Here they come!
Stop, you jerk!
Come and get me!
Come on and catch me!
Damn, we lost him again!
I hate that kid!
I will never forgive him.
Where the hell is he?
I have done a good thing today.
Just a little excitement for
this boring little village.
Found you!
Oh, it's you!
(Usopp's name based on "Uso", Japanese for "liar",
and "Aesop", author of "The Boy Who Cried Wolf".)
Captain Usopp's pirate
crew reporting for duty!
(In Japanese, pepper is "piiman" and carrot is "ninjin".
The Viz manga names will be used here wherever possible.)
Where is Onion?
We're doomed! We're doomed!
We're doomed!
(Onion is "tamanegi" in Japanese.)
We're doomed! We're
doomed! We're doomed!
Pirates are coming!
It's from the north! It has
the Skull and Crossbones!
Liar!
It's true!
It is?
I saw it with my own eyes!
Gotta go!
- It's snack time!
- Dont run away!
I have a disease. If I don't
eat my snack on time, I will die.
Liar!
Captain, don't you
wanna be a real pirate?
Real pirates aren't
scared of other pirates!
It has the sign of Buggy the Clown!
Buggy's pirate crew!
I think I'll just...
It's only just two small boats!
And there's only about three people.
Prepare for action!
Let's defend our village!
Let's go! Follow me!
Okay!
It's been a long time
since we touched land!
Yay!
There is a village ahead, right?
It looks like a small village.
Meat, meat, meat, meat, meat!
There must be some
restaurants in the village!
Can you stop with the meat?
Watch out.
Someone's there.
Where is he? Where? Where?
Watch out!
Wow! Cool!
There is no time for that!
I am the king of the
villlage, Captain Usopp!
People also call me "Our captain."
Captain Usopp!
If you are trying to attack this
village, you better give up now!
My 80 million crew
won't let you do that!
I'm scared!
Oh brother.
Liar!
She saw right through me!
See, I knew it!
I didn't say anything!
What? Liar!
Nuts!
80 million is an exggeration.
But I have real loyal followers!
All three of them?
They are so hard to lie to!
Let's get out of here!
Hey, you three! Stop!
I have never seen a
pirate using a slingshot.
You are so funny!
Hey, don't tease me!
I am a very self-respecting person.
Because my self-respect is strong!
That's why they call
me "Honorable Usopp".
You saw that, right?
My sling shot skill is better
than your gun shot skill!
Since you have drawn your weapon...
...let's fight until one of us dies.
I am not joking.
Who you are dealing
with is a true pirate.
Since you have drawn your weapon...
...let's fight until one of us dies.
Who you are dealing
with is a true pirate.
Wow, I am so scared. He's a real pirate.
I didn't say it.
It was Shanks, who I
most respect, who said it.
You said Shanks?
You know Red-Haired
Shanks? That big pirate?
Yes. Your father is Yasopp, right?
Yasopp is my father.
But how did you know?
("Meshi": Japanese
for "meals" or "food".)
Delicious.
I once saw him when I was young.
My father was on Shanks' ship!
You look so like him, I was
thinking when I first saw you.
Really?
My father was on the famous ship?
I don't know if he is still there.
I think he is still on the ship.
But your father was a sureshot.
Cool!
That's nothing. I can shoot
an ant's whiskers at 50 paces.
Let me tell you, Luffy.
I have a son at your age called Usopp.
I have heared that so many times!
I don't wanna hear it again!
What did you say?
I haven't said it enough!
You'll listen, no matter
how many times I say it.
What a sad story. But I had no choice!
There is only one reason...
...which is that pirate
flag kept calling me!
Usopp.
You story is always the same and my ears
became allergic to the same old story.
Yasopp is a great pirate.
That's right.
My father fought for his dream
without thinking about the future.
I am so proud of him.
Then it's easy to say...
Do you know anyone here with
a ship that I can borrow from?
You see, it's a small village.
Sorry I can't help you.
On the hill...
...there is a big mansion.
Is he your friend?
Can you ask him to offer the money?
No way!
I forgot -- I have
to do something.
I am the boss's good friend.
You just eat as much as you want.
Gotta go! Bye bye!
What's with him? He looked nervous.
You said you want to meet Usopp?
What is this all about?
Come on, it's no big deal.
I just want to talk with him.
Impossible.
That man is a big liar.
For a weak, unhealthy lady...
Usopp's story is too much. [Kaya] But...
Your deceased parents entrusted me...
...to protect Miss Kaya.
I put the medicine on the table.
Make sure you take it.
Stingy.
So stingy.
Absolutely not.
Sorry for disturbing you.
Usopp!
Hi. How come you are still sick?
Sorry.
I wanted to be hospitable to you,
but Klahadore wouldn't let
me, no matter what I said.
He isn't a bad guy.
Don't worry. I am a brave pirate.
Staying in a small
room makes me suffocate.
What's your adventure story today?
Well...
I'll tell you what happened
when I was 5 years old.
I fought with a goldfish
that lived in south seas.
Goldfish?
First of all, its poop was really huge.
I thought it was land and
I even moored my ship to it!
Is this the restaurant?
Yes, the pirates are inside.
We have to save him.
They're real savages.
He could have been
barbecued by the pirates.
Stupid, pirates don't eat human meat.
Listen to this.
This is gonna be the greatest battle
that Usopp's pirates have ever fought!
Usopp's pirates are here!
Who are they?
The captain isn't here!
- Is he...
Hey pirates!
What'd you do with our captain?
Where is he?
The meat is so good.
Meat?
- Did you guys...
What have you done to him?
Your captain...
We have eaten him up.
("Onibara": Japanese for
a demon hag or witch.)
Why are you looking at me?
Who told you to say that?
I am only kidding.
Wow! It's so big!
The captain has been gone
and I think he came here.
What is he doing in there?
To tell lies.
That's not very nice!
No, I think it's really nice!
Right?
- Really nice.
What do you mean?
Kaya, who lives in this
mansion, is very weak.
And after her parents died,
she has been staying here.
No matter how rich she
is, she's always unhappy.
And Captain Usopp uses his
best jokes to make her laugh.
The captain likes his work.
You have never seen a
freak like this, have you?
What? I think he is great.
I like how the captain's always nosy!
I like his cowardice!
I like his lies!
Is she better now?
A lot better.
OK!
Let's go ask her to give us a ship!
It's Usopp's way of making her better.
It's hard to get in there.
The guards are very tough.
What about Luffy?
- I'll go ask her!
What are you doing?
Gum
Gum --
Your arms are stretching!
- You monster!
Catapult!
Then we use the catapult to
bounce us into the air and escape.
What's that?
Yahoo!
That's a great way in!
- You're nuts!
Are you ok?
I am fine!
They all come here to
see what I have achieved.
The new members of Usopp's pirate crew.
We are not.
I need you to do me a favor.
A favor? Me?
Yes! We need a big ship...
- Hey you!
What are you doing here?
Klahadore.
What is the meaning of this?
How can you break in like this?
Who's he?
right now,
everyone is still unable
to grab the true dream
if the world ever changes
take me to myself
that never knew a thing
making sure that memories
won't fade away
What's wrong with that man?
He took me for a thief. I know!
We are only here for the ship.
Sounds like a thief, though.
That wierdo looks like another one.
Who's he?
Isn't that guy the
butler? What's going on?
Next "One Piece":
"The World's Strongest
Weirdo! Django the Hypnotist"
I want to be king of the pirates!