Finally I found them
those which have of so beautiful memories.
Oh, hello.
What is what there is?
Qu… which are you?
Hein?
I lost it? It was concealed to me?
Be to you which you?
Uhmm… I can more nothing swallow…
Still!
Ahaa… ah… ah… aaah!!
Where am I…? And then… which is these guy…?
Eh you!!
Or… yes…
You include/understand something you?
Hein?
Me, I am called Sanji and I am the second Master cock of ship-restaurant BARATIE.
It however seems to me that yesterday, I went to lay down me in my room…
And when I awoke this morning, I found myself with you,
in a place which I do not even know….
You know why, you??
Ah… euh… euuuhhh…
Ah? It is you who saved me?
Saved??
Me I am Luffy, I left my Fushia village to take the sea.
But I found myself in a swirl
I hid in barrels but by turn I disappeared
and… when I realized some, I was here.
I thought just that it was you who had saved me.
Qu… that is what that want to say?
Me also, after having discussed with Kaya.
I played with the children and I returned to lie down.
But I do not remember absolutely more continuation…
Is this similar for them too?
And… you you know something?
Hein?
Do you know why we are in such a place?
I include/understand anything but they have me the odd air,
I will try to deceive them…
OK… I will say it to you…
after all it is normal that you did not remember any more what occurred yesterday.
Since you were made attack by the Large Legendary Whale.
A large legendary whale??
Eh yes, this whale had swallowed you.
But I fought it to save you.
Good Ah… I did not know
Thank you.
Who are you?
Good question!
I am the chief of the troops of pirates who reign as a Master on any Eastblue.
Everyone respects me and calls me Capitaine Usopp!
Wooow! Usopp captain!
You know?
Not! At all!
He He… pay attention so that you say.
There is more than 8000 men in my crew…
QUOIIIIII?!!
More than 8000??!!
Ah… euh… yes… and in more you also you belong to my crew since yesterday.
It is true?
They is false…
Oups… It included/understood.
You see… You ace known as “it included/understood”.
Aarghh, zut… I said “it included/understood”!
You are somebody of intelligent.
Hahahahah… Be to you funny you…
Eh you! Do not make fun of me!
I am a proud man! Me!
This is why everyone calls me Usopp To trust….
What? What is what take to you?
R… nothing… I have the impression to have already lived that…
Me also….
I have enough of it!
Hiiii!
For the moment let us make like that…
Initially it is necessary that one eats
One cannot reflect the empty belly well.
Puffs out it!?
Ah yes… you said that you were a Master cock…
and of first class.
If we are on a boat, there must be provisions.
A boat?
Eh… wait a little! And you, be to you who finally?
Me? I am the future Lord of the Pirates!
Hein?
Eh Ben… it is old this ship…
Eh look at! an island!
Where is what one can be well?
There is a serious problem!
The navigatrice has…
Uhm? It is which they?
They form also part of your crew?
Euh… of course!
You also, you lost the memory?
Ah I include/understand now why the papillons de nuit seek the light…
The human ones also cannot resist what shines.
Are beautiful young people young ladies which your names?
If you are free this evening we let us can dine together?
Ahahaha! It is funny this type.
It completely changed attitude…
Eh! It is which them?
Where am I?
And…
You were mistaken in direction… not?
It is what that?
It is a stag…
Your dirty mouth human!
I am a reindeer!!
He spoke!
Eh let us catch it!
Eh… stops it is odd this trick!!
Hey you! Helps us too!
I do not want! Eh! Do not come here!
Euh… by or will I begin the explanation…?
www.rival-spirits.com
http://kinh.no-ip.org/
http://perso.wanadoo.fr/audiz/
IRC:/irc.kumo.fr/rival-spirits
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/kinh
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/saiyajin
Good… Everyone listen to me….
We are with…
What is what you ace known as?
I said that we were currently on GrandLine.
You forgot that too??
It is true?
Eh! Why are content for you?!
It is said that GrandLine is a sea or there is full with monsters!
If it is said to you that you are in a similar place, normally you should be afraid!
But Ca does not change anything a normal sea…
Be sour for you that one is on GrandLine??
Navigatrice…
Hein? It is of me that it acts?
Is what you recognize this bracelet with your wrist?
Hein?
What is what it is??
Ca is called Logpose.
In this sea one cannot thus use compass it is necessary to use attraction magnetic close islands to advance.
And this tool makes it possible to measure the intensity of this attraction.
To cross GrandLine, it is essential.
To the fact Miss, me I must turn over in my restaurant in Eastblue.
But would have an good idea for that?
I advise you to drop.
That already made a good end of time that one is in this sea, and if you try to only set out again it is suicidal.
We were spirit to advance as Logpose indicated it.
And we arrived on this island surrounded by coral reef.
I cannot believe you!
Moreover why do I travel with people like Ca?
Look at…
Eh it is a flag of pirate.
What?? It is a ship of pirate??
Hein? Ah yes… it is the ship of large Usopp.
Good Ah!
But… Usopp captain.
This tête de mort does a straw hat not wear?
Ahh? Ah yes… thus Ca wants to say that this hat has me.
Eh! How is what you do! Return it to me!!
Ouwatatata!!
Do not touch has my straw hat!!
If you start again I you boot the bottom!!
But… you do not have say that you did not remember any more anything?
I will always remember that! It is my treasure!
Treasury?
When I was kid I received this invaluable treasure of a friend.
I swore on this hat that I will seek companions to become a pirate.
Hum!
Pfff! Pirate per Ci, pirates by there! What a time idiot!!!
But… now I am sour that you said anything to me.
Me I hate the pirates! What I like it is the money and the oranges
it is thus not possible that I travel with such pirates!
Hey hey! SUCH PIRATES? Do not be to you foutu to say that my pretty…
You want to speak about these oranges?
Hein?!
This orange tree…
Huuh!
Whaaahhaaaa…!!
It was what there immediately?
Hey! There are hands which have just pushed!!!
Magic oranges??
Who are you with the Juste?
Drop. These oranges…
They are the oranges of Belmer.
Why the orange trees of Belmer are on a similar ship?
It is damage but I am not with the current of these details.
Can be that you should read your log book?
Hein?
It seems me too to have seen the photograph of Belmer.
It is well my writing.
Belmer…
Belmer!!!
Belmer saaan look at I could harvest all that!
There are still green oranges. Nami!! Look at well before collecting them!!
But they were sweetened.
You ate some?! One must sell these oranges!!
It is not serious! It is we who will eat these green oranges.
Yes! Malicious Nojikooooo!
Quoiiiiii??!!
Huhuhu… Go two, with work!
I must return… can be that it occurred something to Kokoyashi.
In the final analysis… What is what it is that?
Yaah…!
A reindeer bizzaaare.
Hyahaaaaaa!!
A reeeenneeeee!!
Ouwa! Imbecil! Do not come here!
Meat of reindeer…
Is better out of discs, pulp with soft fire to make a râgout.
What? One can puff out this trick?
They is also very good out of steak with the sauce berry.
Out of steak…
Species of…
I AM NOT EDIBLE ME!!
It should not be eaten. He is our ship's doctor.
Ship's doctor?
Huh!
Exact! Even the men do not arrive to him at ankle.
Is not this step?
Heu… Huh… Hu…
Conceal toiii!! I am not at all glad to be flattered by human.
Ohh it with the very content air…
It is a reindeer which has receipt the intelligence of human by eating the fruit of the demon Hito Hito.
And on this subject me also I have to eat the fruit of Hana Hana.
And did Luffy, you also you eat a fruit of the demon is not this step?
Ouais! I puffed out the fruit Gomu Gomu and I became an elastic man.
Aharg!
It… there are three people who puffed out the fruits of the demon… Here is something of low register…
You are pirates… truths?
Yes, but you also you are one.
Of agreement! You also henceforth you make started from my crew!
Hein! Pourquoiiii??!!!!
You really take it with the serious one?
It does not matter. we were crossing this sea with another member of the crew.
Another???
You soon will go down not? Kenshi-san.
[Kenshi-san:Mister the swashbuckler]
Hein?
' Made too much noise as of the morning!
You prevent me from sleeping!
Qu… which… which… which are you? Present!
One must give his name before asking that of others.
Me it is magic Luffy!
Me it is Roronoa Zoro.
Hum? Be to you a hunter of pirate?
Huh…
I never said that I was a hunter of pirate.
They is the different ones which deduced that.
But that does not change anything has what you are, a hunter of premium!
When I do not have any more what to eat I am made pass for a hunter of premium.
It is not my true goal.
But the fact that you would be on this ship shows that you came for the premium from pirates not?
I do not know anything of it.
I do not know same step why I am here.
Are Z' famous pirates??
Eh you ace is envied to face me?! Come if you want it! Y has more than 8000 men under my orders!
Ooho!
Thus you must have a large premium,
that falls well I were precisely dry.
If you insist so much I will make of you my prey.
Eeuhhh noo not N… It is not what I wanted to say… hey! Calm you!
And say something to you!
But there is no premium on its head.
How çaaaa??!!
I must leave at all costs from here…
Hein?
huuuh!!
Gold!!
There is to repurchase the Kokoyashi village enough… and it will remain me even of the currency.
How I will make to carry it with me…
What is what Ca can be well?
Ehh!! It is what this trick?
Aaahaaarg….
Extra! I said myself well that also floated on the sea.
Ah? … It east left…
They is cool its trick.
Miss…
Pff! I include/understand nothing there but I do not have anything has to make here.
Hein!?
Ah… hein? He also it left… What is what they all have…?
What is what it occurs??
Me either I do not include/understand anything any more.
It is embarrassing…