How do you hope to pay?
Ambition of Zenny, prêteur sur gages.
Go, go, you cannot work more quickly than that?
I card-index myself that it is difficult!
Put more heart at the work!
Jii-san, remain calm!
We do our better for you.
All occurs well, Ojii-chan. You calm.
Do you want that I mass you the shoulders?
Is C-C' what this trick?
With the Jii-san fact, why do you build this boat at the top of the mountain?
Ah, it is not a boat.
It is not a boat?
Wait one moment!
If it is not a boat, it is what then?!
It is my…
… coffin.
Coffin?!
Ouais, it is my tomb.
I see, then it is fall it from Ossan.
Do not request now! It is not the moment!
It is still too early!
It is too early for this kind of thing!
Could it be that it already carried out that there remain to him nothing any more but a few days to be lived?
What is there? You seem to me quite nervous…
… living alone on an island, there is nothing evil to build its own tomb!
Since I realized that I could possibly die…
It is not possibly…
… it is very close.
I suppose that a tomb at the top of a mountain it is not so strange only that.
But why a boat pirates like coffin?
Ji-Jii-san?
Await Jii-san!
Coffin, falls or anything…
… it is almost finished! Will not die!
Not now!
Chuuut, it just fell asleep.
I see, then you located the crew of the Straw hat.
Mister! It seems that they accosted on the uninhabited island about which I spoke to you yesterday.
Well, prepare the fleet.
We will encircle the island with our complete fleet.
We will capture the crew of the Straw hat! Until the last!
Commander, wait please!
Some of the members of their crew ate a fruit of the demon.
And an invincible swashbuckler, Roronoa Zoro.
And then? You are afraid, Sergent Minchi?
Surely not. I want just to avoid useless sacrifices.
Whereas do suggest you?
If you follow my plan,
there will be no useless sacrifices!
And it will be a great victory for you, Commander!
Good…
Then, it is in my turn.
Licieux die…!
How do you make this cheese?
With lait de chèvre of the island.
Ca will reinvigorate your health.
But it is like sprinkling of water an ebullient rock.
[Japanese Proverb]
It is your turn, Ojii-chan.
And well…
… échec et mat.
With the king in defense.
Aaahh!! Wait please!
Not question of waiting, Nami-chan!
I lost…
Once again please!
Ok.
I am unbeatable with the failures when I eat cheese all while making me mass the shoulders.
Beautiful catch today!
Sanji, still prepares to us good dishes for Ossan!
Ouais, I occupy myself some!
Jii-san, if you need anything, do not hesitate to ask.
We will do all that we will be able!
Since I die, I would be happy.
It is like the paradise. The paradise.
Known as step that!
Even if it remains little of time…
… do not give up living…
… as long as you are still in life!
Does He, it do without what funny here?
What?
It was not supposed food only three days more?
Ouais, only three days more!
Only three days with living!
It is so short…
Ouais, but the three days passed for some time already.
Oh yes…
But then it could be that it is in perfect health?
It even seems to be better than front.
Cheese rab.
Jii-san, here your drugs for today.
Especially take them well.
I do not need that. Ca wastes the taste of my meal.
Here, échec et mat!
Aaahh, not yet!!
You said that there remained to him nothing any more but 3 days to be lived.
So that I see there, it seems in good health for the thirty next years.
Perhaps that you were wrong.
Not, I do not think.
But if I had made an error, that, isn't this would not be serious?
It is not the problem there!
If it is the case, I will leave this island, it does not matter what it can say!
Ouais, we do not have time to lose to remain here with dorloter eternally an old man!
I want to continue to live adventures on the seas.
Then it is regulated!
Nami, we are ready to set out again!
You cannot wait a little?
How long you still hope to remain to play?
Ca is enough with the failures!
And well, I cannot leave…
I lost many parts and maintaining the boat is with him.
WHAT?!
Which kind of pirate would bet his boat?
I will recover it! Just a moment!
Echec et mat.
Stop that!!
It is an earthquake!
Aaahh, that lasted enough, what will arrive to us!
If you want to recover your boat, you will have to regain it while working on this island…
… you will have to work about ten years…
… unless you have what to pay?
Nami-san…
Nami…
I am sorry…
I thought that if I gained, I could have asked him where its treasure was hidden…
You say that as so nothing was?
If it is right that, leaves this old man and leaves from here.
It is the only solution.
I do not want.
What do you say, Luffy?
If what Zoro says is true, we are likely to work for this old monkey the remainder of our life.
The guy, will be necessary to find a solution!
We will not live other adventures while remaining here, Luffy.
Let us leave from here.
Not!
Luffy!
Is a bet it like a promise, not?
Then I do not want to break our promise.
It is not the moment to be a defaitist!
Do Zoro, you think what of it?
The Captain is the only one who decides.
Luffy!
Y' does not have average.
Echec et mat.
It is…
It seems that one recovered our boat.
And well, Ojii-chan?
I lost!
Ouuuaaaiiis!
I knew that I could count on you, Onee-sama!
How do you hope to pay?
I suppose that…
I already lived a long life, but I had never met pirates as pleasant as you!
The guy, you are the best!
It is time to have fun the festival!
A festival with a feast!
Ojii-chan, you had to be a large pirate…
… you must be accustomed to drinking.
Nami-chan, why do you call me pirates?
If you had not been it, you would not have these fabulous cuts.
It is probable that comes from a treasure.
Wouldn't Nami, you be testing of the saouler so that he says to you where is the treasure?
You could not conceal to you!
Ossan, do you have really a treasure?
I said to you to close it!
There are other means for that.
My treasure is…
… those which held me company since the day when I made shipwreck here.
Goats of the island.
What a noble feeling!
I laugh!
Stop joking and spit the piece!
As you insist, here is my history…
I was a man who sailed on “Large Line” with the best pirates…
I knew it!
… and I lent money to them.
You lent money to them?
Ouais, one called me Zenny the prêteur sur gages. I am not a pirate.
You are not it?!
Damage for you, Nami.
But you crowned one notch to lend money to pirates, Jii-san.
Why that?
Do you really think that normal pirates would restore what they stole?
You had to put your life in danger.
It is true.
They many times tried not to refund me.
These pirates puants break their promises as easily as they jump a meal.
Then you must hate the pirates.
If I had not held head to them, I would never have made any profit!
And each time, to recover my money, I was to face the pirates, face to face…
… risking my life on Large Line.
Isn't this a job where you were to be stronger than the pirates?
Ossan, are you strong?
Any pride put aside, I was weak.
But I had a dream.
A dream?
Ojii-chan?
What?! To recover the money?!
I am known under the name of Zenny the prêteur sur gages!
Until my death, I will not let anybody flee his debts!
You want to die with me?
Att-await, Zenny!
Unless you have what to pay?
And well then, good-bye!
Not so quickly!!
Do not forget that we are pirates!
He, not question! Ciao!
Zenny… How oses you…!
With the next one!
Although I was weak, I had a dream which helped me to beat me.
It is even for that I fought.
And this dream, it was what?
Since my childhood, I want to become a pirate.
A true pirate, the Lord of the Pirates.
It is for that I began my business of prêteur sur gages.
But one of these pirates puants destroyed my boat…
… and I failed on this island.
20 years ago of that.
Then you spent 20 years to build your tomb?
At the beginning, I wanted to build my boat close it shore and to leave from here, but…
… I could not bring wood until in bottom of the mountain.
But I did not give up, and I rather manufactured it at the top of the mountain.
I kept hope… for my great dream! For my great adventure!
With the wire of time, my great dream eclipsed gradually.
With time, although loan, I was too old to go on Grand Line.
Which dream? Which Pirate?
At the end, my dream was nothing any more but one dream like another.
Why do you give up, Ossan?
Hein?
It is not serious which you would be too old. You can always become pirate as long as you really wish it.
He He, Luffy. What will it occur if it takes to you with the word?
It still needs a flag and its boat is not yet completely finished.
Sanji, meat.
Here!
Thank you.
It has just to reduce it from the mountain!
It is not as easy as that!
I see, then it is not too late…
Here, looks at! Now it took to you with the serious one.
Not, you right thirsty, isn't this is, Ojii-chan?
Ouais, I am thirsty. Very thirst!
Oh…
Straw hat, you helped me to open the eyes!
Let us carry a toast to the insane voyage of Zenny the pirate!
Ouaaaiiis!!
You really think that will go?
Can we really capture by ourself the crew of the Straw hat on the island?
As strong as they are, it is right a group of kids ignoramuses.
If you follow what I say, there is no reason to be afraid.
It is not as if I were going to beat me.
You have just to wait and look at.
Can the captain lose vis-a-vis the crew of the Straw hat?
How do you want that I know it?
After attracthaving attracted them in a trap, we will seek the treasure.
Corporal, you will play a significant role. And you will be well rewarded.
Or-yes, Mister.
Doesn't it matter that I would be old, hein?
By saying that to an old man who just wishes to carry out a dream…
Straw hat, you are a dirty villain.
Indeed.
Robin-chan.
He was once a woman who wished only to die. But this Captain saved it of his own boss.
Isn't this better than it is alive?
And well, I am not yet really sure…
You do not regret it.
I can see it on your face.
Robin-chan, your life does nothing but start.
But me… My dreams died here for always.
What does it occur?
Come quickly! The guy, you raise!
Slept well. It is the hour of the breakfast?
It is the Navy! The Navy is here!
What?!
Just a boat.
They do not seem to want to attack us.
What do they make here?
Hello everyone, crew of the Straw hat.
I am the Minchi Sergeant of the Marine fleet. Happy to meet you.
Happy to meet us?
Ouais, my excuses for the other day.
If I had known who you were, I would not have tried to pursue you.
And thus, I excuse myself some.
It is strange coming from your share. The Navy is supposed to pursue the pirates.
Ca seems too beautiful to be true.
We should be wary.
J I beg you, you do not annoy!
It is well your crew which beat Crocodile with Arabasta, isn't this?
It is not question of facing pirates such as you!
Please, believe me.
Moreover, if I had intended to fight you, I would not have come here with only one boat.
What a standard, it is afraid of us!
And by supposing that we fought you until death, us would not have benefitted any from it.
Whereas do make you here?
Oh, I came to explore this island.
As it is not on any of our charts, it is a new island which we do not know at all.
What do you hear by exploring? There are only here an old man and goats.
Where did the old man pass besides?
I see! Then can we make a visit of courtesy in Zenny?
Zenny?
Once our finished investigation, we will turn over to our base.
And a small council. You should leave this place as soon as possible.
The general headquarter of the navy would like to see you all deaths.
I see. We should leave from here as fast as possible then.
I will take food.
And I will speak about it in Robin.
Aaah, it is…
… a trap! The Navy their tightened a trap!
Will we leave, Luffy?
Behind the fog, time is superb!
We will not stop you, then please leave.
I will leave when I would want of it! You will not decide that!
If I were in the Navy, I would try to fight us even with only one boat!
And another thing! How did you know that the name of Ojii-chan was Zenny?
It was not pronounced only once.
E-and well…
I do not know which kind of explorer you are, but that seems to me very suspect all that.
Would you know the treasure of Ojii-chan?
It, isn't this is surely that?
We cannot trust this type!
Then they know already the prêteur sur gages Zenny and its money mountain lent to the pirates…
Ouiiii, I always knew that Ojii-chan was rich!
I feel a gunpowder odor.
Does that come from these guns?
Ca does not come only from only one boat.
Ca comes from so much from guns which I cannot count them!
What do you say?
If we had taken the sea, we would have been attacked by these navires de guerre.
Salt false bottom!
I card-index myself number of ships which you have! Approach!
Have-await!
Excentric!
Usopp!
The guy!
Remain calm! Only one movement and he died!
Fact of shitting, they have already men on the island…
Good work, Corporal.
You, will say to them!
Wait, it is too late now.
Whereas should we make?
If we do not do anything, Straw hat risks…
It is terrible…
What can I make?
Isn't Ojii-san, you are a pirate?
Ridges something.
It is absurd!
I said that I was a pirate, but this boat is right my coffin.
And one is at the top of the mountain!
I donot can what make!
Then you have just to reduce it from the mountain!
The breeze of the island can help us to go down!
We will embark!
What do you wait?
All, let us release the wood supports! We will embark!
Throw your weapons with ground!
Or if not…
Usopp!
Shit…
The guy, flee!
They we will kill all in any event!
Close it!
Shit, band of cowards!
The Captain is not even yet there and it is already finished.
Corporal!
As I feared it.
It is not play!
The balls will not wound me!
And well, us, they will wound us!
In addition to Zenny, I will have had all the crew of the Straw hat!
Now, will die!
Ahead!
What? Does a boat pirate which goes down from the mountain?
Pirates of Zenny, with the attack!
Jii-san!
How do you hope to pay?
www.rival-spirits.com
http://www.zento.fr
www.saiyajin-team.com
www.kyubi-wolf.net
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/rival-spirits
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/zento
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/saiyajin
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/Kyubi-Wolf
CYB3RFR34K-ISO