Then it is you the poor cretins which refused to pay the harbor tax.
Sanji!
Shit! What does it make?
It is that the Rainbow of the Fogs?
Is professor, which this place?
It is Ape' S Concert.
Ape' S Concert? Would this be…?
What is it?
A place from where one will be able to never arise now that we entered there.
A cemetery of boats.
Inhabitants of Nowhere!
Pumpkin Pirates!
He! Look at!
There are boats shipwrecked men everywhere!
Do not say that.
I have the impression that the phantom of a pirate captain of boat will come to attack us.
It is true?
PHANTOM CAPTAIN!
Does not call them!
“Last the misty Rainbow, you enter the ground of the gods.”
“The last paradise remaining on Earth.”
“A place filled of gold and money where people perish famished.”
Here what they say in the book.
It is as I said it.
Anything else that a legend.
Did professor, you know that this place was a cemetery of boats?
Yes. I already had an outline of this place 50 years ago.
You knew? Then why…?
I had warned you before…
I tried to find a means of saving my friends who had been aspired in the Rainbow of the Fogs.
And it is for that I did not worry about people who showed me finger and called me the puppy of Whetton behind my back.
Oi!
Look at that!
My god…
They is too cool, hein?
There is much in the other boats!
Let us continue to explore!
It is perhaps not the paradise, but you cannot deny that there are enormously treasures here, Professor.
Who dares to disturb deaths which sleep…
Is Qu-Qu'est-ce-que it?
Give up this trunk and leave this place!
Ok.
Or if not, the plague of dead will fall down on you!
I am afraid…
Who are you?
They are làààààà!
Now leave the trunk, or if not…
It was close! Bandage idiots…!
Phantom captain!
There is nothing in lower part!
FANTOOOOMMMMEEESSSS!
But the arrow seemed to come from here.
What?
Luffy!
By-there! There is somebody by-there!
OOOhhh!
Listen to me!
Luffy!
Oh! An arc.
Luffy, pay attention!
Luffy!
It is small that…!
HISTSUKAEN BOSHI
[Devastating Star of fire]
What?
Akibi!
Wait, Longo!
Calm yourself, Longo!
Oh! They are right children.
Longo!
Akibi!
Idiot!
Go -t'en!
GOMU GOMU NO!
DAMEDA!
[Stop that]
Yo, thank you for presently.
But, of nothing.
Longo!
Stop that!
“Ape' S Concert” is the property of Pumpkins Pirates!
If you do not want to die, let my companions leave and give up the trunk!
A bomb?
Lapanui!
Is this…?
Oh, oh, oh… if you use that, you will kill everyone here!
We all will be carried!
Between the life and death, we will always choose the best!
Allons-y!
I am afflicted, Lapanui. Longo!
Ok!
Lapanui…
Is Lapanui, well you?
And… Isoka and Longo?
It is you…
You do not recognize me? It is me!
I learned how to play with you in the Cape Ruluka. It is me, Henzo!
Henzo?
You know them?
You want to say that… He?
I-idiot, that cannot be him!
Does not approach you nearer!
J I will explode it!
Do not take a step moreover!
Stop!
Boom n°3.
One of my inventions.
I only use it to frighten people.
Thin! A smoke-producing bomb!
It is what this brothel? You of made of the noise the guy!
You only have just awaked?
Wait, which it is this type?
If I try to explain you, that will take hours.
Oh, they left.
Who were these kids?
He…
Ossan!
Henzo, hurries to join us!
I am afraid!
You do not have to be afraid!
We are Pumpkins Pirates!
When I am tall, I will be a true pirate!
But Lapanui, your father is a Marine.
You think that it will let you make?
Dad, it is dad.
I want to go in a place where nobody forever be!
Did a place where nobody never go?
Ouais! There is full with unexplored places throughout the world!
I want to also see these places.
Me too.
I want to also be pirate!
But then, you are not likely to have to fight the other pirates?
Somebody the timorous one as me will be able to never do that.
Henzo, you are good to invent heaps of things.
You can invent things which will be useful to us in our venture!
Yes!
Then, I will be too a pirate me!
Ca gives pleasure to hear.
We were so happy.
To play with my companions, to speaking with all the others, I spent the best moments of all my life until now.
No treasure could replace…
all these happy days.
So far terrible.
Henzo!
Henzo! Does Ca go?
Boom n°3 is now finished!
Imbecile!
Do not frighten us any more like that!
You do not have anything but that could have been dangerous!
Ca does not feel good!
The city is on fire!
Any Ruluka is burning!
It is not true…
Our city…
Dad! Mom!
Longo!
Burn! Burn!
Take all that has value!
And if somebody opposes to the Pirates of Whetton…
Kill them! It is included/understood?
Do not hesitate, for anybody!
A pirate!
Then there are still people who did not flee.
Listen, the guy.
If we can arrive to the port, one will be able to have a boat!
Let us steal one, any! And let us flee!
But what did it arrive at my parents?
Idiot!
You want to die?
Now go ahead!
Dirty kids.
Boats…
These types all ran them…
There!
Let us take that one!
That one?
It is our only chance, not?
You dispatch!
What will they make on my boat?
Shit!
Splash!
I hope that you made your prayers.
You dispatch! Climb up there!
A kid as you cannot use this axe.
Would not be insolate, kid.
I am not a kid.
I am the leader of Pumpkins Pirates!
Lapanui!
Ca will go!
There is only one guy!
If we put ourselves at it all together, we can beat it!
He Captain!
We already took again the sea?
IT THERE OF ANOTHER!
Hein? Who are you?
What is it?
The Rainbow of the Fogs!
Oh! Quickly, turn the bar!
If we enter there, we will be able to never come out from it!
THE BAR EAST CASSEE!
You… really returned to me furious.
Akibi!
You will not leave this alive boat!
Its shoulder is uncoupled!
Lapanui!
Now you will die!
Henzo!
Let us turn over behind!
Let us make make half-turn with the boat!
We cannot! The bar is broken!
The Rainbow of the Fogs! The Rainbow of the Fogs…!
Lapanui!
Go ahead! Go from the front one!
Do not forget me!
Henzo!
I will be always with you!
I am me also Pumpkins Pirate!
Henzo…
And then…
And then, Lapanui and the others never returned.
I will never have imagined that they were here, working like pirate truths.
But isn't that occurred 50 years ago?
The four that one saw were children.
Usopp! It seems that the course of time is different inside the Rainbow from the Fogs.
Perhaps one day here represents a week.
Not, perhaps that represents even a year in the external world.
What?
If it is the case, it will be necessary to find a means of leaving from here quickly.
Or if not we will be able to leave there never again.
How that?
Be idiotic for you.
What occurred for these kids and Ossan can arrive to us too!
While we well wisely remain here sitted,
Nami and the others will become of collapsing old men!
WHAT?
Oi, Ossan!
Let us leave from here, quickly!
IDIOT!
We do not know HOW to leave from there.
What?
It is true that?
Then there is not only we donot can make?
Moron… You listened to me?
Not.
There must be a means.
It was said to you, see… three times already!
A means of leaving Ape' S Concert.
OAU, how much time?
Pfff, it does not seem to want to give up!
These weapons are really painful!
Enough spoken!
It is the end!
Reik-sama!
Does Ca go Reik-sama?
Who dared to throw this part on me?
It was not us.
Did you see?
It received this part in full head…
I asked whether it were you!
And if it were the case?
Well.
YOU WANTED RIGHT CA?
The marine charge is now paid.
You are officially inhabitants of Ruluka.
Ape' S Concert?
Ouais, the other patrol craft saw your boat entering the Rainbow of the Fogs.
The Mayor said…
That there was a treasure worthy of the ransom of one king inside.
Treasury?
Ape' S Concert is a cemetery of boats.
The rare people to be arisen about it speak about trunks filled with treasures.
The Mayor wants this treasure and asked Professor Henzo to find a way to enter there.
Oh, and this electric armor, it is one of its inventions!
It is really, very cool, isn't this?
This type likes to speak.
I suppose that he speaks about the type which wanted this tax.
We cannot remain here!
We must also enter ourselves this Rainbow of the Fogs!
Yes, Sir, Nami-san!
- Yes, Sir, Nami-san!
- But once inside, we will be able to never come out from it!
Am not afraid!
This treasure awaits only us!
He
I will not let to you enter Ape' S Concert from my city.
Grandpa!
You, idiotic!
Grandpa?
You do not remember the EC what I said to you.
How much time will I have to say it to you?
When you address yourself to me…
Call me Mr. Mayor.
Whetton mayor.
www.rival-spirits.com
http://www.zento.fr
www.saiyajin-team.com
www.kyubi-wolf.net
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/rival-spirits
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/zento
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/saiyajin
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/Kyubi-Wolf
CYB3RFR34K-ISO