Descent of Luffy!
The Adventure in the Closed Area
The will which survives.
The spirit of time, and dreams of all humanity.
Nobody can stop that.
If the man seeks freedom,
then all this is inevitable.
1,2…
Dumbs!
How do you dare to betray me?
Traitors!!
Stop doing that with starboard!
What will it arrive at fish if you do that?
They will be succulent.
It is what you believe!
One will have to wait how long?
It is strange…
Considering the quantity of soft foods which I did put, why I did not still fish anything?
It is not true! Why use you brushes as soft foods?
Don't Luffy, say to me which it is that use you?
If, that must be as good as a hamburger.
You are well the only one to think that of my opinion!
Super!! A fish!!
It is enormous!
I will see what it is…
He!
It is no matter what which you ace caught according to you?
A fish which likes the brushes.
Which idiot question.
Is that well?
What did it occur?
Nami-san.
It is what, that?
Is that eaten?
It is horrible, I do not want any!
Nami-san!
Does not throw it!
And if there were a treasure inside?
Considering the size it is not possible.
It is not a question of size.
I don't care.
If that is not eaten, I do not want any!
It is all considering.
It is open.
Is Nami, there what inside?
Let look at to me.
Of agreement, here.
Go…
It is a skeleton!
It is really not edible.
Water is in perpetual movement, and I ever heard a similar noise.
Which noise?
You should enter the navel of the sea.
Inside the treasures are of which you always dreamed. Jungo captain.
The navel of the sea?
You should enter there?
It is what?
It is what this cavity in the sea?
Inside the treasures are of which you always dreamed.
Jungo captain?
All will be with me this time.
Nami-san, let us carry out a happy life together.
It is very small here, does not smoke.
They is so good to be reprimand by the love of Nami-san!
Luffy, one goes down!
Yep!
Luffy, one entrusts the guard of the ship to you.
Of agreement, but I wanted to descend me too.
It is ridiculous.
I am hungry and I am thirsty.
What?
That resembles a drink for me.
Good appetite!
It is what?
You saw what?
Let see me.
Me also I want to see!
What can that be well?
Do Luffy, you hear that?
There is a gigantic cave in the navel of the sea.
One goes down now.
Do Luffy, you hear me?
Turn a little.
I repeat, one goes down.
Luffy, reduce to us low still!
Do Luffy, you hear?
Kills us, one made a great discovery.
Included/understood.
I cannot withdraw it.
Do Luffy, what you make?
One soon will be crushed!!
It is what that?
Me known as step that they all are of the pirates to the research of the treasures.
With my opinion, one should not trail here.
Who is this?
It is the cemetery of all the pirates.
You also, you will die here.
A bat…
… speaking!?
It is me here the guide.
You would make better leave.
Which is this noise?
What does it occur?
What arrives to you Nami-san? Why do you make this head?
Luffy, goes up us!
Quickly!!!
Luffy!
I believed to hear something. That must be my imagination.
Ah, what a good nap!
What do they have to howl like that?
How I leave it from there?
I will help you.
Thank you Zoro.
And here.
Zoro, you…
What is it that?
It is a letter?
Show.
You include/understand it?
Obviously.
Luffy!
Please!
Luffy, goes up us!!!
If it is like that.
One succeeded, one of it is drawn.
One will leave oneself there!
Where you take us along?
What is it?
One is taken with the trap! What to make?
You made cry Nami-san, I will not forgive yourself it.
One can count on him at least, it is not like certain…
You speak about who?
Luffy cost us our breakfast.
Nami-san, which would you say of an octopus for the lunch?
It was captured too.
And the octopus with the air in anger.
What occurs?
Oh not Luffy…
What?
Really…
Imbecile!
Course to the footbridge, Luffy!
Cling quickly to this rock!
One succeeded!
Shit!
Why does that occur like that?
Zoro…
I am really burst.
Luffy…
Do Sanji, you can more what make?
That me has all the air of it…
It is what?
It occurred what?
It is the Vogue-Merry!
You see it?
That made party of our plan!
What?
What makes Luffy and the other?
Dispatch we to find the treasure.
A treasure?
Good, there are not time to lose.
Nami-san.
You can go there in first?
I will catch up with you in a wink.
Why?
Be sure for you that goes?
Yes.
Allons-y, Nami!
Luffy is not on board.
Let us leave the boat here.
You will be awaited Sanji-kun.
You must cling.
I cannot move really any more.
Hamu, and if you do get caught?
What can one make there?
Please, gives up!
Even if somebody manages to recover a message,
one could not be saved.
Our destiny was sealed 10 years ago
when we decided to remain here.
Although we did not find peace,
everyone was committed continuing its current life.
I do not want!
I do not want…
I do not want to be tortured like Mero.
I have enough of this life of it!
Who is this?
Who are you?
Somebody… with the assistance!
This… letter…
They is good.
You can rise?
I should be able.
Hamu, returns to you util!
Run!
In… Incredible!
Die!
Super! You really came to save us.
I am burst, I will lie down.
He, you two.
You really came to save us?
You came for this letter.
You speak about that?
Yes.
What did it write there above?
I do not include/understand it.
And you?
Do not ask me.
Please, for which reason did you really come?
We fell.
Fallen?
Yes, whereas we seek a treasure.
A treasure?
Then you are…
Yes, of the pirates!
Finally pirate apprentices.
Pirates?
Who y' has?
We thought that you would fight at our sides.
You did not come to help us?
Then… you are only pirates!
Hamu!
What does it have, him?
Please, I ask you to leave at once.
We hate the pirates.
All here, we hate them.
You saved us.
The pirates also know gratitude.
What occurs?
Say it to us, please.
Heard.
You have the strong air.
That made 10 years.
The first pirate to arrive here was…
the Jungo Captain.
I intended some to speak.
Good Ah?
It stole all the richnesses of the city.
It is even…
party with the legendary dormant mountain crowned,
and it succeeded in offending the gods.
What did it occur then?
I do not know!
I do not want the knowledge either.
What arrived to the Jungo Captain does not look at us,
whether it found the treasure or that it died.
Because the monsters which it released,
we plunged in one decade of misery.
This life does not have anything free…
One can count only on ourself to survive.
And…
we hate the pirates for what they did to us.
It is like that.
Does Y' have another monster in top of the mountain?
Then there is not only that which I killed.
He! You, two pirates,
you could save us…
Completely. And then one benefitted well from your food.
Perhaps she wants that one will seek his companion.
You speak about Hamu.
Ham?
Ham or melon?
It lost his mother.
And after that, I am occupied.
The mother of Hamu was the queen of this city.
She was with the current for a long time for the pirates and the fate which had been broken,
and for all that had arrived in this city.
Then, it is assembled at the top of the mountain to kill Jungo.
But it never returned since.
This is why Hamu wants to avenge his/her mother.
And thus, he seeks somebody to come to help it with vanger.
Yes.
It is stupid.
Completely.
He is insane.
He seeks a dead pirate years ago.
This Jungo Captain already died?
Didn't I say you not to interfere you?
But however, his laughter is always heard.
We are there.
The treasure is in top of the mountain.
Really?
It is easy.
On the contrary.
What?
To obtain the treasure, you must overcome two monstrous animals.
What you say?!
Moron.
Why you did not speak about it front?
You asked me anything.
We reached this place.
Where thus did Luffy pass?
Allons-y!
There remain nothing any more but us now two.
The way stops here.
The mountain is right in front.
Is Luffy, one really obliged to go there?
Ouais, I want to see this Jungo Captain.
If it in life, then that is always made ten years
that it is on the track of the treasure.
And then…
I filled the paunch already well.
Exact.
Push yourself!
Does Zoro, that go?
Take that!
Stop!
This monster…
It is with me.
Luffy, you can continue all alone.
Of agreement.
Afflicted.
Good blood, these swords are not very useful.
Good!
I go there!
I must hurry!
Hamu.
It is…
We are there.
Yes.
Here the famous hollow one.
This… this cellar…
do not only say to me…
it is a labyrinth?
Completely.
The treasure must be in the medium.
It is that, is necessary that one arrives there.
It is cake.
If one loses oneself in a labyrinth, it is enough to turn back,
and to seek the right track.
It is at least necessary to be able to leave.
What?
He Ussop, somebody arrives.
Quickly, course!
One is saved.
Ussop, why you have…
Do not precipitate anyhow!
Why?
Because…
Course!!
I do not arrive there.
A sword…
There are so many swords here.
Thank you.
This place is very interesting.
It left!
Why, why you want that I carry you?
Your mouth!
Let us leave quickly!
On the left, on the left!!
I included/understood!
On the left, left, left…
left, left…
Right-hand side!
Right-hand side…
One reconsidered our steps.
It is not my fault.
Where you go?!
Behind you!
Course!
It is what that?
Why isn't there more way?
It is for that I had you
asked to leave!!!
It is odd, why they are all died?
About what you speak, stunned?!
Look behind you!
Behind…
I know.
It is you who did that.
IEA… course now!
Luffy!
Beautiful job!
What you insane?
Hurry!
I cannot rise.
You do not want to seek your friend?
Of course that if.
Then shows me initially,
what you ace in the belly.
And shows me then the talents of your companions!
You want to see that of which I am able?
Ouais, shows me.
Course!
Then, for research…
It is that.
It is finished.
Beautiful job.
But you ace taken a long time.
Was necessary to let me make.
Really…
You arrive too late in any case.
Fortunately that I was there to help.
Miss.
You are wounded?
Not.
In fact it…
If you want it, one could dine together.
It is not the moment to think of having fun!
If they were able to remove me from the last monster guard,
I could finally become again myself.
Ussop, it is there.
Do not only say to me…
Exact.
Super, the treasure was found.
What?
Wait a little…
Wait.
What, be to you really shitting you!
It is necessary that you will kill the last monster!
And why you speak to me like that?
And why not.
The treasure is, right there in front of us.
Who dictated these rules?
It is…
Look at.
Somebody is there to wish you the welcome.
Who are you?
I have them all exploded!!!
Luffy?
Captain!?
Jungo!
Do Ussop, you await what?
Dispatch we to take it!
Of agreement.
An explosive bullet?
That is there, my body is finally reconstituted.
It had however been separate in several parts.
My body….
I will never have believed that you would succeed in with me bringing back it.
Thanks to you, I am again in life.
He, you have really the pitiful air.
It is true, I was abused!
By you all!
It is perfect now, you are all died.
But I am different.
I lived in the shape of a bat during one decade
for this moment…
I finally will carry out my dream.
To find the secrecy of the navel of the sea!
Jungo!!!
Who?
You have much chance, you know?
I have full with ammunition.
Jungo!
Hamu!
I did not think that some would have courage to rebel.
Your face is not unknown for me…
I see!
You are this kid.
Then, the kid, returned to you.
You grew.
And you want to avenge your mother?
This courageous heart which dared to defy me?
Really?
I will show you…
how it finished.
Here what occurred.
Look at.
Not!!!
I came vanger my mother!
Hamu.
Mom fought for the good of the village.
But she knew her force.
Then, I went sought companions
to assist me in this combat.
And like my mother, I will fight for the village.
Companions?
And where are they thus?
Look around you, they are all died.
There are only you and me.
Come, that made one decade that I wait.
Let us regulate that good once for all.
We will see which us two will survive.
Mom, gives me courage.
Grant to me the will to fight.
It is what this light?
Would you be…
Impossible…
How this is possible…
You have so many companions?
I would have liked me well too.
I succeeded…
I succeeded, mom.
What arrives to you?
You are except, then does not cry.
I cry of joy
because you fought at my sides.
I did not help you…
All that I want, it is the treasure.
There is nothing.
The treasure does not exist.
Where is it?
Is He, where the treasure?
That scintillated presently.
One flies!!
Lastly, they set out again.
And I do not even know their names.
It is of no importance.
They are pirates.
Exact, they are pirates.
I would become the Lord of the Pirates!