A serious combat!
Luffy VS Zoro:The duel inatendu!
I cannot die here…
I have an important mission to achieve!
You are really pathetic!
You to make beat by a poor wretch swashbuckler.
Mr. 5, Valentine Miss!
Why are you here?
With my opinion, you know it already.
The Boss sent bus of the criminals here to us hide in this city.
The exact words of the Boss are:
“Somebody bored my secrecy.”
Obviously, I do not know this secrecy.
Therefore, we made an investigation to discover which could have bored the secrecy of the Boss.
The result was surprising!
We discovered that members placed high of a certain kingdom had infiltrated Baroque Works!
We are discovered!
We are rotten…
I will not let to you touch the Princess!
On my name of Captain of the Royal Guard of Arabasta, I will prevent you!
Igaram!
The Captain of the Royal Guard of Arabasta, Igaram.
And the Princess Nefertari Vivi.
By order of the Boss of Works Baroque, you must be eliminated.
Eh well…
And Luffy which is still in bottom…
Quickly, Vivi-Sama!
You escape while it is still time!
Igaram!
Useless.
Monsters…
Then you are a princess, Miss Wednesday!
Stop making the clown, Mr. 9!
This night is less and less sure.
VI… Vivi-Sama!
Igaram!
You are well?
Vivi-Sama.
Of made you not for me.
Dispatch you to flee from here,
for the safeguard of our country!
Without you, the kingdom of Arabasta goes…
Go! You dispatch!
Do not even think of escaping to you.
Do not underestimate me!
I do not include/understand all well that occurs here…
But since we were partners so a long time,
I will try to delay them.
Go ahead, Miss Wednesday.
Mr. 9!
I am rather well, not?
Bye bye, baby!
The only thing which we need,
it is the will to achieve our mission.
This connery of friendship is only one invitation to die.
You will include/understand it!
Mr. 9!
Hey, hey! Here are dangerous droppings of nose!
Hein? You want what?
Master swashbuckler, you have such a force.
Do I can ask you for an irrational favor?
Ca does not interest me! Release me! Low legs!
These deux-là has the capacities of the Fruits of the Demon!
I am not size vis-a-vis them.
I entreat you! Protect the Princess in my place! You accept?
Karu! With the gallop!
She flees!
She will not go far.
Allons-y, Miss Valentine!
Yes, Mr. 5!
The kingdom of Arabasta is far in the east from here.
If you take along the healthy Princess there and saves,
you will touch surely a very large reward!
I entreat you!
Protect the Princess!
Doesn't Ca go in your head?
I announce you that you tried to kill us!
Do not oblige me to cut itself into two!
It is true this history of reward?
It is a sound which I adore.
Is 10 Billion Berrys, it honest, not?
Nami!
10… 10 millia… My my maaa.
I believed you in the vapes.
Oh, go…
Does a city have a cast which organizes a great festival when pirates pass there?
Which idiot would be made have by a similar blow?
I made seeming! Seeming!
I could still swallow some much more!
Ah, super…
Then? It is of agreement for the 10 Billion Berrys, Mister Capitaine of the Guard?
If you are not helped, your invaluable Princesse will remain there.
I am only one private.
I then to promise this sum.
You want to make me believe that the Princess is not worth this sum?
Bring the dough!
If that it is not extortion…
If you guarantee to me that you will lead it to good port.
You have to only negotiate directly with the Princess. I am certain that it will accept.
Approximately, one must initially save it.
While we speak,
the life of the Princess is…
I included/understood.
One will save your Princess.
Ahead Zoro!!
I do not move me, idiot!
Why will I help you with you to put full the pockets of them?
What a idiotic!
My money, it is my money.
But the agreement concerns you all.
And since when you take this kind of decisions?
What? All that you ace to do it is of going to occupy you of these types.
I do not like to be made use. You ace that to ask your moron of cook to take care some.
Be to you saying to me
what don't be able for you to beat them?
Do not be to you well?
Repeat that once again to see!
Be to you saying to me
for how do not be able you to beat them?!
Wee…
And it does it moreover!
You forgot?
You are my debtor!
About what you speak.
In Loguetown, you said that you wanted to buy katanas to you, and I lent 100.000 to you Berrys.
But I already refunded them to you!
I had the katanas free, therefore I have anything spent!
However, when you borrowed them to me, you promised to refund me triple.
I have purchases to make.
I make you a loan, if you refund me triple.
Thus you owe me 200.000 more Berrys.
But I refunded you immediately after you gave me the money!
Too bad…
You are not rotten to even hold a small promise?
If you do what I ask you, one will be free!
I hope that you will burst in atrocious sufferings!
You ace reason! I will go right in Hell.
Shit! I hate you!
Thank you in advance!
Which humiliation…
If I had been more extremely, I could have protected the Princess myself.
You of made not.
It is very strong, this moron.
The Princess…
If something were to arrive at Vivi-Sama,
it would be finished by it kingdom of Arabasta!
She must live!
Course!
Course, Karu!
It has there a boat anchored behind the Rocks of the Cactus!
Will be used it to flee
and to turn over to Arabasta!
Ca is better!
Go, with the dodo.
It is what that?
More quickly, Karu!
Karu, stop!
Mr. 5…
He found us.
Karu, by here!
Quickly!
This escape is vain.
Monday miss!
Flee. The boat is right behind.
I will retain them.
But…
We will be punished in any event
to have lost vis-a-vis this superhuman swashbuckler.
Therefore,
I prefer to die while being used as shield with a friend.
Do Eh well, what you wait?
If you die,
the sacrifices of Mr. 8 and Mr. 9 will have been vain.
Slip by!
Thank you.
Initially Mr. 9 and then you…
Monday miss.
You will not go further.
I make the oath of it.
It is amusing.
You made me pity…
For Works Baroque!!
You are shame!!
Monday miss…
I am able to make explosive any part of my body. I am a human bomb.
Thanks to the capacity of the fruit Boom Boom,
I never failed in any of my missions.
And with the capacities of the fruit Kilo Kilo,
this traitress…
… Monday Miss will be reduced out of pulp.
I am able to change my weight at will.
In this moment, I am enough light to float in the airs.
Look at as I take weight.
Then?
You really think of being able you to leave there?
You cannot escape to us.
I will survive.
To survive and…
I will survive! And I go…
… to return in Arabasta!
Take that!
Mr. Bushido!
… The passage…
Who it is, this type?
I cut droppings!
Why do you insist like that in one similar moment?
Very soft.
I am there to help you.
To help me?
He…
It is what with the Juste, Baroque Works?
It is a clandestine criminal organization.
No member knows the name of the Boss, nor did not see his face.
They are specialized in espionage, the murder, the flight and the collecting of the premiums.
All is made according to the orders of the Boss.
But why does everyone obey the orders of a Boss that it forever considering?
Because the final objective of Works Baroque is to found a “Ideal Nation”.
The Boss promised with those which fulfill their missions successfully
that they will occupy of the stations - keys in the “Ideal Nation” which it intends to create.
I see.
The code name of the Boss is Mr. 0.
In other words, more code name of the member is close to zero,
more the row which it occupies is high.
They are the most powerful members!
The power of those of which the number is lower than 5 is… phenomenal!
You are not the type which sliced all the inhabitants of this city?
Why do you protect maintaining the Princess from Arabasta?
I have my reasons.
Well, that imports.
In are all the cases, you our enemy, not? Release from there!
Exact! Release!
TE VOILAAA!!
ZOROOOOOO!!!
It is what this time?
Luffy!
If came to you to help me, it is not the sorrow.
Unless you do not have also debts towards this woman.
YOU WILL NOT DRAW You LIKE CA!!
IN GUARD!
But what do you tell?
MT MOUTH!
Species of dirty ungrateful!
I will explode you the head!
Ungrateful?
Ouais!
Did He, what occur?
Who did that to you?
Your pal… the type with the green sabers and hair.
What?
They had organized a super festival in our honor,
and you you all put them in parts!!
Do not be to you well??
Bah… Ouais, it is true…
I will not forgive it to you!
This type is completely stunned or what?
They are friendly?
Which wounds, these…
Let us kill them. As all those which are put across our way.
He, Luffy.
Listen to me. In fact, it is…
I CARD-INDEX MYSELF YOUR EXCUSES!
What?
You want to kill me?
Ouais! Burst!
Moron! You will listen to me, yes?
Which moron…
He is serious.
Mr. 5?
In fact, one would say that they do not obstruct us, after all.
One would say.
Well, it any more but does not remain us to achieve our mission.
What is summarized to kill the Princess of Arabasta, Vivi.
You will not escape!
Luffy, listens to me!
Ahead, Valentine Miss.
Yes, Mr. 5.
Ca is enough now! MORON!
What a idiotic!
How do you dare to bar us the road?
What was it that?
Since your friend and have you the air to so much want between-to kill you,
I will have a joy of occupying me of you myself.
Not?
Now, I am in detonator!
I will kill you, thanks to the capacities of the fruit Kilo Kilo!
You prepare!
My weight is only of 1 kg, thus I use the blast of the explosion to float!
Mr. Bushido, do not remain there! This woman…
The farm!
I do not have time to lose with it.
A little exercise, that made of the good.
Ca made me digest.
Mr. 5… Not possible!
An Agent Officer of Works Baroque…
One finally will pass to the serious things.
He, Luffy… The calm one and listens to me.
I arriiiive!
The inhabitants of this city are all of the bargain hunters.
My capacities enable me to vary my weight from 1 to 10000 kg!
They are our enemies!
You finished being unaware of me??
LIAR! Enemies do not offer meals like that!!
Take that!
Luffy.
It would be said that no matter what I say, that does not return in your dirty caboche.
Species of dark cretin!
In my turn, now, to try to kill you!
Then do not come pleurnicher when I smash you!
Bring back yourself!
Wait… What do you make?
Aren't you friendly both?
Here is an good occasion to see
who of the fist or the saber, is strongest.
He. Let us see what you ace in the belly!
(Tornado)
What do I have to make?
I want to flee but…
I wonder whether I do not risk anything…
Brothel…
These types are well foutus of me.
They sullied the name with the Agents Officers of Works Baroque.
Mr. 5.
Let us show them what we are really able!
Allons-y, Miss Valentine!
Yes, Mr. 5!
We are Agents Officers of Works Baroque!! Then stop to you foutre us!
Close it!
DO NOT DISTURB US!!
DURING OUR COMBAT!!
RELEASE FROM!!!