Who are you?
Hein?
Hum? Who are they?
It belongs to your crew too?
Sure Euh. .bien!
You also you lost the memory?
Is young people and pretty young lady which your first name?
It is what that?
It is a stagÉ
Your mouth species of human!
I am a reindeer!
He spoke!!!
Pfff! Pirates per pirate CiÉ per thereÉ what a stupid time!!!
I hate the pirates!
Me what I like it is the money and the oranges,
it is impossible that I travel with such pirates!
'Made too much noise dice the morningÉ
You prevent me from sleeping!
I must leave at all costs from hereÉ
Pff! I include/understand nothing there but I have anything has to make here.
The mysterious boy with the flute
The deduction of Robin
NavigatriceÉ
PhewÉ it is better like that.
It is although the bargain hunter left this ship butÉ
I think that it will go down on the island.
You know the character of our navigatrice,
it will not move of the island as long as it will not have made a good decision.
I hope for it wellÉ
AaaaahÉ I have faimmmmÉ
Agyaaaaa!!!
That with the air Bonn!
Gyyaaaaa!!!
Stop! Do really not be nervous for you youÉ
FinallyÉ one will be able to always think so that one will make after eating.
With the fact Miss I still do not know your name.
It is Nico Robin.
Above could all, you tell us the memories which one lost?
OK!
There is not question of remaining a second more over there!
The pirates can only steal the goods of peopleÉ
It is necessary quickly that I find a means of returning in Kokoyashi.
I am content that you would have come large-sister.
You are the welcomeÉ
It is well too calmÉ
I wonder what could well occur.
If I go up still a little, can be that I will find somethingÉ
NewspapersÉ
Hein? QuÉ what?
AtÉ wait a little!!
Kyaaaaaaaa!
What is this you ace you!
Your mouth! All depends on these newspapers!
I will never give myself them!
Hey you I do not laugh!
I will never give myself it!
The farm! Give me that!
It is me which took it in first!
I of insane!
Be to you which you!?
I will not suffer as Ca if I knew it!!
That is what they all haveÉ
What is what it occurs here?
Hey!
Hum?
What is what there is big sister?
AhÉ I include/understand, you seek a boatÉ
Yes.
On this island there are only the boats which are in this port.
Good Ah?
But there is only of the old dilapidated tubs which do not seem any more to be used?!
Everyone seems to be worried by other thingÉ
If you think that they is false you can always make the turn of the island.
It is small thus I think that will go rather quickly.
But goodÉ take your time.
I am sure that you you will be able to have fun.
I cannot waste my time.
AhÉ I include/understandÉ
AfflictedÉ
NotÉ do not make any you.
AaahhÉ I start to be sleepyÉ
I will return at home.
Ah! Hey!
Go, so long!
They are pirate truths!
Ahh the clouds are soft as usualÉ
An hyena and horse-wingedÉ
Putainnnn! Why I remember nothing?!
Davy Back FightÉ and the large fortress of the sailorsÉ
É celestial islands and country of Arabasta sand.
Es you sure that we lived all these adventures?
Yes, exactly.
J. .j' do not believe in itÉ
The captain of this ship has a premium of 100 million berrys?!!
SayÉ you know others of them? Stories of interesting adventures?
I entered this crew in Arabasta.
It is damage but I do not know what occurred front.
Meeeeerde! What a dommageeee!!
AhhÉ it is not the kind of thing which one manages to believe easily.
But the fact is that the site of these ustensiles de cuisine and spices me sied with wonder.
Can Robin san, you speak to us about the event which occurred yesterday?
Ok!
But then with Mister the ship's doctor come too.
Hiyaa guiiiiiii!
I already said you that it was in the other direction.
But euuuh the fermeee you!
You are hungry not? Come to eat here.
OOhhhhhhh!!
Do not say silly things! I do not want to puff out with the human ones!
Can you say to us of what you think too?
Please, Mister the exceptionally gifted ship's doctor.
Idiotic UhhhÉ! I am at all glad to be flattered!
You ace very content airÉ
We were advancing in this maritime zoneÉ
Are Aaahhh NamiÉ sure for you that it is really this road?
Do not worry you! The Log installation shows this direction clearly.
Don't Usopp, you always see anything?
Await very small little.
Eh! An island!!
It is surrounded by reefs coral.
They is dangeureux to skirt the coasts.
This evening we will drop anchor and one will unload tomorrow morning.
Heinnnn?!
You do not want to listen to what the navigatrice says?!
Sanji-kun, Luffy is private meal this evening!
Quooiiiii?!!
Hay! Nami-san!
I am desolŽŽŽŽŽŽ!!!
And then all the crew left to lie down except Kenshi-san which assembled the guard and me which made research.
Here approximately what occurred.
You know the continuation.
I thinkÉ
According to what you said,
the hunter of pirates fell asleep too.
It seems to meÉ
Another coffee cup?
Yes readily.
ButÉ I wonder well why only Robin-san did not lose the memoryÉ
If Kenshi-san also slept,
the only difference between you and me it is.
É the sleep.
I slept but I remember very well!
We form well part of the crew of large Usopp!
Thus that wants to say that the sleep would have removed our memoriesÉ
I did nothing but say what I noted objectively.
I cannot affirm it with certainty.
I never heard of a similar case.
Maintaining it is with you!
Speak me about your most recent memory.
Me I am to go to gather plantes mŽdicinales with Doctorine,
and I was supposed to return to the castle to sleep but when I awoke I was here.
Me IÉ hey! Do not be unaware of me!
Hum? I was made carry by a large swirl then I disappeared and I regained consciousness I were here.
After having finished my job, I went to lay down me but I awoke here.
And you do not remember anything after CaÉ
Ah? Hum! Ah! Ah!
Ah yes! I heard the sound of a flute!
A fluteÉ a fluteÉ yes yes! Me also I heard!
With the factÉ
A child appeared abruptly in front of my eyesÉ
Can be thatÉ we lost them but only in factÉ
É it is this child who stole us our memories?
One cannot deduce that but it is certain that this child is the key of the mystery.
Me known as step which one loses all our memories by sleepÉ
Hiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii!!!
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
Do not frighten me!!
Wait a little! It is only one dream after all!
The occult facts that does not exist!
Even if it is not the case, one did everything the same dream!
Occult fact or not, it is reality!
I would not like to frighten you butÉ
In the worst of the cases, it is possible that you did not remember even more who you are.
Waa I had peuuur!
One of foutÉ
É to have memories or not.
It is true that it is regrettable not to remember memories cools butÉ
É it is enough to live again of the adventures together!
Do not say stupidities!! It may be that all is forgotten!
SÉ if it is the case, all our past and all our dreams goÉ
They will not disappear!
My dream will never disappear!
And that must be similar too for you.
Which optimismÉ
HuhuhuÉ with or without memories, our captain is always the same one.
It is surprisingÉ
Aaahhh!! My puffs out disappeared!!
Hihihihi!
Uwaaa!
Do not touch with puffs out others!
AfflictedÉ
Do I have to say that it is stupid or notÉ?
I feel really ridiculous to reflect seriouslyÉ
Hihihihi!
Where is the city??
www.rival-spirits.com
http://kinh.no-ip.org/
http://perso.wanadoo.fr/audiz/
IRC:/irc.ff.st/rival-spirits
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/kinh
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/saiyajin
Hihihihi!
Ca excites me!
Ahh!!
What you factories?
One. .un new remedy to find the memory.
Do not obstruct me.
Hey!! Does not touch there without my authorization!
You found something?
NotÉ it is an ordinary island as one finds some anywhere.
Beurk! It is what this bitter trick?!
Yosh! It is ready!
HuhuhuÉ
The great invention of Usopp Master!
It is what these tricks??
HŽhŽÉ good questionÉ
These tricks areÉ!!
One can be reassured even if one loses the memory with that!
I named them:MY NAME PUNT!!
Huhu. good idea.
It is not genti L! I am not a question mark me!
And me I am neither a tanuki where necessary nor a provision!
[Tanuki:left raccoon]
One to coil idiotic?!!
Then, that did you say some?
Superb not?
Ouch! É.
Stop manufacturing conneries!
My memoriesÉ
ÒAre the men so fragile is not this step Zoro?Ó
ZoroÉ
You ace of the Zoro chance to be a boy.
Me also I want to be the best fencer of the world!
The girlsÉ when it growÉ they become weaker than the boys.
It is not right!
Me alsoÉ me also I would have liked to be a boy!
You will say that to me when I overcome you?
How if in fact the capacities count!!
Zoro!
I feel idiotic to involve myself of all my forces!
Then repeat that never again! promise it to me!
One day or the other, one of us will become the best swashbuckler of the world!
It is a race between you and me for becoming it!
IdiotÉ be too weak for you.
Promised!!
MasterÉ give me this saber.
The saber of Kuina?
I will be strong too for it.
So that my name is known even in the skies!
I will be the best swashbuckler of the world!!
I promised to himÉ.IÉ IÉ! hikk hikkÉ sniff.
Of agreement! Take it.
I entrust the heart and the dream of Kuina to you.
After these events I endured hard drivesÉ
É and I took the sea to seek this man.
To become a large swashbuckler.
I remember assembled being aboard the ship and to have sleptÉ
After thatÉ I do not remember anything any moreÉ
Moreover these two sabers are oddÉ
When I had them?
In more they suit me to perfection.
What does it occur?
Who is there?
The last date of the log book corresponds the day before the newspaper.
It is coherent.
I cannot believe in itÉ it thus said true?
If it is the case ..... 0,5350, \ alpha&H00&)}I belong to the pirates?
Me?
NotÉ it is not possible!
And this tattooingÉ
But finally that does it occur? I do not include/understand anything any more.
More nothingÉ
Hyahhahhahha!
How are you poor human?
From now this island is under our control!
It is one day memorable and you will have to buy your life to me!
That which cannot pay will be killed!!
I do not wantÉ why we must leave this village?
I want to remain hereÉ
But as we are poor, one can be the children of Belmer-san more.
Wait!!
Huh?
These 100.000 berrys are for my daughters.
I do not have what to pay my share.
Belmer! You. !!
Excuse to me Gen-san, IÉ I cannot say that I do not have a familyÉ
[Gen-san:diminutive of Genzo-san]
Even if I must die for themÉ
It is true that we do not have any family ties butÉ
It is my family!
Even if they are only words, I want to be their mother.
They are my daughters not?
Belmer-saaaaaan!!
Forgive meÉ I did not can anything make as a mother for you.
It is not true!
I do not want anything else thus do not die!
NamiÉ you must carry out your dream! Remain in lifeÉ
Die because of this ridiculous love.
Nojiko! Nami!
I love you!!
IÉ will belong to the crew of ArlongÉ
I will be their geometrician and I will draw charts.
NamiÉ
I signed a contractÉ
É to repurchase Kokoyashi.
To repurchase the village?
For 100.000.000 of berrys.
If I buy the village one could be free.
But 100.000.000 of berrys it is an immense sum!!
You will certainly not have them, even by working all your life!
I will have themÉ
É and I will do anything for that!!
If I ask of the assistance to somebody there will be still casualtiesÉ
You must sufferÉ
YesÉ
To be with that which killed Belmer-sanÉ
É it is hard.
If you remainders alive it will arrive to you full with good things!
Do not make any youÉ even if I will see his face, I will always smile!
I decided not to cry more!
I decided to beat me all alone!!
Belmer-sanÉ
I am in a hurry.
This evening I will take all the remainderÉ
AllÉ
Huhuhuhuhuhu!
Hum? Thin Ah.
I awoke you?
Not.
You can still sleep.
If there is a problem I will awake you.
Ca will go, excuse me Robin-san.
Do you want a coffee cup to remain waked up?
Yes please.
On the other hand, those there sleep thoroughlyÉ
É whereas they said that they were not going to sleep.
You do not sleep yet?
It is you who stole their memories?
FufufufuÉ you are right.
But it is too late.
You awake! Quickly!!
Ahha! You have a mysterious technique.
Ah??
Hein?
Hi!! It came!
Waaaaahhh!!
What is there? Is the breakfast ready?
It is not very nice big sisterÉ
É to awake everyone.
I do not have any more the choiceÉ I did not want to do that butÉ
Aaaahhh!!!!!! What you insane there you?!!!!
I will not leave you this place!!!
It is my place deprived here!!!
You there assied not without my authorization!!!
I am sorryÉ
OhÉ qu-qu. what is it?
Gyaaaa! it isÉ it is what Ca??
I have peuuuur!
Was CÉ it what immediately?
Isn't EhÉ it badly in point there?
It does not move any moreÉ
Is it toujous alive?
A mŽdecinnnnn!!! A mŽdecinnnnn!!! ahhÉ it is meÉ
I found the memory!!
You are my companions!!
Master cock, swashbuckler, doctor, archeologist and then a liar.
The next episode of One Part!
Let us take again our memory!!!
The pirates unload on the island!!
It is me which will be the lord of the pirates!!