RAISE ANCHOR!
FULL SAIL!
We're good to sail!
- Idiot! Don't shake it, Sanji!
Full speed ahead to the Grand Line!!!
- lf you're scared, don't come up here.
lf you're scared, don't come up here.
S-S-Stupid, I'm not scared!
Sanji! FOOD! Food!
Alright, alright. Wait until I make it already!
Good morning, Nami-san!
Good morning, Sanji-kun.
Aw, c'mon Zoro, let's play tag.
Whaat!?
What? What? I wanna play! Let's do it! Let's do it!
Are you retarded? How old are you two?
I'm gonna take my pre-breakfast nap.
He's afraid he's gonna lose.
What'd you say, bastard? That is not why!
Ha! Look how mad he's getting!
Whaat!?
Come back here, you son of a...
Oh, and name-calling now too, eh? Whoo! Naana!
YOU!
From now on, you're my nakama!
Let's just get one thing straight.
This is ONLY cooperation.
Keep that In mind.
Zoro-san, over here!
Zoro! No fair, you have to play with me too!
I AM NOT PLAYING!
Nami-san, breakfast is served.
Hey, you losers! Time for grub!
AYE!!!
Get your ass back here! I'm not finished with you!
He said that to me, even back then.
What is it, Nami-san?
Oh, nothing.
Ah! I'm so hungry!
Food! Food-food!!
Looks so tasty!
By the way, what do you suppose
happened to Buggy?
Buggy?
Oh! That Buggy!
Who knows, maybe he's off
in the ocean somewhere.
It's hard to say.
When it comes to pirates, they're all different.
Is that so?
Bastard, what's your problem!? You started it!
I was a pirate hunter for a long time.
I know a lot about them.
Are you just going to stand there, Usopp?
Your food is disappearing.
Here's a special yogurt treat just for you.
- Luffy! You ate all of my food again!
Thank you, Sanji-kun!
GIVE IT BACK, JERK!!
ALRIGHT!!
At last, my Super Flashy Raft is complete!
You will all see. The most famous
pirate in the world...
Clown Pirate Buggy-sama...
is makin' a comeback. I'm makin' a flashy return!
I will do it no matter what!
I must have my revenge!
You flashy stinky rubber brat... just you wait!
ONWARD!!
So what if I have bad luck in the beginning!?
I WILL NOT LOSE, DAMMIT!!
FOLLOWING THE STRAW HAT!
LITTLE BUGGY'S BIG ADVENTURE
Somehow... I... I made it to the next island...
Dammit. Tryin' to scare me...
QUIT STARIN' YOU!
Punk, you lookin' down on me?
Looking down on someone like me...
You sure got some guts, pal.
I'm gonna eatcha!
I'm hungry as hell!
Since you dared to look down on my
great self, nothing can save you now!
You're gonna be mine in a flash! Just face it!
BARA BARA HOU!
(Cannon)
Don't bother trying to escape.
It's time to die.
I am SO SORRY! That was so rude of me!
PLEASE FORGIVE MEEE!
Over here, over here.
My plan is perfect.
Baka, baka, baka!
Ha-ha! Gotcha!
Gotcha- huh? Oh shit!
Why is this happening to me!?
Stop that, it hurts!
Already?
Is this how it all ends!?
Stop!
I'M NOT EVEN GOOD ENOUGH
FOR YOUR STOMACH!?
HOW CAN THAT BE?!!
Hey, check it out! It's a hermit crab!
I wonder where it came from...
Maybe from Nami's village?
I guess...
Or maybe he's been hitching
a ride since Usopp's village.
If he has, it's been a long trip for him.
Maybe he wants to stay and sail together with us!
DAMMIT! WHY DO THESE THINGS ALWAYS HAPPEN TO MEEE!?
Hey, did you just say something?
Me? Nothing.
Weird... maybe it was my imagination...
Hey, Luffy! Quit slackin' off!
Oh! Sorry, sorry.
I... Where am I?
GET OUT.
Who's there?
I am the mighty guardian spirit of this island.
If you don't want to die, get out!
Guardian spirit?
And you're one of those, uhhh...
Freaky things!
I'LL KICK YOUR ASS, PUNK!
WATCH YOUR MOUTH!!
You know don't you?
If you take one step into this sacred forest,
you will be cursed, and the Gods
will kill you at that very minute.
Isn't that right?
HOW THE HELL SHOULD I KNOW
YOU FLASHY IDIOT!!
WHY ARE YOU ASKING ME WHAT WILL HAPPEN?
What are these things?
They are the animals of the forest.
You better not touch them if you value your life!
Wow, these creatures are kinda interesting...
Hey! Didn't I tell you stay away from them!?
You shit! You dare to shoot me?
Crap. I missed.
Hold it right there!
What's this!?
Gotcha.
Come out!
Ow ow ow ow ow!
So, you have the power of the Devil Fruit!
And what're you gonna do about it?
People like you... er...
People like you...
You are...?
Are you a son in a box?
Yeah, My mother was too overprotective
of me, and now look what...
OH SHUT UP!
That joke is SO OLD!
Bastard, you'd better not move.
Anyone who dares to hurt these animals, will die!
Oh? So you wanna go at it with me?
I admire your courage.
But it won't be my fault when you die.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Gotcha!
Hold it right there! Idiot!
Hey! That's cheating!
Oh really? What about THIS?
What is it you would say? Bring it on!!
BARA BARA KINKYUU DASSHUTSU!
(Emergency Escape!)
OWW!
Stop right there.
Don't move!
It's a pity,
but I cannot forgive anyone...
They are this island's treasure.
Those animals are treasure?
What do you mean ''treasure''?
Treasure is money, gold, jewels, and stuff like that!
You flashy moron.
Cut the crap.
These animals are the reason you came here!
Why would someone like me care about them!?
I'm not here for sight-seeing!
You're not a poacher?
Of course not!
Until death, I will always be...
The Great Clown Pirate Buggy-sama!
Why would I care about some silly animals?
PIRATE?
You say you're a pirate?
Me too!
I was a pirate too a long time ago!
I'm so so so sorry!
So you're a pirate too, eh?
So whatcha think of my special brew?
It's the best!
It's been so long since I last had a good drink!
Well, drink as much as you like!
And hey, I'm really sorry about
what happened earlier.
I thought you were a poacher, see,
here to hunt the animals.
Oh, come on, you're apologizing too much.
It's in the past!
And besides, you're treating me to this great sake!
That's all I care about...
Treasure and sake!
I really admire that!
Man, you are one awesome pirate.
A good guy...
By the way... how did you
come to be on this island?
Ah, I just came here looking for the treasure.
What? No way!
There's TREASURE on this island?
Hold your horses.
If I'd found that treasure, I wouldn't be here now.
Ah... Oh yeah, I guess you're right.
Anyway, a lot of things happened.
I was left behind by the others, and I've
been here for about 20 years now.
20 years!?
That must've been really hard on you, huh?
Well, I don't know if I'd say that.
I still have these guys here, after all.
I'm used to it, I've become pretty happy here.
No kidding?
You find this more fun than being a pirate?
Well, being a pirate was fun.
It was good.
I still feel that treasure's worth risking your life for.
Damn straight!
Hey, you know, when I collect my crew again,
you wanna be one of my nakama?
We could use a great guy like you.
You've got the soul of a true pirate.
So, how about it?
You really mean it? You would want me?
I'm so glad you said that.
But, these animals are my nakama.
We've been together for 20 years.
Even animals have feelings.
I can't just pick up and leave them.
What? What's so funny?
You know, you just reminded me of someone else...
who asked me if I wanted to be a pirate.
He was a funny young pirate.
Hey, dont worry about it, ossan.
You're lucky we came here, even if it took 20 years.
What if it had been 30? You might be dead by now!
Straw Hat!
He was a good kid, with a big heart.
I bet if you met him, you'd like him too.
A young pirate guy like that was here, huh?
I've met some really awful kids in my day.
Assemble!
BARA BARA PARTS!
Are you talking about these?
Ack! My parts!
That's a real thief for you!
WAIT!
You're goin' flyin', Buggy!
GOMU GOMU NO...
BAZOOKA!!
And that's how I started my journey.
Just thinking about it makes
me fill with hate and rage.
Really?
That must have been hard on you.
Well, there's lots of different
kinds of kids in this world.
Anyway, tonight, let's celebrate.
A nice evening like this shouldn't
be wasted on bad feelings.
You're right.
To pirates!
And to our meeting!
KANPAI!
Hey, I'm really sorry.
Thanks for rebuilding my raft.
What? It was nothing.
So, you're really going to stay here?
Yeah. Together with my nakama.
I see.
Well, take care!
You too!
Goodbye, my friend!
Take care of yourself!
Yeah...
YOU TOO!!
FULL SAIL!
Buggy...
There are many strange sea creatures in this area...
Try to be careful.
THAT'S WHAT I FORGOT TO SAY TO HIM!
RUN, BUGGY!!
Watch out!
Run! Watch out!
What's that?
SHIIIT!!!
Hot damn...
Who is that?
Well, if it isn't a beautiful lady.
Well, looks like he's saved.
I was afraid for him.
Whatever you do, take care!!
Man, I really owe you.
I thought I was a flashy goner there!
It's no big deal.
You're Clown Pirate Buggy, aren't you?
How do you know that?
Just who are you?
I'm looking for a certain person.
You know this man, don't you?
YAA! Shitty rubber kid!
You jerk! You watch out' I'll kick
your ass one of these days!
Just you wait...!
This is the man you're looking for?
Come on. I'll make us something to eat.
I see now.
So that's why you saved me.
Exactly.
So, what do you think?
Shall we cooperate?
I think so.
If we both work towards the same goal,
we can get results faster.
Wonderful.
Then, kanpai.
Kanpai.
Sanji... gimme food...
You just ate...
have some... self-control.
You guys, shut the hell up.
How am I supposed to get any rest...?
You freakin' sleep all the time.
Help out a little, will ya?
Arguing with each other in their sleep...
They're such weird guys.
Well, I guess I should go to sleep too.
Good night.