Fixing of the cradle confirmed!
Barco Hunter stowing…
Succeeded!
WHO SUMMERS YOU BROTHEL?!
Who dares to come to encroach on my territory?!
Ah, a monkey.
It IS WHAT CA?!
It IS WHAT?!
Appearance of monsters!
Do not touch with the friends of White Beard!
Boss!
Boss!!
It is what this trick?!
It is what?! A continent?!
No idea, I want the knowledge!
I do not have anything considering! I do not see anything the whole!
It is right a dream!
A dream?! Really?!
Ouf… God thank you it is only one dream.
Thus said…
Our three friends have simply…
summer devoured alive with this wreck.
DO NOT SAY CA!
The pipes of air leave its mouth.
It is thus obvious that…
DECREE!
LUFFY AND THE OTHERS WERE EAT!!
ALL IS OF MT FAULT!
You dispatched them in the abyssals zone of Large Line!
You said that all will be well whereas you
knew any nothing and now they are…!
You are right…
Afflicted!
It is almost that… but not completely.
We would make better cut the pipes of air.
Without that, we will finish at the ocean floor.
Robin, be to you hefty man you, not true?!
Something dodo please!
I cannot.
It is too large.
Go the guy!
Everyone on the cord! Let us save the Boss!
It is the honor of the pirates of Masira which depends on it!
The Boss is always in life!
They are right!
It is the honesty of the crew which is put to the test!
Usopp!
Ouais!
Cut the pipes! Our safety passes above all!
You are démoniaque!
A DEMON!!
Hein?
What occurs?!
The night fell suddenly!
It is impossible…
It is not yet the hour.
THEN WHAT SE PASSES?!
LUFFY!
ZORO!
SANJI!
It is ill omen!
One fallen sudden night is the sign
precursor of the appearance of the Titans, Captain!
They will run our boat!
Dispatch we to save the Boss and draw us!
LUFFY!
Luffy, that goes?!
You did not die?!
Zoro! Sanji!
Weigh the anchor!
We draw from here!
This type is nut!
I am so glad to see you in life!
You are right!
Let us flee far from this tortoise!
A tortoise?
Not, there was a monkey under water!
Still one of these monstres marins!
At the beginning, he got along well with Luffy…
Normal, between macaques!
But when he saw us carrying tricks of the wreck in our bags, he became insane!
How a mad gorilla!
It is Masira, the king of the fishing out.
But it is a miracle which you have
escaped with the jaws of this tortoise!
A tortoise? But which tortoise?
Hold, the tortoise acts oddly…
It as is paralyzed with the open large mouth…
It is for that you could escape to you!
OUAAAH! It IS WHAT THIS TRICK it?!
AWAKE you!
It is this thing which swallowed
the wreck in which you were!
Hein? It makes already night?
Luffy! Spin to us a knack!
One draws from here!
PAS SI VITE!
THE GUY!
Do not believe that you can subtilize…
treasures found on the territory of
Masira-sama, and to draw you like that!
Treasures?
You found treasures?
Ouais! Full!
Ca fears…
If it starts to devastate the boat…
B-B-boss…
Behind you…
Mmh… what?
GEAAAANTS!!
I do not return from there…
These things… were too enormous to be true…
And Ben, Grand Line is right one
succession of strange phenomena…
And today…
A gigantic ship falls us above…
Then the needle of the Log Poses which points towards the sky…
A monkey mild nutter unloads and fishes out the wreck…
But then, a monstrous tortoise devours it…
The night fall abruptly…
And of the monsters hundred times more
large how of the giants appear!
I acknowledge that even me, I was cold of it in the back.
RELEASE!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
Thank you Yonda, you are our first leecher
Pfiouuu… These monsters
were really titanic…
Ouais.
I hope that they will never be re-examined.
You know, Chopper…
If I had wanted, I could have put a beating to them.
It IS TRUE?!
I already embanked ten like that of them, once.
TEN LIKE CA?!
By here, the guy.
You want that I recall you why you plunged?
All that you have
paid, it is this heap of refuse!
I do not see any index on the means of going in the sky!
There was nothing of all that in bottom. Nothing the whole!
It is the truth, Nami-san.
The ship seemed to be attacked.
Or then, there was a mutiny and the crew entretué itself.
It is precisely for that it
we was necessary information!
You include/understand?
If ever we manage to reach this celestial island,
we could undergo it well
even leaves that this crew!
More the life could save us!
These rusted swords, these old plates and this octopus do not interest me!
It is of a log book and charts which we need!
What is it that, Luffy?
An armor.
It exploded the armor!
Look at, Nami-san!
I brought back pretty shells to you!
You can put yourself them where I think!
Nami-san is so nice when it is in anger!
Stop that.
Release to him the tennis shoes.
You are furious?
Difficult to make differently.
I am surrounded finished cretins!
One is completely lost now.
Hold!
Hein?
Eternal Poses…
It is…
I subtilized it on the ship of this monkey… if.
You are only on whom I can count!
He, it is well an octopus that?!
One has only to be made stuffed pellets!
You must undergo much stress.
Jaya?
Ca must be their general headquarter.
It is there that one goes?
It is YOU which decide, cranium of sparrow!
Ok!
Cape on Jaya!
Jaya, here us are!
Nami… It is by where?
With starboard.
Chopper, helps me!
I arrive!
Jaya, ahead all!
He, wait one minute…
If one goes to Jaya…
will our Log Installation be given to zero, not?
What wants to say…
that we will not be able to go any more in the sky!
STOOOOOP! ONE DECREE JAYA!!
He, Nami!
It is what this history?!
What thus?
It is you who decided to go in Jaya.
Ah yes, it is true.
But I did not know that!
It is not my fault if you do not reflect!
The Log Poses always functioned like that!
Ah yes, it is true.
Good, your attention please!
I am the Captain, then I will decide our course!
I want to go on the celestial island!
Very well, and how?
One should perhaps ask somebody.
Yes, let us ask somebody.
Therefore, why not in Jaya?
OK! Jaya, here us are!
All that for that!
The Log Installation will spend some time to change.
Let us return in Jaya and
let us leave ahead that it is not reloaded!
Let us hope for how the chance is with us!
Ouais, one has only to do that!
It left, the guy!
Let us leave for Jaya! Country of the Meat at will!
OUAIS!
Stop fantasmer!
I wonder what resembles Jaya.
Nami-swan! Robin-chwan!
I prepared you “pellets
special with-octopus-single-with-world " lady!
Shit! It was which these guys, brothel?!
To send people in the air like that…
Captain…
Captain!
What?!
You… you are certain that it is here?
The place where the John Captain hid the treasure…
that it piled up while sowing
terror by thirst for richnesses…
The legendary cave?
Yes, I am sure.
Be careful and continue!
Listen, the treasures are always kept or protected by many traps around!
One moment of carelessness and
you are dead men!
Which kind of horrible creature will attack us?
Which person who is damned traps will make us discover the Hell?
Go, the guys! Still a beautiful day to dig a tunnel!
Yes, chief!
Oh, you are undoubtedly the new ones!
Ah, to perspire a skilled, they is marvellous, chief!
Yes chief, a man anything else needs only one pickaxe in the hand!
Ouais, a pickaxe!
And our sweat will build this tunnel in order to give the smile to all those which will cross it!
Ouais! Ouais!
And after this hard labor, we will drink one pint in a bar and…
HOW YOU DARE ME
TO MAKE WORK AND SWEAT?!
Baggy captain, we do not find the treasure of the John Captain.
Moji, moron!
Have more tact!
The Captain obviously chose the bad island!
The others do not have
to notice how it is red of shame!
WHO HAS A RED NOSE AND A LARGE BOTTOM?!
At all events, Captain…
Do we have really time for that?
What will we make?
This person who is damned Straw hat and its crew…
are already regarded as large pirates on Grand Line.
You are only one noisy imbecile. Keep the head on the shoulders!
We will let them sail.
What do you want to say?
, You listen know the witches?
Before eating the small children,
they start by fattening them!
You see?
In other words, more the crew of Straw hat goes up high…
I included/understood!
Then as soon as you get rid some, your fame is even larger!
Completely!
It is a brilliant plan!
Captain, it is necessary to celebrate that!
We will have fun the festival all the night!
There is not really what to make the clowns, the guy!
Which is the interest to work out
a plan to put Luffy at the step…
whereas you do not even know where it is?
Let us go, awakes, Alvida!
It is necessary to be burst above all!
Do Oh, you seek Luffy? I will say to you where it is.
You see?
This type will say to us where it is!
But be to you which you?!
Oh, sorry to stop your small festival.
I was simply attracted by the delicious odor of your feast.
I am called Ace.
Please, accept my excuses.
Oh, useless to make manners.
We should excuse us too us.
I asked you which you was, brothel!
I insane of knowing your name!
You unload and you underestimate me, dumb!
Captain!
Captain, this man…!
It is the Burning Fist!
Ace with the Burning Fists!
The commander of the second fleet of White Beard!
White beard!
Do Ah, you know the old man? Cool…
HE FELL ASLEEP!
NOT.
Why not?! It is an unhoped-for chance!
If one gets rid of Ace to the Burning Fists, we will become famous in one nothing time!
I AI SAY NOT!
Listen, band of imbeciles,
remember that well!
Whatever the situation, never, with large never,
one does not touch with the men of White Beard! It is clear?
White beard… This man…
This legendary man was the only one with being able to compete with the Lord of the Pirates, Roger!
To date, it is without question it
the most powerful pirate in the world!
He is the man nearest to more
large of all the treasures, One Part!
And more than all, Barbe White does not tolerate that one of its men is made kill.
Here is what a kind of man it is!
You seem to know it well.
Oh that yes…
A long ago…
Here, on Large Line… I dealt with him.
Hein? Then as that you know the old man?
HE EAST AWAKES!
Go the guy it left! Go!
And this festival then?
Heu ouais!
We was having fun the festival, it is that?
He, be rather sympathetic for you like guy, say to me!
Go, wood!
Oh! Oh! You have a lion!
Go!
Jump in this circle of fire!
Do what say you the Sir, Richie!
Groar!
Where the Boss passed?!
BOSS!!
I AM, THE GUY!
He does not seem to be here!
HE HO!!
Let us see further!
AYE, AYE SIR!
HE! RETURN!
DO NOT LEAVE!
I ask for myself… which kind of island east Jaya.
I said it to you, it is the Country
meat. Country of the Meat.
You have just invented it.
In any case, one can say that heaps of pellets were eaten.
Then stop eating some.
They are the shares of Nami-san and Robin-chan.
They said that they did not want any!
Return them to us!
Close it!
Return them to us, dumb!
Return them to us, moron!
Close it!
Return them to us!
But… is there really an island in the sky?
Up to now, we never met anything of tel.
Even if our good sense is some shaken, there is no reason not to believe in it.
It is that, the logic of this ocean.
The key to go on the celestial island…
… is on Jaya.