Aniki...
To a wound that would make an ordinary man die...
l won't give in!
Ryu!
TATSUMAKI!!
(Tornado!)
Gotta hurry... and save Luffy!
Idiot...
Sorry, this is all we can do for you right now...
l see.
I just gotta break the stone and hell be free!
This is getting interesting!
Whatever do you humans intend to do next?
PROUD, TALL WARRIORS!
DRAMATIC BATTLE OF SANJI AND USOPP
So it's the guy from Cocoyashi Village.
What useless effort...
Dammit! They've found us!
If you're trying to extend his life, what good
is it if you're going to die anyway?
I'll end it right now!
Where do you think you're going?
You... mere human!
You're really trying to challenge me underwater?
Holding your breath with all your might,
like an inferior creature would!
As you wish! Let's do it!
Gyojin Karate! Itomaki Kumite!
What now?
Your kick is only haIf as powerful underwater.
That's the limit of humans.
But my Merman Karate...
loses none of it's power down here!
On the contrary, it's twice as strong!
Gyojin Karate, Kaisoku!
Harakuda Shigeri!
Gyojin Karate...
Ka Ka Kakato Otoshi!
Kachiage Haisoku!
Hissatsu...
Joudan Bakushou!
Finished.
Air, air, air, air!
l've lost too much air!
Suffocating... can't breathe!
Where do you think you're going?
Shit, let me get by!
What amazing perseverance.
Never thought a human would have any.
It was you, wasn't it?
Who said that a man who hurts
a lady is a piece of shit?
But take a look!
Look where your mediocre chivalry has gotten you!
There's no escape for you, so you'll die by my hand.
I'll kill that sheriff, and while I'm
at it, that rubberman too.
Zoro, the long-nosed guy,
I'll massacre all of the villagers who revolted!
And of course...
That little traitor, Nami, will be no exception!
Understand?
In the end, once your smooth talk
of chivalry gets past your mouth,
Let alone Nami...
You can't protect anyone!
You may have some skill,
but...
All you really are is a puny, weak human.
Your body can't take rapid pressure change, can it?
That is to say, if I took a sudden
nosedive to the bottom...
The pressure change would make your
body explode from the inside!
Appakushi Chokakouro!
l won't ever forgive this bastard!
l can't...
Protect even a single person!?
This guy... he's not dead yet?
Well, as you wish!
We'll do it one more time!
These guys...
Use their lungs to breathe on land.
ln the water, they use gills.
That means...
He's just a talking fish!
Shall we try it a second time?
lf something blocks a fish's gills, he dies!!
Since you're a fish,
you'll suffer just like l am right now!
You...
Oi...
Don't worry, he's okay.
Really?
Half of him.
Half?
Tell you later.
But first... Get your ass outta
the water, you fish freak!
I still need to kick your small-time ass!
You still don't understand, do you?
It doesn't matter whether it's underwater or on land.
It's still the same.
You've really angered me.
I'll show you the essence of Merman Karate.
The move that blew you out of the park...
Was a Hyaku Mai Gawara Sei Ken!
But my special move is the Sen Mai Gawara Sei Ken!
The chances of you surviving are...
ZERO!!
COLLIER!
You said my chivalry was naive?
EPAULE!
That I can't protect anyone, huh?
COTELETTE!
SELLE!
POITRINE!
GIGOT!
Why you... Bastard!
You bastard!
Kyuu Koku Sei Ken!
Senmai Gawa...
MENTON SHOT!
Guess you...
don't need dessert.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
What was that?
What's happening up there?
Kuroobi...
Hachi...
In the end, they're just ''seafood salad''.
A fish taking on a cook? Not in a hundred years.
This game...
Is ours.
You bastards...
You killed so many of my beloved brethren...
One after the other...
Don't you think you've gotten a little
caught up in the moment!?
Hey, when you said Luffy's HALF
okay, what did you mean?
Well, he's not gonna die.
But if you wanna free him, I gotta
go underwater again for a bit.
And it doesn't look like this guy
plans on letting me do that.
Amazing...
Really amazing!
They've taken out two of Arlong's best men!
I couldn't take it any more...
I can't hold my breath any longer.
Gen-san, let's switch.
I'll go this time.
He looks much better.. less pale.
Yeah, he's thrown up a lot of water.
What's going on over there?
Everything's all right. Nobody died.
Speaking of which...
Until now, I've been holding it back...
I feel like I don't want to believe it, but...
This battle's rekindling my hopes again!
Chu! What a handful he was...
So damn fast.
But it only took one blast from my
'water cannon' to finish him off.
Well, time to head back.
Things should be pretty much
done back there by now.
Whew, that was a close call!
Success!
Good thing I made the 'Ketchup
Star' for a time like this.
He thinks he killed me with his 'water cannon' thing...
I should go back now.
Man, they're a horrible bunch.
They took out all the poor people in that village.
I know Nami can't change things alone...
And I really want to help her, but...
Huh?
Must be my imagination...
But I'll gladly pass on dying!
Stll, besides the ketchup,
I should try to look like I made more of an effort.
I know, maybe if I get myself dirty,
I could say, ''Oh! So sorry!
I got lost!'' or something...
Hmm, what should I say?
Maybe I should go like, ''Oh,
that jerk? He got away!''
Nah, that'll never fly, will it?
Aren't we nakama?
''Hey, don't cry, Nami.''
''We did our best!''
I'd rather die, than lose!
Or... ''Well, we each fought our hardest!''
It's a hundred times better than
a worthless piece of shit...
who'd dare hurt a lady.
Or... ''I was in a deadly situation!''
This is for my business.
I have no other choice!
Or... ''My wounds aren't that serious...''
Nami-aneki was crying!
She's risked her life.
Do we need any other reason?
For a 10-year old Nami....
Do you have any idea how difficult
that choice was to make?
WE SHALL FIGHT!!
Or... ''M-my b-battle... was...''
''That was... why...''
You ain't seen nothing yet!
WAIT RIGHT THERE YOU FISH FREAK!!
Oh?
You're not dead yet?
Chu!
Of course not!
I won't die from some stupid water cannon!
When I left Syrup Vllage, I left everything behind!
Tranqulity... Safety...
They face hardships every day,
and they laugh like they're really having fun!!
That's why I decided to go out to sea!!
I want to laugh until I cry, too!
But if I don't fight with everything I've got,
There's no way I deserve to be
on the same boat as them!
THERE'S NO WAY I CAN LAUGH WITH THEM!!
Fool!
You were better off pretending you were dead.
You must be a little slow in the head.
Chu.
Is it...
...over already?
Yeah, it is!
It's over.
Just like you are!
It's over, huh?
USOPP...
HAMMER!
USOPP WAGOMU!
(Rubberband!)
Chu?
Ah! Shit!
How did I fall for something like that!?
Why that li'l bastard...!
HISSATSU!...
- Sake? (Wine)
(Ultimate lead star!)
HISSATSU! NAMARI BOSHI!
Is this the only way you know how to fight,
you inferior creature?!
Chu!
No matter where you may hide,
I'll blow you away with my water cannon!
Being stupid or cowardly has nothing to do with it!
This fight... there's no way the manly
Usopp can run away from it!
If I lose, I die.
I'm a pirate now!
MIZU TAIHOU!!
No way!
So powerful!!
Why should I have to fight with this idiot?
He's so obvious!
I'll blow you to pieces!
Hyappatsu Mizu Deppou!
Oh no! H-how, how did he find me!?
Crap! Crap! Look, Usopp Pirate Crew!!
Kaya!! I went to sea to become a real pirate!
I'm going to fight so I can become
a brave warrior of the sea!
Those lazy days and the silly pirate games...
ARE ALL OVER!!!
What's all over?
This battle!
Wine is flammable!
HISSATSU KA EN BOSHI!!
(Ultimate Fiery Flaming Star!)
Hot, hot, hot-chu!!
Water, water, water, water, water...!
Hot, hot, hot!
Oh, wait!
Water-water-water! WATER!
USOPP...
HAMMER!!
Chu!
USOPP HAMMER!!
Bastard...!
USOPP HAMMER!
USOPP WAGOMU!
I won... I beat a merman!
You see that, loser?
I CAN DO IT!
You see that, you jerk?
Don't look down on me, dammit!
Please, breathe!
Please come back to life, or else, you'll lose...
Your nakama are...
I feel faint... was that a dream?
I'd even started to have hopes for this battle...
That shark guy, what's he doing?
No clue!
It looked like he was just throwing water around.
But then, the two of them started bleeding!
To kill humans like you,
I don't need to do it myself.
A little water is all it takes.
That's the difference between
you humans and us mermen.
Stop talking!
He's not joking...
to him, he's just playing around with water.
But it feels like a shotgun!
Is this, the power of a shark?
The most powerful among the mermen...
He's on a completely different level.
You should just give up.
Your lives aren't all that important anyway.
ARLONG!
Nami-aneki!
Nami-san!
Nami-chan!
Yo, Nami.
I was just giving some loser pirates
a demonstration of our power.
What brings you here?
I'm here to kill you.