Usopp VS Daddy the Father
Duel in full day
Do not make the idiot! Stop! You will lose your arm! Its edge is exceptional!
I take it!
Seek Luffy!
It must hide some share
here in Logue Town!
Yes!
It is not worthwhile.
I am certain that it will be shown!
The bracket! The bracket!
The last vision which the Lord of the Pirates had before dying, I want to see it!
I want to see that as quickly as possible!
But… it is where the way towards the platform?
Colonel Smoker!
It is true that this man, Luffy, are on this island?
If it as quickly as possible is not stopped…
It is not necessary.
But it is intolerable!
Stop! Do not go further,
it is the office of the Colonel of the Navy!
Yo, Smoker.
It is you, Daddy?
Pete the Gangster and the Brothers Raidy Defrauders.
Rewards for these three?
There is another with the cemetery of them.
I need your signature to touch the rewards.
Not less than one million Berrys for the four!
That delinquents…
In this city there is full with premiums on large pirates who want to leave towards Grand Line.
For easy and sure work,
it is to better concentrate on the small criminals rather than on the large ones.
The man who was most talented before of the snipers of the Navy,
starts to drive out small preys.
It is odd.
I want to risk my life never again.
If you die, your daughter where to go, isn't this will not have nowhere?
Say hello to Carol of my share.
Yes, I will inform him of hello of his Smokey Uncle.
Isn't the bargain hunter Daddy Masterson?
Yes, it was my equal formerly!
It was an elite: it was responsible for the safety of the HQ of the Navy.
Why such a man…
A cursed saber?
Interesting.
That with the air to be excellent a katana!
You make what brothel, do not surprise me like that!
What do you make here, Zoro?
And you then?
Me?
I am lost!
Y' does not have what to be to trust.
Ah, say to me!
By where one must pass to go to the platform?
I found it! It is him!
Hein?
What?
Jerk! You ace dared to sell our comrades with the Navy?
One will make you pay very expensive!
Fire!
Return at home and tell your mom to prepare you cake, fiston.
Ouahh! Cool this Ossan!
Ossan: pejorative term to designate somebody of old
This man, it is surely…
Daddy the Father.
He He He! It is with me, with me, only with me!
I have all that it is necessary for me to become a honest warrior of the sea.
Did I forget something?
Ah yes. Most important, glasses!
A tireur d'élite of 1st class must have the best glasses,
it is the base of all the bases!
Even if all my money passes there, I must find a pair of it,
it is something which my heart of gunner will never regret!
Glasses! Glasses!
These are perfect!
Yes, these is these that I want!
I will take them, grandmother!
You ace the eye to locate quality!
It is the last model of North Blue.
I had them by a group of Navy before they leave on mission.
What? You do not have money?
I do not have time to lose with the poor.
Then you do what?
Euh… it is that…
Ah yes, there!
I would like these glasses, please.
Ah! Such a nice little girl!
Yes-Yes-Yes!
You have the air very happy!
They are the only glasses of this kind in all the city.
Wait a little!
I saw them in first…
No the chance, Ossan.
It called me “Ossan”…
He! Stop!
Let us be clear on top.
I am not a “Ossan”.
Me “Onii-Sama”, included/understood calls?
Hein? What you insinuate Ossan!
Aaah! You still called me like that?
Return to me these glasses initially,
I saw them the first!
Hein?
You ace a problem with me? Hein?
If you continuous on this tone,
I will call the Navy!
Navy?
Yes. I am a friend of the Colonel of the Navy of this city.
Smokey uncle.
It is which that one?
Obviously, you did not recognize me.
The large Usopp Captain,
who destroyed the pirates of Arlong!
It was really a combat until death!
They sent 200 to me, not 300 man-fish with my cases…
But I all beat them myself
by great blows!
Thanks to that, a premium of 30 million Berrys was put on my head!
Really, 30 million?
Yes, it is that.
Dad!
“Do Dad”, why you call me like that?
Hold, it is a gift for you Papa.
Happy birthday!
Oh… Carol!
You are really an angel…
I love you Carol-chan!
Dad, I adore you too. Dad.
It is what this relation father-girl?
But you know, but you know, Ossan tried to seize some.
Hola, hola. To steal it is not well.
Not well of the whole!
One should not make fear with the others!
Me…
It is you who ace annoyed my small Carol cherished?
And you know what?
Would Oh, your head be worth 30 million Berrys?
Let us see that…
They are the new research opinions?
Yes, I have just taken them with the Office Navy.
600.000…
1.300.000…
700.000…
30 million,
Luffy with the Straw hat…
To have a first precedes also high…
Wait, kid!
What is there?
Euh… you know…
In any event, I am not a required criminal!
It was a lie, a lie!
I wanted simply to frighten him…
Euh, I believe that I must
to leave now! With the r' to see!
It is you, not?
Yes, it is true. There is no doubt,
it is well me!
But lets warn you to me…
If you oses to pose a finger on me,
my Luffy captain will be completely furious!
He alarming, is made thirsty for blood and diabolic…
Never no enemy survived after having faced it!
You you have a child, not?
The life is an important good.
I see.
It is indeed a big problem.
It is true that this man is worth 30 million Berrys,
this Luffy must be a guy out of the commun run.
Dad! You must become stronger at all costs than him
because Papa is best world!
Carol! They is good!
If Dad gains enough money to live in happiness with you, it is more than enough!
You are more expensive in my eyes than the fact of becoming best world.
Dad…
In the final analysis, this guy seems sensitive and also intimidated…
If it is the case…
Then? You know now with what a not I am dangerous!
I will not speak to him about it,
but now return to me these glasses.
Hein?
Do not worry you.
I will refund you the price…
Thus… go, go, go!
He you!
I have just offered them to Papa and now, you want that one…
Dad…
Thus say, that you would think
of a duel in public to see which is the best?
A duel?
Take that.
By “duel”,
You insinuate a face-to-face discussion?
If you gain, I will return the glasses to you.
1,2,3,4,… 30 firearms?
Not!! You would not be…
Daddy the Father?
Indeed.
A duel!
I heard spoken about a duel!
Daddy the Father was defied by somebody!
He told “to Daddy the Father”?
The most gifted bargain hunter with the gun, it is Daddy the Father.
There are still the insane ones in East Blue?
I ask for myself what a kind of imbecile would like to face somebody like him!
This face…
Courage, length-nose!
Am not afraid to lose,
one will bury you in a quiet place
and your funeral will be prepared!
How did I arrive from there there?
I am weak?
The rules are simple!
After 10 pas, one is turned over and one draws!
Hum… Of agreement.
What you insane, you?
Nami!
To defy are Daddy the Father, stupid for you or what?
Keep silent yourself… it arrived like that!
Your mouth and looks at!
A duel in only one round.
Loans?
Yes.
Ahh…
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Thin… that occurs badly for me…
I am not likely any to overcome Daddy the Father!
Six!
I will die here?
It is not true…
Seven!
The adventure has just started!
I must still find courage and
the attitude of a true man.
Eight!
Thank you and goodbye!!
Dad!
Brilliant, Dad.
Be too cool for you!
What? It is pathetic.
You call that a duel?
I thought that it would be more exciting.
What a waste of time!
I have right makes him release his gun.
Why you fled ace?
Species of coward, species of microbe…
Already, since the beginning you did not want to beat you, not truth?
I am sorry…
Forgive me!
Here is my true nature…
Even if you take my life,
that will not be useful to you with nothing.
Of agreement? Of agreement?
It is my only wish…
With… Wait!
Nami?
Ah, yes!
If it is money which you want, it will give you all that you want!
Then, I beg you, do not draw.
Save my life, please!
You…
Why you hide behind a woman?
In any event…
You make error.
Forget what I said.
It has nothing to do with all that!
If you draw on me, does not imply it then!
Usopp…
Please, I beg you.
Usopp?
You are called Usopp, it is that?
Yes.
Not possible…
Hein?
You would know a pirate of the crew of Russet-red Hair named Yasopp?
Yasopp?
It is the name of my father.
You… You already met my father?
I see… his son…
Dad?
In connection with this day… Until now,
I never spoke with somebody about this day.
But for you, it is different.
That occurred in a port as this one one day when the weather was hot…
Allons-y, Lieutenant Masterson!
A match in a round!
One!
Two!
Three!
It gained!
Yasopp gained!
How?
Its adversary was a sniper except par of the Navy.
It was an obvious victory.
It is of Yasopp very spit!
Yasopp, finish it.
Yes, y' has anything more pitiful than somebody who lost a duel like that!
Kill to me.
I lost this duel,
I must die.
Ah, it is very noble of your share.
What do you make?
It is your daughter?
Return to me that…
You are a Lieutenant of talented Marine but,
by keeping that on you, you become rather sensitive.
Do not make me morals, pirate!
You are right!
Ah, played well Yasopp!
It was nothing.
This wound proves that I am not yet rather extremely.
But your adversary was Daddy Masterson!
What enabled you to gain, it is your talent.
None among us of it would have been able…
Afflicted, chief…
Thank you to have looked at the duel in silence.
They is good.
Want you, Lieutenant?
The family?
It is not really my field.
I have a son you know, his name is Usopp,
I did not see it since years!
I weighed the anchor by leaving it whereas he was yet only one baby.
Why?
You did not like your sons?
It is not that the problem.
This flag pirates…
Jolly Roger called me!
You ace well done Yasopp!
In any case…
I did not can anything make for my son.
A father as useless as me,
like me, that is enough!
You should remain close to your daughter.
Does not leave it all alone.
Good, of course, I am a little badly placed to say that to you.
I lost the duel.
Yasopp, finish with me!
I do not want your pity!
Not thank you.
If the Navy captures a pirate, it must carry out it.
For a pirate, to kill or not depends on its mood.
Good-bye!
History of an elite of the Navy which is reconverted as an bargain hunter,
it was thus that…
Dad… Dad lost against a pirate,
and it saved your life?
You lie, hein Papa?
But it is brilliant! Your father is a brilliant type!
He beat Daddy!
Moreover, he did not forget you!
There are chances that it is crossed
during our voyage.
Usopp?
Ahh, I include/understand what you feel.
Not, it is not for that…
It is not because of that I cry!
Is it normal?
To tell did the history where you come very close to death?
To tell such a history with a coward like me?
You said that to me to give myself courage!
A history which normal people would have hidden at the bottom of them!
Even by knowing that I am if loose, you told it to me…
How my father carried out his life…
It is that?
That irritates me to be weak and loose!
Carol… Your Dad is a very large warrior.
Somebody moreover more extremely, one can always find some…
However, I ever saw as strong and nice somebody as your Dad…
I… I cannot lose the face like that!
If I do not gather all my courage,
I will be a shame for your Dad.
Daddy, gives me a chance,
I will put my life concerned this time
and I will not flee like presently!
Included/understood.
This time, it will be a true match.
Chosen the weapon with which you are more at ease.
Eh well, with that…
Let us see…
Prove to me that you are able to touch this whale.
The whale over there?
If you miss…
Ah, you will draw me a ball in full heart.
Usopp!
This time, it is about a duel where his life is risked!
Impossible…
How could you the touch with a weapon like that?
Co… As usual…
If I draw as usual, that should do it.
Yeah…
Concentrate!
It missed it!
Stop Papa!
Do not draw, Papa!
And why I would do it?
Usopp touched its target!
It is true!
It touched the crown!
Usopp!
What a talent!
It is the son of Yasopp very spit.
If you do not forget this courage,
one day,
you will be able to become like your father!
Goes on Grand Line.
Yasopp is without any doubt over there.
Daddy…
Be rather good for you, Ossan!
Oh, but it is…
That is appropriate to me. Hello.
Dad!
Carol, you do not have the right…
How can you say “hello”,
is not necessary to be too familiar!
Forgiveness, Dad…
As a girl of Dad,
I want to become a beautiful woman,
then forgives me!
You are already beautiful as you are now!
But I want to even become still and more beautiful!
After being fallen in disgrace,
he fights to protect those which he likes.
I want to become a man as courageous as Daddy.
I will become a true warrior one day
and I will be able to find myself face to face with my father!
Yes!
Sanji!
I sought you Sanji…
Since ten years!