In Spiders Coffee
The meeting of the leaders at 8 p.m.
With the kingdom of the Oases.
Three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
In a howl of sadness, this desiccated ground sinks from now on in an enormous wave of agitation.
With an aim of stopping the rebellious army, Princess Vivi wishes to meet and discuss with her Leader.
They have just left the city in ruin of Erumalu, and are on the way for the oasis of Yuba.
Eh Luffy!
It is what this thing which your brother gave you?
Bah, I do not know too much.
It is right a piece of paper.
A piece of paper?
Let see me that.
It is really right a piece of paper.
It is not a post-it or another thing.
For what that is used then?
I do not know either…
EH! DOES NOT EAT IT!
Imbecile.
Luffy, gives me your hat.
Hein? That one?
If it is also important, I will sew it on the back of the ribbon.
Oh, thank you!
Do that well!
Yes, yes.
Here it is done.
They is good, take again it.
Thank you!
Now I will not have to worry any more!
There is really nothing writing above.
Is this really important if you lose it or not?
Ace said to me to keep it with me, then I keep it.
Your confidence is ridiculous.
Leave me quiet!
All always goes for best with me.
What?
Really?
Zoro, carries me.
Everyone, once we will have passed this rock, we will be almost in Yuba.
Let us continue to advance still a little.
Ouais!
Yuba!
Ouais, Yuba.
Ah, Zoro, carry me.
Get stuffed!
Can one?
Also carry me, Zoro!
Burst!
The plan starts in two days.
Did you very arrange?
Yes, without any difficulty.
I set up 150 Billions at Nanohana.
Mr. 2 was also pointed out.
It would seem that he did not succeed in catching Mr. 3.
The Agents remaining Officers meet this evening.
Spiders Coffee, at 8 p.m.
Very well.
It is already 17:30.
They will start soon to gather.
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Merry Chri… Merry Chri…!
A little tired!
Badly with the back!
Miss Merry Christmas
And zut! It is of your fault, Mr. 4!
You are so tedious that you gave me badly to the back!
P---With---R---D---O---NR
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Are Paula, how the businesses?
It is completely empty today, not?
Place vacuum.
Pla- VI.
Pla…
P…! Isn't this?
Ca made a long time.
Welcome, Miss Merry Christmas, Mr. 4.
Paula
The Coffee was reserved for you today.
You will take Pekoe Orange.
Black tea very strong fact starting from whole sheets…
… and Mr. 4 you a tea with apple, isn't this will take?
I do not want it hot!
I it want at an ideal temperature to be able to drink it immediately!
Now, the-I gives quickly!
Give the-me!
Bring the-me!
You seem in the fine shape.
How is work?
It is always also shitting which of hab!
Of course, we are in form.
Idiot!
Idiot, id… id…
You must be right.
I excuse myself.
One, two!
Ora!
Kura!
What is it that?
You play the funny ones of songs in this coffee?
A song?
Not, it is a sonata which one hears, not a song.
One, two!
Ora!
Hein?
One, two!
Kura!
Look at your fingers with your nose!
One, two!
Kura!
Kick on the side!
One, two!
Ora!
Time…
… before our birth…
Lesson!
Eyes and…
… will mascara it!
Let us speak…
… of will mascara!
Practice each day!
It is… the ideal…
Lesson!
It is the way of the transvestite!
Yes, smile everyone!
Ah, most extremely!
Most extremely!
Oh am my way!
Hello at the assembly!
Thank you.
How I was?
You resemble an idiot.
I am not an idiot, Paula!
Why you requests?
Because I am a dancer.
I must have a poulpa.
A “poulpa”?
Stop joking!
A perfect octopus.
That goes from oneself!
Eh, the guy.
You all can set out again now.
Yes!
Do not forget to practice the dance!
One, two!
My large! The old woman!
You are already there?
You will keep silent yourself, brothel!?
Ca goes directly in my back, then stops with your cries!
Ah! It is true, it is true!
It even appears that the duet of Mr. 1
will come this time, hein?
I never met them…
Thus I am, how could I say…
I await them impatiently!
Ah…
The night…
It is so dark…
It is almost the hour, 20 hours.
I am bored!
I am bored so much that I think that I will turn!
I am turning!
ME!
Ca only hurts me to look at you then stops that.
What is there, the old woman?
You want a piece of it!?
If you think that you can have me!
Wait!
Please, you calm both.
Did qu qu What arrive to you, the guy!?
Why did you pass through the wall?
N- Not… It is him…!
What?
You know them?
They had an odd behavior outside in the desert.
What?
It is not as if they were about to die.
You seem rather close.
Tattooing, an old way of writing “1”
But from the relations of no importance to only will harm you.
They are my men!
Stop, Mr. 2!
What is it that?
He passed easily through the wall!
Not… Did it break the wall?
You thus chose to die.
Wait.
I must stop you, Mr. 1.
Remain apart from that, Miss Doubles Finger.
I will kill it.
Really!
Stop! Let to me go there, the large one!
Mr. 2, do you want to calm you well?
Ah, will you leave, at the end!?
Stop that now!
It is 8 p.m.
All the indicated Agents are joined together.
And an order was delivered in Spiders Café.
We must travel towards the City of the Dreams, Rainbase.
The man that we call Boss,
and we never saw the face…
… awaits us over there.
They should leave for Rainbase about now.
I sent Banchi to escort them.
They should arrive a little later during the night.
Who could have thought that you were Miss Double Finger…
Miss Doubles Finger
I do not remember to have said that I was not it.
Did one find substitutes for the Billions which were killed in Nanohana?
The substitutes are already in place.
I sent Erimaki to deliver the new orders with the Billions.
Well.
All is well.
Ah, over there.
I saw something shining.
Do we Somme in Yuba?
There is so much sand which flies that I cannot say to you.
Which is this sound…?
There is something which bell here!
A tempête de sable!
Yuba is devastated by a tempête de sable!
Oh not…
They is rather bad…
This place is hardly worth better than the town of Erumalu.
Where is water?
It is not supposed being an oasis, Vivi-Chan?
The sand level climbed…
The oasis was absorbed…
You, isn't this is travellers?
You must be tired by your voyage through the desert.
I am sorry. It seems that this city is a little bit dry for the moment.
But I think that you will be able nevertheless to put back you a little before setting out again.
If you seek inns, there is full.
After all, it is thanks to that we are known.
Excuse me…
We intended to say that the rebellious army used this city as bases…
What do you have to see with the rebellious army!?
Me known as step which you want to join them!
He! He! Qu What…?
What are you making?
You could hurt us!
Stop that!
Stop!
These insane already left.
What do you say!?
It is not true!
You the tempête de sable which has just blown, isn't this saw?
It is not the first.
These three long years of dryness made assemble the level of sand.
And the tempêtes de sable did not stop devastating this city.
Absorbed gradually, the large oasis of the past is now in the state where see it to you.
Without the trade of the city to help them, the prolonged war of the rebellious army could not continue.
They moved towards Katorea.
Katorea?
Where is it, Vivi?
Is Katorea close to us?
It is the oasis very close to Nanohana.
Katorea!? It is the city where I met Matsuge!
“When you saved me…”
Matsuge says that it supplied the rebels of the town of Katorea.
Why you did not say it to us, dumb of camel!?
I you emmerde…
Do not say “Bwwaa” like that, filth of camel.
Thus we made all this way for nothing?
Vivi…
You have just called it “Vivi”…
Ossan = Large father
He, Ossan!
VIVI IS NOT a PRINCESS OR a TRICK IN the KIND!
DO NOT SAY TO HIM, IMBECILE!
Es you Vivi-Chan?
It is you?
You are still in life.
I am so content!
It is me.
Don't you recognize me?
I can include/understand…
I lost a little weight…
Louse-Ojisan…
Yes.
It is that.
Not…
So long, Vivi-Chan.
We will not see we during a small moment.
Once the city will be finished, come to visit us!
Yes! Louse-Ojisan!
Yuba will make this country prosperous, it is sure.
It is sure…
Louse… Ojisan?
Listen to me, Vivi-Chan.
I rely on the King.
He is not the kind of anybody who could betray his country.
Isn't this?
This rebellion is ridiculous…!
These imbeciles…
It has not rained for three years. And then?
I rely on the King.
And a large part of the country too.
Many times…
Many times, I tried to stop them.
But no matter what I say, it was always in vain.
This rebellion will not cease.
Their force already reached his limit.
They intend all to stop with their last attack.
They are with end.
They intend to die!
Please… Vivi-Chan!
Stop these imbeciles, please!
Sit of the rebellion
Where is the Leader?
Inside.
Louse-Ojisan.
Do not worry you.
Vivi-Chan…
I will stop the rebellion.
Thank you!
So long, Vivi-Chan.
We will not see we during a small moment.
Once the city will be finished, come to visit us!
Yes! Louse-Ojisan!
We will create an incredible city and will help the country to become prosperous!
So long, Vivi!
You will become a large Princess.
Yes!
Kohza.
We received contacts of our forces of the other cities.
It is time for us to move.
Yes.
The problem is that we always miss arm.
No importance, we have the choice, we must act.
This country…
We go…
… to protect it.