For the sake of defeating this man!
THREE SWORDS SECRET TECHNIQUE!
Don't regret it after you die!
THREE THOUSAND REALMS!
ZORO!!!
-THE EMERGE OF THE SUPERB KICKING SKILL!
-SANJI VS THE TRON WALL PEARL.
Ha!! They wanna fight too!
This is so exciting!
Old man, let's make a deal!
If I kick 'em out,
I won't need to work here anymore, ok?
It's all that I could wish for.
If I really let you work here for a year,
This restaurant would cease to exist.
Great!
Becoming the Pirate King. Are
you serious about that?
Yeah, of course!
I WILL become the Pirate King!
I see a lot of people who talk beyond their strength.
But I rarely see someone who says it so confidently.
I heard that you were once a very strong pirate.
You also wanted to become the Pirate King, right?
I have forgotten about the past.
Right now, I'm the Head Chef of this restaurant.
This is enough.
Men!!!
As long as we have that ship, we don't
need to fear the Grand Line anymore!
This is better than disguising as a marine ship,
Or giving up by waving a white flag.
That ship will make it easier to get
near the enemy and make a raid!
It's perfect for carrying out deceptive tactics.
After looking at that ship...
No one will ever imagine that it's full of pirates!
But... but Don...
Even thoug we can go to the Grand Line...
What will happen if we meet someone
like Hawk Eyes Mihawk again?
What are you still afraid of?!
No... nothing...
Do you think that a normal person
can split a ship in one stroke?
That is the power of the devil's fruit.
According to legend, there are lots of people in the
Grand Line who possess the power of the devil fruit.
Like Mihawk, who must have used a
special power to cut the ship apart.
That straw hat guy won't be anything special
once he enters the Grand Line.
However, Red Leg Zeff has been
there for a whole year.
I can only guess that Zeff has used some kind
of strategy to confront those monsters.
A strategy that he should have written
down in that Journal he possesses.
Also, information about One Piece might be included.
I see! You're so great, Don Krieg!
With that ship and the Journal, we will have
the opportunity to get One Piece!
Do you understand now, men?
Let's go and steal the ship!
That ship belongs to us!
We absolutely can't give it to them!
No matter the cost!
How do you move this?
Hurry up!
The restaurant will become a battlefield...
I was thinking about a restaurant on the sea...
I can survive and leave here, I'll bet the
rest of my life on a huge restaurant.
I'll bet the rest of my life on a huge restaurant.
Go to the control room and open the 'Fin'.
Eh! That...? Open the 'Fin'...
We're gonna give the enemy a place to fight?
Who cares?
We can't let the inner part of the
restaurant become a battlefield.
If we fight inside, The old fart'll never shut up.
Did you say something, you little shit?
Yeah, I said you never shut up!
Go.
They're finally here! Here they come!
And here I go!
GOMU GOMU NO ROCKET!!!
That guy is flying here!?
And...
GOMU GOMU NO SCYTHE!!!
Way to go! Waiter boy!
What... what the hell is he!?
In the Grand Line, there are many
of these kinds of people...
Sanji.
Watch carefully how he fights.
Watch him until the battle finishes.
They gave you food to eat, but
instead you attacked them!
You don't even know how to be grateful!
I'll send you to the sky!
You've chosen to fight on the sea
where there is nowhere to stand.
I know people who possess the power
of the devil fruit are afraid of the sea.
Hammer boy.
But I can stretch instead!
Sanji!
The 'Fin' is going to open!
What is this!
From the sea...
A platform just appeared outta nowhere!
Wow! That's so cool!!!
Why don't we fight to our hearts content, pirates?
Oh So I see
The restaurant won't be harmed.
How convienient for us since we're going to take it.
Now I want this ship even more.
Don't you ever think about having this restaurant!
Yeah! Don't underestimate us!
We are fighting cooks!
Let's go!
Baratie's sea weapon 'Sabagashira #1'
Those who are afraid to die,
grab your shoes and run!
What is that?
Cool!!! I want one too!
Pedal faster!!
I'm trying to!
Fire!!!
It's going to sink!
Good! Great!
Patty, Carne! Finish them!
It's not bad.
Don't look at the other side! Target them directly!
Krieg! Take this!
I'll show you the power of Baratie Restaurant's sea Weapon!!
What happened?
Did it hit something!?
It doesn't move!
I am Don Krieg!
The man who will conquer the world's sea!
I've told you before that I'll be the one to do that.
I don't have time to play these games!
What strength is this?!
It's flying over here!!!
The restaurant is going to be destroyed!
Sanji!
Leg...
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
What a kick!
He just kicked away that strange ship thing!
Was that kick technique...
It appeared! Sanji's kick!
Not bad!
Sanji! You bastard!
You tryin' to kill your own people!?
Yeah.
Whaddya mean 'Yeah'?! I'll
cook you like an octopus!
You nearly lost us a powerful weapon!
You Italian Spaghetti!
This is no time for babbling! Everyone...
Let's go!
Even though you carry weapons,
cooks will always be cooks.
There's a large difference compared to us!
Go do your cooking in some
kitchen on the mainland!
Hey, why are you losing so easily?!
Is that what you call fighting cooks?!
They are strong, completely different
than the pirates we've fought before!
Don't compare us with those useless pirates!
We are Krieg's Pirates, the king of East Blue!
Announce it!
Tell everybody that this ship
belongs to the Krieg Pirates!
Forget it!
You won't step one foot inside here.
Right!
We've been cooks for more than ten years
And we've been in 300 restaurants.
During those days, We'd be fired
every time we started a fight.
Then finally, we arrived at this place!
Is anyone here?
Is Red Leg Zeff's Restaurant here?
Is it true that damned cooks are welcome?
Yeah, it's true.
It doesn't matter if they're evil or
if they're an escaped criminal.
Whenever someone comes here hungry,
I'll let them be full.
Both of you are ready for this?
Aye !
How can you serve this disgusting
soup to our customers?!
Why did you hit me?!
This represents my determination Don't complain!
Here we can fight and cook as much as we want.
There's isn't another great restaurant for us like this!
That's right. Understand, Krieg?
Every day preparing meals is like a battle.
These guys are nothing compared to those days!
Right!
Let's fight!
Protect the restaurant!
Protect the Owner!
What is...
What are you doing?
Who is he?
Iron Wall! Also known as Krieg Pirate's
Invincible Iron Wall Shield Man.
It is I, Pearl san!
Pearl!
Patty, Carne are you OK?
How could they be OK?!
They were defeated by my killing
punch, 'Pearl's Present'.
Great! Great!
This knife's not bad. I'll take it.
Let it go, give it to me!
Leave it!
You bastard, leave it!
He really knows how to kick!
I'm definately interested in him...
A knife is the soul of a cook.
An outsider doesn't deserve to touch a cook's knife.
Sanji...
Hold onto it and lay there.
I'll finish these guys off.
We won't be defeated by a bunch of useless cooks!
What do you mean by useless cooks?!
I'll gut you like a fish!
Are you so arrogant that you only kick them?
Is this your principle?
A cook's hands are his life.
He cannot injure them in battle.
So I'll finish you with these feet.
Finish me?
Impossible.
In my last sixty one battles, I have won
them all COMPLETELY unharmed.
I have never even spilled a single
drop of blood in a battle.
Not a single drop.
This justifies how strong I am.
I'm the strongest of the strongest!
I'm strong, huh?
Is he joking? It's not very funny!
Hey, straw hat guy!
If you look somewhere else, you'll get hurt!
Even the Marine's cannons can't resist me.
No attacks can hurt me.
He scared me!
I nearly fell into the sea...
Oh no...
Oh no, blood!
Pearl, everything is alright!
It's only a little nose bleed!
Not an injury caused by the battle!
Pearl, don't worry about it!
What happened?
This this this this is dangerous!
He looks strange, what happened to him?
Something about the nose bleeding?
Stop it, Pearl!
Don't get mad over a nose bleed!
What the hell is he doing?
BODILY HARM! BODILY HARM! BODILY HARM! ! !
Stop it, shit!
When Pearl gets threatened, he sets himself on fire!
What did you say?
FIRE PEARL!
Special favor!!
Ah! It's hot!
Pearl! ! Don't be like this!
Hey, you guys...
With these shields of fire, I'm indestructible!!!
Idiot!
Are you planning to burn the ship
that we are going to steal?
Hot, hot, hot!
Shit.
Damn it!
We can't jump into the sea with this fire!
Oh no! The restaurant will be burned!
He really wants to burn this restaurant.
Burn! Burn!
Bastard!
Stupid! You're gonna get fried! !
Sanji!
Don't you dare burn this restaurant!
How come he's so impudent!
Isn't he afraid of becoming a fire ball?
He even attacks Fire Pearl, someone
who is even feared by beasts!
Baka.
If I'm afraid of fire, then how
can I call myself a cook?
Argh! What an annoying guy.
Get this!
That hurt!
Pearl's Iron Wall was broken!?
What kind of cook is he? This isn't good!
Damn! Damn! Damn it!
Fire! Fire!
Fire Pearl keeps on burning!
The restaurant is going to be set on fire!!
If those fire balls get into the kitchen,
then the restaurant is finished!!
Owner! Run away!
Owner!!
My Fire Pearl...
This is nothing.
He blew out the fire with the wind of his kick!?
How can that be!?
Is it that Red Leg Zeff still has his skills?
The old man is strong!
If that's how it is, then I'll sink you and your 'fin'
into the sea before the fire burns the restaurant!
Sanji, be careful!
Oh no! He's surrounded by fire!
Hot! Hot!
The waiter boy!
GOMU GOMU NO BAAZOKA!!!
He shot back that spkiked ball!?
Pearl is defeated!
Pearl san!!
What was he doing?
This guy is stupid!
Every single time,
I have to do it by myself in the end!
This time you can end it, right?
Yeah! Shoot him!
The Red Leg Chef!
You only need to kill him and the restaurant is ours!!