The famous hunter of pirates!
The wandering bretor, Zoro
One will drink all the alcohol of this bar!
Oi! Billy!
How do you make to drink as much?
What do I know some?
Yosaku (a few years ago)
This guy… One offers 5.000.000 berrys for his head.
Johnny (a few years ago)
5.000.000 of berrys?
What do you say some?
It is left?
Oi, Johnny…
One cannot continue to run afterwards of the guy unimportant all the time.
The bargain hunters must show their courage and seek the large catches!
But if one tries to catch it, one is likely to remain there.
I drop the 5.000.000 from berrys.
Give me to eat.
You ace of the money?
Not yet.
But…
I will have some when I collect the premium for this guy behind me.
What do you tell?
Before you me sizes,
I will have reduced to you in crumbs!
Do not tire me too much.
I am too hungry.
Answer me!
Does Y' have a premium on your head?
Ouais! Listen to that!
My head is worth 5.000.000 of berrys.
Good Ah?
Ca should be enough.
What?
Here your money.
Give me to eat now.
O-Oui, Me sior! Immediately!
This guy, it is good.
I do not see it in the research opinions.
If it were an bargain hunter, people would have recognized it…
You believe that could be celebrates it hunter of pirates?
I intended to say that it is very strong…
Not, the hunter of pirates uses three katana.
And one of them is Meitou with a white sleeve.
Moreover, it is said that this guy is a demon which would have taken the shape of a man.
He surely does not resemble that.
In this case…
One cannot leave it, after it took our target!
Oi, Johnny!
Oi oi, Nii-san…
If are to you an bargain hunter, I will demandrai you to follow our rules.
One does not want to cause problems with the bar,
Then it was waited until it left to catch it.
One had seen this guy the first.
Oi! Oi!
You did not hear me!?
There are rules between bargain hunters!
Eye of Falcon.
You know Mihawk Oeil of Falcon?
You want to say Mihawk Shichibukai?
[Shichibukai = Captain Corsair]
I travel to beat it and become the largest bretor of the world.
Times, I need a premium to eat.
But I am not an bargain hunter.
The largest bretor of the world?
Hear you that, my pal!
It is impossible! You ace not a chance!
You dreams, it is all!
I decided it when I was kid.
It does not matter what the others say.
Even if it is your dream of childhood…
It is right…
I did not know that it was with you.
Afflicted!
Bring back it to the Navy.
The premium is with you.
V-Vraiment?
But do not forget to pay my note here.
There was the jackpot!
5.000.000 of berrys!
Now, one can put the job on side for some time without dying of hunger.
Oi! What doesn't go?
Do not be content for you?
He…
Why did you become bargain hunter?
Hein? Why?
It is not obvious?
It is to eat!
I was born in a village from countryside.
Gangsters always came to plunder it.
But then,
A group of bargain hunters continued them.
I wished to become like the bargain hunter
who defied these gangsters valiantly.
Now, I am there thanks to these ambitions.
“Perhaps a day I will be able to overcome these dirty rat just like him.”
It is what I said myself.
And there, a few years later, I decided to become bargain hunter.
In fact, I always wanted the being too.
When I heard what this “better world” said,
that made me look at behind and recall these days.
Oh! What is what you do to me there?
Ca does not resemble itself.
Oh, your mouth!
What occurs?
What doesn't go?
It occurred something?
Gangsters!
The band with Dick attacks the stores at the end of the city!
Dick the Gangster?
I have it.
Whore! 10.000.000 of berrys for this scélérat!
Go the guy…
Plunder at will!
Ouais!!
There is to take much here!
One was not mistaken today.
It is them.
Does Oi, what one make?
They all will take!
One cannot undertake these gangsters!
If it take your life, not average to take it again!
Whore…
Well, with the following.
Empty all!
Ouais!
What do these idiots of villager make there?
It is right a band of yellowbellies!
They do not have the notch to be opposed to me!
Or then, they are just there to look at.
Robber or stolen.
Nowadays, be to you one or the other.
To be weak is a crime in oneself.
Only an idiot tries to be opposed to more extremely!
There is an idiot here?
R-Rends our food!
Everyone worked hard to have it!
One needs some for ourself!
Harry!
Apparently, you have at least notch.
Shit!
Harry! Not!
You ace no chance!
Harry!
One will help it!
Does not go there, partner.
If it is attacked, one will be made kill.
It is not that.
This kid…
He is like me at the time!
before I do not become egoistic.
When I was only one impressionable kid!
Oi! JOHNNY!
What is that you want, good-for-nothings?
Who are you?
We are the famous bargain hunters!
What?
Then you are bargain hunters.
And I am your target?
You, imprudent good-for-nothings, you type me on the nerves.
What?
If it is money which you want, I will spin you from there so that you break.
As long as you do not disturb me.
One does not want any!
Today one feels like dispensers of justice to change!
Hein? Johnny.
Dispensers of justice?
Oi!
Partner.
Do you want to help me to be a man?
Johnny?
Johnny? You…
Very well.
Now, there is no more good or of evil!
The law of the strongest!
There is only that!
One is serious!
Brothel!
One nevertheless delivered a type which is worth 5.000.000 of berrys to the Navy this morning?
Navy?
Billy…
YOU SUMMERS THOSE WHICH TOOK MY LITTLE BROTHER!?
WHAT!!
The katana that I left is ready?
Yes!
Very good work!
Ca was not easy.
You are too hard with this beautiful katana.
An ordinary katana would have had the same destiny as the two others katanas that you brought.
I see.
I will pay more attention.
I will become stronger… for it!!
Until my name reaches the skies…
I will become stronger!!
I will become the largest bretor of the world!
Thank you to have repaired it!
I would like to pay you for work,
But there, I am ruined.
Forget that.
They are not the every day that such a wonder is seen.
It was a true pleasure.
This old gross sword does not even make the weight.
Oi, Oi, wait. You joke?
How did you do that?
With this pace, you will break each blade which you will touch!
Shit, I broke another of them…
Afflicted, I promise to pay you.
Dick the Whale of the Mountains
It is a gangster who fights with a giant firearm. There is a premium of 10.000.000 berrys for its head.
Gangster?
Precedes?
Whore!!
It is nutcase!
It are not even able to touch it
What arrives to you, good-for-nothings?
You really had my little brother?
It was only delivered. It is someone else who overcame it.
What do you say CA?
Of what you do praise yourself?
I said myself well that you were weak.
Your mouth!!
Well.
You do not know when it is necessary to leave!
Stopped He!!
Still you.
I saw you enough!
Chief!
One put the spoils in the cart.
Well!
I believe that it is the moment to leave.
These good-for-nothings make me waste my time.
Wait!
Wait here, criminal!
One avoided risking our life vis-a-vis hundreds of sought criminals, but…
to let you flee in front of our eyes…
would be an unbearable humiliation!
Do not even test.
You do not have anything to gain there.
It is perhaps not what an bargain hunter should do…
But…
Times it are necessary to know to fight until death!
You are insane truths.
You knew it since the beginning!
I suppose that yes.
Go the guy, finish them!
Ouais!!
Let to me go there!
It fight because of me!
If you will fight…
Reflected!
Think so that YOU can make.
Which pity, they are completely useless.
Their faces is completely marked by the blows.
It is the moment to finish some.
You to crush did not bring the least benefit to me.
I suppose that it was the destiny.
You were not likely to fall on me.
I will kill you together, are not sad.
Good then!
Go!
It is not enough?
The combat is finished.
You?
Since this morning.
Afflicted, but I can take your target once again?
I need money.
Ouais.
OK!
This man…
A katana with a white sleeve
I will borrow your sabers too.
Of agreement, but…
what you go…
Three katanas?
CA cannot…!
The hunter of pirates! Roronoa Zoro!!
Then here the famous hunter of pirates?
Now I do what?
I found my forces.
But if I do too much of it, my katana will break.
I should not act imprudently.
I must be able to call upon all the force of each one of my katanas.
Roronoa Zoro!
Even by using three katanas,
you do not think all of overcoming us at the same time?
“To use” three katanas…
and to practice the “Santouryuu”, it is not the same thing.
[Santouryuu:Style to the three katanas]
Santouryuu?
I would like to see that.
All on him!!
Whoa! It all had them!!
It is incredible!
Caution!
COOL!
Great hit…
I said to you never to approach me.
You will catch cold like that.
Those which catch cold have the weak heart.
Then, somebody will have heard the rumors on Zoro, the hunter of pirates.
Do not call me hunter of pirates.
Then which gave you a so pretty name?
Who knows? Ca has nothing to do with me.
Shit, of water!
ONI GIRI
[Cut of the demon]
It is… Santouryuu…
Yosh, they are not broken.
Thank you for your assistance.
Roronoa Zoro!
Your style of combat is adored.
One would like to devote us to you.
The children who cry dry their tears as soon as they hear our name.
The bargain hunters who flee the limit between the life and death…
Yosaku and Johnny…
If that pleases to you!
Aniki!
[Aniki:My brother]
www.rival-spirits.com
http://www.zento.fr
www.saiyajin-team.com
www.kyubi-wolf.net
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/rival-spirits
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/zento
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/saiyajin
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/Kyubi-Wolf
CYB3RFR34K-ISO