Divine Plugging Protection
Technique with 2 sabers
Vagueness of the Falcon
Technique of the fist
Surpuissant
9 with hot blood
Beats without fear
Dance with the tempting perfume
Drive with the Home-Run beats
Explosive Santoryu!
Zoro VS Baroque Works!
Welcome on Large Line!
Welcome in our city!
The city of the celebration… Whiskey Peak!
It is really delicious.
Which chochotte.
I do not feel well.
There is about a hundred hunters of premium here.
I will deal with you,
Works baroque.
Was Oh, it supposed being a secrecy?
Since you know our small secrecy, we thus will have to eliminate you.
This night still…
We will add a new tomb stone on the Rock-Cacti.
Kill it!!!
It… disappeared!
It left!
Where it slipped by?
Well…
One goes there?
Dumb, you insane of us!
Fire!!
Imbeciles!
They were entretués.
It still disappeared.
You move!
It is only one poor swashbuckler!
A small question…
A new tomb stone, that will be enough you believe?
Here it is!
Here!
Bandage idiots!
You want also to draw me above?
Stop!
Where it still left this type?
It was a light machine gun its trick?
It failed well to have me…
One would say well
that we will owe us
in occupying ourselves.
He believes himself able to beat us
with him all alone?
He however said to know Baroque Works.
He, nice, thus approaches a little.
Song with the glory of Usopp N°721…
It left!
Then this so accessible city, Whiskey Peak, are a true den of hunters of premium…
I was sure!
Where is it?
Find it quickly!
My new toys which I had in Logue Town:
Yubashiri, Sandai Kitetsu…
Here is the occasion to test you both.
One goes défouler a little on these types.
I found it!
Burst!!
Shit!
Let us start with… Yubashiri!
It is light.
A good katana.
It was found! By here!
Do not move!
Found, hein?
It goes up on the roofs.
Take that!
I was hot.
Be stopped to you!
Monday miss!
It was good wine.
Which waste…
What does that want to say?
Which terrible desire of blood,
Sandai Kitetsu!
Meitô is supposed to slice only when its Master orders it.
You have me the quite capricious air.
It is that to have a cursed blade?
Oh, God, grant to us your divine protection.
Have pity.
God, grants to us your divine protection and saves us!
The blow of the innocent ones,
it goes only with nice people.
I struck you with the dish of the sword,
be grateful.
It continues to go up!
Encircle it!!
It is there!
Stop it! Encircle it!
Me above was walked?
Gente rams, would you grant this dance to me?
It is all that they have like treasures?
In here is a den of hunters of premium…
Whiskey Peak is rather a den of mown.
It cannot hide any more!
The scale is falling!
It comes towards us!
Fire!!
Made blunder, I bored a hole here.
Outch! It failed to have me!
Do not play finest.
Nobody can compete with my force.
It is the end for you.
Which loss D… My my maaa.
Which waste of time.
But it is finished, one would say.
“The end”.
What?
Semi… Monday miss!
And Ben then, the frimeuse one?
You did not want to measure you with me?
One continues, Baroque Works?
A baston, it is not fun.
Semi… Did Miss Monday lose against him in a épreuve de force?
It is not possible…
I included/understood!
The Navy had to be mistaken on the research opinion!
I see.
Is very explained then.
If it is him which is worth 30 million Berrys,
then it is normal.
It is him the true Captain.
It is that.
That astonished me that this buffoon has a premium of 30 million on his head.
When well even, which humiliation
to be beaten by a swashbuckler alone.
The Boss entrusted this city to us,
we of it are responsible.
It is finally in our turn to play.
You know it perhaps already…
With Works Baroque, plus the number is low,
more the level of the member is high.
Us three:Mr. 9,
Mr. 8
and Wednesday Miss,
sums of the agents to a figure.
What wants to say that all those that you beat up to now
are well loins behind us.
Which is the interest to praise itself right in the middle of a combat?
It is strongest which will gain.
It is as simple as that.
With the attack, Wednesday Miss!
Ok, Mr. 9!
Come here, Karoo!
I said to you “come here”, not “raises your wing”!!
One will show him your super speed faster than that of the leopard!
Who said to you “slept”?
It is what this brothel?
You believe that you can let yourself distract?
Let us see seeing as you manage my talents of Acro-beater!
These beaters are out of tempered steel!
Attention not to break your sabers!
What is there?
Be paralyzed to you by the fear?
Then it is that, your talents of Acro-beater?
Since you hold to with it as much as that, here they are!
Eh well, I hope that it was not the best.
The best?
It is me!
Prepare, Mr. Bushido!
Come… Leave yourself enivrer by the soft fragrance of my perfume…
Nice fellow.
The coup de grâce…
Ahead, Karoo!
You exceeded it!!!
This combat starts to become embarrassing.
It slipped by this hole.
It is useless.
You will taste with the true terror!
This machine-gun is a true wound.
I do not see how I will approach him.
How did you dare to do that to me??
You will pay it to me!
Fell to you all alone.
You ace an arm in less, now!
A steel chain…
You had it.
Go ahead.
Kill it, Mr. 8!
You cannot escape any more.
Well, does not move any more.
With the least suspect gesture, your invaluable friend leaves the life there.
Perfect, Wednesday Miss!
Now it is impossible for him to flee
or to counter-attack!
This moron could at least awake when it is taken as an hostage.
Armament of the guns!
Guns avoided to draw!
What?
This type is a machine of war or what?
Luffy, I need your belly!
What?
Well! It is finished!
Finally. It is one night calm and quiet.
Hein? What do I card-index outside?
Such an amount of worse, with the dodo.
Incredible. It beat the 4 agents.
They however had a number lower than 12!
But, by where one flees?
One of fout!
Planquons us until they leave the island.
Unluckies!
At… Wait!
One did not flee… One…
Please.
Known as nothing with the Boss!
Wait!
This city is well agitated
whereas one is still in middle of the night.
Which wound that one ordered to us to come here in first line.
I cannot rot here.
I have an important mission to fill!
You are really pathetic.
You to make beat by a poor wretch swashbuckler.
Mr. 5!
Valentine miss!
You card-index yourselves, it is to us that?
You construct now the ditch which separates us.
You came here to make fun you of us?
Yes, amongst other things.
Of course, we also we have a mission to achieve.
Thank you.
Thanks to your assistance,
one will regulate his account to him.
It is true.
Please, you of him occupy!
You foutez yourselves us?
You believe that one is there in reinforcement?
You believe that one came until this part of Large Line to help you?
How?
Then, which is your mission?
With my opinion, you know it already.
The Boss sent bus of the criminals here to us hide in this city.
The exact words of the Boss are:
Somebody bored my secrecy.
Obviously, I do not know this secrecy.
But the directive first of our organization is “discretion”.
Consequently, we do not tolerate any investigation on the identity of our members.
And if somebody were to learn the secrecy from the Boss,
it is obvious that this somebody should be eliminated.
Therefore, we made an investigation to discover which could have bored the secrecy of the Boss.
The result was surprising!
We discovered that important members of a kingdom had infiltrated Baroque Works!
Of a kingdom?
Atten… Wait!
I in vain carry a crown, I am not really king!
It is to give me a style!
We did not speak about you!
The spies are not other than people having disappeared from the kingdom of Arabasta.
We are discovered!
We are rotten…
Burst!!!
I will not let to you touch the Princess!
On my name of Captain of the Royal Guard of Arabasta, I will prevent you!
Igaram-Kun!
The spies are:the Captain of the Royal Guard of Arabasta, Igaram,
and the Princess Nefertari Vivi.
By order of the Boss of Works Baroque,
you must be eliminated.
Eh well…
And Luffy which is still in bottom…