Cherry trees of Hiluluk!
The miracle of the mountains of Drum
I will make flower of the cherry trees here.
If I can conclude my research, this country will be saved!
As a doctor, I will cure this country!
You do not want rather to say to destroy it?
It is a covered with snow island, it makes cold all the year.
Never no cherry tree will be able to flower here.
They will flower!
I was only one dead loss despaired at the edge of the pit.
However, when I saw these cherry trees, I took again taste with the life.
I felt completely transformed…
Ca wants to say that any man in this world can be saved!
There is not a disease in the world which doesnot can be neat!
This flag with the tête de mort enabled me to face all the diseases!
Because you see, it is the symbol of a will which defies the impossible one!
By holding up this flag, I will fight like a pirate!
Chopper, you should take the sea one of these days.
You will realize that your concern is really unimportant!
Doctor…
I…
Found!
He! Wait, wait!
Join us!
Are you well, Dalton-San?
Yes, that goes.
I lost consciousness a few seconds.
I have right need for a little rest.
He, you others.
D- Doctor Kureha!
Does Ca go, the snotty-nosed kid?
Bring the casualties to the infirmary.
You are this species of old witch of the other time!
And do not forget anybody!
Yes!
There are not the time of trainailler.
Unless you want to undergo the same fate only this type.
Nami-San, you should perhaps remain time here that you would be completely restored.
Keep silent yourself!
If we do not leave now, it will be necessary to wait two days before being able to put the course on Arabasta!
Do you want to see Vivi suffering even more?
Stop feeling sorry for you…
… and turns over immediately in your room!!!
I am Usopp! The Usopp captain!
As I thought it, it worsened its state.
It is what arrives when one wants to make some too much.
Well, now…
Dalton. Where is the key of the arms manufacture of the castle?
You know it, not true?
The key of arms manufacture? What do you want to make some?
What I want to do, that does not look at you.
Wapol always kept this key on him.
And in this case, it was dispatched in the airs with him.
What? Are you serious?
Ca will pose a problem…
Doctorine…
What would you say to look after our crew free?
And so could you let me start from continuation?
I think that you know already the answer.
The price to be paid, it is all the gold and the cargo of your boat.
And you must remain here for at least two days more.
Nami-San, it rightly!
You must let it deal with you!
I am well.
I am not with the article of death.
There is not the question!
You this key to open arms manufacture, isn't this needs?
How you had this key?!
Is this really the key?
What does that want to say?
I stole it.
You have really base to make me blackmail.
You are really only one small chieuse.
Well.
I will not ask for any payment for your care.
But it is all.
As a doctor, I cannot reach your second request.
He, wait a little!
In this case, give again to me the key!
Return the-me!
Listen a little, salts gamine!
I must go away one moment to regulate some businesses.
And nobody is assembling the guard.
There is a coat in the convenient one at the bottom of the room.
Moreover, I finished operating the vertebral column of this greenhorn, but…
Listen well!
Do not try to flee!
You, you come with me!
I will need strong arms!
Yes.
In fact, she wants that I put a coat, that one takes Sanji-Kun with us and that one leaves from here.
It is also what I included/understood.
Ca makes a small moment that I run, now…
It makes already night.
I do not hear it any more…
It would be said that it finally gave up.
It is better thus.
It is out of the question which I leave.
It is the full moon, this evening…
He!!!!
THE REINDEER!!!!
Become a pirate with me!
It is not true! He is always after me!
He, Luffy… drops.
It will not be shown just because you howl like that.
He does not want to be a pirate.
I want that he unites with us!
And it will join us!
CA It IS WHAT YOU YOU WANT!!!
It is not that I do not want to leave…
THE REINDEER!
GO SHOWS ITSELF!
The reindeer!
But I cannot!
I cannot leave!
I am not like them!
The reindeer!
Tony-Kun.
He! Become a pirate with me!
Hein?!
I cannot.
Go, you will see! It is brilliant!
You did not even hear his explanations yet!
I want to say…
I want to say that I am a reindeer!
With wood, shoes, and…
And a blue nose!
You think of being able to cure his ravaged heart?
I want to become a pirate, but…
I cannot be the friend of human, here all!
I am a monster!
Somebody as me cannot be your companion!
Then…!
Then, I came…
I came to say thank you.
Thank you for your proposal.
I will remain here, but…
If the heart of said to you, return to see me one of these days and…
Close it!!!
ALLONS-Y!!!
“It Closes ". It is like that you hope to make it come?
Nami.
You are sour of better being?
I am well, I breathe health!
Yosh, now I will finish my bonhomme de neige.
He, shouldn't we say goodbye to this old nipple like with this same of doctor?
That you are stupid.
Let do it its good-byes with all alone Doctorine.
Stop! Drop that, rather will prepare the télécâble!
Ca makes now six years that they live side by side.
There surely will be many sadness and tears.
Doctorine can appear hard with the first access…
… but it has really an enormous heart.
Really?
Then, one will leave like that?
Exactly.
As soon as Chopper returns, the mountain will be descended…
… and one will put the course on Arabasta!
Vivi isn't, that is appropriate to you?
Yes, since we have a doctor.
A doctor?
Very well. Then I will prepare the télécâble.
He, Luffy! Come to give me a knack!
I did not even know that there was a télécâble!
It is brilliant!
After the left assets all,
put them on line, directed towards the sky.
Dr. Kureha!
Why are we emptying the arms manufacture of all its guns?
Instead of nothing to make, put yourself at the job.
Eh well, one would say that it misses some patients here.
They left.
Without listening to your orders.
I see…
Which band the irresponsible ones.
Doctorine!
I must speak to you!
Was Chopper, but where you?
Goes in bottom, to help to install the guns.
Listen to me, Doctorine!
I will become pirate!
I leave with them!
What do you say?
I take the sea!
I will be their companion as a ship's doctor!
I will make the round the world tour!
WOULD NOT BE STUPID!
Listen to me well, you are my only and single assisting!
Say a little to me… who taught you medicine?
Or don't you thus have any regard for me?
C it is not true…
Doctorine. I am attached to this place.
Because it is here that I met you as well as the Doctor.
Then remains.
Where can you live elsewhere than in this large castle?
Piracy is not made for you!
I do not give your skin expensive!
Little imports me!
Stop speaking like an idiot!
Who already saw a reindeer taking the sea?!
It IS TRUE, I AM a REINDEER!!!
BUT, I AM ALSO A MAN!!!
Since it is thus!
I will never give myself the permission to leave!
If you want to leave, it will be necessary that you me master keys on the body!
Doctorine?
How a chiard as you can be claimed a man?
What a joke!
But Doctorine, it…
Close it!
ALLONS-Y!!!
… included/understood…
CLOSE it!
I will not admit your selfishness!
YOU WILL NOT GO Nowhere, CHOPPER!
RETURN HERE!
He, one would say that it occurs something.
Do not pay attention.
If one did not finish leaving all the guns outside,
Dr. Kureha will start to be irritated and to balance us above tricks.
Yes, you are right.
Return!
You will not leave!
CHOPPER!!!
HEAT IN FRONT!!!
What? It would be said that something occurs in the castle.
Really, which lack of respect.
Can't they thus make less noise in this night when two people bid their farewell?
I am afflicted, Doctorine!
But I want to discover the world!
I wonder what somebody as suits you to go to make on the seas!?
You believe that you just like will live in a dream this charlatan of doctor?!
You are mistaken! It was not a dream!
RESEARCH OF THE DOCTOR SUCCEEDED!!
Is He, it him?
What occurs?
She pursues it!
He! The télécâble is ready with…
HOW EVERYONE GOES UP IN THE SLEDGE!
ONE WILL GO DOWN FROM THE MOUNTAIN!
WHAT?!
He, look at!
But what is it that?
The sledge of the witch…
What was it?
It was the reindeer of Dr. Kureha!
The pirates were in the sledge!
But what did it occur up there?
And Wapol?
Is Dalton-San well?
It was brilliant, this descent!
He, let us remake one!
Imbecile! One from goes away!
I believed well that I was going to die!
Where I am?!
Are Sanji-San, you awaked?
Summers you sure that will go, after you to be left kind?
One of my pets left, here all.
I hate the good-byes.
Go!
One will make them a colourful good-bye!
IEA…
I finally succeeded!
It is the reaction which I had waited for 30 years!
Doctor, it was not that a dream, isn't?
Your research succeeded, not true?!
Or was this still only one lie?
I succeeded, Chopper!
My research succeeded!
You have says that before dying…
… because you do not want that I would be sad?
“Nothing is impossible for a man who lives under the banner with the tête de mort!”
Repetitions it once again, Doctor!
DOES ANY EAST AVOID, THE SNOTTY-NOSED KID!?
YES!
FIRE!!
Listen to Kureha, this powder…
Dr. Kureha, what you…?
Close and looks at it!
Ca comes from the castle!
Does Wapol make a fireworks?
Imbecile! It is the artillery!
What occurs?
Made attention with the boulets de canon!
Shit, it shows too dark them!
Dr. Kureha! All the shells were sent!
Light!
Incredible…
Yes.
Splendid!
It is the fruit of my 30 years of research!
They is… so marvellous…
You cannot include/understand what it occurs in the head from insane.
I will make flower of the cherry trees here!
If I can conclude my research, this country will be saved!
BREAK FROM HERE, CHARLATAN!
Shit! I was persuaded that with an eye of triton it would go!
Listen! This red powder is not ordinary.
It will be fixed at snow in the atmosphere…
And snow pink will make shine!
Doctor…!
Doctorine…!
I do not want to make you of evil!!
My name is Dr. Hiluluk!
I am a doctor!
Tony Tony Chopper!
It is well like first name, not true?
Thus I will call you.
Chopper, you will make a good doctor.
I promise it to you!
Even after my death, my dream will become reality.
It was really a formidable life!
Thank you in you, Chopper.
Goes, now!
My wire idiot!