Alarming Bananawani
and Mr. Prince
With the kingdom of the Oases.
Three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
Nanohana
An impostor presented himself in front of the people while claiming to be Cobra.
He informed them that the shortage of rain was its work.
And then it started to destroy the village…
… and to persecute its inhabitants.
According to the tortuous intentions of the trap of Crocodile, the hatred of the people exploded.
The flames of a violent rebellion seized all the country of Arabasta.
The rebellious army is now solved for its final and decisive battle with Alubarna.
But Luffy and its crew…
are always imprisoned in Rainbase.
The army rebels approaches while we speak!
Listen attentively!
We will sacrifice our lives to protect Arabasta!
Do not fear death!
You give to bottom!
We will attack the rebellious army!
Prepare you to intercept them!
Let us reverse Alubarna!
Does Ca go, Kohza?
This wound is not serious!
With this pace, we will reach Alubarna with the lever du soleil!
We will maintain this pace during all the way!
Included/understood!
The battle…
...com will mencera at dawn!
What a coincidence!
We were also going to leave in Alubarna.
If you want to accompany us, you are the welcome.
Or…
… will you save them in the place?
It is…!
The key of the cage!
Give the-me!
This key!
A trap door!
I cannot say that how long will take before they start with entretuer.
Even while travelling as quickly as possible until Alubarna, you will be able nothing to probably make.
If you want to stop the rebellion, I advise you to leave immediately, Miss Wednesday.
Or will you save them in the place?
Unfortunately, I accidentally made fall the key in the part in lower part…
Banana Croco
Bananawani Den.
Bananawani…!
Bananawani?
What is it?
There is a crocodile under a banana!
It is what these monstrous crocos?!
Would that like to say that… this part is under water!?
Mysterious bananas…
Moron, looks at well!
The bananas are not under the crocodiles.
They are strange crocodiles.
Is He, what there, Vivi?
One of the bananawanis swallowed the key!
What!?
Goes to its continuation and make spit to him!
I am unable!
Bananawani is a wild creature, they are predatory sailors.
He will eat me at the second when I will approach it!
I am afflicted, I held the key so awkwardly.
And moreover, I do not believe that you will be able to say which swallowed.
What!?
What a idiot!
Shit, if one could open the cage,
I would deal with these monstrous reptiles.
Be to you an idiot, Zoro.
We cannot leave because it swallowed the key.
I know it!
Well.
The hour had just left.
Still a thing, this part car-will be destroyed in one hour exactly.
This secret base that I used to direct Baroque Works me is not any more any utility.
Water will fill this part and will run it until the bottom of the Lake Rainbase.
A million innocent people?
Or four pirate poor wretches who don't have any future in front of them?
One or the other.
The chances of all to save them are tiny.
It is with you to see, Miss Wednesday.
You like the bets?
There are so much idiots in this country which my plan was too easy.
Especially these young bold rebels and this old man who digs holes with Yuba.
Q- What did you say!?
You want to speak about the grandpa!?
He tries to dig an oasis died, day after day, with this desperate face.
Which old stupid man.
With time, the tempêtes de sable came and he refused to give up.
You…
Say to me, Luffy with the straw hat,
you believe that tempêtes de sable…
… always fall down on the same village by chance?
What does that want to say?
Yuba…
… cannot be made overcome by simple sand.
I will ressusciterai it.
It does not matter time that will take to me…
You…
… ace does that!?
Vivi-Chan.
I believe the King.
It is not the kind of anybody to betray his country.
I will kill you.
He! water starts to invade the part!
This rate/rhythm, the part will be entirely immersed!
Vivi! Helps us! Do something!
I do not want that it is my last hour!
Calm yourself idiotic.
Zoro! Be to you a cretin! Water goes up!
How I can calm myself at one similar time!?
If we do not reflect, we all will die!
You do not include/understand!?
My country or my companions…!?
In any case, you no, isn't this will let to me have some?
You will have killed me before even as I reach Alubarna.
I know…
… how nothing will stop as much as I will not have killed you!
You do not know anything…
… in connection with the inhabitants of this country…
… nor of their history…
… nor their lives…
You do not know anything the whole…!
Vivi!
Do something!
Make leave to us from there!
Luffy-San…
Do Ah, then you have fear of dying, Luffy with the straw hat?
It is true…
I suppose that everyone fears death.
If us…
If we die here…
who will explode to him the mouth?!
Would not be pretentious, kid.
It is you here the kid.
If you give up them, it would be time, Miss Wednesday.
You want to stop the rebellion above all.
It is imposing…
Yosh!
Burst it, Vivi!
Would not be ridiculous!
It is well too large!
Vivi!
Flee!
You cannot fight against that!
But…
Save us!
It is you which are ridiculous!
One moment, look at!
Behind the window!
They make all the tail to go to eat!
They think that we are their meal.
In one hour, we all will be in their bellies!
Whore! Too much fast!
It crunched the staircase of only one blow!
What jaws!
Vivi!!
Shit! This monster is unbeatable!
Vivi!
Flee!!
Be raised!
Vivi, it will devour you!
A message.
What is it?
Hello?
Does this trick function?
Yes, I hear you.
You of the Million, isn't this is one?
Does He, that go?
Baby Den Den Mushi = Snail Phon of pocket
I had never used one of these Babies Den Den Mushi before…
Yes, that functions.
Continue to speak inside.
What is there?
Go ahead spits.
What did it occur?
Ah, I already heard this front voice.
He, thank you for the call.
Here the Restaurant of Shit.
The Restaurant of Shit, you known as?
Hein?
It would be said that you remember.
I am flattered.
He, thank you for the call.
Here the Restaurant of Shit.
You want to place order?
Stop talking cock, jerk!
Den Den Mushi?
What do you want to say?
I did not make use of Den Den Mushi when I was on Little Garden…
The four pirates of Straw hat are locked up in this cage.
The only one which remainder must be their pet.
Is there another of them?
Did He, you hear!?
The Restaurant of Shit.
Ca must be…
San…
Wait, Luffy!
They do not know it yet!
This day when Mr.2 was on board.
He did not see it because he was in the kitchen.
Sanji-San…
It is true!
Sanji-San and Tony-Kun are always outside!
Who are you, poor shit?
Me?
I am…
Mr. Prince.
I see, Mr. Prince.
Where are you?
I cannot say it for the moment.
If I said it to you, you would come to kill me.
Even if I do not think that you can reach that point.
I am not also stupid to give information.
Not like you, Mr. 0.
Prince-San!
The Help!!
One does not have any more as a a long time!
Save me too!
Prince-San! Make leave to us from here!
One is in the soup!
It would be said that my crew is not far from you.
Well, I suppose that I…
The dumb…
Hello?
One had it.
What do we have to make of this type?
Sanji-San…
Not…!
Where are you?
Give your position!
We are in Rainbase in front of the doors of the casino Rain Dinners.
This good with nothing got caught!
It may find it beneficial to be still in life!
Sanji!
Our last hope…
All is perfect.
Let us go to the door.
You are sure?
The Million is unaware of still the identity of their chief.
I do not go there as a chief.
Nobody knows our identity with share the Numbers Agents.
But as a Crocodile the owner of the casino,
nothing prevents me from going to see what occurs.
What is there the curious one with that?
Vivi!
What do you make?
There remains still time before this part is not flooded!
I leave to seek of the assistance!
Ouais, Sanji cannot be dead!
If Vivi can release it in one way or another…
And Chopper is him outside too!
Ca should go…
Attention, Vivi!
Vivi!
Do not test anything stupid.
Ahhh! Vivi, begin again yourself!
Vivi, awakes!
Make leave to us!
Vivi, saves us!
Vivi!
If you hold so much with your friends, you have to only die with them.
As soon as water fills the salle à manger of the crocodiles, this part will start to run.
I think that I will bring back this impudent of Mr. Prince at the same time for you…
At least its corpse!
Make shit!
Oh, Main Crocodile.
You are with the current in connection with Nanohana?
Hm? Ah yes, I know.
The rebellious army and the royal army are about to clash!
The whole city east…
Not, the whole country is without top-below!
Yes, eh well…
The King is the kind of anybody who does not raise the little finger when the villages are attacked by the pirates.
That does not surprise me at all.
He look at, it is Crocodile-San!
It is him! What a class!
It is really him!
It is never shown in the casino!
Crocodile-Sama!
Which popularity.
Oh, does not look at me like that.
Monster, when did you touch my face?
I did not touch it, I struck it!
You forgot, my large wolf?
What?
You want to fight?
Stop that. There are others of them to fight.
They is tedious.
Why do I have to make a so tedious mission with these so tedious people?
One card-indexes oneself if they is pleasant or tedious…
We are with range of sight of Alubarna.
Oh yes!
Show to me! Show to me!
Really?
Thus it is Alubarna…
Over there, the curtain will open on our play.
The ambitions of Zero-Chan will flower like a flower of the desert.
Vivi!
Until now,
they always protected me and always took care on me.
I cannot give up them and let them die!
It succeeded!
She east flees!
The panes yielded and water goes up more quickly!
This train, the part will run in less than 20 minutes!
This part is foutue!
Vivi!
Does Ca go!?
You all!
Hold good still a small moment!
I will seek of the assistance!
It is out of the question that I let to you die!
Well!
Go ahead, Vivi!
That devil…
… did it occur here?
In addition to the losses caused by Pell the falcon…
all the Million this city was crushed.
What did it occur here?
He!
The man who is made call “Mr. Prince”.
Didn't you say me that you had caught it?
Where is party?
It has just left towards the South…
At the moment?
It is him.
Poor insane…
He believes capacity to escape to me…
Why not let it slip by?
Close it!
I killed all the people…
… which had enough notch to resist to me!
He, that does occur?
An earthquake?
Oh not!
The bridge of Rain Dinners crumbled!
How did it can crumble so quickly!?
What does that want to say?
What caused that!?
How did that can arrive!?
We cannot turn over downtown any more!
There is no boat!?
How did that can arrive!?
The bridge… crumbled…
Oh not… I cannot leave any more from here now!
It is not that we cannot leave any more…
But the fact that Baroque Works doesnot can return any more here.
All occurs as envisaged.
Chopper is being used as soft food and makes it tower of the city.
We would make better press us, the rebellion started.
Sanji-San!
Say to me only where to go…
Princess.