FOXY THE SILVER FOX!
AN INTERVENTION FORCES
The race was tightened!
The coral barrier is right in front!
At the head, we find Cutie Wagon of Porch-chan.
Barrel Tiger of the crew of the hat
of straw and My-iikada are behind.
Impressing!
Ca resembles the horns of Chopper.
Which are these long projecting corals?
It does not matter their length, the corals cannot
not to be with the top of the sea level, not?
Look at!
Ca created a strange current.
One must go there calmly.
I would never have thought that the race would go also far.
Cleaned, I count on you!
We cannot forget…
Come from the right-hand side, our Oyabi, Foxy the Fox
Silver plated, which awaits its chance to intervene.
I wonder what it will do.
Massacre them, Oyabi!
Assigned time is almost past!
The boat of the crew of
straw hat loses speed.
Allons-y Nami! Let us row!
Not yet!
They widen the gap more!
It is too early!
It is too early for you also Sanji-kun!
How you will want!
Cutie Wagon is digging
an increasingly consequent variation.
Allons-y, Monda!
Hey.
What doesn't go?
Cleaned!
They return.
Cutie Wagon goes in the bad direction!
But why thus?
Why?!
I was on!
I knew that this current was suspect.
Let us increase speed!
Follow us!
IEA aïïe, Sir!
Test once again, Monda!
The team of the straw hat increased her pace!
From now on, the participants move
together towards the long corals.
Barrel Tiger and My-iikida
can return more behind!
It is what that?
Finally, here it is!
The démoniaque intervention of Foxy!
Can one escape that?
What does he want this dumb?
Impossible to see what occurs in front.
They is too dangerous for the team of the hat
of straw to advance, even inch.
Operation “Cloud of successful White Snow”!
Let us see seeing, how you will cross
this coral labyrinth while being blind!
Succeeded, hein?
Wait!!
They are escaped!
They left the cloud with facility!
I would have suspected it…
The crew of the straw hat sails
quietly among the corals!
While waiting, Cutie Wagon is…
… still being made push back!
The boat moves all alone forwards.
What occurs?
There is a labyrinth of currents.
Labyrinth of currents?
Ouais.
Because of the swirl which is in front.
There is a series of small swirls in the barrier.
It was not the sorrow to be concerned with visibility.
Once the entry passed, the current
we will take along out of the barrier.
Brilliant!
Did you see that?!
The talent of our navigatrice!
As always, you are incredible!
Nami-swan!
Shit!
But their joy is of short duration.
Once they will have passed the forest of
corals, they will be on the “Long Boxing ring”!
This swirl will carry out us right in hell!
Ussop!
Stop howling and uses your gadget!
Which gadget?
Impact!
Hein? This trick there?
Impossible, nan. nan. nan. nan.
Go! Use it!
Hey.
When you have…
Hurry!
If you dispatches not, us
will be swallowed by the swirl.
Since when you carried that with you?
I did it front, but when I use it, my shoulder…
I do not worry of what will arrive at your shoulder.
It IS OF MY SHOULDER about WHICH YOU SPEAK!!!
Go ahead Ussop!
We do not have any more time!
Zut! Just when I thought that them
things were going to be calmed for good.
It was a bad idea of
to take part in this competition.
I feel terrified only by looking at that…
All is regulated, Long Conk…
I would be never…
Look at to me that, Barrel Tiger!
They passed over
swirl in company of My-iikida.
It is perhaps better to fly than to sail.
They also pass the Long one Wraps.
Will they land on water now? Not…
Ca broke…
My-iikada landed on Length
Wrap and received large damage.
From now on, they cannot
to continue the race, impossible!
My-iikada is disqualified!
I am afflicted, Nami-san!
Do not make any you for us and sinks right in front!
Ok, does not worry you!
Barrel Tiger is at the head with a broad advance.
Invincible Cutie Wagon T he will know the defeat?
I think that you took to us a little too with the light one.
Porch-chan, hold of all your forces.
I count on you!
Combination.
“Driving Poisson Double”
Wait, they did not lose yet!
They created a combining engine
a man-fish and a shark!
They leave in hunting, while passing through the corals!
From now on, the race in is already with its half.
Barrel Tiger, which fights, is always at the head of race!
Ussop, rises!
Impossible!
Hurry and rows!
The boat moves towards a strange direction.
Direction of the race!
On the right…
It is that, turn right!
You really believe that one was going to fall in it?!
It was destroyed!
The false control panel
of Oyabi did not function!
Doesn't this girl thus believe of anything the whole?
The farm up there!!
It is also coarse!
The race continues!
And Barrel Tiger goes
to confront with the next obstacles!
It is what these water pillars?
While being high towards the skies, they
pass through long the jets d'eau.
Is this really a natural phenomenon?
Grandmother.
Oyabi!
Nan… Grandmother.
I drop… I am useless.
I never knew but Mikabi Ozon
was the small son of Oyabi.
Eh you, on the boat.
Can you stop and come to help me?
What all does that mean?
They completely ignored the old patient and a child!
Either they do not have any sympathy or they are egoistic!
Nami, the navigatrice in the middle of ice!
Hey you, I said to you to close it!
Who would be enough stupid to be made trap by that?!
It is also coarse!
Here is the arrival!
How one small moment before the victory!
Allons-y!
Cutie Wagon is catching up with the leader.
It is the first stage, Donut Race!
Who will be…
The winner?!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
MUGIWARA-TEAM
Who will be…
The winner?!
I said to you…
To buckle it!
She saw trickery!
The false finishing line did not function!
It is too strong!
Do you know what is a “pure heart”?
I of insane!
Not well! My words do not affect it!
The true finishing line is probably close.
I cannot use impact any more!
I know!
And at the same time, a tragedy occurs!
The team of Porch-chan is
stopped with the false finishing line!
Did one gain?
Hey! Where did they go?
Its innocence is so touching!
But go counts of your error, Porch-chan!
It is right a delay!
If one loses against these gugusses,
I would have shame all my life!
And over all, they want
to take one of our companions!
Oh not! It is not the true finishing line.
What?! Who would make a similar thing
In this moment, Barrel Tiger is in front of,
and skirts the long coast of bamboo!
It is the last stage before the arrival!
It is true, I can see the arrival!
Wait!
Hey, they start to catch up with us!
One cannot compete in term speed.
It is that Ussop! You can cut down
some of these feet of bamboo?
Bamboo?!
Yosh!
Like that?
Still, still!
More quickly, Kabouti!
I undertake to run them!
Ok!
How that, like that, that, that?!
Wow! Bingo!
Oh not! Kabouti!
These unpleasant…
they will not be left there like that!
It is what? Magic flowers?
Ah, it is of Shuriken…
Oh shit!
They is not good, there is a hole in the hull of the boat!
Ca will go, it will hold good.
The arrival is right in front of our eyes.
The first round of Da Back Fight the “Donut Race”,
is about to finish!
Cleaned, hold good!
I really do not want to lose against them!
Dispatch you to catch up with them!
If that continues like that, one will lose!
Allons-y, Oyabin.
Who will gain?
Oh, just in time…
Brilliant, the group of Nami is at the head!
Nami-san!!
Robin-chwan!!
I like when you sink!
Damage for you the guy.
Why? One will gain!
For the moment, but look at.
Oyabi is there.
And then? It can nothing make from now on.
You know, Oyabi has the capacity
of a fruit of the demon, like you.
Cutie Wagon is victorious!
The winner of the first round of
Da back Fight is our idol, Porch-chan!
It is what you deserve, idiotic!
Iyan, thank you with all!
Porch-chan, you are the best!
It is an obvious result.
We will take a member
of your crew now!
Nobody can overcome the crew of Foxy Pirates!
It is time for you to say goodbye…
with the one of your companions!
Will Ca go? You are not wounded?
Not… we are well.
Did Hey, what occur?
And Ben, I…
It is what I would like to know!
Why we lost?!
Ben, I thought that you had gained, but you
be all become slow and you were exceeded.
There is nothing odd in it!
The reason of your slowness is my Noro Mako!
Hey, bloody little fool! What you made them?!
“Noro Mako”?
It is a particle which does not have yet
summer scientifically recorded.
All that bathes in this light, that it
that is to say a form of life, a liquid or a gas,
Will not lose energy but will lose its physical swiftness!
I included/understood anything, you must be idiotic.
Devastation…
Iyan, Oyabin!
But… that seems…
“Impossible”? It is what you want to say?
You should know that on this sea,
this kind of words does not have a direction.
All that it key becomes slow.
It is that “Noro Mako”!
Ah, if you say it like that, I include/understand.
I became a Man-Noro.
My body is able to emit these rays.
Look at… my capacity!
[Noro:Slow]
The ball of gun is…
The effect of Noro Noro lasts during 30 seconds.
After that, the ball of gun will find
its speed, as so of nothing was not.
You your eyes of them, isn't this does not believe?
It is…
Oyabi!
Shit. Ca wants to say that one was made have.
Ca explains their confidence compared to the play…
To have our delayed capacities…
At all events, you that, isn't this likes to do?
You, bad losers!
The winner of the first round, Donut Race…
… it is US.
Was Iyan, it tight hein?
The first round is finished, and now it is
the hour to take a member of the opposing crew!
Then to begin the first that I want it is…
YOU!
The doctor, Tony Tony Chopper!
Hein… Me?!
Exactly. Bring it.
Not… Chopper!
It is an incredibly unusual animal!
And it is even softer than I imagined it!
Iyan, Oyabi, leave me the touch too!
SUPER NICE!
We will take this one!
Chopper!
Which dumb, therefore was its objective Chopper?
It is true that it is a rare pearl from rare.
It is a maniac of the nice things.
Or a maniac of the furs.
Cease your stupid things! It is not a joke,
they took one of our companions!
My friends…
Oï, Oï, Dr. Chopper.
You are one of the members of my crew now.
You will have to obey me. First of all, mets this mask.
My companions…
Forgive me, Chopper!
It is because one lost…
Shit!
It is really unusual!
It is amazing, a reindeer which speaks…
Be content for you hein?
Enchanted, partner.
My friends!
I only came because you want me!
I do not want that!
I do not want to do that, Luffy!
I only came at sea
because you asked it to me!
Together with these guy…
It is not where I want to be! I am a member of the crew of the straw hat, Tony Tony Chopper!
I do not want!
Stop pleurnicher, Chopper!
They is ashamed!
Zoro…
To come at sea was MT decision. MT responsibility.
It does not matter how that occurs, it is your responsibility.
Does not blame us.
We accepted this play.
Ussop, has you, everyone
fought of all its forces.
In this universe of piracy, anybody
any sympathy will not show.
If are to you a man…
Sit down, buckles it and looks at it
remain of these whores of tests.
How can you say that?
You know what it feels?!
Of agreement, made as you want!
Chopper!
Yosh.
This epeist is cool!
Yosha! Zoro, will show them!
Bring back for us Chopper!
Oyabi, let us take this epeist the next time.
The reindeer has also tripe!
Let us begin the second round.
Tears… I am crying!
It is true. There remain still two rounds.
It is necessary that one recovers our small ration of
survival, before it is done too many concern.
Sanji, one counts on you!
The deal was made. Serious things
make that to start in this Da Back Fight!
Wait one minute… Chopper is supposed to be
in the second round. But they took it.
Exact.
It is the best moment of the play!
I will say it to you…
in agreement with the rules, you
donot can change the participants.
In the second round, Groggy Boxing ring, the crew of
straw hat has only two participants!
Therefore, an easy victory for Foxy Pirates!
What?!
Be free for you to stop, wet hen.
Not question. I could say to you
the same thing, face of fart.
Difficult to think that these deux-là
can work in team…
You want to fight?!
Stop that!
Now, I will explain the rules of Groggy Ring!
There are two goals on each side of the ground.
It is necessary to put the ball in
goal to gain. However…
the ball is not made of rubber.
Ca will be human!
Each team will have, in other words,
somebody who will be the ball!
Hey, you two. Who would like to be the ball?
By here the ball.
It is not with you to decide!
YOU ES the ball, head of alga!
Oh, they arrive! It is their entry…
Champions of Groggy Boxing ring!
They are still unconquered!
Butt them!
They are Groggy Monsters!
And they enter now on the ground!
First of all, we have “Full Dash” alias Hamburger!
Behind him, we have “Tackle Demon” Pickles!
And behind, the being is found
semi-giant semi-man-fish…
“Big Bang” Botan!
They are really the monsters of the boxing ring!
Go! Go! Go!
What is it that?
But it is what this enormous man-fish?!
And it is him which with the ball!
You are not likely any to gain!
Unexpected?
At all.