Speaking of anniversaries, tomorrow
will certainly be a day to remember.
I can't let them get to the village!
Head straight north...
Head straight north!
Whoever dares to lay a hand on
my treasures is... Unforgivable!
Damn!
I can't get past this...
You're a hindrance!
I can't allow you.
to go beyond this slope...
Because I'd like to keep lying as
I've always done in the past.
This village will enjoy another day
of peace like any other day!
That's why I can't allow let you pass!
They're late.
Those bastards...
They should clearly understand what'd happen
if my plan were to be disrupted.
I will kill them all!
THE TERRIFYING DUO!
NYABAN BROTHER VS ZORO
They're finally here
You guys are that strong?
You guys are way too slow!
It's all thanks to you, dragging
me down that oil slick!
That was an accident.
There was nothing I could do about it.
Rather than both of us slipping, it's better
to have one of us make it through.
Then why not you?
Go north, don't go north... you never
even told me which way was north!
What?! You're the one who
ran off, full of confidence!
That happened unconsciously... out of whim.
The sky's been bright for a while now.
Captain Kuro is a very impatient man.
Comrades! Don't tell that you're going
to allow mere kids to defeat you?
to alIow mere kids to defeat you?
Listen, we don't have the time to fool around here.
They're strong, so we'll just have to be stronger.
Now, stare into this ring.
With ''One, Two, Jango!'', you'll become strong.
Your injuries will heal and you'll become
very very very very strong!
What's he up to?
Hypnosis.
Making them believe that they're
strong... that's just stupid!
You'll become stronger... much stronger!
One...
Two...
Jango!
No way!
Th... the cliff's totalIy destroyed!
What power!
They're reaIly hypnotized.
They're really hypnotized.
That's just one of 'em, and there're so many!
Go!
Break the necks of anyone that tries to stop us!
You two get out of the way!
We'lI take it from here!
Hey Luffy!
Luffy?
You're hypnotized too?!
What a simpleton!
GOMU GOMU NO...
MACHINE GUN!!!
Captain Kuro made a big miscalculation.
They're not your ordinary brats.
Where's he going?
What's he doing?
Go! Luffy!
He's destroying the ship!
No!
He wants to whack us with it!
Hurry up and think of something, Capt'!
Crap, this is no time to just watch.
With ''One, Two, Jango!'', you will fall asleep.
One...
Two...
Jango!
What?! That caretaker, Kurahadol,
headed for the coast?
He looked very scary.
Is Kaya-san alright?
Yosh! The Usopp Pirate Gang are off!
Hey, don't sleep!
But it's still sleeping time.
This is not the time to sleep!
There might be something horrible happening.
I still think that the pirates are going to attack.
Although Captain said that he was
lying, I don't really think he was.
I think so too.
Me too.
Captain was acting really weird yesterday.
You don't think..?
I remember that Captain always
come through this way.
No use, it's sealed off.
Let's find another way in!
You!
Dare to make fun of me?!
Just because pirate's blood flows within me...
You look down upon me!
Please stop, Usopp-san!
Kurahadol...
Kurahadol, are you there?
Kurahadol?
Meri!
What's wrong?
What happened?
Hey, wake up, Meri!
Don't die on me!
Ojousama...
Thank goodness you're alright.
Meri...
Meri, who did this to you?!
Kurahadol...
He... did this to me.
His... His true identity is a pirate!
What are you talking about?
He became interested with the family fortune.
That's why he got close to you.
That's... that's just ridicu...
It's the truth!
Then...
What Usopp-san said yesterday was...
Come to think of it, he was the only
one who knew of the truth.
He risked his life trying to save us.
But none of us would believe a word he said...
Get out of here, Kaya!
Or you'll be killed!
In any case, let's get out of here for now!
In any case, let's get out of here for nowI
We only thought of protecting the bad guy...
And made that brave young man...
The man who wanted to protect the village...
the man who risked his life to warn us...
We chased him out of the village!
Anyone! Is anyone here?! Anyone!
Ojousama...
Ojousama... it's useless.
Everyone's gone on vacation since yesterday.
That can't be...
Then I...
Now's not the time to panic!
Nothing's happened yet.
It's vital that you calm down and
think of a solution for all this.
If Kurahadol's motive is just to
own everything in this house,
then just give it to him!
It's not worth your life to protect it.
Yes.
The problem at hand now is that you're
the only one who can stop Kurahadol.
Can you do it?
Even though this is not your responsibility.
I understand.
I... will not run away from this.
I understand the consequences.
I will talk to Kurahadol!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
What do you think you're doing?
Hold on to them tight!
But these iron bars are too slippery!
We still need to climb over, even if it is.
Aren't you worried about Kaya-san?
Someone's coming.
Hide!
It's Kaya-san!
She's okay!
She seems to be troubled by something.
Kaya-san is leaving her house alone.
Somethings up.
Something must've happened!
Seems like they got wiped out.
Looks like it.
Hey, we should be more concerned
of Luffy being under that thing.
He's not gonna die.
You'd better worry more about your own injuries.
That brat really screwed us over.
Now the plan's all messed up!
If Captain Kuro sees this, we'll all be killed!
Hey, hey.. Buchi!
Look what happened out here!
What's all this?
We still have our trump card.
Come out! Nyaban Brothers!
You called, Captain Jango?
You called?
Sham and...
Buchi!
Together, we're the Nyaban Brothers!
Buchi, Sham..
We must get passed this slope, but...
As you can see, someone's in our way.
Take care of him.
Th... that's impossible for us!
Right, Buchi?
Yeah, he seems to be very strong.
Moreover, our responsibility's
just to look after the ship.
Ah yeah, you're right. We're
not responsible for battles.
What's this? Aren't they supposed
to be their trump card?
Sham, just go do it!
Eh?! M-me?!
Get goin'!!
Fi... fine... I'm going.
He looks completely different.
What're they up to?
How can he possibly fight like that?
Hey you! Be prepared, cause I'm gonna
to tear you apart with these very claws!
What am I supposed to do with this guy?
You! If you don't stop, I'll kill you!
That is if you can kill me.
What?!
This bastard...
You...
Took me too lightly.
You blocked it well.
I was acting so well too.
I may be tiny, but you'd better not take
Sham of the Nyaban Brothers lightly.
Lose something?
I wouldn't know anything about it.
There it is...
Cat snatch.
Return those katanas to me!
Return it?
Isn't your katana in your hand?
These will only get in the way.
Now... I feel much lighter.
How dare you throw my precious belongings!
Bastard!
What?
What were you trying to cut?
I'm a cat after all.
Come Buchi! Your turn!
Gotcha, Sham!
Watch this!
Got him!
Damn! He got away.
Hey, hold him down properly Sham!
Sorry, my bad. I didn't expect him
to have such brute strength.
You gotta be kidding me.
If he had actuallt hit me with that, all my bones would've shattered to pieces.
He won't get away this time!
Of course not!
I'm not too familiar with one sword techniques, but...
Let's go, Buchi!
Gotcha, Sham!
Cat Claws Attack!
This is bad, Zoro's under heavy pressure.
What're you trying to do?
If they keep attacking him like that,
there's no way he can win.
I'm covering him!
Go..
NAMAIIBOSHI!
An opening!
Why are you hitting our own people!
That's not what happened.
He's the one who moved to get hit.
Eh?! He did it himself?
You moron! Usopp!
You wanna die?
Maybe...
We're the ones who were saved.
If you had hit them with the pachinko,
then those two would've probabIy...
Directed their attacks toward us instead.
That guy...
This is no time to be worried about us!
Damn.
If only I had one more katana.
I'm going to fetch his katanas.
If Zoro gets his katanas back, then he can defeat them!
Then I should...
Don't push yourself.
You can't even stand up straight.
Hey Nami!
Nami!
What do you want with these katanas?
There's a good reason for this...
The sky's been bright for a long while.
Why didn't you act according to plan?
Ca... captain Kuro!
We're gonna be killed!
What?
This is bad.
WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?!!