Luffy attacked by the magic!
Color trap
Brogy-San!
And now, my Candle Service!
Transform them into wax statues!
My hands cannot move any more!
I do not want to die like that!
One can thus nothing make?
He, Ossan.
Would Ca say to you to butt these guys with me?
One tests?
There I will not let to you only go!
What do you believe capacity to make?
I go you botter the bottom!
What?
They destroyed the duel of the giants-Ossan!
Brogy Master!
We are here to avenge your sorrow!
Usopp…
Before that, Luffy…
Wouldn't Ca say to you to break this pillar initially?
I will leave them afterwards to you.
Okay!
I do not think.
Destroy the pillar, Luffy!
Do Zoro, what you make?
If I become a statue, I would like that it is in this installation.
It is not the moment to joke!
I do not joke.
In any case, do something for your legs.
I have badly only by looking at them.
Then does not look at!
And in any event, I said to you that it was stupid to try to cut your legs and to flee.
It is not that. I would have cut them to be able to beat me.
It is even more stupid.
You were to joke!
The farm.
Good blood, you do not have really any good sense.
We are loins of being able us to leave there,
and they do not seem anxious whole.
Do He kid, you give up already the combat?
Ouais, one will say that this time it is necessary to let another fight.
I see.
Mr. 3, these people have the air really quiet.
And you also, Miss Week Golden delicious!
Whore…
He, you would make better take the installation now.
Do not mingle me with your odd ideas!
Mr. Bushido, be serious please!
I am always serious.
This is why you are so stupid.
You are the last person to be able to say that to me!
It would be said that one does not represent any more one threat for them.
What does that want to say?
It is more enrageant.
Since this man arrived, they…
Impossible!
Yosha!
However, in my opinion, it does not resemble somebody on whom one can count.
Mr. 3!
Let finish it to us!
To finish?
You must joke?
Look at it!
Your attacks were ineffective.
It is for that it is held in front of us living.
This man cannot apparently be overcome by somebody of your level.
You two, occupy you others.
I will personally add Luffy to the straw hat to my collection of wax statues.
You never close it, vermins?
Bastard, you went too far!
Give up as much as you can it!
Small fry.
Allons-y!
Well, the preparations are ready!
I cover you Luffy!
You said something?
Go, it left!
What is it that?
Luffy-San?
What, it was already made have?
Asshole!
What is it that?
It is heavier than a hammer.
It was too easy.
And now, your hands!
Ouahou, it is perfect!
Giant-Ossan!
I borrow you for one moment!
What?
What does it try to make?
Tonkachi = Hammer
Brilliant!
What a chance! The hammer with my feet broke!
We are alive…
Saved!
The situation did not change a hair!
It was right!
Why you did not run?
One cannot move!
You do not see it?
Oh, indeed one would say that you cannot.
But said you to me to break the pillar.
You joked?
Can one really give our lives between his hands, Mr. Bushido?
At the point where are we, we do not have the choice.
My arms already hardened.
I beg you, are serious now!
Wait, my body hardens more and more quickly.
I cannot move any part of my body!
Cretin!
To have brought closer the candles to you accelerates solidification!
Now you with being prepare my wax statues!
This bastard! To play with people as he wants it!
Do He, you transform itself into wax statues?
It is what one says to you!
Hurry to break this thing, Luffy-San!
Okay, I included/understood!
I will not let myself intervene!
I said to you not to intervene!
Arts mori = wax Harpoon
Not spiced enough.
You must use powder with the reduction.
It swallowed my Kayakuboshi…
They is not good.
Ca stiffens.
Fortunately that I could take this installation.
Cretin!
Luffy-San! Hurry please!
Is Yosh, it this pumpkin which does that, not?
Hold good!
It is useless!
He, out of my way!
It would be rather with me to say that!
I must insist that you do not interfere with my Article.
I have a new hammer!
Oh not!
Mr. 3!
Impossible!
Luffy, hurries to break this trick while you have a chance!
Not.
Stop joking and do it!
It is not the moment to make the idiot!
Luffy-San please!
Why would I have?
I do not want to save you.
What do you tell?
Color Trap!
He! Luffy!
One cannot about it any more!
Stop making the idiot and helps us!
Yes.
I included/understood.
If you include/understand, magne!
Yes Luffy!
I included/understood but…
But, I do not want to save you.
What do you want to say exactly?
One transforms oneself into wax statues, you include/understand?
We will die!
Ouais… But I do not feel it.
One of fout that you feel it or not!!
This cretin… who does it arrive to him?
If it does not hurry,
our companions will die!
I will clear up the ideas to him!
Allons-y, Karu!
You were there!
Give up! It already fell into a trap.
Completely. Can you see the mark on which it is held upright?
On which it is?
Hum… Let us see that…
Brothel, there is a kind of black drawing strange over there.
What is it to the Juste?
It is right ordinary painting.
Painting?
For all to say to you, you two,
as well as the others,
you all will die together.
Karu, one must be folded up for the moment!
It tries to escape with the bird!
Let us continue them!
Sink right in front!
He! Cretin!
I am not yet on you!
Karu!
Eh well, stops!
Let go up to me!
Why are you afraid of me?
Let climb to me!
Miss Week Golden delicious.
It is you the person in charge!
Uragiri No kuro = the black which betrays
Once you touch black painting, even if your team-members are invaluable for you,
you will betray them!
What does she say?
Say to me what she tells.
It is a “realistic painter”. She can make real the emotion which a color evokes.
Its refined drawings enable him to directly influence the spirit with coloured painting.
“To influence” do you say?
They is not good!
This simple ball of spirit is even more sensitive to the suggestions than the normal!
Therefore, we must just make it move EC painting, it is that?
Luffy, you must move…
Not like that!
Luffy-San, please does not move of the circle of black painting! No matter what it arrives!
Vivi, why?
We do not want that you save us!
Not.
I include/understand.
Is necessary to say the opposite to be sure that it betrays us.
Hein?
I felt odd during one minute.
Luffy-San, quickly!
Yosh! I will save you the guy!
But now that I think of it, I prefer laughter!
Why?
You…
What now?
Warai No kiiro = laughing yellow
Cretin, was not necessary to move of this spot!
It is on its clothing.
Luffy! Hurry to take off your tee-shirt!
Not, it is more important to laugh now!
Whore!
At the speed to which fall this powder, we have some for one minute at the maximum.
Are cretins, you there to amuse you or what?
Look at! When Usopp and Karu ran up against it, they erased painting on its back!
You still had me.
He, you! Remove that immediately unpleasant plague!
My wasn't Warai No kiiro amusing?
The farm! Stupid child! Idiot!
At all events, I must break this pumpkin!
Tougyuu No aka = Red of the mad bull
Where did you aim whore?
You should not break that!
Mr. 3 will be irritated.
What is it that?
A such bull charging a red cape,
you will attack only this red mark.
Damage for you.
You me tirednesses!
Release from there!!
It is funny?
It is useless!
All is against him.
Its force does not have any effect on it.
Now, I will mix Warai No kiiro of your back with my kanashimi No ao and…
Kanashimi No ao = Blue of sadness
Nagomi No midori = alleviating green
Ah, this tea is very good…
Be idiotic for you or what?
Good… and now?
He! I had said to you to take the installation when you still had the chance of it.
Now you must be disgusted.
How can you be still also unconscious?
Shit! How can they run also quickly?
Missed!
Karu good work!
And here is the ransom!
Namari Boshi = Explosion hoisted which undoubtedly kills!
We direct towards Luffy and the others!
We will not catch them while running simply.
Indeed.
I did not want to use it for similar waste but we will not be able to pass some to us.
Revolver Flint Lock Gauges 44,6 blows.
A new model of South Blue.
Excel for the fast shooting.
And when I use it, the balls are invisible.
Reason of the odd behavior of Luffy,
as said it the two others,
it is this painting!
It is that the cause!
When I ran up against Luffy presently,
it had some on the back!
No the possible doubt!
If I can do something for painting…
More quickly!
This tea is very good.
This tea…
Luffy! What you…
This tea
is very good!
What do you insane, salt stunned?