The first obstacle?
The giant whale Laboon appears
He! I can see Reverse Montain!
What?
One cannot even see the top through the clouds!
Here thus Red Line!
It is incredible…
Water really climbs on the mountain!
One succeeded!
Towards the top!
We reach the sky!
Now we will go down!
The largest ocean of the world…
Large Line!
It is really immense!
You have not just heard a trick?
Hein? What?
I heard a strange sound!
That must be the wind!
There are many odd rock formations which can cause that.
What is it?
Nami-San!
I see a mountain right in front of us!
A mountain? It is impossible!
But I see it in front of us!
One of fout!
One goes there!
After the twin points, there should be only the ocean!
It is not a mountain!
It is a black wall!
You are mistaken!
Then it is what?
It is a whale!!!
Qu… Qu… What does one make?
One fights?
Cretin! One cannot fight with such a thing!
… … The current sends to us on it!
What will one make?
Wait one minute!
The more one approaches, the more that resembles a wall!
Then, where is its eye?
I see!
It did not should yet have noticed us!
If that continues, one will be crushed dead tops…
He! There is an opening on the left!
A port!
Right towards the port!
The rudder is broken!
Is necessary to do something!
I will help!
Ah! Here!
I have just had an good idea!
Luffy?
What do you make?
Tireeezz!!
That will not turn!
It is not worthwhile!
Do not give up!
Too much late.
The gun???
One stopped?
Oh… shit…
That failed to kill me.
My special seat!!
Flee
while you can it!
What does it occur?
She did not notice that she was caught a boulet de canon!
She is stupid or what?
One of fout! One goes there!
Aahh! My ears!
Rows! Continue to row!
Il faut qu'on s'éloigne d'elle !
Luffy?
You…
My favorite seat…
Why you broke it brothel?
Cretin!!!!
She saw us!
You ace considering that?
I go you botter the bottom!!!
The farm, ball!!
What…
Luffy!
I must move!
I will not die here!
What did I make?
The others were eaten.
He!
He! Dirtiness!
Recrache others!
Recrache them!
Return them! Return them!
Salts it to you…
Bastard!
You plunge?
Stop!
He!
He!!
Wait a little!
Return to me my companions!
He!
I said stop!
We must live venture together!
They are invaluable for me!
Return them!!
What you of known as?
“What I think” you say?
One of fout of what you think!
We were swallowed in an obvious way by a whale.
Is this a dream?
Yes.
Surely a dream.
And thus the house on this island…
An illusion.
Ah… and that?
A giant squid!!
It would be said that there is somebody in the house.
I hope that it is a person…
Enough! I want to return to the house.
If Luffy were there, it would know what to make…
Ah yes! Is Luffy well?
It is what all that?
Why this whale has a door
and maintaining a corridor?
A boat?
Kill it!
Disintegrate the island with the gun!
Not, wait one moment.
Somebody leaves.
It is a flower!
A flower?
As much for me! It is a person!
It is which this type?
This old man killed the giant squid.
Did it fish
or did he want to save us?
Say something, dumb!
One will fight with you if it is what you want, dumb!
We have a gun!
Stop, or somebody will die.
And would that be which?
Me.
You?
Whore of…
He, does not irritate you.
To play with me like that…
Grandfather, say to me…
Where are we?
And which are you?
If you want something of somebody,
it is more polished to present to you initially!
Yes! It is true.
As much for me.
I am called Rorono…
I am Crocus.
I am the guard of the headlight of the twin points.
I am 71 years old.
Gemini, blood group AB.
Can I kill it now?
He, of the calm one!
You want to know where you are?
You are in my particular island.
You shout of the insults in my connection.
You believe that you are in the stomach of a rat?
Therefore, we were really swallowed by the whale!
But, that does not resemble inside a whale…
Wait a little!
What will it arrive to us?
I do not want to be digested!
Stop doing that!!
You donot can appreciate a good gag of repetition?
A gag?
For the exit, it is over there!
One can leave?
Wait one second!
Why there is an exit in the stomach of a whale?
And what makes this door in the sky?
Wait…
Look at attentively.
Sky, clouds…
And even the gull…
That was painted!!
All is painted in the stomach of the whale!
I like to have fun!
Whore, what you made there?
They is good, leaves it quiet.
Now, one does what?
Nami, there is an exit.
Then let us leave from here.
Ouais it is clear.
What?
It starts again.
Look at that!
It is not an island!
It is a boat,
and it is made of metal!
It is true!
That means that this “ocean” must be made of gastric acid!
If we remain too a long time here,
we will be digested…
He!
It starts again what?
You explain!
This whale…
Laboon started again to be thrown against Red Line.
What?
I remember,
this whale had enormous scars on the head,
and it looked at the sky.
What do you say?
She suffers!
I see!
Then, the plan of the old man was…
Probably.
It tries to kill the whale of the interior!
Eh well…
What a way of killing horrible!
Let us leave from here now that we cleared up the mystery.
Our boat will be digested there if you remain to feel sorry for you.
Well, the businesses of whale are not my onions.
And I do not see myself saving that one.
Let us leave from here!
Shit!
The waves are too large!
One will not be able to arrive at the exit like that!
One will try to row.
Take the oars!
We must leave now!
We must see what arrived at Luffy!
It is outside!
I saw it being ejected mouth of the whale!
The old man plunged!
Hein?
Why does it do that?
It will be digested!
Why?
To turn, turn, my eyes turn!
I am where now?
An ocean?
A river?
A pipe?
Well.
Our infiltration is a real success.
Now, Wednesday Miss.
Other side of this door, it there with the stomach
and this old curious croûton also.
It must be eliminated
for the good of this whale.
Yes, Mr. 9!
This whale is the most invaluable good of our city.
He! the old man remakes surface!
Be unaware of it!
We must find how to open this door.
Ok, Wednesday Miss?
“3, 2,1, Baby” and we open the door.
Do not hesitate.
Roger, Mr. 9!
When you want.
I cannot stop!
Which is this voice, Mr. 9?
I do not know Miss Wednesday!
Still them!
Oh not, Wednesday Miss!
In lower part, there is an immense ocean of gastric juices!
Luffy?
Yo! You are well?
While passing…
Help me please!
Luffy joined us…
But it brought with him two odd people.
He! The old man left!
One of fout.
It is necessary to save Luffy.
Stop Laboon.
Stop making you these terrible scars.
There remains an only little sedative.
It will be necessary that I remake some later.
This wall is the wall which separates the oceans from the world.
It will not break even if you slaps stronger, Laboon.
That is calmed!
The whale calmed itself!
One would say…
Thus…
We saved your buttocks.
Now which are you?
Mr. 9, they are pirates.
I see it, Miss Wednesday.
But I think that one can convince them…
Probably.
You are still there, both scélérats?
Made me not repeat!
As long as I will be in life,
you will not pose a finger on Laboon!
Oh, the revoilà.
Who is this old man?
Tell what you want,
we will not give up.
To kill this whale is our mission.
We will not let to you interfere with our whale once more!
We will make a hole in its stomach!
Allons-y, Baby!
Roger!
Bandage…
The old man stopped the balls itself!
Incredible!
He thus protects the whale?
Stop your pathetic resistance!
If you want to protect it so much,
you will have to remake it!
The whale will nourish our city!
What does it occur?
Luffy?
I do not know.
I was to strike them.
You helped me much.
But why?
I did not help you.
I did not want to see that, it is all.
He, which is these people?
And what you made inside the whale?
These two scélérats are of a city not very far.
They want the meat of the whale.
Laboon could nourish their city during two or three years.
Laboon?
It is the name of this whale.
It is a whale of the islands.
It is in West Blue that saw
the greatest species of whale of the world.
How could I let it become food?
There is a reason for which it continues to strike its cranium against Red Line
and why it deals with Reverse Montain and its sky.
A reason?
Yes.
This whale…
This whale has a heart like a person.
And it indefinitely awaits a certain group of pirates.
Since 50 years…