Everyone brace yourselves on the ship or get into the cabin!
THE SEA'S GONNA EXPLODE!!
Unfurl the sails, right now!
If we've got wind and an ocean, it can be navigated!
Who's this ship's navigator?
IT'S NAMI-SAN~!?
WOW!
THE SHIP'S FLYING!
I wonder what we'll find above that cloud!
WE'RE ENTERING THE CUMULOREGALIS CLOUD!
This is the sea of the sky! The knight of the sky and Heaven's Gate
Hot damn! They got away!
They're pretty lucky.
How can you be taking this so lightly!?
Our prize just got away!
Do something, Captain!
Let's go after them and finish what we started!
Don't lose your head, Burgess.
It's not like they've disappeared from the world itself.
We'll see them again soon enough.
As long as they remain on the Grand Line.
Precisely.
Everything in this world moves according to the will of the strong.
Like a fine piece of clockwork.
See!
Jeez…
Damn…
What the hell happened?
Everyone still here?
Oi, everyone take a look!
Look around the ship!
What is this place?
It's SOOO white!
Clouds!
We're on top of the clouds?
How are we floating on them?
Sure we can float on them.
They're clouds.
No, we can't!
Oh no! Usopp's not breathing!
WHAT!?
Do something!
Try CPR!
Yosh! I'll give Nami-san CPR-!
Yutz.
Usopp! Hang on!
Usopp!
The clouds…
What!?
CLOUDS!
Too many clouds!
What's going on!?
This is like the sea of the sky.
Sea of the sky?
But, look. The log Pose is still pointing up.
We seem to be in the middle layer of the Cumuloregalis cloud.
So we have to go higher? How?
That I don't know.
Who're you calling a yutz?
I forget.
A sea…
For his first course, Captain Usopp is going for a swim!
Let's see it!
Oi, oi, oi! Don't do anything stupid!
We still don't know the nature of this sea.
A sea is a sea~!
Awesome!
He's so brave!
There's so little resistance…
And the visibility's so low that I can barely see anything.
I can dive deeper, so easily.
Deeper…
Usopp's lucky…
I wish I could swim too…
It's probably really fun…
Oi.
He's … not coming up.
Just a thought…
Is there a bottom to this sea?
YOU THINK…!?
That idiot!
Did he fall out of the cloud!?
USOPP!
What's that idiot doing!?
Stretch your arm as far as you can!
But I can't see the bottom-
Don't worry.
I'll handle it.
Ojos Fleur!  --  Eyes Flower (Spanish)
I see him!
Where!?
Veinte Fleur!  --  20 Flowers
Ok, pull him up!
You got him?
Yosh!
Is he heavy?
I don't think so…
C'mon Luffy!
Don't give up!
Yes! There he is-!
Something else came up!
They want to eat Usopp!
You don't have to be that scared of this!
Man… this place… sure takes the breath out of you…
Now, this is a weird-lookin' animal.
I can't even tell if it's a fish.
That octopus was almost like a balloon.
But they were still animals.
They were moving.
Animals in the sky?
So we really should think of this more as an ocean than a cloud.
What is this flat snake?
It's a flatfish. 'Cause it's flat.
So this is a flatfish?
For the love of…
What is it now, Usopp?
My overalls…
There's something in them!
Usopp!
Sky Island scary...Sky Island scary...Sky Island scary...Sky Island scary...Sky Island scary…
He's had a rough day.
Would you say this is a Skyfish?
The strange fish Norland mentioned in his logbook.
Since this sky sea has no bottom.
They must have evolved various adaptations to survive.
Like becoming balloons or flattening out their bodies?
To reduce their density.
This sea's buoyancy is significantly lower than that of the sea below us.
Its scales look like feathers.
And it's unusual for it be a carnivore.
I sautéd it.
This is great!
WE'RE NOT DONE LOOKING AT IT YET!
What do you guys think you're doing!?
Oh, you're right.
It's delicious!
What is it?
I've never tasted a texture like this.
I'm glad you like it, Nami-san! ?
Let's eat that big one too!
That one's too scrawny to be worth the trouble.
Where's Sky Island?
Oh, a ship.
A ship-
Oi, guys! A ship!
And a person?
Oi, what's wrong, Chopper?
Chopper, you see a ship?
Is there a ship over there?
NO! I mean, there was-
But the ship's gone now!
What?
There's a bull charging right at us on a square cloud!
I don't understand!
Calm down!
The hell…?
A person!
Someone's coming!
He's riding on top of the clouds!
Oi, hold it!
What do you want?
I shall reject you!
He wants a fight!
Fine by me!
What? What?
H-Hey! What's wrong with you three!?
HE'S GONNA SHOOT US!
Sky Island scary...Sky Island scary!
That's enough!
What!?
Who is it now!?
I am the Knight of the Sky.
He's retreated.
What's going on here?
Just who was that?
And what's more…
What's wrong with you guys?
That was pathetic!
All three of you together couldn't handle him!
Thank you for helping us!
No need for thanks. This is a service.
Dammit… I'm disappointed.
Somehow, my body…
… won't move that well.
It must be because the air's so thin.
Yeah, now that I think about it…
Are you Blue Sea dwellers?
Blue Sea dwellers?  What do you mean?
Oh yeah, who are you?
I am the Knight of the Sky.
"Blue Sea dwellers, is the general term for those who live beneath the clouds."
Knight of the Sky?
So, I presume that you traveled up from the Blue Sea.
Yeah, that's right.
Then this is no surprise.
This is the White Sea, 7,000 meters above your Blue Sea.
Furthermore, above this sea is the White-white Sea, 10,000 meters above your own.
Ordinary Blue Sea dwellers' bodies cannot handle it.
Yosh, I think I'm getting used to it!
Yeah, I feel a lot better than before.
No, no, no, no, no, that's not possible.
I have to know! How was that guy running on top of the clouds?
Yield, yield, yield. I am certain you have many questions for me,
But first we must talk of business.
Business?
I am a free mercenary.
And this is a sea of many dangers.
Since you know not the battle of the sky, you will be easy targets for the guerillas or the Skyfish.
One whistle and I will rescue you for a price of 5,000,000 extols.
What're you talking about, Ossan?
You fool! It is a small price to pay!
I will not take one extol less!
I have to make a living, you know!
But what's this extol thing you keep talking about?
And what do you mean by whistle?
You mean you did not come by way of the High West?
But you must have at least stopped by one or two islands!
C'mon, what're you talking about, Ossan?
Hold on! You mean there are other ways to get to this sky sea?
And one or two islands?
You mean there's more than one Sky Island?
You mean that you-
We rode the Knock-Up Stream here.
Riding that monstrous current?
To think there are still souls brave enough to dare to do that…
I knew it wasn't a normal route!
I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA DIE!
IF WE'D GATHERED MORE INFORMATION WE WOULD'VE HAD AN EASIER TRIP!!
We're here now! It's all good!
It's all your fault!
Sky Island scary… Sky Island scary…
IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT!
Have you lost any of your crew?
Nope, we all made it!
The other routes would not have been so merciful.
If you had brought 100 people, it would be a gamble as to how many would survive.
But by using the Knock-Up Stream, either you all die or you all survive.
There are few left willing to risk losing everything.
Especially in recent years.
I have great respect for your brave and trustworthy navigators.
Well, it was the course I picked, after all!
"I'm the navigator!"
Hey.
One whistle means blowing sharply into this.
I will descend from Heaven itself to lend you aid.
I normally ask E5,000,000 for future visits,
But I shall give you on whistle as a present.
Wait! We don't even know your name!
I am the Knight of the Sky, Gan Fall!
And this is my partner, Pierre!
I should have mentioned that my partner, Pierre…
… is a bird who has eaten and gained the ability of the Uma Uma Fruit. (Uma - Horse)
The bird?
Meaning, he can become a winged horse!
Namely…
Oh my!
How wonderful! A Pegasus?
Yes, a Pegasus!
That's… questionable.
Brave souls, may luck be with you!
Well that was certainly strange…
And by the way… was there any point to it transforming?
Dunno…
In the end… he didn't really tell us much.
Yeah!
Not a damn thing!
We can blow this and he'll come back.
How are we gonna get higher?
Yosh! I'll call that Ossan and ask him!
W-W-W-W-W-Whoa, hold it luffy!
That's only to ask for help in an emergency!
What if that weirdo in the mask shows up again!?
Anyway, let's move the ship somewhere.
Hey, look over there!
I wonder what that is.
Weird clouds, huh?
It looks like a waterfall.
Yosh, that's that then.
We'll go over there.
Hold on!
Stop, stop!
Some large clouds are blocking our path.
What do we do?
They're floating above the sky sea, so they can't be part of it.
What kind of clouds are they then?
If they're ordinary clouds, we can just sail through them.
I'll touch one and find out!
GOMU GOMU NO PISTOL!
Ah, it bounced off!
Look! I'm bouncing!
I'm not sinking!
It's so soft!
Just like cotton!
What is it?
It's almost too fun!
Wooow~!
What a strange phenomenon.
Quite mysterious.
I'm going too!
Me too!
Ahh~! This feels nice!
It's so warm, I think I might fall asleep.
It's more comfortable than a thousand futons.
But, that means we can't take the ship through any place where these clouds are.
Hey, look for a route the ship can use while you're up there!
Okay, yosh!
Oi, Luffy!
There's something else over here!
What? Really?
Hey! Where're you going!?
Quit playing around!
What's that?
A gate?
Yeah, there's a huge gate underneath that fall-looking thing.
So there's something man-made here?
Nothing is out of the question on this sea.
Well, we'll know once we get through here!
Go left next!
No, right!
IT WAS LEFT!
I'll call the Armor Ossan!
DON'T!
Stop!
Moron!
Yosh, we made it through!
It really is a gate…
And look! Those clouds that looked like a waterfall really are a fall!
It's flowing over that new type of cloud we just saw.
Let's see, let's see… "Heaven's Gate"
A gate to Heaven?
Oi! Is this a joke!?
It's like we're going to die!
Or, what if we're all dead already?
Oh. That would certainly account for all the weird stuff here.
Huh!? We're dead!?
Heaven, eh? Sounds like fun!
Funally goin' there!
We're not going to die!
What was that for!?
Because you made that bad joke!
Why did you hit me too…?
Oi, look over there!
Someone's coming out!
Look! On her back!
W-Wings!
An angel!
So that's a real angel?
She looks like a prune!
E-Excuse us…
I am the appointed lookout of Heaven's Gate, Amazon.
Sightseeing?
Or fighting?
S-Sightseeing would be closer, I guess…
We wanna go to Sky Island!
Sky Island's on the other side of this gate, right?
What do you mean, fighting?
It doesn't matter which.
Just pay the immigration fee, E1,000,000,000 per person, and be on your way.
That's the law.
1-1,000,000,000!?
There's that extol thing again.
How much is 1,000,000,000 extil in beli?
No matter what it is, 1,000,000,000's gotta be a lot!
1,000,000,000 for one person… 7,000,000,000 for seven people.
We're only going in.
Why does it cost that much to enter?
This old granny must have her wires crossed-
Excuse me, but about the money…
If… If by some chance…
… we didn't have enough…
You can pass.
We can!?
Or, you can also not pass.
I am neither a guardian nor a warrior.
I only listen to your will.
Okay, let's go!
Let's go to Sky Island!
We don't have any money, but we're going through, Granny!
I see! Seven of you, yes?
Yeah, but…
How do we get up to Sky Island-?
Something's coming up!
Inhabitant of the White Sea, the Speedy Shrimp.
W-We started moving!
Whoa! A huge shrimp!
It's going up the fall!
Hold on tight!
This thing's fast!
It goes all the way to the top!
I, Keeper of Heaven's Gate, Amazon…
… call to the Priests of the almighty God!
Into God's Domain, Skypiea, seven individuals have now illegally entered!
Bestow upon them Heaven's Judgement!
At the time, these guys were crying and had given up on thier lives, but I told them :