Luffy and its crew entered
in the Lost Forest of Upper Yard…
Where they face the terrible one
Ordalie of the Bubbles of the Satori Priest.
Meanwhile, Gan Fall is
embanked by the Shura Priest.
KNIGHT OF THE SKY!!!
He, Nami!
You see something of up there?!
It will be a declaration of war
against God Very Powerful Eneru!
Firm your mouth! Your
bad breath escapes.
Here Ordalie of the Love!
THIS MEC EAST SHINGLES!!!
To crush!
Let us revive the Flame of Shandia!
Wiper the Warrior
Gan Fall, Former God,
Upper Yard penetrated.
Eneru will be caught some with him.
You think that Gan Fall
projects to defy Eneru?
You believe that this old wreck has
enough tripe to do it?
That there is,
Aisa?
Two votes have just died out.
How?
Hein, Mantra?
Yes.
Very of a blow, at the moment.
It is what your Mantra you said ace, Aisa?
Two was keep silent?
You are sure?
No doubt.
Each one of us knows.
Since it was born…
it has this mysterious gift to feel
remote people, Mantra.
Two votes are
extinct, it is well that?
Yes.
At the same time.
I believe… that it acts
of Gan Fall and a Priest.
They were entretués?
Good work, species of old turned sour.
Ca leaves us three Priests.
What a aubaine!
It would be said that the Paradise
heard our prayers.
It is the occasion or never
to crush the Priests!
Ouais!
You for the attack prepare
general on Upper Yard!
Ouais!
Today still, Wiper frightens you.
Go, releases maintaining me.
He, Laki! Wait!
What?
It is not Gan Fall
who overcame the Priest.
There are other people over there,
it is they which did that!
Other people?
These inhabitants of the Blue Sea
who are assembled on Skypiea?
I do not know, but
they are very strong!
Then…
Pay attention.
Of agreement.
Aisa, gives me your bag.
Hein? Not, I cannot
! It is my secret bag!
There is a treasure inside!
I know.
I will report a memory to you.
It is true?
Yes.
One finally arrived there.
Us to ridicule at this point…
It is which, these guys?
How it made for
to guess our attacks?
HE!
Luffy! Sanji!
I found the boat!
Quickly! It will leave the forest!
Is Oh, Usopp well?
He, it says that one will lose the boat!
Ca fears! Still a little and
it will reach the exit!
He, come by here and
you with me stud!
With you?
It left!
ussop has
Perfect! I have it!
Ouah! Be the best for you, Usopp!
Ca hurts, dumbs! You
please me complete or what?
Very well, all on board!
Cretin, I have the back
in crumbs now.
He, you fixed it well.
Nothing is impossible with me.
For once you have an good idea!
You worried for nothing!
Have-HAVE-await!
The cord goes…
Afflicted, Sanji-kun! One
would say well that one will die!
You are sure?!
Me too?!
Why?
That you serf of lesson.
It… was enough that I catch the boat.
BoiBil in choua, bwon buiblé Ba Boblêt Bedue… (At all events, one left the Lost Forest…)
I… I cannot swim.
The Knight of the sky…
The funny one of bird also…
It is true, it has the capacities
of a Fruit of the Demon like me.
Shit!
I cannot save anybody…
It is the end…
I lose consciousness…
Did Satori fail?
It lost the control of its Mantra.
That proves its lack of experience.
These inhabitants of the Blue Sea
have the air different from the others.
This incident on the Furnace bridge
Sacrificial was not envisaged.
But even if they are escaped,
they will not leave this island.
Now, most important, it is…
Priest of Skypiea
Celestial guard Gedatsu
You hear the sad one
voice of the warrior, Holy?
It does not matter the number of times,
the result is always the same one.
Gan Fall was overcome by Shura,
but Ordalie of the Bubbles failed.
This day proves very animated.
We will not let them pass.
It is stupid to imagine
that they will be able to see God.
The sun goes soon
to sleep on Upper Yard…
Priest of Skypiea Ohm, Celestial Stockbreeder.
But the situation goes
to worsen more and more.
Priest of Skypiea
Shura, Celestial Rider
Fugitive or not, that is equal for me!
I finally found somebody
worthy to receive my anger!
Listen to me, warriors!
Upper Yard is plunged in chaos!
We will have never again
an occasion like that one!
Our goal is the Sanctuary of God!
Do not fear Eneru!
The Large Karugara Warrior
we will protect forever!
OUAIS!
Braham!
Kamakiri!
Genbou!
Ouais!
Laki!
Yes!
Return in life.
One separates here.
Us swearwords in front of
Large Karugara Warrior!
To revive the Flame of Shandia!
OUAIS!
You here is, Shandia!
Would this island be…?
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
It was what?
An explosion, obviously.
I heard one of them presently,
but this one was different.
Good, we do not stop!
Does all go well for you, Nami?
You acted oddly since
that you are descended from the tree.
What did you see?
You saw God or what?
At all!
Even if I say it to you,
you compren…!
Ca becomes ridiculous!
Why this is so difficult
to go on top?!
But it is you who said that
this way would be faster.
Enough lost time,
stir up yourself a little!
What you ace seen at the end?
It does not matter, satisfy you
to follow me!
This way will carry out us
straight to the shore.
But come to help me!
If you are followed, you are
judicious to go in front.
The shore?
Yes, completely.
I need me
to bring closer to be sure.
Because I always do not arrive
not to believe my eyes of them.
Me either.
Something worries me too me.
I do not have any final proof…
But if my assumption
proved to be true…
that would become interesting.
Very interesting.
My reason to live
would exist indeed.
But for the moment, it
is only one assumption.
Hein?
I am… alive?
Ouiiille!!
The Knight of the Sky!
A doctor! A doctor!
Ah yes, it is me!
God thank you, it is alive.
But, it is strange…
One had run all.
Who left us from there?
Hein? Who?
“God”?
Who said that?!
How…?
We are close to the sea.
Hein?
I hear the waves.
Listen.
It is true! One is there almost!
One goes there!
Say to us what you ace considering!
It is what these “ahahah”?
I hear another noise
mixed with that of the waves…
Ouais, a noise rather disturbing…
Noise of all one
army which passes to the attack.
A little as one heard in Alabasta.
You believe that one should worry?
Do not make any you for Chopper.
It is left there very well when it wants.
Not him, but it
Captain and others.
Luffy?
After our removal, it has
had to leave to our research.
It was very excited
to come on this island.
I do not know only God
for making…
but it surely does not go us
to let pass also easily.
And then there are these guys who
fight between them, over there.
The situation becomes complicated.
It is certain.
But they will be left there.
There are all our own problems.
They are not while being done
concern for them that they will be helped.
It is true.
He, Nami!
He!
I swear you, Usopp, you make like that!
Of agreement.
“He! Upright, cretin!”
“What? Already the morning?”
It is Completely Zoro!
You finished you
to split the mouth, cretins!
We do not know what is
arrived at Nami-san and Robin-chan…
And for Zoro and Chopper?
There remain still three Priests over there.
They must undergo one of their Ordalies.
“It is Ordalie of the Love.”
For the moment, one must keep
the course on the sacrificial Furnace bridge.
Included/understood?
Boui.
(Yes.)
Soft be unemployed décholé.
(We are sorry.)
Why it has
accelerated of a blow?
Whore, as soon as one arrives
to the sea, it will drink the cup.
Then my eyes had not been mistaken.
Look at that!
He, Nami! I have some enough.
Say to us what occurs…
Not need to make
a drawing, not true?
Look at that…
Doesn't Ca say anything to you?
It is not a fairy tale.
It was seen right this morning.
But what does that want to say?
What this trick which
was in bottom fout here?
It is exactly the same one.
Not, not completely.
It is a piece of it
that we saw in bottom.
A piece?
Ca intrigued me since one moment.
There should not be
of ground on the Sea of Opal.
It was impossible that this island
was formed without ilonimbus.
What wants to say, that this
island which one calls Upper Yard…
was on ground formerly.
I knew that there was some
thing of odd with this house.
There was a stage, but not
of staircase to go up to the first.
And it was no beneficial to build
a house at the edge of a cliff.
The shore was formed afterwards
a tear of the island.
IN-INCROYABLE!
Imbeciles, look at more attentively.
Isn't a dreamer?
It is right
slap-with-l'oeil.
How that?
It was that a decoration?!
It is a piece of the same island.
This island was Jaya!
Then, a day, this island
separated into two…
and a half is
found in the sky.
But how is this possible?
A band of Birds of the South… But…
Why?
Why they are so large?!
Ca can be only
this gigantic running.
As insane as that can appear.
It is you who saved us?
Hein?! This man is God?!
My name is Montblanc Cricket.
Afflicted for presently.
I thought that you had some
after my gold like these idiots.
You want to say that the island
celestial does not exist?!
I know somebody who
its existence affirmed, but…
It was famous to have been
largest of the liars.
It IS NOT ME!
“Norland, the Liar”
“I saw a gold mountain
on an island of the Large Sea. “
The courageous King, wanting to see that
of its eyes, embarked immediately.
But all that the King and his men
discovered was a simple jungle.
It is represented with one
to smile idiotic on the drawing.
But he died in sadness,
eyes full with tears.
He affirmed that the city had finished at the bottom of
water, following the movement of the tectonic plates.
But for everyone, it was only one
poor dead loss seeking only to justify itself.
It is a duel against
that which ruined my life.
It is for that you plunge each
day until you do fall sick?
My goal is not
to prove its innocence.
I want just to regulate
that, before clamser.
Q-which man!
Let us stop…
Norland.
Give me your hand!
STOP SINGING!
The gold city that Norland
had discovered in bottom…
did not run.
Jaya always was there…
floating in the sky!