Bastard, what the hell are you doing?!
STOP IT!
What the hell are you doing to my sea maps?
I don't give a crap about mermen,
Or the sea maps!
The situation!
I don't know anything about it, but
I'LL DESTROY IT ALL!
GOMU GOMU NO...
ONO!
(Axe!)
NAMI!
YOU ARE MY NAKAMA!!
YAHOOOOO!!!!
SETTING OFF WITH A SMILE!
FAREWELL MY HOMETOWN, COCOYASHI VILLAGE!
ARLONG PARK HAS FALLEN!
We're...
We're free!
Everyone! We're gonna dance and celebrate!
Arlong Park has fallen!
We've been living for this day for eight years!
We've been living to rejoice upon this day!
YEAAAHH!!
Tomorrow and the next, let's party until we drop!
Yeah!
Onee-chan!
Oh, Chabo!
I just had a look at Arlong Park.
It's amazing! It's all smashed to bits!
Pretty impressive, huh?
Yeah! Whoever did it must be an awesome guy!
Who was it? He's still here, isn't he?
The man who defeated Arlong?
Yeah, he's right over there.
Which one? Who?
The guy wearing the straw hat.
Is that really the guy who freed the island?
I found it hard to believe myself.
Meat! Meat? Isn't there anymore?
They're still working on him?
He looked pretty torn up, that Zoro.
Well, duh.
Any other guy would've taken a year or two to heal!
Fool!
You tried to handle an injury
this serious by yourself?
It hurts!
Are you guys really pirates?
Don't you,
have a doctor on your ship?
A doctor? Not a bad idea!
Luffy...
But we need a musician first, right Zoro?
Why?
Because, pirates love to sing. Don't you know?
So, why is that more important?
Hey Doctor, where's Nami?
I don't see her anywhere.
Nami, huh?
Well, if she's not here, then she must be there.
Huh?
What's with you, Nami?
You're still here?
They're looking for you, your nakama.
Hey, Nojiko...
Gen-san...
If Bellemere-san was still alive...
You think she'd stop me from becoming a pirate?
A pirate?
Are you kidding?
She'd never let her precious
little girl become a pirate!
She wouldn't stop ya.
NOJIKO!
And even if she did say ''No'',
Would you listen?
NO WAY!
Now I get it...
What's with you, Gen-san?
You two are without doubt, Bellemere's daughters.
Gen-san?
Nami, you've made up your mind already, right?
So just do what you feel is right.
Just like your mother did.
Bellemere would've wanted no less.
Boy, I'm full.
It's nice to have someone feeding me for a change.
How's your wound, Zoro?
With rest and a good meal, I'll heal up soon enough.
That's good.
Seriously, why's this stupid party still going on?
It's been three days now.
Ain't that a good thing?
When you feel happy, you should
be able to enjoy yourself.
Hey Sanji! You were eating
some kind of melon earlier.
What was it?
What about all that meat you've
got there in your hands?
Oh, that?
It's called Namu-Hamu-Melon, because
it had Namu-Hamu on top.
NAMU-HAMU-MELON? Sounds tasty!
W-Where was it?
Beats me.
It's a potluck party for the whole island,
so someone must have brought them...
He's gone.
He's been eating like that for three days.
Well, my stomach's full.
So now it's time...
TO PICK UP THE CHICKS!!!
I'm the one who defeated the invincible mermen!
Go Go!
The hero who fights bravely, for the sake of love!
CAPTAIN USOPP!!
So let's sing about the exploits of the brave Usopp!
Who? Who? Who defeated the mermen~?
Man, this's so lame.
I thought you'd be more like,
That would be Usopp-u-chachacha!
''It's not fair! Why couldn't this happen
before my father had to die?''
Or something.
Well, I did think that, at first.
But now, I'm more concerned about my future.
Your future?
See, we were saved by the Straw-hat Nii-chan.
But starting tomorrow, we're gonna
have to take care of ourselves.
We shouldn't forget the past,
but it's not important now.
Rather, the important thing now, is the future.
What do we do from now on? What did we learn?
We are the future of this village.
That's what I've been thinking about.
You're too mature!
W-Why are you pinching me? What did I do?
Man, I wanted to pick on you a little more.
You ARE picking on me!
You, you tattooed skank!
''Skank'' is fine by me!
Can it be removed?
Leave it to me. I've been thinking
of how to remove it.
But there will be some scarring, it's a tattoo after all.
That's the nature of these things.
I was stupid.
I knew I couldn't take it off.
I don't want anyone to see this!
ThIs... This awful tattoo.
The truth is... I'm not one of Arlong's nakama!
I don't want to wear his mark!
Nojiko, what's that?
What? Oh, this?
It's nothing, just some body art.
Just like Nami, Right?
Hey Doctor.
I'd like you to make a new one for me.
Of this.
Hey, those guys can dance, too!
Song #185 of ''The Praise of Captain Usopp!''
Hey, BelIemere.
Your daughters have grown into
wonderful, strong individuaIs.
Just like you were, long ago.
What'd you say?!
You're joining the Marines?
Yeah, don't try to stop me!
'Coz I'm goin'!
My mind's made up!
We'll work hard, to live our lives to the fullest.
We've been through so many hardships.
And so, I think I'll laugh to my heart's
content, until I look like a fool.
NAMU-HAMU-MELON!
Eh? There's nothing to eat here.
Guess I'm goin' back.
WAIT, BOY!
Huh? A grave?
Someone died?
Yeah, a long time ago.
Oh. That's unfortunate.
Then I should say, ''Gochujousama deshita.''
Or was it, ''Gosuchousama deshita...''
Or, ''Gotsujou...''
''Gotodou...''
''Goshuushou-sama deshita!''
Yeah, that '-deshita'.
Listen' boy. I know Nami's going
to sail with you, to be a pirate.
It's a dangerous journey,
I know it can't be helped.
That's okay.
But if you ever take Nami's smile away,
I'm gonna hunt you down and kill you.
Well, I don't plan on steaIing anything, so...
UNDERSTAND?!
I got it!
Sing it again~!
Here comes song #368 of ''The
Praise of Captain Usopp!''
Who is it? Who is it?
The cooolest guy in the wooorld...? Usopp~
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Wow! The food looks so delicious today!
Hey, you two, do you know what day it is today?
It's the day I first met Nojiko and Nami!
The day you became my daughters!
Hey now, stop crying.
It's just a storm. So what If our crops get ruined?
It's just a storm. So what if our crops get ruined?
You two need to be brave and smile, be strong girls.
And if you do, happy tImes will come again.
They'll definitely come.
Nami! Could you pass me the salt?
So you drew this sea map all by yourself?
I've been studying navigation!
Navigation?
It's Nami's dream, right?
I'm gonna sail around the world using my skills!
And then, I'll make a world map
of all the places I've seenl
So, this map of our island marks the
first step to your dream, right?
It's finally over, Bellemere-san.
It took eight long years, but we're finally free.
Me, and everyone else.
It's just like you said BeIlemere-san...
As long as you keep living, good
times will eventually come again.
It came true!
And now, everyone in the village is smiling,
from the bottom of their hearts.
Me? I've decided to leave the island!
Don't worry, I'll be okay.
They're really good people, and pretty strong, too!
For the last eight years, I've drawn so many maps.
But this is the onIy one I managed to save.
From now on, I'll only draw maps for myself.
I want to see the world! Together with my nakama!
That's my dream.
So...
So, I'm not sure when I'll be coming back.
I'm going now, okay?
This is the last one, right?
Yup!
Everything's onboard?
Yeah!
Alright then. They've stocked us with
food. Looks like we're ready.
We've only been here a few days,
but I feel like we've made so many
memories on this island, y'know?
Yeah!
Aniki's, thanks. We owe you all so much.
We're goin' back to our normal
jobs as bounty hunters.
We'll bid our farewells for now,
but hopefully we'll meet again one day.
Take care, a'right?
You too, Aniki!
Alright, let's get going too!
H- Hey! Wait a minute!
What about Nami-san?
I thought she wasn't coming.
WHY NOT?!
Bastard! You said something
rude to her again didn't you?
Why would I do that?
Why else?!
I see, that's true, he's got a point.
You're trying to ge in the way of
me and Nami-san's true love!!
She doesn't have a reason to be a pirate anymore.
She'll be happier if she stayed here.
- What'd you say!?
WHAT ABOUT MY HAPPINESS?!
IF NAMI-SAN DOESN'T GET ONBOARD,
I LOSE 98.72% OF MY REASON TO BE HERE!!
Hey! Y'know I never found that Namu-Hamu-MeIon!
Hey, where's Na-chan?
I haven't seen her since this morning.
What did you say?!
She left all the money?
The whole 100 million beli?
Yeah, she left it with a letter.
She's not planning on bringing any with her?
But she worked so hard for it!
She said she'd just steal more.
Once she makes up her mind, there's no changing it.
This is ridiculous!
We didn't even get to thank her.
Nami-san!!
Nami!
Nami?
NAMI-SAAAAAN!!
START THE SHIP OUT!
Huh? What's up with her? She started running?
She said to set sail.
B-But!
Wait, does she plan on leaving without
hearing our thanks and appreciation?
She can't-!
Lower the sail!
Hey, they're setting off!
Wait! We haven't thanked you yet!
Stop, Na-chan!
Stop right there!
This is terribly rude! I won't allow it!
Hey, you sure you wanna let her leave this way?
It's alright. It's her decision.
NAMI!
Why?
NAMI!!
Don't tell me?!!
My wallet's gone! Mine too!
Mine too!
Take care everyone!
YOU LITTLE BRAT!
Oi. She hasn't changed a bit.
Who knows when she'll turn on us again.
Nami-san, GOOD!
You li'l thieving cat!!
Come back here with my wallet!
You bad girl!
Come back anytime!
Take care!
Thank you so much!
BOY!
Don't you dare forget our promise!
Goodbye everyone! I'm off!!
She really did it!
Unbelievable! My sister's a real piece of work alright!
Have fun.
Here, Genzo.
What's this, Doctor? A piece of paper...
That silly girl.
She hasn't changed. She even got another tattoo.
What's this symbol?
She said it was a tangerine and a pinwheel.
Hey Gen-san, where did your pinwheel go?
No need for it anymore.
I'm off...
Hey! Gen-san!
Don't get so close to Nami!
But, I only wanted to see her smilel
Gen-san, your face is too scary, it's making her cry!
But what can I do about that?
I got it! Maybe if I did this?
I'll just keep it right here.
How 'bout this? Nami-chaan~
You've got to be kidding. It's just
a pinwheel, Nami's not going to...
Ah! She's laughing.