IMPACT
burn blade!
You believe capacity to move
more quickly than the lightning?
FLEE, WIPER!!
NOT!!
Voices… The voices disappeared…
Thin then. My electricity seems
to be itself propagated in Milky Road.
The poor imbeciles.
Disappeared ISCED!
Splendid ruins of Shandora!!
Which talent.
Nami-san, they is marvellous!
It is again with you.
Yes, thank you.
I adore it.
It is much faster.
Yes, the Jet Dial had disappeared
since hundreds of years.
I was surprised to see
that this Waver was equipped with it.
But… What we must
to make now?
If everyone were there, we would have
been able to guide you towards bank of Skypiea.
Yes…
For the moment, I must carry out the boat on
the coast where we were given go.
I think that they are well…
Lastly, if all the four are together,
they will be left there.
There is no group
from four on the island.
Hein?
There is no group
of more than two people.
If four people were
together, I would know it.
Mantra?
The gift which this God has
and isn't its Priests?
I make use of it since my birth.
It is for that I am afraid.
You cannot imagine as it is
horrible when a voice disappears…
You still cry?
I DO NOT CRY!
Stupid girl of
Blue sea! Cretin!
Waver d' Aisa-san is damaged…
And found we it whereas it
made attack by celestial sharks.
What did you intend to make here?
I do not know.
But, it was necessary that
I do something!
Laki…
You all…
I wonder whether all
the world is well…
Oh not, that fears.
My backpack is outside.
The trees died and
there is no fruit above.
I sought this Bentou
for the breakfast.
It would be said that I fell
in funny of cave.
I still did not see the exit.
I wonder whether the others
found the Gold City.
Ca must be pretty with all this gold.
Ah yes, a long time ago of that, somebody in the bar said that gold delicious was cooked with the frying pan.
Ca makes one moment that I walk.
It is the hour to eat.
Not bad.
Who is there?!
What you tests to say to me?
You want my bentou?
You will not have anything!
Break!
Stop following me!
Listen!
I swallowed all my bentou!
I do not have anything any more to eat!
And even if I had some,
I would not give any you!
Now, out of my sight!
And you steps of through.
In which direction you do look at?
You want to fight? Hein?
In three hours, only 5
people on 81 will be still upright.
My prediction will be achieved
in one hour.
Currently, there remain 25 about it.
It is impossible!
Eneru God!
What does it make here?
I will kill it!
And now,
it of remainder 24.
He well, He well, my expensive!
You do not have the air so strong only that.
STOMACH
The monument!
Veinte flower
Calendula!
You will protect this city
in ruin still a long time?
You do not feel…
pas le less interest towards
our historical heritage.
I am not interested in the past!
Words of insane.
For which you take to me?!
PUNCH
I must attract it with the variation of the ruins.
If not, this cretin all will destroy.
This day…
I believed…
that my goal had been buried with
the underground sanctuary of Alubarna.
Believer to have very lost, I decided
to accompany Luffy in its voyage.
But like the unknown history
disappeared from the world in lower part,
there are perhaps indices,
some share in these ruins!
You intend to run like
that still a long time?!
You… finished running, now?
Yes.
But it is too late.
Too much late?
Never I will forgive myself.
You will never forgive me?
You make a point much of protecting these ruins.
Even if they do not belong to you.
Indeed.
The ruins do not belong to anybody.
I do not want to discuss
longer with you.
Do not make any you.
In little time, you will not be any more
able to speak, even if you want of it.
You will be soon
flattened like a pancake!
DROP
Here, we can fight freely.
Treinte flower
You charge a such mad bull.
Discover the weight of
the history which you destroyed!
Pound!
It is heavy…
Take that!
TEN-FOLD CENTERS!
CENTER MOUNTAIN!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
My eyes!
What?
Hein?! He, wait!
Dials are with back!
Wait! Dials.!
The monuments which you destroyed
had a priceless value.
Invaluable treasures with
incommensurable importance.
The history can be repeated, but them
men cannot turn over in the past.
But you do not include/understand
not, isn't this?
I… Co… include/understand…
I…… will not start again
more, forgives…
I will never forgive it.
Then, I will have to kill you!
My fingers!
My fingers!!
Seis Fleur
Delphinium!
Ah, what?!
Stop!
Wait!
Where are you…?
Stop!!
No matter what you say, it is too late.
Ca hurts…
Clutch!
What you have fact is unnamable.
It must be the center of the city.
This monument does not appear on the chart.
Perhaps the buildings were dispersed
during the propulsion in the sky.
I do not include/understand…
Then why did you come here?
Hope and prediction
are two different things.
I expected to find
Rio Ponéglyphe.
Of all Ponéglyphes
existing on this ground…
It is the only stele which
tell the True History.
It is Rio Ponéglyphe.
True History? About what is it?
Ca is enough.
I sought during twenty years…
And it was the last
track that I had found.
This place was my last
hope, and it was a failure.
If I must die here, that is appropriate to me.
I am tired to follow
road which carried out me up to now.
Whereas I do not wish
that to learn the history…
Too many enemies are put
across my dream.
There is something of strange.
Is this really the City of Gold?
As I thought it, proportions and
topography are completely different.
And most unusual…
The single entry is at the higher level.
This would be…?!
I can go in lower part!
They is roomy.
As I thought it, these
ruins hide something.
They come from the Blue Sea, but
seem to be built on a îlonimbus.
I knew that something clochait.
The ruins on the clouds are in fact only
the upper part of the buildings of the city.
There is much more in lower part.
Light?
800 years ago…
the city of Shandora disappeared suddenly.
But it of it is nothing.
A great part remained intact…
And always also splendid.
Here the Gold City, Shandora!
This would be…?!
Another question, if I…
You want to say that the wire of the history
buried can be woven between them?
And what this Ponéglyphe is the trace?
It is here, in obviousness.
The ancestral writing of Ponéglyphes.
Only those which have creates Ponéglyphes
are able to decipher these symbols.
“Keep the truth in your
hearts, the closed mouth. “
“We are those who
will weave the history, “
[Belfry = bell-tower, turn of guet]
It is true.
There was here, an enormous gold bell.
It was in the book
of edge of Norland.
All books of
city were flarings.
History of this city…
was éradiquée.
They will be left there
all alone, not truth?
Stop following me!
Does Ca go down now?
Ponéglyphe was
transported in this city!
I am sure.
They fought here,
against a powerful enemy.
The Gold City, Shandora,
fought in order to protect
Ponéglyphe then was destroyed!
If it is the case,
Then the Large Belfry
between the four furnace bridges…
Perhaps tell the True History…
It is perhaps Rio Ponéglyphe.