Against the Forces of Wapol!
Capacities of the Fruit Baku Baku!
This odor…
It is him!
Doctorine! Come quickly!
It…
Wapol is of return!
I see.
It is him?
This dumb of Jamagushi!
Look at, nothing did not change since my departure!
It is MY castle.
The Kingdom of Drum can finally reappear!
Please, Wapol-Sama!
Look at the top of the tower…!
What does this hideous flag make up there?
Where the flag of the Kingdom of Drum passed?!
I cramé it!
Te here is finally, Dr. Kureha!
The surviving last of my great “Hunting for the Doctors”.
This castle does not belong to you any more.
It is not a place for a band of snotty-nosed kid like you.
Leave this country!
The Kingdom of Drum does not exist any more.
What?
WAIT!
I will put a beating to him!
W-W-Wapol-Sama, it is straw hat!
Wapol-Sama!
It was right…
You gave us wire with retordre, the last time.
It would be said that you are still across our road.
What do they make here, these?
The other time, I had to escape because I carried the people wounded on my back, but this time…
I do not need more to retain me!
Dumb! How oses you to raise the hand on the King of the Kingdom of Drum…
… and to make this unforgivable act?!
Exact! He is the King of this country!
You are held in front of the King who controls all the inhabitants of the island!
And then?! I have anything with foutre strictly of it!
Eh kid.
You know them?
Ouais, it is Jamagushi!
Jamagushi the pirate!
Jamagushi?
It does to nothing but pose problems us!
He ate my boat and drove out my friends.
This time, it will not draw any on so good account!
, You wait do not have cold, equipped like that?
Look at yourself.
He said that he was a King?!
Then it is not a pirate!
DO NOT OCCUPY You OF HIM!
Ah! The imbecile!
Finally you realize of your insolence.
Wapol-Sama is the king of the Kingdom of Drum!
When we met it, he devoted himself temporarily to piracy for reasons which are clean for him.
But today, it is not pirate any more; it thus comes to take again its throne and to control this country again.
Eh! It curdles here!
It IS WHAT I STOPPED NOT SAYING to YOU!
It makes -50°C!
Do they foutent us?!
Wapol-Sama!
Now… I am really in anger.
Straw hat…
I will puff out you very believed!
Can Euh, said, you wait a little?
Luffy left to seek a jacket.
IT LEFT?!
I wanted to ask you…
Did its arms lengthen?
Ouais, it can lengthen them.
It is an elastic man.
C-how that?
It is a monster!
Like that, this old witch and Straw hat squattent my castle.
Once these eliminated dogs, nobody any more will dare to rebel against me!
You are right completely.
This day will be that of the glorious return of the Kingdom of Drum!
And you will pass there the first, Dr. Kureha!
You one right cheek to install you in my castle during my absence!
You even set up this monstrous flag there!
This castle is fall it from Hiluluk.
I insane completion of this dilapidated place.
I see that you did not realize that it is this reindeer which hoisted the flag of Hiluluk up there.
This flag with the tête de mort enabled me to face all the diseases!
Tête de mort?
It is the symbol of a will which defies the impossible one!
As a doctor, I must save this country!
While raising this flag, I will fight like a pirate!
The Doctor fought to save this country…
To raise this flag…
Lead me near the patients!
I came to look after Isshi-20!
You still do not include/understand? It is a trap!
Isshi-20 go very well, as you can note it!
What?
I am relieved. Nobody is sick here.
I really thought that the country was in danger.
That to say if it is not that… I fell into the panel.
Eh yes.
When do you believe that people die?
Doctor!
When a ball in full heart is drawn to them?
Not.
When they are reached of a terminal illness?
When they take a soup of champignons vénéneux?
Not!
They die when… they fall into the lapse of memory.
Even after my death, my dream will be carried out.
The ravaged heart of the people will be cured.
Why do you cry, Dalton?
You think… that it is the same thing for this country?
Will is needed.
Do not worry you, Chopper.
It is not your mushroom which will be right of me…
It was really a formidable life!
Good-bye, charlatan.
Thank you in you, Chopper!
The Doctor in front of this castle…
He died to save this country!
And now…
It is fall it from the Doctor!
Fall it?
Of this imbecile of doctor?
To profane my castle with this dirtiness of flag?!
CRAMEZ ME THIS FLAG AT ONCE!
You will not put the feet in this castle…
NEVER.
Wapol-Sama, it is…
I remember! This day…
It is him, the monster which ran after this stupid doctor!
This flag represents…
… will of the Doctor.
I will not allow anybody to touch there!
NEVER!
No pity!
We will take again the castle!
Do not save anybody!
You will also fight, grandmother?
Grandmother?
If you cannot occupy you, I will undertake some.
Thank you well…
Wapol-Sama, leave the-me!
I will do myself them one by one!
Doctorine!
He, He, He Afroman!
To balance your ball afro on a woman, that is not made, my brother!
I see that ended you up including/understanding.
Ca sticks.
What?! What occurs with this foutue swell afro?!
Static electricity?
Precisely.
Ca curdles… that curdles!
A jacket… a jacket… a jacket…!
Where is my jacket?
What occurs outside?
There is much noise.
Outside, it curdles.
You do not know where is my jacket?
It is not what I asked you.
I want to know what occurs outside.
Oh, just a small brawl.
Isn't all is well?
Yes. Rendors.
You can take my jacket.
Your jacket is really not signal!
In any case, it holds hotter than holds it!
Did Ah ouais?
Good of agreement, since I do not have cold.
I go back there!
And to say that I thought that it occurred something.
Dumb!
I will make you the skin, Jamagushi!
SHIT!
It is what this ball afro?!
I cannot disencumber me!
When there is not more, there is still!
Electric Marimo
Whore, it is what these tricks?!
Moreover, it is disgusting!
Eh, the reindeer!
Instead of you to turn the inches, come to help me!
I arrive!
Quickly, removes to me these tricks!
It is too feeling reluctant!
And it is disgusting! It is disgusting!
Ca is stuck to me maintaining, take again it!
Moron, does not give again them to me!
Guards at least one!
Not question, it is feeling reluctant!
Ca returns to me sick!
Stop!
But what do you foutez, both?
It would be said that you do not have the esprit d'équipe.
Let warn you to me, Eleki-Marimo are perhaps “feeling reluctant”, but they are very flammable.
Shit!
It will put fire at the balls afro!
He! Where you go?!
To launch the Soft food Plan!
The Soft food Plan…?
BUT It IS ME the SOFT FOOD?!
Snow! Snow! Snow!
Release!
Wapol-Sama!
Oh not!
Chopper!
Ah! Attention, I arrive!
Luffy!
My leg catches!
Your leg?
Like that?
It is impec, clings well!
Not badly.
Thank you! You are really brilliant!
He, Luffy!
Ca would not be the jacket of Nami-San only you carry?!
Ouais.
Look at! This guy is always in life!
It is its hippo which was dispatched in the airs.
Remove it! Shit!
Are Wapol-Sama, you well?
They are much stronger than it was thought!
I hate them!
I… all will kill them!
I will show them…
… capacities of the Fruit Baku Baku!
Wapol-Sama…
Look at doing me, now!
Oh! It was raised!
It should not be able to be raised after such a blow.
It is really resistant!
Chess!
Say to me what we had with the menu today.
Then, on the boat, we had “a gun jumped to butter”, “a rare extra gun”…
… and to finish, “one salade composée of powder and boulet de canon”.
We also had “a house roasted” at the village.
But it puffs out anything, that one?!
It must surely puff out all that it finds.
Observe attentively…
… how I transform my meals into flesh and bone!
It prepares something…
What?
Shoku = Food
A house?!
Supeeeer!
I keep the best for the end!
My royal technique!
What?!
IT IS PUFFING OUT ITS HENCHMEN!
It IS a CANNIBAL!
He finished.
Now, let us see seeing!
This splendid fusion!
What? A fusion?
I am the largest warrior of the Kingdom of Drum…
CHESSMARIMO!
PF, there is of them just one which is assembled on the shoulders of the other…
Too much brilliant!
DECREE TO SAY CONNERIES!
Remain your guards of course.
If they were as weak as they have the air of it,
their hunting for the doctors would have been a failure.
And the plain people could have put an end to it.
Regulate n°1 with the Kingdom of Drum:
“All those which disobey the king die!”
It is like that one controls this country!
Because this country is my country…
and this castle is my castle!
I will never admit that a shit of flag as that of this foutu doctor is hoisted there!
He soils the castle!
The symbol of the pirates…
He, the reindeer.
This flag…
For a man who raises the banner to the tête de mort, nothing is impossible!
It is what I taught you, Chopper!
Eh you! It is the flag of the Doctor!
The Doctor tried to save you too!
Chopper.
Do not hate the men.
Now, this country is sick.
The heart of the king is sick.
Why?
Is doctor… it likely no there to save this man?
I…
I will not have any evil…
… if you free this country immediately!
But what you tell, Chopper?!
You really believe to be able to reason a type like him?
But… I want just…
CHOPPER!
He, Jamagushi!
Straw hat!
When you claimed to be a pirate, that was only one lie, hein?
A pirate who did not want to risk his life…
You do not even know what this pirate flag represents!
What it…
Does what represent a pirate flag, Straw hat?
How if this stupid banner could represent something!
This is why you are if loose!
How?
One does not defend this flag with the light one!
Imbecile!
How if the king could die to hold up a pirate flag!
And you oses to put this flag up there!
Attention with you! It draws you above!
You believe that you can destroy this flag?
Luffy!
It touched it!
I dispatched you in the airs, microbe!
You see!
It is not destroyed!
Im-impossible!
It is nutcase!
I do not know with whom is this pirate flag, nor from where it comes…
… but it is a flag for which one engages his life!
One does not defend it with the light one!
IT IS NOT a FLAG WHICH YOU CAN HAVE FUN TO CLEAN UP!!
Narcotic…
It is thus that…
… a pirate!
You will never destroy it.
The tête de mort symbolizes our conviction!