There is a frog which makes crawl
What?
Turn and looks at!
Really?
Oi, Luffy.
You believe really what this idiot of admiral said?
It is impossible that a frog which makes crawl exists!!!
This frog makes crawl!
Everyone, let us follow!
Aye!
There is a headlight why here?
There is somebody over there?
It flew.
Yosh! The frog stopped, stop it as long as we can it.
We are wedged on something.
It is what this sound?
Back, behind, turn of approximately 180 degrees.
The train sailing on the sea
The watery city Seven Toilets
It is what that?!
Go quickly! Turn on the right, quickly!
It is what?
What is what it is that this scrap heap?
A boat?
Not!
It could not sail at sea with this form!
Eh, Frog, leave from there! What is what you insane?
It had it?
This boat was raising smoke?
Pirates?
Gran' my! Gran' my! They are pirates!
What? Is Ish it true Chimney?
Yosh! Come with `ze den-den mushi~!
It is a problem, somebody left the building.
It will call of the assistance?
Hold, Gran' my!
Ah, hello?
Um… What is what it was? I forgot it…
A drunkard?!
It is a good snack with saké.
Wow, delicious!
I am Chimney…
Here my cat, Gombe…
And it is Kokoro, my grandmother.
You are not robbers of train, is not this step?
I am Luffy, that which will become the Lord of the pirates!!!
Really?
Ouais!
Which interesting man.
Is Eh Chimney, a bateau a vapor?
But, normally, it should not be able to sail with this form.
You never saw it front, not true?
It is the only place in the world where will find it to you…
This Umi Ressha, we call it Puffing Tom.
Puffing Tom?
He turns his pallets and advances thanks to the vapor, and travels along a way on the sea.
A way?
Ouais!
It transports passengers of island to island.
Using a way under water surface.
He traverses the same road each day.
He transports also postal boats and articles.
It is true, there is a way!
Then it advances there above?
Indeed.
It is dangerous to enter a sector with marks and signals!
You should put the signal on other side. We did not know anything on this subject!
Even with all this danger of which you speak, he would not realize any!!!
It was cruel, you struck it with force! It was OUR prey.
Euh? You speak about Yokozuna?
Yes, the frog which makes crawl?
Yokozuna will not die of that. It is the major problem of Shift Station…
He adores to test his force against Umi Ressha. He will return…
To test its force?
For this reason he did not flee. He has some in the belly.
Stop joking! He disturbs us!
The pilot was destroyed several times.
[Pilot:bar of front fixed at the engine.]
To each time it comes, it causes wrong to the customers!
Then it is as that which it is.
Yosh, I will not eat it! I do not eat people who are given thoroughly in what they make.
You should think like that in any event, it is a frog.
Then now, where do you want to go?
If you want to take Umi Ressha from here, it will take you along.
“The city of the queen of Spring”, Holy Poplar…
“The city of the gourmet”, Pucchi…
“The city of the carnival”, San Faldo…
All these places are funny.
For the authorized people of the government, there is also another special route.
The island of the gourmet, Pucchi?
I see, it is from here the ossans not-populated islands came.
Yes, now that you mention it…
Ouais, let us go to the city of the gourmet.
Not question!
We have a boat, then we will not travel by the train…
We will follow the log poses.
Towards where it points?
In the East from here.
I see, then you move towards Water Seven?
The train comes from this island “Blue Station”.
It is a good place called “the watery city Water seven”
Seven toilets?
It is the best of all, a city filled with shipyards.
The engineers are best world there!
It is the principal supplier of the boats of the world government!
Impressing, isn't this?
Then there must be exceptional naval engineers too!
It is sure that there is! It is a difficult task for the best carpenters of the world.
Usopp!
Yosh, it is decided!
We will go over there and will find we a carpenter for our crew there.
I see, I see…
Then, wait one moment!
I return!
What?
Wait…
Hold… it is a simple chart of the island and an invitation letter!
Give that to the man named Iceberg and ridges to repair your batea well…
Water Seven is a very vast city. Then do not lose you there!
It is super sympathetic Kokoro-san! You are very nice.
We will also return to the house to Water Seven, before a long time.
Ouais, it is right!
If we meet again, I will show you my preferred store!
Oh really… Then I hope that we will still meet…
The log installation takes one week to be reloaded in Water Seven. You will have time to see certain things.
Ok, thank you!
Yosh, everyone! Loans for the departure!
Ouais!
Well we leave, thank you for information Kokoro-san, Chimney!
Made attention!
Attention with people of the government!
Allons-y!
The city of the meat!
What are you listening?
Which good breeze.
Perhaps what will we arrive at Water Seven earlier?
I hope for it.
Luffy, leaves me the task seek a naval engineer.
I will find a tempting beautiful woman!
Baka, it is a naval engineer!
That must be a man as large as a mountain!
5 meters!
If it is so large, it will not be able to remain on the boat!
It is not serious, as long as it is qualified.
The question is:Does somebody among them want to go up well on a boat of pirates?
I cannot wait any more… We will have another Nakama!
We are lucky to be arrived at the station in first…
Because one has this chart now!
If we follow this chart and return visit to this person called Iceberg.
Not far from there…
I see…
I INCLUDE/UNDERSTAND NOTHING THERE!
This drawing is same style as Luffy.
5 meters
Good let us seek a guy like that!
If ever there exists, I leave!
Me also, if I could find a boat, I will leave at sea!
But it seems to have octopus blood, it will drive out me probably also sea!
About what speak?
You all, come here!
I will distribute the money for the week!
Really?! Waaah, me initially!
Which chance.
Oh, remains on line!
Go, on line!
What is what does not go, Usopp?
These plates of iron and these parts rafistolées
still in memory of our adventures.
When I think of the way in which they will be completely repaired, the emotion gains me.
I include/understand, but!
More especially as since we entered Grand line, Merry underwent large damage!
The platforms squeak and the hold flees…
If we leave it like that, they will be dangerous as well for us as for the boat.
Ouais, but now we have much money.
We can renovate still best!
We can also improve it.
Yosh, let us add some guns!
Ouais, let us add a bronze statue!
Is Oi, it well here?
There is an island, I see an ISLAND!!
Yosh, that everyone rows!
There is enough wind, do not spend our energy unnecessarily!
Marvellous.
Narcotic!
It is what Ca?!
What a énooooooorrme fountain of water!
It is large, surely an industrial island!
There is Umi Ressha!
Impressing! All this water.
From where is what all that comes?
Very interesting… from the fountain, water descends all the channels towards the sea!
Oh, do we have to make a race in this water slip?
A race?
Not question…
Aho, leaves it. Be stunned for you or what?
[Aho:idiot.]
Ah, it is true!
But what wants to say this number?
Where that?
On this wall?
Where it is.
It is probalement an entry for the large naval engineers of 5 meters!!!
Does Y' have some as much as that?
Isn't the thing in front of us, it is the station?
It indicates “Blue Station”.
Very well the port is.
It is not this road?
Oi, you all!
It is not good that the pirates enter by front.
Turn to the bottom of the alley, over there!
Haaai! Thank you!
Wow, Marvellous! A city on water!
Impressing! It is brilliant here, what a beautiful city!
But the city is flooded, the houses are in water!
Not, the city was built on ground!
Look at!
It is true, the pillars are built in height!!
I see, therefore one calls that a “watery city”.
Oi, let us dispatch, and will visit this wonder!
Oh! Oh you, no pirate boat is authorized here!
Why did you come here? You come to make a plundering?
Not, we want to repair our boat!
Do they ask normally if it is for a plundering?
Good, there is a course a little further, you can remain over there for the moment!
Haai!
Thank you.
Not yet!
If one cannot be helped, we are pirates!
Here would not be a sure place?
Although it is not a very pleasant place.
Yosh, raise the sail!
What is what you ridges?
Not, I just drew the cord!
It was unexpected…
Is Going Merry if damaged that?
But why the citizens fear don't pirates?
It is probably that the pirates are also customers of the shipyards.
Cease speaking and fix this!
Perhaps that there are bodyguards rather strong!
To deal with strong pirates?
There must be in a city like this one.
Really, that will be made? They is not dangerous?
They are not dangerous, we are customers!
It is true!
Yosh, one goes there!
Wait, Luffy and Usopp!
You can follow me!
Until where?
Initially we must find the man called Iceberg and give him the invitation of Kokoro-san.
We will count on him to repair the boat and…
We must find a place to exchange gold against money!
Of agreement.
Yosh, good allons-y!
The town of Seven Toilets!
We forget gold!
Zoro! Fix the good!
You leave just?!
Attention, Nami-swan!
Now, I lost my chance to go outside!
Let us leave all together later!
Really?
Are there bookstores?
Yes certainly.
Shouldn't we leave to the bureau de change initially?
Why? Let us leave to the shipyard!
Frankly, to carry all this gold returns to me nervous!
Is the value the same one if one changes gold into money?
Yes, we must pay attention with that if one would cross robbers by chance!
We are the robbers!
It is true. If we change this into money, we will transport it more easily!
It was a little hard!
You say that because you want to even carry it you.
You will make it fall or will lose it to you!
It is what will occur! Because it is Luffy!
How is what does not go with you?! You do not rely on me?!
Not.
Ca makes too badly, I think that I will not recover there!
Is this the only entry of the city?
“Store of hiring of bulldozer”
What?
What let us can rent itself here?
Is C " what a “bulldozer”?
I do not know… a bulldog, perhaps?
Not it is impossible!
Excuse me… Can I rent a bulldozer?
ASK WHAT It IS IN FIRST!
Welcome! Is a bulldozer, it Ca? How much be you?
Three.
Which type of bulldozer want?
The types are Yagara, Rabuka and King.
And well, two will yagaras should make the deal for three people.
Ah, treat the good!
It was a strange conversation!
Does summers you come here while using the log pose?
Ouais.
It is impressive of your share.
Good… you do not know anything about the bulldozers, not truth?
To make short, here is a bulldozer, Yagara bulldozer. They are used all around the city!
It is a kind of fish which swims the head out of water.
Here the city of water. There are more channels than of normal roads!
The bulldozers are essential for the inhabitants from here.
Even for the tourists!
Do these fish draw us?
No traction, we will be on their back!
It is like assembling a horse on the ground!
It flopée one there of fish over there, find in the comfortable ones.
Two will yagaras assembled bulldozers, that made 2.000 Beries
Ahh, kawaii.
A horse fish would be said! A horse fish would be said!
Dumb! What do you make, dumb?
He loves you. You can take that one.
Can they carry heavy things?
They are really strong. They can be employed for the removals!
It is a luggage? What is what there is inside?
Gold.
Good, in other words, they is good!
Look at!
Aaah, gives me that!
IN YOUR DREAMS!
What a terrible viel man!
AND YOU, NÉGLIGEMMENT DOES NOT SHOW IT has OTHERS!
Why? It is not as Ci that came from everywhere!
Ca surprises me!
Good then… both Yagaras bulldozers will be to 100.000 Beries.
You increased the price, viel man!
Forgiveness… They is 500.000 Beries.
It IS EVEN MORE EXPENSIVE!
You updated to me!!!!
The guy, that cannot be too dangerous!
Hold, 2.000 Beries, it is that?
Thank you.
Is there a bureau de change not far from here?
Yes there is one of them but with all this gold, they will not have enough money!
It would be better if you leave in the center the island naval construction.
The center of the island of naval construction?
It is what?
It is over there!
Take this!
A chart!
It will be useful, thank you!
Old man, are the shipyards over there too?
Yes, the best of the world!
Excel. We can go to the shipyard after having changed gold!
Yes, finally we will be able to repair Going Merry.
And to find an engineer naval, too.
I am impatient.
Then…
Let us go there…
Yosh! Go, Yagara!
Made attention!
Quickly with the shipyard!