You ace plus a radish.
And now…
You would not like to bet
your pants, frérot?
You ace of the vein, finally.
When one defies Roshio, it is necessary
to expect to be caught a beating.
Afflicted, my pal. I have you
plucked like a pigeon.
Drop.
It was an equitable part.
You cheated ace, hein?
Acknowledge!
How that?
When I would have…
Do not lie!
I know that cheated you.
Useless to try what
how it is, kid!
Sarquiss.
SARQUISS!
Hum?
What is there?
You ace well considering you too.
This guy cheated.
Cheated?
Oh!
Ouais!
Of course that he cheated.
I saw it my own eyes!
Never considering a similar grugor!
CLOSE IT, BROTHEL!
YOU DO NOT KNOW HAS WHO YOU DEAL!
Stop dreaming!
Mock Town, the scorning city!
One arrives soon, Usopp?
Not, still not of ground at the horizon.
Jaya should not be any more
very far however, not?
Yes, time with the more stable air.
We are undoubtedly already
in the maritime zone of Jaya.
Then Jaya must be
a spring island.
It makes good, it is pleasant…
Which beautiful season that spring.
Even the gulls have the air happy.
THEY WERE CUT DOWN!
One will be able to be made yakitori!
They were cut down?
I did not hear shots.
Look at, a ball!
According to the direction towards
which they flew,
the balls come from
some share right in front of us!
But the island is still not in sight!
It is impossible, Chopper.
But I do not have them
left eyes however!
This type would have really the sharpened eye, a sophisticated ultra weapon and it would be a tireur d'élite of genius.
It had to draw randomly and these poor
gulls did not have a chance.
Sanji! Gulls, gulls!
The poor animals…
Ca must be painful…
… not to die on the blow.
Lastly, thus the destiny goes,
determined by our daily acts.
He, you!
You know who I am?!
How I would know it, cretin?!
Very well, I you will say it!
I am a champion of Wrestling!
Cool!
Ca with the sympathetic air like city!
It is me or one would say
a station balnéaire?!
Station balnéaire?!
More quickly, Merry!
It is true!
I want well to remain there
a little to release me.
Heu, on the other hand, it is me or all the ships
moored resemble pirate boats?
Oh, crowned Usopp!
As so pirate boats could throw
anchors it in a port to the eyes of everyone?
O… Yes, you are right!
THE HELP!! IT WILL KILL ME!
WHAT DOES NOT TURN
PAS ROND DANS CETTE VILLE?!
What a weakling!
He Ben!
Would have done you better
not to smash this type!
Look at this emblem!
It is one of the men of Roshio.
You never heard of Roshio,
the man to the 42 Million Berrys?
It is degenerate!
Pay to!
I do not believe in it.
There was not
cheating in this part.
But this guy has beautiful
and descended Roshio well.
You do not know who it is?
It is Bellamy!
He?! That of which the premium
rise to 55 Million Berrys…
Bellamy the Hyena?
Captain!
Who did that to you?
It does not matter, will find a doctor!
Quickly!
Captain, hold good!
Y' has animation by here.
This amusing city with the air.
They is not good.
One can be sure that these deux-là
troubles will create us!
Ouais, it is the perfect place for that. I do not see how the things could occur well…
You are right…
They are not good!
N-N-Nami
!
Wait! Luffy, Zoro!
It left.
All will be well if it
is with these deux-là.
What? If Nami-san there
goes, I accompany it!
AHH!!
NOT! REMAIN!
IF EVER THE BOAT EAST
A-A-ATTAQUE DURING YOUR ABSENCE…!
I You IN PRIIIIE, DO NOT LEAVE PAAAAS!
Ok, they is good!
Release maintaining me!
Well, I have only to do a little
tea for drinking in private conversation with…
Hein? Where is Robin-chan?
It is…
part.
Sanji-kun, of the tea?
Do it
yourself.
“As long as I would be in this
city, I swear not to slip by… “
“I swear not to beat me!”
“I swear not to beat me.”
Well. You swear it, both?
Ouais.
It is what this lack of enthusiasm?
You know, if you
sow the disorder here,
one will expel us out of this city!
And that, that would like to say
good-bye the celestial island, measuring rod?
Eh…
Is Oh, it which that?
Look at. It fell.
Ouais. It fell stiff.
It with the air to suffer.
Ouaip, it suffers.
Hum, forgive me, Sirs.
Could you raise me?
You are sure of step better lengthened being?
Luffy, take this with dimensions.
Ok!
Hop!
Oh, thank you well.
Of return seals some.
I am of fragile constitution.
Go, on the way, Stronger.
THE HORSE TOO?!
Whore, which parasite…
I am sorry
to cause such a gene.
I would like to reward you,
in pledge of my gratitude.
You want one of them?
Ca me with the air a little too equivocal.
One does not want any. Go, drops!
Oh! Apples! Thank you!
HE! HO!
It was what that?
What occurred?
They ate apples of the odd guy.
As soon as they bit inside,
they exploded all the five!
It is not true!
LUFFY!
RECRACHE CA!
RECRACHE THIS APPLE IMMEDIATELY!
Donot can, I already swallowed it!
Dumb, what
try to you to make?!
Not, it will be well.
I cannot believe it.
All is in ruin!
It was not charged. Without what,
he would have died in the first mouthful.
You are…
a lucky devil.
Is He… it what all that?
It is the last residence
of Roshio the Executor.
It would be said that there was
one crowned brawls here…
It does without things so much
terrible in this city…
Ouais, even witnesses of the scene
do not manage to believe what they saw!
All that one knows… it is that
Roshio fought with this Bellamy!
Bellamy the Hyena?
It has certainly
eaten a Fruit of the Demon.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
In which town of nutcases
one still fell?!
Go, calms itself, Nami.
You realize that you came very close to death?
Ben, that arrives.
And they is cool, it is that?!
Here how that begins again to him!
Does Ca make how much victims already?
I ever heard of him,
there are no premiums on its head…
Where it leaves?
Bah, I do not even want the knowledge.
Better is worth to be held distant…
of this champion of Wrestling.
CHAMPION?
STOP! YOU PROMISED to Me!
I start to ask to me whether one will really finish
by finding information in this city!
What do you say of this corner?
Hum, it is not very animated.
Ca you can say it. This
place is splendid!
This city is true a cut-throat,
whereas here it is really the paradise.
There is a villa on the sea.
Y' does not have a rat on the other hand!
But that feels good food…
Oh, hello everyone!
You will attract each other troubles!
You would make better leave from here!
In this moment, the Tropical Hotel is entirely
occupied by the crew of Lord Bellamy!
This is why we are constrained
to refuse any other customer!
Oh, it is a hotel then…
If… if Bellamy-sama found you
here, it would be a catastrophe!
I thus regret of you
to ask to leave, please!
Oh go, one can nevertheless
to throw an eye inside.
And then it is which this Bellamy?
Does He, what occur?
Say to me from which leave these vermins?
SARQUISS-SAMA!
Be welcome!
You are healthy and except!
Nothing with foutre!
Insane them outside and quickly!
How much you believe that one pays you
to occupy you of this place?
It is true.
Go, breaks from there, p' tite shit.
He! I can smash the head to him?
NOT!
To smash me the head?
One fell on comic.
You really made pity the guy.
Hold!
Thus buy to you
correct behaviors with this money!
Sarquiss, you really waste
your tunes with similar good-for-nothings.
Undoubtedly I would have done better
to balance them in a ditch.
Woa! It is for us?
One draws.
One ridicules oneself!
He, He, I can walk all alone!
Don't Ben what, you want any?
Sarquiss! Lily!
Release to them the bunch a little.
Oh, then you are you there.
It is not no matter who, looks at, they
are given evil to arrive up to now.
Hold!
But they are only microbes
compared with Bellamy or you.
Except that they manage
rather well for microbes.
Ouaip, but they will not hold a long time
with the arrival of the New Era.
But… 30 Million…
for this soft figure?
It is necessary that Bellamy sees that.
Brothel, I am in detonator!
Ah, I am sorry.
Mock Town became the paradise of the pirates
who spend their time running out their spoils.
The pitiful pirates are not
not welcome, not truth?
It would be said that I will not arrive
not to comfort you.
Hold! It is the house which offers it.
This city gathers
so much of rich people,
That brawls and them
murders are currency.
But they are not caught any almost
never with people of the city.
Here.
It is nevertheless a dirty place.
You know, I you
include/understand completely.
Afflicted to say that, but you will not find
no normal people in this city.
Bah, your Log will be reloaded
within four surroundings days.
You quiet by then hold, and raise
anchors it before having troubles, of agreement?
Four days.
Then only we are not needed
remained more than two days.
Forgiveness, but…
HE, PAPI!
Hmm? That there
does it have?
- This tart with cherries is REPUGNANT!
- This tart with cherries is DELICIOUS!
- It is what this PISS OF CAT?!
- This drink is EXELLENTE!
Dumb, your papillae
gustatory talk cock?
And, it is to you the brain, not?
He Ho, if you have reproaches
to make, you address to the cook.
He, papi! Put to me 50
pieces of meat to be carried.
Grandfather, I want 51
tarts with cherries to be carried.
I wanted to say 52 pieces!
One minute, I wanted 53 tarts.
Not, 54 meat ends!
55 tarts.
60 meat ends!
70 tarts!
80!
100!
YOU SEEK ME OR WHAT?!
CA RHYME HAS WHAT THIS BRAWL?!
Isn't Luffy, you promised?
In any event, we do not have
not enough of money for that!
One did not come to make the races!
Be to you a pirate?
Ouais, exact!
With how much does rise your premium?
30 Million!
30 Million?
You?
Te insane step of me?!
YOU LIE!
NOT! It IS the TRUTH!
Ca is enough!
The calm one! I do not want
brawls in my bar!
Take-that and insane the camp!
50 tarts with cherries.
Y' has it a pirate with
a straw hat here?
C… It is Bellamy!
Then it is you which am worth 30 Million
Berrys? Luffy with the Straw hat…
Hein?
It would be said that it is with
you that it causes, Luffy.
He, Bellamy, it is not the name of the type which
all the hotel where one held went?
You ace heard that? This kid
a premium of 30 Million would have!
He? Be sure for you?
I meet full
asparaguses today.
Give me your the best
twist-bowels, tavernier!
And serve what he wants with this kid!
Very well.
Hold. Y' has really world here.
It is what this hole with
rats? They is crasseux!
And one must be useful that bibine here.
Look at, they are them
guy of presently.
You could at least us
to release some seats.
What a wild!
It, isn't this is him?
It is Big Knife Sarquiss.
Does Ca feel the brawl, you do not believe?
Really?
The crew is complete.
If that is, they have
simply desire of glass, not?
Useless to interfere itself! Better
is worth to remain apart from that.
Bellamy is incorrigible.
You said it.
With holds.
Oh, thank you.
Be really sympathetic for you, you.
Ca is there!
I did not expect that, Bellamy!
With what you cheeks, sailor?
It is rather with you of
to answer this question.
Zoro! Stop that!
There is none yet
information for the moment!
The farm!
This guy seeks the brawl
and I will give it to him!
Be able to you to be raised?
Ok, then…
I hope that are ready for you.
Oh! They have the intention
to defy Bellamy!
Go! It left!
Ca will not be a brawl,
it will be right a test!
Go ahead! Show it
that you can make!
Luffy, wait!
Tavernier, we seek
information on the celestial island!
You know something?
What is this… that it has just said?
It is a joke, not true?
If ever you know
road towards the celestial island…
The celestial island?!
It is quite good!
Hein? But the Log Installation is
pointed right towards the sky!
Oh nooon, the Log Installation is
pointed towards the cieeeel!
The Log Installations talk cock
all the time, you know!
Let us go, go, of the calm one.
You really believe in this history to sleep
upright which speaks about an island in the sky?
The guy, in which
time do you live?
There is a whole heap of phenomena
strange on Large Line.
One of them carries it
name of “Knock Up Stream”.
I suppose that you in
ever intended to speak.
The ships which are
trapped in this current…
Are propelled high in the sky, for
finally to fall down and be crushed on the ocean.
Formerly, of the sailors ignoramuses saw these boats falling from the sky, and they believed that there was an island up there.
“A floating world in the skies!”
What cretins!
All these phenomena have
a rational explanation!
All the dreams can be explained!
I am disappointed.
If had made a success of you the test, I thought of enlisting you
in my crew to sail about the New Era.
But you are not worth the sorrow of it.
Listen well!
The time when pirates
dreams had is COMPLETED!
The Gold City? The Emerald City?
The large treasure, One Part?!
These idiots who dream
fabulous treasures…
all do not even notice
the richnesses which surround them!
All the largest pirates of the seas are
died by continuing this kind of dreams!
And what them
do people end up saying?
“He lived happy in
continuing its dreams! “
What a rengaine losers!
To look at a cretin of
dreamer in your kind…
Ca returns to me sick!
Luffy!
It is because of mops in your kind that
reputation of pirate truths as we is tarnished.
Bar you, band of larvae!
You waste the taste of my rum.
Bellamy rightly!
You draw, stunned!
You break this city!
Bellamy!
It would be said that they want spectacle!
They will not be disappointed.
Luffy! Zoro! One
forget this promise!
You can put one
beating with these types!
Zoro.
We will not beat we.