HAWK EYES MIHAWK!
SWORDMAN ZORO FALLS INTO THE SEA!
What did you say?!
Nami ran off with the Going Merry?!
What exactly happened?
Everything happened so suddenly.
What's up, Nami-anekI?
Huh?
You've been staring at that
bounty list for a while now.
Oh, it's nothing!
That's our Nami-anekiI
That's our Nami-aneki!
You've chosen the most valued pirate!
But it'd be best not to target Arlong alone.
Not only is he fierce but strong.
There was a time when he remained quiet.
But, I've heard that he's been moving about lately.
The 20 million beli reward sure is tempting.
But he's too strong that even we
can easily get butchered by him.
Nami-aneki?
Excuse me, but I'd like to change a sec,
so could you two turn around?
W-Wait!
Can't I?
Here? Right now?
Please! By all means!
She's quite daring.
Just a little peek won't hurt, right?
YEAH!
W-What are you doing?
''What?'' you ask?
Business, of course!
I'm a thief that steals from pirates.
So I'll be taking this ship.
I don't recall saying that I was one of them.
I was merely cooperating.
Although it was a rather short relationship
with Luffy and the gang, I enjoyed it.
Tell them that for me.
If we're meant to be together, we shall meet again!
Nami-aneki
Th..This is a problem!
We were asked to take care of the ship!
And that's how we lost the ship!
Forgive us!
Damn! She took advantage of us!
That ship was given by Kaya!
Hold up! I can see it!
It's the Going Merry!
Where's your ship?
We still have it, but...
Zoro, Usopp, leave right away!
Fetch Nami using their ship.
Never mind. Let it go.
There's no need to chase that woman.
I can't be without her as my navigator!
Fine!
What a pain-in-the-ass captain...
Hey Usopp, let's go!
Zoro-aniki, the ship's ready!
Luffy, what about you?
I haven't fully repaid this restaurant
yet, so I can't go.
Do be careful.
Things here are abnormal.
Yeah. I know
W-What? What's going on?
The ship's been split in two!
Look! Over there!
It's him!
Don Krieg! It's that man!!!
The man who destroyed our fleet!
That man is...
That scum...
He's come this far to kill us!
We're doomed!
Zoro, who the heck is he?
The man I've been searching for,
Hawk Eyes Mihawk.
Hawk Eyes Mihawk?
The strongest swordsman in the world!
That's the guy who instantly sank Krieg's fleet of 50
ships, which should've withstood the Grand Line?
And he Just destroyed another one of Krieg's ship!
But, he looks no different from
any other ordinary person.
And he doesn't seem to be armed
with anything special.
His weapon's on his back.
No way, you can't mean?!
He destroyed that huge ship with that sword?!
He's the great swordsman, Hawk Eyes.
A swordsman, above all of the world's swordsmen.
I never thought I'd be abIe to meet him so soon.
Finally, the destined time has come.
Bastard!
Why did you attack us?
To kill time.
Bullshit!
W-What?!
I'm sure I was right on target!
It deviated.
He redirected it with the tip of his sword.
That's ridiculous!
Hey! Who the hell are you?
Swords, three of 'em! Could it be..?
I've never seen such graceful skill.
A sword with power alone is not powerful.
So this ship was cut apart with that sword, too?
Of course.
It's clear now. You're the strongest!
I've been sailing the seas to face you.
What's your mission?
To be the best!
Fool.
You've got time to spare, don't you?
Let's duel, shall we?
This guy is...
Zoro! The ''Three Swords'' Roronoa Zoro!
What?!
Pirate hunter, eh?
That guy?
Hey!
Things are getting worse, Luffy!
Going Merry is about to be gone from our sights!
Hey Luffy!
Duel?
Such a pitiful weakling.
If you really were a fine swordsman,
You should've been able to Judge the difference
in strengths without drawing your sword.
Challenging me...
Are you that brave? Or simply reckless?
This is for my own ambition!
And for a promise to my fallen friend
The world's greatest swordsman Hawk
Eyes Mihawk vs Pirate Hunter Zoro.
What kind of fight will it turn out to be?
No one can win against Aniki!
Aniki's the best!
Hey now, what's the meaning of this?
I'm unlike those idiots who use
their all to hunt rabbits.
Though you're famous enough
to be called a swordsman,
this is the weakest of the four oceans, East Blue.
Unfortunately, I'm carrying nothing smaller than this.
Quit mocking me!
Just don't regret it when you die!
You're but someone who's yet
to experience the real world.
DEMON CUT!
Wh..what?!
Zoro!
Aniki's demon technique was broken!
But, that has always worked 100% of the time!!
What in the world happened?!
I can't move!
What just happened?
No one could avoid this technique
before, but just with his toy, he...
Is this really happening?
Is a strength like his really this far away?
That can't be!
It can't be this far away!
The world shouldn't be this far off!!
This can't be happening, Aniki!
Please fight seriously!
Aniki!!!
It can't possibly be this far away!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Such unrestrained skill.
Just with that thing, he's taking
on all of Zoro's three swords!
That's a monster superior to monsters!
I... I didn't come all this way to
lose against this toy-like thing!
Zoro!
You're lucky, Zoro... because you're a boy.
I want to be the world's best too!
If only I was... If only I was born as a boy.
After defeating me, don't you dare
say such demeaning things!
That's too shameless!
You're my ultimate goal!
Zoro...?
Promise me.
That someday, either you or I will become
the greatest swordsman in the world!
Promise me!
It's a promise!
To become the greatest in the world...
I... have to become strong, for her sake too.
My strength will even reach the heavens!
I'm going to become the strongest in the world!
We promised... I will...
If I could just defeat this man...
What's your mission?
Why do you seek the ultimate power, you weakling?
Aniki's a weakling you say? You damn bastard!
I'll teach you a thing or two!
Stop! Yosaku! Johnny!
Don't interfere!
Just hang on!
Luffy...?
I can't afford to lose!
TIGER...
That's great! The world's greatest swordsman, eh?
As the Pirate King's Companion, if you're
not at least that, I'd be in a dilemma.
HUNTING PREY!
Do you wish to have this go through your heart?
Why don't you step back?
I don't know.
I'm not sure why myself.
But if I were to take even one step back,
I believe that all those important oaths, promises,
and many other deals 'til now,
will all go to waste and I'll never be able
to return before you, ever again.
Yes, and that's called ''losing''.
That's why I can't step back.
Even if it means death?
Death may be better!
What strong will!
Preferring death over defeat.
Kid, announce your name!
Roronoa Zoro!
I'll remember that!
It's been a while since I've seen
such strong will. As a reward,
A gesture to a fellow swordsman,
I will wield this ''Black Sword'',
The most powerful sword in
the world, to end your life.
I appreciate your offer.
It's out!
The sword that cut the ship!
This is my last chance.
World's number one... or death?
That's enough, Aniki!
Please stop!
THREE SWORDS SECRET TECHNIQUE!
THREE THOUSAND REALMS!
I lost.
Losing wasn't something I'd ever imagine possible.
So this is what it is to possess the
greatest power in the world?
What now?
Attacking from behind is a shameless
act among swordsmen.
Well said.
ZORO!!!
Don't rush your death, young lad.
Zoro!!
Aniki!
Why?
When I decided to become the greatest swordsman
in the world, I've already discarded my life.
in the world, I,'ve already discarded my life.
When I decided to become the greatest swordsman
in the world, I've already discarded my life.
That guy and his stupid ideas
His opponent was the true world's greatest.
The result was obvious!
Why didn't yougive up your ambitions,
realizing inevitable death?
It's simple!
To abandon your ambitions!
This is Grand Line's power?!
The world's power?
Even the Pirate Hunter Zoro didn't stand a chance!
Damn! Damn! DAMN IT!
Aniki!
What the hell is that?
That kid's got the ability of a devil fruit?
Bastard!
You're the young swordsman's comrade?
Thank you for watching over him.
Rest assure, that man's still alive.
Aniki! Aniki! Say something!
Zoro!
Zoro!!!
Hey, quickly get him on the ship!
Here's some medicine! Apply it quickly!
It's still too early for you to die.
My name is Juraquille Mihawk!
Find your true self, true world, become stronger!
No matter how long it will take, I will
await you in my strongest form!
Surpass this sword!
Surpass me!
Roronoa Zoro!
Aniki! Aniki! Say something!
For Hawk Eyes Mihawk to declare such words...
Kid, what's your mission?
Pirate King!
That's a difficult path, harder than surpassing me.
Like I'd care, 'coz I'm gonna become one anyway!
He's alive!
He just lost consciousness!
Aniki!
Aniki! Say something!
Zoro!
Aniki!
Luffy, can you hear me?
Yeah!
Sorry for worrying you.
If I don't become the greatest swordsman in
the world, you'd be in a dilemma now, right?
Aniki! Don't say anymore!
Aniki!
I will... I will never...
LOSE AGAIN!
Until I defeat him and become the greatest
swordsman, I'll never be defeated anymore!
Any problems with that,
Pirate King?
None!
Good team.
I hope we meet again.
Hold on there, Hawk Eyes!
Didn't you come for my head?
East Blue's greatest, Don Krieg's head?
That was my initial intention.
But I've had more than enough fun.
I'm headed back to sleep.
It may have been enough fun for you,
but I haven't done my bit yet.
Don?!
Why is he intentionally stopping him?!
Die before you go!
A true fool.
He got away.
Usopp!
Luffy!
Get going!
Take care of Nami.
Gotcha!
Me and Zoro will definitely get Nami back!
You Just make that cook one of us!
Then we'll make a party of five
and head to the Grand Line!
Yeah! Now go!
Men! With the interruption gone,
the real fight has just begun!
Let's get that ship!
YEAH!!!
Old man, if I get rid of 'em, can we call it even?
Do as you please.