The key of the destiny and the great escape!
Doru Doru Ball!
With the kingdom of the Oases.
Three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
In a howl of sadness, this desiccated ground sinks from now on in an enormous wave of agitation.
The plan of Crocodile extremely well started.
In Nanohana, Good-Clay took the appearance of the King.
From this fact… the rebellious army passed to the action.
During this time, vis-a-vis the danger with which Luffy and its crew are confronted with Rain Dinners,
Vivi managed to escape to seek the assistance of Sanji and Chopper.
Will Arabasta be destroyed?
Or will it find peace eternal?
The countdown of the sand glass of the destiny arrives in the long term.
I am Mr. Prince!
Is Tony-Kun a lure?
Ouais.
All will go well for him.
We, Vivi-Chan dispatch.
Say to me what occurred!
But Sanji-San… I believed that one had drawn you above…
Me?
Hello?
We had it.
What do we have to make of this type?
Where are you?
Give your position!
We are in Rainbase in front of the doors of the casino Rain Dinners.
Well, you were wise.
A superb interpretation.
Now your boss will leave.
Thank you, Mister.
P- Do I can go there, now?
No Sir.
I did not believe in it…
Look at, Chopper!
Still more their men gathered where we were presently.
Ouais.
Now, it is with me to play.
I count on you.
What do you want?
My name is Mr. Prince.
Thus it is you, the dumb who put our pals in this state!?
With me to play…
My name is Mr. Prince!
Brothel, that did occur here?
L- The type which is made call “Mr. Prince”…
He.
Oh not!
The bridge crumbled!
And it is more or less what occurred.
Will that go for Tony-Kun?
Ouais.
It has more than one turn in its bag.
What did it occur to Rain Dinners?
I intended to say that the bridge had crumbled.
The dumb…
Where do you hide you, Mr. Prince?
I will seek you and I will kill you.
Water!
We will mouriiiir!
Water! Water! Water!
If the cage fills, we are foutus!!
Stupid He croco!
Be given to bottom!
What do you make, Nami!?
I want to make it furious so that it breaks this cage!
I included/understood! Excellent idea!
Come there, stupid banana!
Blasted banana!
Not, you are mistaken!
You see well that it is a crocodile.
The banana pushes on its head.
Be inflating to you… Close it!
For example, take “Monkey Dance”…
He banana!
Listen when somebody speaks to you!
What?
For example, take “Monkey Dance”.
The monkey is an animal, but “Monkey Dance” is a dance.
Do not touch with that!
Pay attention!
The bananas and the crocodiles, both eat themselves!
It arrives!
Ca did not go!
What is it that this cage!?
Vivi, hurries!
He, you.
How can you remain also calm!?
Think of a means to leave us from here!
Say to me what you know…
Which is the objective of Crocodile?
This woman who was with Crocodile…
… has been sought by the world government for 20 years.
The reward for its capture exceeds the 70.000.000.
70.000.000!?
E- And then!?
It is as much as for Crocodile…
If these deux-là works together,
it is not a question any more of reversing a country.
If they are not stopped, that will involve a disaster for the whole world.
The whole world?
What do you want to say?
Maintaining it is too important to engage there.
About what do speak you?
Since when must we have a reason to burst a guy like him!?
Very well.
Then…
How will you make to leave from here?
Water already reached my buttocks!!
We will die!
We will die! Naaan!
Ah, I empty myself my forces…
Oh shit!
Ca fears!
Hold good, brothel!
It is what Vivi said, not true!?
Vivi, that must really be hard for you…
You are so in a hurry, I am sorry!
Shit…
If I were a better epeist…
… this cage would not be a problem!
“Never not to make noise when one eats.”
Then the guy.
Did I make you wait?
Prince-San!
We are saved…
Stop glander and finds the key now!
Nami-Saaan!
E- Do you like me!?
Yes, yes.
Yes, I love you.
Now the door opens!
I arriiive!
Its stupidity is unbounded…
Mellorine! Mellorine!
Vivi! Played well!
Look at, they arrive all at the same time.
Go ahead Sanji!
Burst to them all!
It does not matter your number, try me to beat, bananas of shit.
All merdeux enough louts to attack a woman…
… require that the good mannerss are inculcated to them.
Sanji! We do not have time!
Butt to them all in one second!
Not, in one moment!
Butt the third which has just entered the part.
What?
How can you know that?
You are cretin and deaf?
This growl.
It is the same growl as that which swallowed the key.
I do not arrive there…
It destroyed the bridge to save time.
What wants to say that it has more companions than envisaged.
Thus it tried to pass to us under the nose to go in the part.
Probably.
Ca arrives!
The key of the cage!
What is it that this trick?
Ca does not resemble a key!
Saved!
What!?
D- Water!
Water all around me!
They is really miraculous!
He! It is this type…!?
3!
Mr. 3!
Why were you in the stomach of the crocodile!?
I live again!
I thought of being at the end of the roller!
Crocodile, if you wanted to remove you from me, you will have to better do.
At the moment when I was going to be devoured by this animal,
I used my last forces to make this Doru Doru Ball and…
What do we have there?
This key!
Give it!
Still you…!!
What?
Their to give this key?
Wait.
A closed part which fills of water.
A steel cage.
And… a key.
I included/understood what occurs.
Therefore, you are Mr. 3?
“You launched me.”
Es you Mr. 3?
Give me this key well nicely.
I know…
What do you say a launched length?
What!?
I do not know who you are, but you must be one as of theirs.
If you want the key, will seek it!
On the other hand, I am not responsible if you do not find it!
Dumb…
What would it occur if they found the crocodile which swallowed the key?
Ca will not be useful to them with nothing.
Even if they managed to find the good crocodile,
it is always me which have the true key.
Even while being given to bottom, that will not be sufficient.
You are diabolic.
It is not there any more!
It disappeared!
This dumb…
He is intelligent to have included/understood all that so quickly!
We do not have any more time!
Sanji-Kun!
Which shit, you are making me…
One second, Sanji!
Couldn't it make a key for this cage thanks to its capacity Doru Doru?
Good idea.
Eh?
Good work, “man candle”.
Can one go there?
It does not remain us much any more of time.
Ouais.
The tunnel which they took earlier…
… must lead to Alubarna.
But there is still too much Bananawani blocking the passage!
It is all!?
Where is the remainder?!!!
They will not be a problem.
And to say that I had so much evil to fight only one of them…
Not, not.
It is their force which is not normal.
It is not your fault.
Brothel!
I cannot go there seriously with all this sea water!
The wall yielded!
Moron!
You do too much of it!
Even the passage crumbles!
It is time to leave!
Let us leave from here!
I have of it enough of these poisoning small plagues.
It is time that I finish them myself.
What…?
With later - Croco of shit - Mr. Prince
Are He, alive for you, Luffy?
Usopp-San! Awake!
Shit!
What be to you making?
Awake and swims!
Whore, those which have the capacities of a fruit of the demon take large risks.
Smoker!
He, He, Zoro!
Why did you help the enemy?
Close it!
I did not want.
It was the ideal moment to get rid of him.
Anything.
We do not have any more but to go there!
We lost a good end of time in it.
Can Vivi-Chan, one arrive still there?
I do not know.
Nami-San.
Do you still have this perfume which I bought in Nanohana?
Eh?
Yes, why?
Put.
Like that?
Ah! Until the end of the world!
To fall in love!
Stop joking and allons-y!
Roronoa!
Why did you save me?
He, Zoro!
Save it!
Hein!?
It is an enemy!
Let us leave it!
But if we leave it… he will die!
It is an anvil!
Not, I want to say… I know all that!
But it is…!!
I followed the orders of the Captain.
Do not believe that you must thank me.
It was one of its whims.
Forget that.
Then, I suppose that you me will not want of it if I exert my official duties.
You hear that? Here what one gains to save somebody of the Navy.
You found the pirates of Straw hat?
Yes, and Colonel Smoker is over there too!
We will lend strong hand to him!
Yes!
Very well, my men!
We go right to Alubarna!
Where is Crocodile!?
Ah, they finally regained consciousness.
Smokey! You want to fight!?
Gah!! Smoker!
He, Luffy, do not do that!
Let us leave!
Is it serious, there?
By there!
More quickly!
Leave.
But it is the last time that I let to you slip by.
The next time that we will meet, you died.
They are there!
Move back, Colonel Smoker!
He!
Do not let them escape!
Yes!
Allons-y.
The Navy arrives.
It is by where Alubarna?
By there!
Full Is!
Luffy, hurries!
What do you make?
Ouais…
They will not flee this time!
Yes!
You know, I taime well!
Insane the camp now!!
They go by there!
Halt!
All after them!
More quickly! More quickly! More quickly!!
Yosh!
The guy, we go right to Alubarna!
Ouais!!!