Cape on the clouds!
To find the Bird of the South!
What do you want to say to us, papi?
Listen, the guy.
To start, I will say to you
all that I know about the celestial island.
I do not know if it is veracious,
thus free with you to believe me or not.
Ok, I believe you.
Not already!
It occurs a strange phenomenon
in this part of the ocean.
The night falls down sometimes suddenly
in full day on part of the sea.
It was seen!
Ca arrived to us!
Not true?
Ouais!
The night fell,
And a whole heap of monsters emerged!
You speak about the colossi?
There is a theory
interesting on their origin.
But let us pass for the moment.
This sudden fallen
from night is explained by…
darkness caused by
the accumulation of cloudy masses.
They would be cumulonimbus?
But of the clouds cannot
to create such black darkness.
Papi, be too stupid for you!
When there are clouds,
it is said that it is covered!
Ouaip, a covered time!
Cover!
CLOSE IT AND
LISTEN TO me!
Impérionimbus… It is like
that which one calls these clouds.
They accumulate with very high-altitude, but cause neither rain, nor airstreams.
Only, when they appear…
they block the light completely of
sun, and the day becomes night ici-bas.
A theory claims that them
impérionimbus would be…
clouds “fossilized” after having wandered
in the sky during thousands of years.
Like petrified clouds.
It is impossible!
No cloud is formed without
to create airstreams!
Free with you not to believe in it.
I already said it to you.
Approximately, they is magic clouds.
One can say that.
Science still does not explain them.
Luffy, it is brilliant!
You include/understand? If the island
celestial exists indeed…
it can be only over there!
Oh, of agreement!
Direction clouds!
Zoro, awakes!
Already the morning?
Cape on the clouds! All
the world at its station!
Cape on the clouds! Ahead all!
Ahead all! Cape on
clouds! Thank you for the pipe, papi!
Ahead all! Ahead
all! Ahead all!
HOW MUCH TIME I WILL SAY TO YOU
THAT ONE DOES NOT KNOW HOW TO GO THERE?!
Let us pass to the serious things.
Let warn you to me that
you will have to risk your lives!
One is already with half dead…
Knock-Up Stream, it is
the vertical current…
that you will have to succeed in taking
to go on the celestial island.
Here is the theory, measuring rod?
It is a kind of geyser which will propel
is our boat in the airs, it that?
Oh! Then, one has just with
to fly away above the clouds!
An ascending marine current?
But, one intended to say that the boats which
took fell down to be crushed on the ocean.
In general, yes.
It is a question of timing.
At first sight, that can seem
easy to take a marine current.
But I ensure you that it is
far from being a nice cruising.
To fall on Knock-Up
Stream is a disaster.
Usually, one seeks
to avoid it at all costs.
But how a marine current
can it go up towards the sky?
I never heard
to speak about such a phenomenon.
Exact.
There still, there is not
of scientific explanation some.
But you will not find anybody
of enough insane to go to check.
Here the theory:
There would be a vast cavity
underwater, a such air pocket…
in which would engulf themselves
basic water temperature.
The heat of the earth's crust
would transform into vapor….
whose pressure would cause
an underwater explosion.
The powerful breath would generate one
running marine rising to the skies.
During one surroundings minute,
sky and sea communicate together.
One minute?!
It an explosion must be needed
titanic to produce such a geyser!
The explosions do not occur
never at the same places.
And there are only five per month of them.
It is a blow with
to make put in part…
Lastly, at all events, it is
a fantastic natural phenomenon.
One does not explain it with
great words or of beautiful theories.
But then…
This marine current which
proclamation that five times per month…
is the only means
to reach the celestial island?
Ouais, and the risks are enormous.
If you do not find anything up there,
You will be crushed with
the surface of the ocean…
And you will finish all in charpie.
O-Ok!
One drops the celestial island!
It is madness!
Listen to me!
Would be necessary to be hyper hyper hyper hyper
ultra lucky mega to arrive there!
Do not make any you! Allons-y!
I was sure.
What amn't I done any?
You of ace the good ones, you…
You ace that to throw an eye
on the Vogue-Merry!
You is ace seen in which state it?
He would not survive an adventure
similar under these conditions!
It is true. Even very new, this hull
nut could never do it!
WHAT?!
Speed, weight, resistance…
this tub would be immediately
put in part by the explosion.
M… But…
You see?
As I said it, it is impossible.
But of made you not for that.
Masira and Shoujo go
you to help to repair it.
Of course, they go
to reinforce its structure.
Ouais! Let make us, the guy!
Thank you, they is cool!
Is necessary always that they make some too much…
Do you know what you do?
Ben what?
And Ben, to start…
Ah yes!
One cannot remain on this
island that until maximum tomorrow.
At the end of this period, the Log Installation will be put at
to indicate the direction of the next island.
It is that! It is that!
Even time is against us!
He, papi!
I know that are not to you a soothsayer, and
you do not know of it surely anything, but…
this When-is that place will have
next Knock-Up Stream?
Not, not, not, not, not,
in how much month, rather?
Or in how much years?
Tomorrow afternoon. You would make well
to begin your preparations immediately.
THEN ONE WILL DO IT?!
Ben what?
Is not necessary there to go if you do not want.
You lie!
Y has eel under rock there!
One hardly knows oneself!
And you would not be a little too friendly?!
E-and it is not all…
Eh, Usopp!
You, the farm!
This celestial island…
Our only chance to reach this legendary island which one does not even know the site…
… it is tomorrow?!
And you propose even your assistance
to repair our boat?!
It is too beautiful to be true!
Thus acknowledge what you schemes!
The blood of Norland the Liar runs
in your veins, it is well that?!
One cannot trust you!
BOSS!
The dinner is been useful…!
You move!
Nami-swan!
The dinner is ready!
Q-that this is
that you ace?!
T you want to fight?
Masira noticed…
that when the night falls down
suddenly on its territory…
impérionimbus are formed
in the South the next day.
Therefore, taking into account the cycle
of five times per month…
I think that there will be one
Knock-Up Stream tomorrow.
And that should also be in the South.
I guaranteed nothing…
but there are strong chances
so that occurs tomorrow.
Ca pleases to me to have met
a band of nuts like you.
Go, pass to table!
I offer to you my
hospitality for this night…
Friends.
With table! Usopp, is brought back!
Ouais, you grouillez!
Chopper, will seek Robin-chan!
Ok!
One would make well test
of sympatiser with him.
If we want to go in the sky.
But in the final analysis, it
will be a question of chance.
Nami…
You find that I am
a wet hen?
Doubled of a perfect cretin.
I know what you feel.
You should excuse you.
OWNER, I AM SORRY!
Mr.-MR.-but what you
tell, brothel? What a rough!
Does not approach me with
your nose full with snot!
Moron!
Good god, rum is
delicious, today!
Go, eat! Empiffrez you!
Y has sardine with
will and it is not all!
And here!
Fell to you into
panel, face of repechor!
It was my Bomb in Tabasco!
RETURN HERE, LONG-PIF!
He, thus come to sit you
with me, soeurette!
Dumb! You ace hundred years of
too much to dredge Nami-san!
The right eye of cranium…
I saw gold through.
Gold?
Filled up tears, such were them
last words that Norland wrote.
“I saw gold through
the right eye of cranium. “
It was the day when Norland was carried out.
Even since my arrival with Jaya, I
still the direction of these words does not include/understand.
The right eye of cranium…
It is perhaps the name of one
antique quoted now disappeared.
Unless it is not about one
metaphor on its own imminent death.
The white pages which follow
do not give any explanation.
It is for that one plunges!
With the continuation of the dream!
At the bottom of the seas!
Ouais!
One will fly away!
One will never fly away
if you puff out as much!
The night settled well.
But one can see the coast, Bellamy.
You with the unloading prepare!
Not question of leaving good but to mildew
between the hands of stupid dreamers!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
“Today, I accosted on Jaya.”
“May 21st, 1122.”
Norland! Norland!
“Hardly we put foot
with ground, which we heard… “
“… the strange cry of one
bird coming from the forest… “
“… interfered with the sound one
large, very large bell. “
“The sound of a pure gold bell…”
“… which resounded with
through all the island… “
“… like testifying to
prosperity of the antique quoted. “
“On this immense ocean, this fugacious sound
proved that a splendid civilization… “
“… opened out
since generations. “
Norland! Norland!
“For us and our some
decades of existence… “
“… there was not
words to describe it! “
“The sound resounding of
bell cut us the breath! “
Superb history, Norland!
A gold bell! I dream some!
Does owner, what that want to say?
In the final analysis, like you Norland!
Look at that!
Ouah! A gold bell!
In what is it so enormous?
It is not the bell about which he spoke.
It is right an ingot run in form of
bell. I found three at the bottom of water of them.
Ingots?
Then, the Gold City
indeed existed!
Ca proves anything, you know.
Ca can be in
any ruin.
But that proves that there is
well have a civilization here.
An ingot is a block of corresponding gold
with certain criteria of weight.
What means that it there
also trade had here.
Exact, and the cry of
this strange animal…
Eh, Masira.
Ouah, still has there!
It is large that one!
It is all that one A.
Ah, it is splendid!
A made a gold bell and bird.
Ca was to be them
symbols of Jaya formerly.
I wonder whether it is not only one
part of a larger unit.
It is a Bird of the South, and it
lives precisely here, on this island.
And is its cry odd?
Ouais, like writing in the newspaper.
In old times, one was useful oneself
birds of the South aboard ships for…
GOOD BLOOD!!
What!? What there is?!
Ca fears!
You must go in the forest!
The forest in the South!
Hein? Which fly has you piqué, papi?
It is necessary to capture one of these birds!
Immediately!
Hein? Does it like?
This sparrow? But why?
Listen to me well.
Tomorrow you will face
Knock-Up Stream!
You will have to go full South.
But how you count
you to return there?!
Ben, while going straight pardi.
One is on Grand Line!
Once at sea, it will be to you
impossible to locate you!
Ah yes. It is true that our objective is not
not an island but a point on the open sea.
No compass will be able to help us.
But then how can one make?
You will need
assets of this bird.
Certain animals are equipped with one
natural direction of the orientation…
who allows them
to always know where they are.
Then that wants to say that Zoro is
still stupider than a bird!
Be to you really badly
placed to speak, you!
The Bird of the South is it
more astonishing of them.
It does not matter the extent of the grounds
or the agitation of the sea…
Its body will be always
turned in the same direction.
In short, without this bird, you
would never reach that point.
And you will not have the shade of one
chance to reach the celestial island!
AND It IS ONLY NOW
THAT YOU TELL US CA?!
There remain not planted!
Time presses! You move!
It makes black night and you want that one
will walk in wood?!
You forget that!
One deals with repairing your boat.
It was not the moment of
to feast in any event!
You could not say it earlier?!
Listen well!
You must capture a Bird of
South and to bring back it here before the paddle!
Nothing there is seen!
Release me, cretin!
O-Oui, I know, but…
My hands… do not want…
I ate so much that
I do not manage to walk.
I will have evil
to capture this bird.
Good, it is where this bird
odd? Odd bird…
Grouillons us to catch
this sparrow and let us turn over drinking!
How things
can they turn also badly?
Move!
Zut, one could not make
did that when it make day?
Is Eh, it where this bird?
If one knew, one would be
not there with galérer!
All that one knows, it is
that it has funny cry.
And it resembles the form of
gold ingot of presently.
Ca exists really a sparrow
with a similar mug?
And then, “funny of
cry ", it is too vague!
How
will one make?
Ben, it said that once in
forest, one could not be mistaken…
This old man…
OUAH! What a funny of cry!
No the doubt.
Perfect!
Now that one is
there, as much to take care some.
There are three scoops.
We into three separate
groups and let us seek!
OK!
It left!
One goes him botter the bottom to this sparrow!
But not, it is needed
to capture, it is all!
Would be without fear.
I would protect you from all
dangers, Nami-san!
Sanji-kun, and me then?
I have anything with foutre you of it!
Stop a little pleurnicher!
Dispatch we to capture one of
these birds and let us leave this forest!
Tendons well the ear to test
to locate from which its cry comes!
Jiyoooo!
This cry!
Jiyooo! Small, small, small! Jiyoooo!
Cretin!
Jiyoooo!
Why you catch me?
Oh, Nami! It is pretty
specimen that you have there!
You found it where?
About what you do speak?
A SPIDER!
Ben what? It is that a spider.
Poor small bébête. Come-there!
I AI HORROR OF the SPIDERS, MORON!
BALANCE THIS TRICK FAR FROM!
Moved away from it, Usopp!
It is perhaps poisonous!
They fall from the trees!
It IS WRETCHED!
Be to you a kind of
is tarantula, it well that?
You do not worry!
Since I do not irritate it
not, it will not bite me!
I have the practice of me
to beat with spiders!
What a abomination! These
small beasts are feeling reluctant!
With which say it you! I hate that!
Balance it! Immediately! Go!
Good Ah? You prefer the butterflies
and the millepede behind you?
NOOON! It IS STILL PIIIIIIIIIIIIIIRE!
DO NOT LEAVE ME ALL ALONE!
I heard howls.
Occupy you.
A scolopendre.
He is really hefty man.
Avoid killing all them
creatures which one crosses.
The poor animals.
Had that with step to cause me.
But…
What still?
You set out again on our steps there.
The cry of the bird.
By here!
Caution! The ground is spongy, here.
Eh!
Await me!
I hold it!
Look at, Chopper!
It is an atlas!
An atlas?
Ouais!
In the whole world, the atlas is one of
the most required beetles with the hercules!
Beetles kabuto?
You do not know?
One cannot catch it by the head!
It is still better than One Piece?
Ahhh… Not easy to say!
Luffy! There is another here.
It is Miyama!
It CATCHES!
It flew away!
One runs to him afterwards!
Does not let escape!
A swarm! CASSOOOS!
It IS WHAT THIS DRILL INFERNAL?!
Luffy! Look at!
The sparrow!
It is him which balances us swarms!
Eh?!
T-T' ace included/understood what he said?!
“I would kill whoever will break
the calm one of the forest! “
He, frèrot, frèrot,
does not cause us!
You unload in the middle of the night, and
you hope that our gold will be yielded to you?
You bar!
There is bread on the board.
You are bodyguards?
Ah yes, this crowned pirate… Cricket.
I had wind of the tragedy
history of Montblanc to the tavern.
I had the tears with the eyes of it.
I find the fruits
labor of the others…
… particularly with my taste.
You know how one calls me?
The Hyena!