LUFFY IN TROUBLE!
MERMEN VS LUFFY PIRATES!
What's going on?!
Which one's Arlong?
Arlong...
Arlong... That is my name...
Me I am Luffy...
Luffy...
And who are you?
PIRATE!
Oh! lt's him!
He's here!
The ni-chan who likes to take walks!
Not so fast there, you.
Where do you think you're going?
You got some explaining to do to us first, ni-chan.
C'mon, hey...
lf you don't stop...
GET OUT!
And what does a pirate want with me?
Who the hell are you?
Luffy !
Help-me...
DON'T YOU DARE MAKE MY NAVlGATOR CRY!
You bastard!
How dare you hit Arlong-san!
You weaklings stay out of this!
Honestly...
Bursting in alone like that...
lt's not like l'm going to lose even if I was alone.
Idiot.
Since when did I say I was worried about you?
I'm just telling you not to hog all the prey.
Oh, okay.
U...uh... l don't really mind,
if you hog them all...
That's some bravery you got there.
That's him! lt's that guy!
The unknown swordsman!
That's Roronoa Zoro.
As l thought, l knew it!
He's the one that tricked me!
He rode me... I mean, I gave him a ride...
Look, that long-nose!
Huh?! But Nami killed that guy!
He's alive...
Which means...
I knew it! l was right all along.
That woman's a traitor!
Hey, who are those guys?
Hold up.
He blew Arlong away?
Unbelievable!
That's not something a normal human can do!
Those guys...
You still wanna fight?
If you guys join in, you'd just
make things worse for them.
You'd just get in their way.
But, why are they fighting?
What reason do they have to fight them?
A reason?
Nami-aneki was crying.
She risked her life.
Do we need any other reason?
Pirates, eh? l see.
So that's the relationship between you guys.
I thought you were just Nami's victims.
But...
But what can four inferior beings possibly do?
You guys are idiots.
You think Arlong-san will waste
his time with the likes of you!?
He'll be enough for the job!
Could it be?
It's coming...
That is...
Wha... Wha... What's going on?!
You guys can be his next meal!
Come out! Mohmoo!
It... lt's a monster!
The monster from the Grand Line
that crushed Gosa Village!
It's huge!
That's...
It's the sea bull, Mohmoo!
Oh, it's just him.
So he was a nakama of the mermen?
Hold on! Mohmoo!
Where do you think you're going?!
Hey! Wait! Wait, l tell you! Mohmoo!
Mohmoo...
What are you doing?
Well, if you wanna run away, I won't stop you...
Would I , Mohmoo?
It's coming!
Yeah! Get 'em! Follow Mohmoo!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'll take care of him!
This is a waste of time!
What the hell is he gonna do?
l've got a bad feeling about this.
His arms stretched!?
He possesses the power of the Devil's Fruit!?
What?!
Who cares!
Let's go!
Oi! Run!
What? What's he gonna do!?
I dunno, but it's not gonna be pretty!
GOMU GOMU NO...
KAZAGURUMA!
I didn't come here to fight these guys!
The one l want to take down...
IS YOU!!
That's just perfect.
I was just thinking about how
I'd like to kill you now too.
That was dangerous, you idiot!
Did you want to kill us too?!
Huh?
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Such destructive power...
It's unbelievable that a human who can
throw a monster like that even exists!
Is this battle of this world?
What the hell did you think you were doing?!
Huh?
How dare you do that to our crew!
Looks like we have to get our hands dirty now...
I think we need to teach them the
difference between our species.
So, the main forces have finally shown themselves...
Arlong-san, please stay right where you are.
lf you fought out of rage,
Arlong Park would turn to dust.
We'll take care of them!
Yeah, do whatever you like.
Scary...
Hey, um... wait...
Looks like the octopus is up to something.
First, you boil the octopus in salt water, slice,
then flavor with olive oil and paprika.
It makes a great appetizer.
Um, wait, can you hear me out?
Take this!
SHlKAI-ZERO!
TAKO-HACHI-BLACK!
You moron! Why didn't you dodge it?!
Aah!! I can't see!!
And to finish you off...
Hey! Luffy, run away!
Yeah, that's just the problem.
I can't seem to move...
Huh?
My feet won't come out!
Idiot! Didn't you stick 'em into
the ground in the first place!?
What was he thinking...
TAKO-HACHI-BLACK On the Rocks!
This is just great...
Ooo! Sanji!
Nice one! Nice one!
Looks like I ended up with a complete
moron for my captain.
We're on the same boat.
He's... Awesome!
Well, at least it's a hundred times better
than being with a low-life bunch that hurts a lady.
A lady?
You came here all the way here
for ''that kind'' of woman?
You guys make me laugh.
''That kind'' of woman?
Say that again, and I'll cook
you in a buttered frying pan.
Making you into a Meuniere, Fish-man!
But a pirate who fights by chivalry
can only be mediocre.
Why don't you see for yourself,
if my chivalry is mediocre?
l was raised by an unbeatable pirate.
Seems like you're really unfamiliar with
the superiority of the mermen race.
I still ain't getting free.
Not yet? Can't you pull 'em out yet?
Not yet.
I don't think l can get out just by stretching.
Are you even trying?!
Do you even want to free your legs?!
What are those two fooling around for?
This is Arlong Park for crying out loud.
I'll kill you!
Crap, Crap.. Come on, dammit, get 'em out!
We gotta get outta here!
Wait!
Hey, Octopus.
Those two are busy.
l'll be your opponent.
Nyu, Roronoa Zoro!
I almost forgot about you!
That's right! Then you also killed
some of my brethren!
l'm not interested in any of that old news.
Your reason for wanting me dead...
I don't care about it.
The situation's changed.
It's not you who want to kill us.
It's us who want to kill YOU!
Alright, Zoro...I'll let you have that octopus.
Nice.
Ahh! Luffy!!
Huh?
I'm back to where I started.
Bastard!
Goodbye...
Looks like you really want to be killed...
lsn't that the guy who saved Gen-san?
Aren't you guys from Cocoyashi Village?
Seeing that you have all these weapons,
I can assume you guys are rebelling?
You guys are all...
KAENBOSHI!
Usopp-aniki!
Your opponent, is ME!
lf you wanna die so badly, I'll kill you right now!!
What's with that guy?
He stands up to fight, and then he
runs away... He's a strange one.
Get back here, you long-nose!
Hey, same with your mouth!!
Why did these guys become pirates?
Same old, same old.
Move!
This is getting boring. l just can't stand watching.
Arlong-san, I thought we asked
you not to get violent here.
I'm not going to, I just thought
of an interesting game.
A game?
l'm gonna
DESTROY YOU!
Do you guys seriously think you can win against us?
So what about it?
Of course we think that, you idiot!
Let go of my hand!
Seems like he wants to say something.
Whoa! What the, what's going on?!
People who possess the power of
the Devil's Fruit are dead-weights!
Well, even if you didn't have those powers...
You'd still sink in this situation!
He can't be thinking.. into the sea?!
GOMU GOMU NO...
GOMU GOMU NO PISTOL!
OUCH!!
ldiot!
Why you!
Useless.
Luffy!
Bastard!
l'm coming to save-!
Idiot! Don't get worked up!
If you jump in, you'll be right
where they want you to be!
The mermen have the upper hand underwater!
There's only one way to save Luffy.
Take care of these guys quickly
and then jump in the water?
Let's do it!
We don't have much time.
Right!
How many seconds do you think he'll last?
That rubberman.
Ah, so this is the game you were talking about.
I see.
The fish is yours.
You got the octopus.
I'm in troubIe.
I don't have any strength to move!
Oh no!!
He can't do anything by himself like that!
Luffy-aniki is gonna die!
You can't even breathe underwater.
Humans are such inferior beings.
Come on!
I'm your opponent, you freakin' octopus!
Game! A game!
I'll finish this up in 5 seconds...
No, 3 seconds.
Don't be in such a hurry!
No matter what happens,
you have no hope of living after this!
TAKO-HACHI-BLACK!
Hold on! Luffy!
I'M DOOMED!!