And then the Legend started!
Until the end of the Rainbow.
Father, that exceeds all our hopes.
Look at that. All the treasures present here are from now on with me.
Leave from here!
He the guy!
Of made not too much!
This is the property of Pumpkin Pirates.
As long as Lapanui will not have returned, we will defend this place!
Professor!
I am also a member of Pumpkin Pirates!
I will fight at your sides!
I will also help you, Ossan!
Professor!
I was touched!
Bandage imbeciles. How can you let these kids walk you on the feet!?
Whetton!
It did not change since the last time!
Not, in fact, I am the grandson of Whetton, Reik.
One resembles oneself this point?
Ouais, almost identical!
Is Oh, it true?
Then Grand-père was as beautiful as that.
What does it have?
Which strange character…
Give us the treasure immediately!
Or I will use this electric combination to reduce to you in ashes!
Take guard! This type uses electricity!
Electricity, hein?
I was held there, waiting patiently until you attack me.
If electricity is your only weapon, I will use my katanas…
and to cut it into two!
Hum, one cannot do that with electricity…
Ca with the funny air.
Thus test!
I awaited that impatiently!
It is calm, you do not find?
Ouais, too calm.
I wonder whether everyone is well…
Who knows.
“Which knows”?! How can you say a similar thing!?
Aren't you anxious for the others?
One does not have to be done some for them.
The question is more to know if this moron of Mayor will return or not.
If Luffy puts a beating to him,
We will not have to pay these taxes.
Ouais, you are right.
One goes there?
Ouais, it left.
GOMU GOMU NO!
ROCKET!
What is it that?
One stopped.
C-captain!
V you, dumbs!
How you dared to penetrate in my Rainbow of the Fogs!
Pay maintaining to me a tax of 50 million Berrys to be entered there!
Not.
What you ace known as!?
Do you want to say that you will not obey the order of Whetton-sama!?
Whetton…
It is you!
Yes, I am the tall one and splendid Maire of Ruluka, Whetton!
What!? A pirate who proclaimed itself Maire!?
Does Ca pose a problem to you!?
C-captain! This kid, it is him which stole our ship!
What?
T you are… the horrible brat of the other time?
Then was Ruluka set fire to and you became Maire?
I cannot accept that!
I will never accept that!
Your mouth!
Lapanui!
Kid, being Maire it is brilliant.
You remainders sitting with your office and you take the money which the citizens gained hard.
You drive out your enemies and you have never to worry about be stopped by the Navy.
Each day is like a paradise for me!
It is really an easy work.
Since you returned, you should try to obtain a capacity such as mine!
Compared with the statute of Mayor, to play pirate is a waste of time.
Captain!
Father!
Dumb, which are you…?
You do not know what is a true pirate.
What?
Luffy…
The capacity is useless.
We, the pirates, have a dream.
Does U-Un dream…?
My electric combination is invulnerable.
You will not escape to me!
To escape? Who would do that?
I said that I was going to cut your electricity!
Is explained, what you understands by “cutting” electricity?
We should cut it.
Take that!
Rolling Thunder!
Hein?
What occurs?
If the energy source is cut, that becomes useless, not?
Fact of shitting!
Why did you make a similar thing?
Give the current, small bitch!
Would be cursed!
It is cheating, whore…!
He, I need a knack!
I run! I run!
Save me, somebody?!
Close it!
A dream?
What does that want to say?
I would like to know what is this “dream” that you all have.
You want just gold and money, not?
With capacity, you can precisely fill the pockets.
The dream of a pirate…
Is to become more the great man on the sea.
I am that which will become the Lord of the Pirates!
Luffy…
Fact of shitting!
None of those which fought against me survived!
Now you with being prepare put in parts!
Wait, Capitaine!
Father, I want to come too!
I of insane!
Captain!
It still occurs something!
The Tower of the Rainbow!
It is destroyed!
Whore…
What occurs?
It gave up us here…
Whetton, dumb!
It is not any more my captain!
Make shit!
Luffy!
Lapanui!
It is Lapanui!
It returned!
Thank you my god… Lapanui.
This time, I really was afraid for him.
Whore, this guy is really emmerdant.
Q - What is it that?
Would this be?
Professor?
The existence of Ape' S Concert rests on a very fragile balance.
Following this giant explosion,
One cannot know what it will occur!
It is what this brothel?
The distortion of space develops!
At this speed, one all will be aspired and killed!
What!?
I cannot believe in it…
The Tower of the Rainbow…
Completely buried.
Whore. I knew that it was not finished, but I did not think that it was going to disintegrate.
But good, that does not have any more importance.
Maintaining this pitiful band of morons will return never again.
The treasure is with me!
The sky falls…
We do not have much any more of time!
Surely less than one hour!
One is badly barred! One must leave from there!
But… how?
The author of this book wrote these pages apart from Ape' S Concert.
The means of leaving must be written in it.
Q - What is it?
“The continuation in last volume…”
Where is it?
YOU DO NOT HAVE It!?!?
Over there!
What is there?
Luffy, this light!
It is the sunlight!
The light of a sunset!
A sunset!?
There is a breach in space…
And the sunlight is engulfed inside!
Presently, we ran towards this light and we almost left!
V-Vraiment?
We dispatch!
This light can disappear constantly!
Hoist the sail!
Everyone! Take the oars and put all your forces there!
Ouais!
He, the guy, go up!
Lend to us strong hand!
One from goes away from here!
Ok…
But brothel, what you insane?
Be satisfied to row!
It is what I do whore!
Ah, they broke!
What do you foutez!?
Shit, one is badly barred!
He, look at, the light attenuates!
Is this the end…?
You them guy, go down and push!
Be sick for you!?
If you push all together, then perhaps…
CRETIN!
So only there was a powerful wind…
You require that the wind blows?
He! What do you make!?
I will explode our ship!
It is a ship of the Navy after all.
There is a large cargo of boulets de canon.
If I light them,
They will cause an enormous wind!
But…
Wait, Lapanui!
If you do that, then you will be…
What will it arrive to you!?
My treasure!
Mine!
Now I will be Maire for always!
He.
I think that our companions are inside this fog.
What doesn't go?
I hope that you will not say to me that you returned only?
Then?
He, remains there!
Lapanui!
He, where do you go? Return!
We are Pumpkin Pirates!
We swore always to remain together, with our companions, until death!
The guy…
Lapanui plunged to save you the guy!
Do not waste its bravery!
You will do nothing but die with him!
We will not die!
Henzo, we will return!
It does not matter how much years that will take, we will return in Ruluka!
Isoka…
Dirty waste!
Do not think that you can attack the Mayor and you to leave there also easily!
The militia of the city will make you pay 90 million Berrys!
You will regret it!
I have of it really anything with foutre them.
There is already boot to them the bottom.
What?
But it is the duty of the citizens to pay taxes!
Why the pirates should pay taxes?
B-Ben…
Sanji!
The Rainbow of the Fogs…
Disappears!
What?
Luffy and others…
What their did it arrive?
Now they will return never again!
Never!
No matter what you make,
There is no weakness with my capacity!
Up there!
What!?
What occurs!?
Merry!
Are they well?
My castle!
Ca carries all my richnesses!
Nami-san! Friends!
Not, how is this possible!?
Our ship…
Sanji, that made a long time!
Nami-swan-!
Why…!?
Hmm, I am irritated so much!
Why, Nami-san…?
All the treasures which we had on board are flown away.
I advise you to remain far from it during a small moment.
It of it is enough, pirate!
Navy?
In fact the types pursued us front!
Save us!
These gangsters try to steal the goods of the citizens!
This jewel was stolen by pirates 100 years ago and one believed it lost forever.
The Ring of the Illusia Queen.
Why is it in your possession?
Ben, you see…
I hope that you did not steal it.
Not! It is absurd!
This treasure was hidden in Ape' S Concert!
Yes! Yes!
We left it an old wreck!
I see.
Thus do I can consider that it does not belong to anybody?
What!?
Mayor!
We have to find a great quantity of treasures which could be saved
Very well.
The Navy all will confiscate them.
Stop!
I will not let to you touch with my treasures!
They are mine!
The treasures not having owners belong all to the World Government.
If you continue to act thus, you will be regarded as a pirate!
Ca is enough!
Before I was a pirate in any case.
I took all that I wanted by the force!
Take guard!
I now will have to act consequently of your acts.
I hope that does not disturb you, Pirate Whetton.
What!?
Would this be?
Summers you…?
Lapanui!
Not possible!
Hadn't I said you that we would return?
Isoka!
Stop Whetton and its gang!
Ok!
You all are in life the guy?
But how?
After the explosion we were propelled outside us too.
But it was in the world of 50 years ago.
As I thought it.
The Fog was able to modify the course of time completely.
Then, why didn't you say it earlier to me!?
To make fall Whetton with all the capacity which it had piled up, we needed a capacity even larger.
Yes, we needed the capacity of the Marines.
It is what we carried out.
But to obtain this capacity really took us much time.
I see.
But even if I carry this uniform of Navy,
Here and now, I am Pumpkin Pirate!
Henzo, your comrade.
Now and for always!
Lapanui…
And…
I forgot to specify that the pirates of Luffy are also in a state of arrest!
What!?
Species of monster without heart!
And in more I made you eat, morons!
The Navy swore to make owe them…
To make reign justice, and they will not accept that required people escape.
But…
What a brothel!
We must transport Whetton and his gang to the HQ of the Navy!
The Pirates of Luffy could escape right under our nose!
We are not numerous enough!
But during this time we can go to make a small round…
Ca could take one or two days before returning!
And if they are escaped during this time, one can nothing make there!
AH, I GIVE UP! I DONOT CAN WHAT MAKE!
You did it purposely…
Afflicted, we cannot repair it completely.
But these provisional repairs should avoid to him taking water.
I thank you, Luffy.
You and your companions.
Maintaining my years of research are finished.
One cannot say that.
One does not know when the Rainbow of the Fogs can return.
With this trick in the vicinity, one must always remain vigilant!
We need you to create something in order to counter the Rainbow of the Fogs.
I can do that.
The Rainbow of the Fogs is a lost Kingdom.
It has neither day, nor night.
And it, if it is not completely, is practically deprived of evil.
The sea gleams like emeralds.
The sky, easily confused with milk, wraps us deeply.
The unhappy ships which were victims of this kingdom there left an immense fortune.
It was really the last paradise on ground.
We were the kings of this Lost Kingdom.
As a combatant the pirates who wanted to invade it, we preserved the peace of this paradise.
We were Pumpkin Pirates!
I decided that our many adventures inside the Fog…
Beings had written here.
For the adventurers who will visit this Kingdom.
And these adventurers who guided us on the way of the return…
Were the Pirates of Luffy!
And Ben, it was a sympathetic place!
Really?
This cemetery of boats was a horrible place!
Nan, it was horrible and all, but…
I will like to go back there later!
What did that have of so sympathetic?
Rain?
This… is not rain.
Hail?
I do not think…
Ca resembles rather…
www.rival-spirits.com
http://www.zento.fr
www.saiyajin-team.com
www.kyubi-wolf.net
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/rival-spirits
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/zento
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/saiyajin
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/Kyubi-Wolf
CYB3RFR34K-ISO