The Hero of Arabasta
And the ballerina on the bridge
Release! Release! Release!
Crocodile-Sama!
Crocodile!
It came to save us!
Crocodile?
One of ShichibukaiÉ?
Crocodile!
The farm, imbeciles.
I came only for the head from these pirates.
How it is beautiful!
You known as that, but you save us each time!
CROCODILE, BANZAI!
The guard of Arabasta!
Crocodile!
The King of the desert!
Good, call me as you want.
However, you will regret having sown the disorder in this countryÉ
Dirty pirates.
You it pètes not a little?
You think of being able to all alone beat us all with you?
You sold your heart with the authorities,
salt dog of the Government!
You seek to do what, by comprising you as hero?
How those which do not want to die hide!
Enough spoken! It is only one boasting!
Kill it!
And all the richnesses of this city will belong to us!
Ouais!
What a terrible Shichibukai!
We really do not play
in the same category of piracy.
Salt pig.
CrocodileÉ
Crocodile-SamaÉ
Crocodile!
Still CrocodileÉ
Kingdom of Arabasta. Palate of Alubarna
It still arrived before you?
Time that our troops arrive at Nanohana,
it had already done the housework.
I see.
It is not serious, since the people are healthy and except.
King d' Arabasta. Nefertari Cobra
We must be to him grateful about it.
There is no doubt on top.
The boat moves right on Arabasta.
I will be soon of returnÉ
Luffy! Do not lie me!
Say to me what you know.
Eh! Why you divert the head?
Look at me!
Not, not! I really do not see what you speak.
Oh, then I you will ask it directly.
How it is made that the vivres planned for us eight
until our arrival with ArabastaÉ
É suddenly disappeared in the middle of the night?
Do not try to roll me!
You are a nullity with the poker!
Eh, there is something around your mouth.
Ah, zut! I forgot to wipe me the mouth!
It WAS WELL YOU!!
Cretin.
Ah, Nami-San.
You saw that?
My giant trap is not yet rather large!
Perhaps could you buy a lock for the refrigerator to meÉ
ReallyÉ
I will think of it.
After all, our lives surely depend on it.
Well! We must fish fish for Sanji-Kun!
Does Oh, all go well here?
Sure B-Bien!
I see starsÉ
Good blood, I cannot release you eyes one second.
Ah, I am hungry!
You think that one will be able to catch something in this manner?
Luffy! If nothing is caught, it is because you ate all the worms!
Without soft food, we are not likely to take something!
You of eaten ace, you too!
Euh, only those which were stuck to the lidÉ
Luffy-San, Usopp-San.
You caught whichÉ
Karu!!
I wonder whether we will catch a shark with that.
I prefer to take a monstre marin!
YouÉ
What do you makeÉ in Karu!?
What is it?
If that could be barbe ˆ papaÉ
I will warn Nami-San.
Nami-San, there is something of odd! Come quickly!
Ah, does not worry you.
It is nothing.
It is a just little vapor.
Vapor which rises ocean?
Yes, it is a Òpoint chaudÓ.
It is what that?
It is an exit point of the magma.
At this place, there is an underwater volcano.
There are volcanos even at the bottom of the oceans?
Of course.
Moreover, there is even more at the bottom of the oceans that on the dry land.
Which interest? Ca is not eaten.
If the things remain thus,
in a few thousands or tens of thousands of years,
É there will be a new island at this place.
You are marvellous, Nami-Chan!
Ten thousand yearsÉ
I wonder whether I will be still in life.
Not, you will have died.
You are human.
Still nothing caught?
Oh, Sanji!
I am famished.
Something will prepare me.
You despair me.
Good, I nevertheless will excavate the basic store-room in roof to see whether there is something which trails.
Ca been able sulfur!
I do not see anything! With share of the vapor!
Be patient! One soon will leave there!
Mr. 2, Good Clay-Sama!
What is there!?
Smoke raised at 12 noon!
No importance!
Continue straight!
In any case, it is necessary that I finish some with Mr. 3 or I will be in danger of death!
We enter the cloud of smoke!
It is what, all this fog?
One does not see any more in front of oneself.
One is come out from it.
Mr. 2, GOOD CLAY-SAMA DISAPPEARED!
Excavate the cabins!
He is not there!
Impossible!
Mr. 2, GOOD CLAY-SAMA!!
Oh not!
Why I cling to a giant duck which I have just met!?
U- A siren?
Do not thinkÉ
Help me! Please!
I am a true anvil, I cannot swim!
On its back:Good Clay
OhÉ I believed well that I was going to die, this blow!
In fact not!
Swan, swan.
Swan:Swan
I was saved by pirates whom I do not even know.
I will never forget your kindness!
Oh, I wondered whether I could have a quite hot soup bowlÉ
AND THEN WHAT STILL!?
ONE DIES OF HUNGER TOO!
Oh!
How you are nice!
My pretty small fruit, I would like to devour you well!
Biz'
Which funny of typeÉ
Then, you cannot swim, hein?
It is that.
I ate a Fruit of the Demon.
Ah, and which?
GoodÉ
I imagine that I have a little time before my boat comes to seek me.
I can make you a small demonstration very well.
My skill will impress you!
What is this quÉ!?
Wait! Wait! Wait!
I said to you that it was only one demonstration!
No concern!
But it is me!
I had you! I had you! I had you!
It is enough to a small slap of the left handÉ
And here, I take again my normal aspect!
It is the capacity which I acquired by eating the ÒBasket Basket FruitÓ!
Basket:Imitation
Its voiceÉ
And even its attitude are identical!
TOO MUCH COOL!!
In fact, I do not need to type very extremely.
He! Look at!
If I touch my faceÉ
É of the right handÉ
É I can imitate no matter whomÉ
It is as simple as that!
Ca also goes for the body, of course!
Ca is enough!
Does Eh, that go?
Good,
I believe well that I can nothing show you moreover, unfortunatelyÉ
Be incredible for you! Still!
Ah, I do not have the choice!
Since you insist!
Go ahead! Go ahead!
He likes to be made wish.
Well, well, I will show you something of other!
My storage capacity!
Loan?
It is too odd, that one!
And that one then?
It is too well!
It is shitting.
Then, you found that well?
I do not show it with everyone.
It was giant!
Do not flatter me! Do not flatter me!
It tears! It tears! It tears!
They saoulent me.
Hold, it is my boat.
It is largest! It is largest!
It is the moment to say itself goodbye.
It is well damage.
Please, do not leave!
Do not be sad!
Separations form also part of the voyages!
But do not forget this:
In a true friendship,
time does not have any importance!
Do not cry me!
ONE SE WILL RE-EXAMINE!
Good, the guy, is necessary to go there!
Yes, Mr. 2, Good Clay-Sama!
Mr. 2!?
It was himÉ Mr. 2 Good Clay!
Vivi didn't, you recognize it!?
Not, I had never met Mr. 2 or the partner of Mr. 1 beforeÉ
É I do not even know their capacities!
I had some rumors of courseÉ
Mr. 2É
They said that Mr. 2 was an extravagant ballerina with the voice engravesÉ
É which carries a coat to the pace of swanÉ
É with the back of which one can read ÒGood ClayÓ.
Could you have collected.
Does Y' have something which does not go, Vivi?
Among the memorized faces which it showedÉ
É there was the face of my father!
The face of King d' Arabasta, Nefertari CobraÉ
If it can be made pass for the KingÉ
it is certainly not with a charitable aim.
One has just let leave a dangerous guy.
It is an enemy?
He will pose certainly problem if he is being our enemy.
When it realizes that we are enemyÉ
É it will be able to use its capacity to be made pass for one of us.
Then we will not be able any more to trust us.
And then?
Listen to me, LuffyÉ
Wait a little.
Although this type does not have anything on what to found its opinion,
it rightly by saying that we should not fear this guy.
I think that it is a chance to have met him.
We can now envisage a response?.
One, two, three!
Mr. 2 Good Clay-Sama.
How are four said?
You seem to be of good mood.
I was made new friends!
This trick is enormous!
Chacalot!
A monster of the seas!
OUR FIRST MEAL IN FOUR DAYS!
WITH TABLE!
The course is good!
I would like to be already there.
PUFFS OUT!
Eh, it is run away!
Is necessary to continue it!
BEHIND! BEHIND!
C-C-like if it were possible!
Do not let it leave! Catch it!
You ace interest to be edible, salts monster!
STOP!
Vivi did, what take to you!?
For Why? Vivi-ChanÉ
You should not eat it!
For people of Arabasta, it is a crowned creature!
You could not say it earlier?
Do the oceans abound in surprises, hein?
You ace to learn still much if this trick you frightened ace.
Yosh.
And if I told you the time where I cut down some of these monsters in Calm Belt.
Monstres marins!?
And not small.
Y' had heaps of them!
My meal was made the trunkÉ
Do not worry youÉ
Soon, you will be able to eat as much as you want.
REALLY!?
Which kind of cat it will be, this time?
Vivi, the wind and the climate seem to be stabilized.
Yes, we entered the climatic zone of Arabasta.
The presence of Chacalot confirms it.
I bet that what there is behind usÉ
É is an additional proof of the proximity of Arabasta.
All these boats! When are theyÉ?
Oh! They carry all the emblem of Works Baroque!
They start to gather.
They are certainly the ÒBillionsÓ.
They are under the orders of the ÒAgents OfficersÓ.
They are at least two hundredsÉ
Moreover, they form the elite of Works Baroque.
They are quite higher than the bargain hunters of Whiskey Peak.
In this case, let us open fire as long as we can it!
LET US STOP QUICKLY!
Not, it is faster to sink to them above and to put to them p‰tŽe!
ALLONS-Y!
Not, waitÉ most important is until I eat initially!
Imbeciles, stop panicking!
It is only small fry.
It is true. One should not lose sight of the fact our true objective.
We are only eight, do not forget it.
Well, be certain to have tightened it well.
We are unaware of still many things about our enemies.
Well considering.
With this sign, we will not have any problem to identify us quickly.
It was so much resembling?
When it used the capacity of the ÒBasket Basket FruitÓ?
It is more than one simple resemblanceÉ
É he was us!
Should to you have seen that!
One even danced with him!
The male ballet dancers do not interest me.
Knowing that there is a similar type at the enemyÉ
É we should not act individually.
And me? What do I have to make?
Do of tone better!
It is not worthwhile to make some more than you can it!
It is normal to flee an enemy whom you cannot beat!
To do my utmostÉ
Heard!
The island is in sight!
We will stop in the port of Nanohana.
We will be able to hide the boat there.
Well! No matter what it arrives from now onÉ
É this mark on our left armÉ
É is the badge of our friendship!
And now, with us dry land!
Towards a restaurant! Oh and afterwards, ArabastaÉ
Revise your priorities.
We will face a herd of assassins, Luffy.
Ah, it is true.
Thus acted not according to your instincts! Included/understood?
Ouais, it is of agreement.
I included/understood, I included/understood!