The island which lives under snow
The rise of Drum Rockies!
I will take you along there.
Then do not die now.
Nami.
Sanji.
Ah! Look in front!
It is them, wapol-Sama!
WAIT! KID!
What? You are who you?
How oses you still to humiliate me?
I you will make it regret!
Release!
Wapol uses the word hippopotamus
(Kaba) Instead of idiot, naive (Baka)
Which hippopotamus?
Why
I should release?
The girl on your back and the type that
you carry have the air almost died.
Wait!
Ah, that is there!
Chess!
I come just from
to find a new law.
Write that.
Yes!
“Whoever will ignore the King will be carried out
at once
! “
You two!
I will start with those
who are unaware of me more!
Kill the patient and the casualty initially!
What do you say?
Leave me the girl!
I undertake the unconscious type!
Take that!
Listen, Luffy!
No matter what it arrives, you
do not have especially to fight!
If you start the combat
or take a blow,
it will be Nami-San which
in the shock will support!
SHIT!!
I WILL REMEMBER IT!
DO NOT FOLLOW ME!
Species of coward!
Ca is not used for nothing!
Let us show him
how we fight
in a snow-covered country.
What?
They are not there any more…
How is that done?
Did they give up?
Here our speciality.
The hiding-place in snow!
If you are also weak,
you will die at once!
You lost!
STOP!!
Ours polaires?
Of Lapahn?
Did they protect them?
It is right a coincidence.
Lapahn are not
friends with the human ones.
You…
Thank you!
Thank you for your assistance!
Do not let them escape!
Yes!
What does that want to say?
Doctor…
Here it is…
I cannot even see the top of it.
There high,
there is a doctor.
Hold out still a little…
Nami, Sanji!
An avalanche…
It carried us.
Usopp-San?
USOPP-SAN!
Usopp-San!
Hold good!
Awake!
It is always in life.
Usopp-San,
cling!
Cling,
Usopp-San!
That there is, Vivi
? Let sleep to me.
I was in the train of
to make a fantastic dream.
It was in a marvellous world,
with fields of flowers
splendid and of the superb rivers.
REMAIN HERE!
Ah the river, the river…
Rendors not! Upright!
Now, come! 74.000 members
crews of Usopp the pirate!
Not! Awake please!
Usopp-San, do not die!
Usopp!
Usopp-Saaan!
Ah! You saved me, Vivi.
It is thus that which one
invite to return from the hell!
It is brilliant, I am in life, but…
It is me, or is this
what my head is swollen?
This are
engelures, of engelures.
It is me or my head is heavier?
These countries of snows
are dangerous, you know.
It is me or my field
of is vision smaller?
It is necessary to hurry.
It is necessary that one gathers our information
and that one gives a progress report on our situation.
Ouais, it is surely with
cause my imagination.
WHAT SE PASSES?
I give up.
I saw a field of flowers…
It is too cold. And
this whore of avalanche!
But good, that must be like
a bath in an ice-cold water.
Zoro?
Oh, Vivi!
Ah, it is you, Usopp!
What did you make?
It would be rather with
us to ask it to you.
Cretins of animals!
You, miserable rabbits, have
tried to oppose to you to the king!
I must admit well that I did not think of having
need for all my power against a rabbit band.
You did not can make differently.
It is the species more
wild of the Kingdom of Drum.
I arrive…
HAT OF PAAAILLLEEE!!
Doctor…
Doc.… tor…
Doctor!
IEA!
SANJIII!!!
It was right…
A winter bath?
Ouais.
I swam in the river and, all
with blow, I did not know any more where I was.
Then, I moved away towards the broad one, I lost sight of the fact the bank and I lost myself in wood.
Completely naked?
, You are to you a moron know?
I of insane Usopp,
lend to me your coat.
Out of the question.
I wonder whether Nami-San is not
patient because of this mental tiredness.
Your shoes then!
Not.
A shoe.
Not!!!
You must pay for your errors.
Look at that.
These people who are over there.
These constructions me
say something.
You are right!
It is Bighorn!
We returned to
our starting point!
You draw aside!!
Dalton already died!
It is not sufficient to kill Dalton!
You were the soldiers of Dalton!
Don't you feel anything?
We serve our King, Wapol!
Those which are opposed to
Wapol-Sama will be killed!
He. What occurs?
You requests what occurs…
You would not like rather to know
why be equipped to you like that?
Dalton-San… is buried
under an avalanche!
Dalton-San?
Yes…
But, because of them, one
cannot leave it snow!
You draw aside!
All those which have a problem, approach you
and show us what you are able!
Usopp.
I already saw these front uniforms.
These are those that one
met at sea.
I am right?
Yes, that with the air.
Thus they are our enemies.
Hein?
Enemies.
Euh?
What are they then? Allies?
Euh. They are enemies, but…
What that made?
You are afraid, even without Dalton here?
Mr. Bushido!
Who is this?
He, you! Stop!
You are causing them!
Pretty and hot! I take it!
You attacked it for that?
He, looks at! They have
air irritated now!
You!
You were on the same boat as
the guy who overcame Wapol-Sama!
You are a little slow with
relaxation, comrade.
You seek…
that?
Kill it!
What? Already finished?
What a band of nazes!
Incredible.
Well!
Good work, Zoro!
You followed my instructions!
Let us find Dalton-San!
Ouais!
Thank you very much!
We dispatch!
Dig here!
Eh well? What occurs here?
You will wonder it later.
We must help them!
Dalton-San… Remain
in life please!
Doctor!
Doctor!!
Hold good…
One is there almost.
Do not die!
I arrived there.
Doctor…
Doctorine…
The antibodies react.
Yes.
It is normal.
Then, which is
this disease causes?
Can you say it?
Kestia.
It is exact. It is Kestia.
Deal with the girl.
Yes.
Who?