The resolution of Dalton!
The army of Wapol Unloads.
It is a snow-covered island!
These mountains are Drum Rockies.
Located on the most peak, in the center of the mountains,
a woman saw whom people call
“witch”, the single doctor of the country,
Dr. Kureha.
He Nami.
Cling!
One goes there!
Take guard in Laphan.
It is a voracious rabbit race.
If you meet them, it is assured death.
They have the speed of rabbit, and bear forces it.
They generally attack in group.
We break!
What do they make?
These foutus rabbits! It is not true!
Do Oh He, Sanji, what occur?
What does it occur?
Let us leave, Luffy!
To flee? But where?
Anywhere! Also far you can!
Too much late!
THEY HAVE CAUSES AN AVALANCHE!
These Rabbit whores!
They will pay it!
What does one make?
How one draws from there, Sanji?
I do not know!
But in any case, the 1st priority, it is Nami!
2nd:Nami-San!
3rd:Nami-San!
4th:Nami-San!
5th:Nami-San!
You ace measuring rod?
Manage to save it!
Included/understood!
But how?
There! This rock!
A rock?
Course!
We must put ourselves in height!
It arrives!
Ouf! It was less one!
Oh not!
It is not high enough!
It is Wapol!
Wapol returned!
What?
Dalton moves towards Bighorn!
That all those which can fight,
take the weapons in direction of Bighorn!
Quickly! That those which are ready to fight,
on the way for Bighorn!
All at the sides of Dalton-San!
Wapol is of return!
With the weapons everyone!
Let us protect our country!
With the weapons!
On the way for Bighorn!
YES!
He, Vivi. Be sure for you that one is on the good way
is Gyasta village where this witch?
Now that you say it, I am more very sure…
If are not sure for you, one in one is crowned kneader!
Imagine that Luffy and the others arrive at the castle and that they see that there is no doctor.
They will set out again by wondering where it passed!
If we do not find the doctor quickly
to say to him to turn over to the castle…
I know that, but…
If you know, then do something.
Be to you a Princess, not true?
Ca does not have anything to see!
I am not a witch, I am a Princess.
Ouais, ouais…
Then why you would not look at the chart, Usopp-San?
Would not be idiot!
All is covered with snow… One can nothing make some even with a good chart.
Then, you do not know either where one moves?
Not!
I have any idea absolutely of it!!!
You should not be about it to trust.
At all events. Some share along this way, one would have
normally to have a panel for Gyasta.
One should not miss it.
Well! You can count on me!
You can trust me! No problemo!
He, you listenings what I do say?
DELICIOUS!
, You listen others!
All in this country
is my snack!
I am…
VERY POWERFUL!
And why…
Kuromarimo!
Say to them!
Naturally!
It is because you are the King!
Your Glorious Highness.
It is exact!
Exactly!
This is why, I must have my cooked houses at point!
Wapol-Sama.
I have new information to report to you.
Which?
If I then to allow me…
We received information
that the pirate with the straw hat and them his
would move in direction of your castle.
What?
Why?
They transport a sick woman
over there to consult a doctor.
These morons!
There is no doctor in my castle!
There is nobody any more over there!
Moreover, of the same report/ratio,
It would seem that Dr.Kureha
currently lives in your castle.
WHAT?
Is this old witch in my castle?
Until where she will humiliate me?
Listen!
I will foutrai it outside.
And I will puff out it, it and this snotty-nosed kid with the straw hat!
My brave men.
We will turn over to the castle!
OUAIS!
Ca is enough!
Who dared…
Ahh! It cut me!
I will die!
Dalton-San!
I came to kill you.
Your death is only justice!
Dalton, salts bastard!
Then be to you always in life?
You dared to raise the hand on Wapol-sama…
Alas, not sufficiently.
You qualified doctors de Drum,
eminent doctors of the country.
Just.
Isshi-20, Surgical Team!
It is with you!
Loan for the operation.
Scalpel.
Fasten.
Plates.
Hammer.
Wow. I believed that I was going to remain there!!
Thinking only of your person, you prohibited
with people of this country right to consult doctors.
They had of another choice to only suffer from their diseases.
Wapol!
Wapol?
It is Wapol-Sama!
Dalton, my vassal.
It is true!
You do not have the right to address to you to him this manner.
Formerly, you were like us two,
advisers of Wapol-Sama.
Aren't we its honest servants?
It is true that while
you inflicted these sufferings with the people,
all that I did as vassal
was to observe and let make.
I assume the responsibility for it.
Wapol.
Let us leave this island.
We do not have any more our place here.
Dalton-San! You did not do anything of evil!
It is true!
You are the only member of the government
who fought for us, to defend our country!
Even with the danger of your life!
He!
It would have better done to die as
Captain of the Guard of Royaune de Drum.
I am, in any case, surprised that you have
survived in a country without any doctor.
The other countries consider that the kingdom of Drum
is very advanced in the medical field.
But what they are unaware of,
it is that only 20 “doctors of elite”
work in the laboratories of the castle,
while all other doctors
were condemned to the exile!
Of course!
Thus, those which fall sick must beg me for their life!
It is according to my mood, it is not like
if I did not want to let to you see Isshi-20.
If you do not want to die, then you must venerate me.
How a king!
What makes my capacity absolute.
It is my way of controlling!
Do THESE METHODS HAVE NOTHING TO DO WITH the POLICY?
Ca is there you finished.
Cut down it!
Kill your former chief!
I knew that you would not include/understand
even if I said it opposite to you.
I always studded myself with the hope
that the son of the advised sovereign that I was useful
would end up opening the eyes, but it is without hope!
Ushi = Bull
Caution! The fruit Ushi Ushi!
Model:Bison!
Do not hesitate!
Fire!
I am not able to touch it!
He dodges all the balls!
Old subordinate clauses or not, I will be without pity!
He is too strong! Which power…
Zoan:(Zoanthrope) human able to metamorphose itself in animal.
It is the Fruit of the Demon of the Zoan family!
The force in a wild state!
I do not test any more any pity for you!
A country whose King escapes with the first sign of danger
do not deserve to exist!
You do not have any chance vis-a-vis us two.
Give up.
Dalton-San!
One came to help you!
One came to fight!
One came to save our country of tyranny!
Your problem, it is that we are of old knowledge.
Damage for you!
Stop!
I know your weakness…
Why?
It protected us!
Dalton-San!
Dalton-San…
Here it is your weak point!
You are too nice Dalton-Kun.
Here is a death worthy of you!
It is what that?
It is what? A seism?
It is bad that!
Snow is so thick that one cannot advance any more.
One took the wrong road,
one was inserted too much in the mountain.
It is what this tremor?
Ussop-San?
You believe that it is…
An avalanche!
25.631!
25.632!
25.633!
Hein? It is what that?
It is bloody noisy!
25.634…
Oh not! It is not high enough!
What could I make?
Ah, I know!
SANJI!
Catches!
Saved!
Ouais, but…
Even if one is not absorbed by the avalanche,
one goes down again at any speed the way which we have just climbed!
WHAT?
You laugh!
One was nearly the foot of the mountain to be climbed.
One was with a step of the castle of the doctor!
Luffy! Find a means of stopping this trick!
Brothel! Rabbit filths!
The next time that they are seen, one transforms them into stew!
WHAT?
What does one make, Sanji?
There is only one thing to make…
TO FLEE!
It is what these insane furious?
ATTENTION, Luffy!
Look in front!
Ahh! A rock!
One will be caught it!
That should be avoided!
Do not forget only you carry Nami-San on your back!
You say that in vain, but…
ONE SE WILL TAKE IT!!
You must always treat Ladies…
Hein?
carefully!
Sanji!
I am inserted, shit!
Moron!
Remake a similar trick never again!
SANJI!
It arrives!
It does not stop!
The whole city will be buried!
Save which can!
Let us flee!
Chess! Kuromarimo!
Go up!
Robson!
Passes in mode “serious things”!
Wapol-Sama!
Take us along too!
The farm!
You clear up all alone!
More quickly, Robson!
It is already there!
All… All… All will be well!
No panic Vivi!
Even if you are made take by the avalanche, I should save you!!
He, Luffy-San and others…
Luffy-San and the others are perhaps
taken with the trap in this avalanche?
Wapol-Sama!
Are Nami, you cold?
Hold out still a little.
Listen, keeps to me that and await me here.
What, it is you the guy?
I wondered what gave this unpleasant syrup taste.
It is still them, I bet.
Which want you to speak?
Bah! It was THEM!
Who that “them”?
Pirates of Straw hat.
You said that they move towards my castle, not true?
And here what arrives!
These small rancorous wants
to be avenged for what one did to them!
They caused an avalanche in the mountain!
Ah! It is thus that which occurred!
Then this avalanche belonged to their plan!
Allons-y!
Let us follow their traces in the mountain!
I will teach them what it is a true battle of snows!
I will take you along up there.
Especially, do not die.
Both.
I see them!
Look at, Wapol-Sama.
They are over there.
Wait, kid!
You dared to carry reached to my person on several occasions!
You will pay it to me!