What goes it
to happen?
This belt of clouds
resemble a river.
Ah, Nami-san! Mellorine!
Ca cannot be the work of nature…
Ca does not have anything naturalness!
The exit!
There is a sign!
“Godland”.
“Country of God, Skypiea”!
It is not an exit!
It IS an ENTRY!
Divine Earth of Skypiea!
Angels of the beach of cloud
An island!
It IS the CELESTIAL ISLAND!
Said…
This sign said… Skypiea.
Yes!
The same name as that registered
on the chart found by Luffy!
The wreck which fell to us above…
… had come well up to now!
They contemplated the same one
thing two hundred years earlier!
It is what this place?
Ca feels the adventure!
Wait, cretin!
It is not deep, one has foot.
He, nothing of broken?
Usopp!
This island is made
of this marrowy cloud?
One would say well!
It is the marrowy cloud!
One unloads!
Celestial island!
Me also, me too!
I will change!
He, Luffy!
What does one make for the anchor?
There is not basic here, it is that?
One card-indexes oneself some, not?
Ouais, one is card-indexed some!
One card-indexes oneself some?
Take that!
Me also, me too!
He, come!
This beach is marrowy!
Roll!
Let test to me!
And Ben, this landscape is
rather astonishing nevertheless.
One would believe to dream.
Ouais, you said it.
Look at gallopping them like kids…
They are irremediable.
You can speak.
Afflicted! I excuse myself!
One took along the Bird of the South with us.
One forgot to slacken it.
It would seem that people live here.
Y' does not have to worry for him.
The birds can manage.
Yes, it is true.
You dropped anchor?
It is wedged in the cloud.
They are these bulky clouds
who support this island.
Then that means that the island
float on this sea…
But I wonder whether it
never change place.
Bah, one will see well.
All really seems
difficult to believe, here.
But one can at least be sure
to be arrived on the celestial island.
Look at!
I am me there too!
There is not what to be afraid!
Come with us!
Ca will be better when you
will have posed your feet above!
And you?
Ouais, I arrive.
The perfume of the adventure…
To sail and explore,
it is that the adventure.
I had never found
that exciting before.
The celestial island would be
perfect for a nap…
Ah, here the Captain.
Y' has funny tricks so much with
to make, I donot can by what start!
Finished!
Here Usopp!
And if one took holidays here?
Finished!
Holidays?
Ca sounds well!
Negative!
Negative?! Ca wants to say not!
Hold, it is well
strange flower which pushes here.
These sheets resemble balloons.
They will explode
like this octopus?
What a happiness!
The navy will not come
us to seek up to now!
One will be able to release itself a little!
He, Chopper, look at!
What is it according to you?
Funny of fruit!
Good appetite!
It is what this trick?!
It is too hard!
He, Usopp!
You want fruits? Catches!
Ca hurts, cretin!
Wait a little, you will see!
Ah, Robin-chwan!
A flower of the celestial island
only for you!
For Robin-chan.
And the other…
NAMI SWAN!
NAMI-SWAN!
MT FLEUR!
They are also made in cloud!
I imagine that they can manufacture
heaps of things containing cloud.
But it is not like
marrowy clouds.
NAMI SWAN! MT FLEUR!
It is well stuffed.
How can one wet them
feet in a sea of clouds?
Oh, perfect.
Afflicted!
It is what, that? A fox?
Music?
He!
Y' has somebody!
On top!
Still this warrior?!
The whistle!
Quickly, whistles!
That it flies to our help!
Not, wait!
It is not him.
It is…
an angel!
An angel?
Heso.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
Heso! Heso?
[Note:Heso = Navel]
She really said… “heso”?
Ouais…
Does Ca want to say what “heso”?
Not, “heso” it is the navel.
Come here, Suu!
You come from the blue sea?
Ouais, one comes from in bottom.
You live here?
Indeed.
Welcome on the Beach
angels of Skypiea.
Do you want to taste that?
Ouais…
The hull of the conashe is
last like steel.
One cannot crunch it.
Therefore, by in lower part…
And here.
It is too booooon!
Did Ah ouais? they is good?
Make taste, make taste!
It is boooon!
I am called Conis.
And here Suu, a fox of the clouds.
If you wish anything,
I will be happy to help you.
Well, on this subject…
Your glance transpierced my heart…
Move from there!
We have much of
questions to pose to you.
All here seems to us so strange.
Of course. Ask what you want.
He, Something arrives.
Ah, it is my father.
Conis-san, heso!
Yes! Heso, father!
Heu… About what do speak you, the guy?
What is what it is that?
This thing which it overlaps.
Do Ah, you speak about Waver?
They is too cool!
Waver…
Yes, excuse me!
I stop immediately!
Is nobody wounded?
AND YOU THEN!?
He, Luffy.
This machine does not resemble
that which you did fish out?
If, at bottom.
It was thus that the boat which sails without
wind about which Norland in its newspaper spoke!
They are your friends, Conis-san?
Yes, one has just met.
They came from the Blue Sea.
Thus hold.
Ca had to be a difficult voyage.
This is the Sea of Opal. Forgive me.
O-Oh not, it is nothing.
I did not present myself.
I am called Pagaya. All my excuses.
Not, no problem.
Father, did you fish fish?
Yes, a good catch.
With the fact, which you would say
to pass at home?
You will be entitled to all
celestial hospitality.
One can?
One goes there! One goes there!
Kitchen of the celestial island?
Could I help you to prepare it?
But front, I can you
to ask something?
It… does not have a veil
to take the wind…
And you did not row with…
How can it advance on water?
Don't Oh, you know Dials?
Dials?
PPP that moves
in all the directions?!
Ca does not want to stop!!
Oh my god!
I hope that it is not wounded!
What a tragedy!
Afflicted, I would not have
to lend my Waver to him!
With the fact, which it arrives to the people
equipped with capacities in this sea?
Good question.
Is this sea different, not?
Perhaps that it will be left there.
It ran.
Does Ca fear, not?
OH NOT!!
He Ben…
A little more and it fell into the vacuum!
The fault with which?! It is you
who remained planted with papoter!!
That is what has you
taken to plunge too?
The alarming celestial island…
the alarming celestial island…
It is of my fault, I have
let a beginner borrow it.
The hull of Waver is very light.
Even a small wave can
to make move the rudder.
It is necessary well to know
sea to be able to control it.
I am sorry.
I hardly start
with knowing to be useful to me about it.
It is so difficult?
Ten should be counted
years of training.
Name of god!
IT ARRIVES THERE!
It is brilliant!
Nami-san! You are the best!!
Oh my god! Here are which is surprising!
I have evil to believe my eyes of them!
How can it control this trick?!
It is not easy to take in hand!
It is well too delicate
for you, Luffy!
He, Nami!
One goes to pépé!
Go down from there immediately!
IDIOT!!
He do not speak like that!
Leave in front!
[Note:“O-jisan” means “uncle” but that can too
to designate the men of more than 35 years as it is the case here.]
O-jisan, I Can
to control still a little?
Yes, but would be careful!
A boat which can split them
floods without worrying about the wind! My dream!
I wonder whether it goes
on our seas with us!
He, it is a building site
of construction that?
Oh, it is the career of clouds.
It is here that we extract them
clouds necessary to our constructions.
You really can
to cut out clouds?
To come to the Sea from Opal…
you took Milky
Isn't Road?
Milky Road?
You want to speak about this
cloudy snail road?
It was manufactured to leave
clouds cut out here.
There exist two kinds
natural clouds.
Those on which you arrived
in boat are océonimbus.
And those, more marrowy, on
which you could walk…
are ilonimbus.
It would be impossible
with normal clouds.
Yes, the process of condensation
of each cloud is different.
[Kairouseki:“marine granite”)]
In the Blue Sea, there exists one
matter called Kairouseki, not true?
Kairouseki?
But there is a relationship with that?
Yes, one finds it in Pyrobloïne, a particle
of sulfur transported in the airs by the volcanos.
And once charged with water, the difference in pressure determines if in fact ilonimbus or océonimbus will be created.
Oh, Ben ouais, of course!
Yes, yes, I know already all that.
I played already with these particles
of sulfur when I was kid.
BEN LET US SEE!
Lastly, in short…
The clouds which you find here
are océonimbus, ilonimbus…
like those manufactured
starting from the ilonimbus.
We are there.
What a seen splendid!
I manage to see Nami on Waver!
He, Luffy!
What do you make?
This Nami…
Why it arrives there so easily?
RUN!!
Cretin!
To me am bitten the language, Sanji!
Heu, grandfather…
Where is the kitchen?
Yes, it is by there.
Doesn't something go?
Not, I had never seen that front
then I wanted to taste a little…
Ben, that tears off serious!
This… sauce color blue sky.
My language is all engourdie…
It is mildewed. I am sorry.
THEN DO NOT LET IT TRAIL!
I swallowed a spoon
whole of this trick!
I am sorry. You cut yourselves?
It would be said that he has fun.
It is insane in front of joy
refined celestial kitchen.
NOT!
Even if we come
to arrive, Miss…
Could you say some to us more to the subject
of these Dials about which you did speak to us?
Of course.
Let us see seeing…
How to say…?
Ahh… Which pleasant
and marrowy armchair.
It is what, that?
Does Y' have shells here?
Yes. Try to say
something inside.
Ok!
Usopp is an badger!
For… For… Why you say that?
And now, press
the top of the shell.
It is what a top?
Top of the shell!
“Usopp is an badger!”
“For… For… Why you say that?”
AH! SHELL SE
FOUT OF the MOUTH Of USOPP!
And with your voice!
“And now, press
the top of the shell. “
He, it is not badly that.
Ca recorded the sound.
This shell is Dial?
Yes, it is a “Audio-Dial”.
It can record and rejouer sounds.
It is one of the shells
sea of Opal.
However, this sea does not have basic.
Where do these shells live?
On the reefs of not very deep water.
But I do not see how
that can propel Waver.
Yes. Propulsion of
Waver comes from that one.
It is not very large, but the principle
is the same one as for the Audio-Dial.
The wind leaves this one then!
Give to see!
It is a Breath-Dial.
He aspires the wind and slackens then it.
The capacity varies according to the size…
But by putting it at the back of a boat,
it can move small boats.
It is thus that Waver.
I include/understand.
Then that blew of
air to move it.
Brilliant this Waver!
In fact, there is the different one too.
Of Skate-Dials
and of Board-Dials.
But Waver is it
only that I control.
I want to test it!
What a chance it has!
And one has some too!
You found Waver?
Ouais, finally by chance.
One found of them an old man very dented.
But after two hundred years,
he must function more.
Eh well, not necessarily.
Dials are made leave
remainders of shells.
As long as their shell
is not broken…
They will be almost
always functional.
Hear you that?
But you cannot still lead it.
Let dream to me…
I bet that it in
exist other kinds.
Is that one too?
Yes, this is a Lamp-Dial.
Oh, the shell shines!
There is also which
aspire fire, the Flame-Dial.
And another which aspires scents
and flavors, Aroma-Dial.
And still another which reflects
images, Visio-Dial.
There is of all kinds.
They is too cool…
They is too cool!
They form integral part of
our daily celestial life.
I see.
Thus, culture of the celestial island…
… evolved/moved with the energy of Dials.
Here, it is ready!
Specialities of the celestial island
with fruit trimming!
Ca with the succulent air!
Brilliant!
They is extra!
It is a super presentation
for shrimp!
They is too good!
He!
Where did Nami-san pass?
It is over there in the sea.
Not, it is not there.
It is probably
part to explore then.
It knows what it does.
Father, goes it
to leave itself there?
Yes, Conis-san… I am not
not quiet me either.
What? Does Y' have a problem?
It is in Skypiea a prohibited necessary where,
no matter what it arrives, no one should not penetrate.
It is very close to here.
In Waver, one is there in one moment.
They are immense…
What is it?
One should never put at it
feet… And why that?
It is a crowned ground.
A crowned ground?
This ground is called…
[Note:Upper Yard =
The higher garden]
The Field of God, “Upper Yard”.