This bastard with the straw hat?
It was not expected that Roronoa Zoro does not know its force.
How that?
Do He, you want to fight against Luffy?
I see…
You found something, Robin?
I know who am the culprit…
Not…
I know who am at the origin of these attacks.
Is this foutu kid?
Go, leave for the Palate the Divine Sea.
The Palate of the Divine Sea?
It is what?
Splendid, is not this step?
Zoro sharpens its sabers!
The combat against a wild beast!
Would this be the way of the refuge of this foutu kid?
Yes.
Really? Who is behind all that?
Say us please.
You will include/understand while arriving at the Palate.
Would they intend to attach me to a tree and to steal me my gold?
How is what I do!
Does there really exist?
It is very quiet here.
R… Re… Remain on your guards. It is the refuge of this dirty kid.
Perhaps he has ENORMOUS monsters under his orders?
Monsters?
The monsters are perhaps…
Hidden some share by there and go suddenly…
To attack you like that.
Yes… When I travelled on the ocean…
I often fell between the claws from these monsters.
He! You! Look behind you!
Hein? What is what there is?
Did you already see a monster here? There is not…
AAAH! REMOVE CA!
Never! Does not approach you me!
What is what they do?
One stopped…
This giant snake was afraid of the Usopp Captain and fled!
He!
We lost the others!
What one will make now, jerk!
It is not good that!
What is what one will so do of the monsters attack us?
Ah, does not worry you. It was right a joke to frighten you.
Oh, it was a joke…
You make fun of me, crét…
Monsters!
Then it was true.
If you come, then it puffs out!
Although it is a tanuki, it is delicious!
Stop! DECREE!
Was Ah, it only you? You really did us fear.
Aaah, not good…
Other the insane furious one returned.
But it was not like that on the boat.
Well, If you are able me to convince and me requests to join us…
I will make you member of the crew of the Usopp Captain… ah?
He… He… Listen to me.
Wait! Do you know where are the different ones?
He!
Do not leave me all alone!
He! Await me!
Ah, Zoro!
Still this foutu swashbuckler?
Hum? It is…
You decided to come with us?
Pay to!
Captain!
What is what it is?
WHAT!
Why you excite yourself of a blow?
Stop both!
Hum, you would not have.
The behavior of this foutu swashbuckler changed much.
It is…
They was dangerous!
Stop!
It will be crushed!
Where is the guy with the straw hat?
You are really unconscious!
There by amicable agreement do not seem to be solutions.
But what does it have this guy?
It seems to be under hypnosis.
It is certainly the fault of this kid.
Ca becomes tedious.
Let us attack it all together.
Do not interfere.
Continue.
I occupy myself some.
Ok, one goes there.
But it is Zoro, the hunter of pirates.
It would seem that you must beat it if you want to calm it.
Yes. The first thing to be made is to stop the boy.
GOt (380,630, \ fs72)}DRIVEN  GO  DRIVEN  NO
WORSE (410,900, \ fs72)}TOL
Is this a way of calming a companion?
If it strikes it with its punch, it will be seriously wounded.
Because it is his/her companion…
And because he knows his force…
He must all give to stop it.
Really?
I travelled with guys without pity.
Go, one hurries.
I let you make, Zoro.
Santouryu?
[Style with three sabers]
GOr} DRIVEN   GO   DRIVEN   NO
GAr} T   LING
OI (1800,2050, \ fs72)}GI  IH
Yes!
There is a cook, a doctor, a gunner and me, the navigatrice.
Nothing prevents us from going up on the boat.
He, you all!
Will you really follow this woman?
The pirates all are covetous and loose.
Luffy and this woman mislead you!
Try to include/understand!
Follow me, I will carry out you where you will want.
Do not want you to turn over in your villages?!
I want to turn over at home!
I need some really.
I do not know where they hope to take me along.
I would make perhaps better join it, instead of remaining with these monsters?
I would well also like, but…
It is true?!
Then why you hesitate?! Let us return on our premises all together!
I understand that you have evil to trust me because of your amnesia…
But follow me please, even if you think that I mislead you.
You hear?
It misleads you!
We all must carry out our dreams.
Think so that you ridges!
The men cannot live only for their dreams.
You do not let have!
It is true…
But…
What has you there it of more important than your dreams?
“Achieve your dreams, it is most important! ”…
Is probably what the captain would have said.
I am…
I go with Nami.
Let us return on our premises, in our villages!
I remain with Luffy.
Why!?
Luffy regards me as his/her companion.
Just like Dr. Hiluluk and Doctorine!
First of all, before we return on our premises and that we carry out our dreams…
We must catch this foutu kid and him botter the bottom.
Incredible!
In this case, we go there.
Is not this step?
Shit! I cannot return without having to find my memory!
Wait!
Then I will return all alone.
My treasure…
SAN (360,660, \ fs72)}TO  RYU
OUt (290,380, \ fs72)}GI
GOt (240,480, \ fs72)}DRIVEN  GO  DRIVEN  NO
Beats (400,980, \ fs72)}ZOO  KA
[Three thousand turns]
SAN (550,1100, \ fs72)}ZEN  SE  KAI
It does without the strange things sometimes on Grand Line.
Did you already meet people, who travelled on the seas and which lost their memory suddenly?
Thus this phenomenon is present only here?
It was written on the tomb stone of presently.
History of a monster which nourishes memory of people.
It uses this island as refuge now.
It is a legend, but this history is appropriate perfectly for the situation.
The memory is manufactured each day. This is why it makes use of the inhabitants of this island to nourish itself.
I see… it is like a pantry…
It is difficult to believe all that, but our memories are in danger.
You stop!
The pirates are really obstinate.
I will take control on you, as I did for the swashbuckler, and will make you you entretuer.
Oh, not!
Ah! Hands! Hands which come from nowhere…
It would seem that I must initially deal with you.
To strike a kid is not in my practices, but…
Not, it is not the kid…
Qu… That is what I have…
Is this you who stole us our memories?
Cook, the kid was only hypnotized.
The person in charge is…
He you… Wait.
I will not let myself go further as long as you will not have returned to us what belongs to us.
“As if I were going to give up these delicious memories! Baka!”
What!?
Doctor-san includes/understands what the animal says.
Speak normally, you it OCTOPUS!
“Polished Remainder! I am not an octopus. I am a hippocampus!”
How is what I have with foutre!
You!
And you!
Spit all that you have!
What? I am…
Still not…
It IS FINISHED!
Sanji-kun!
Ca returns to me!
We found all our memory!
Cook! And you?
Me as well sure!
Robin-chan and Nami-swan!
You are all the two beautiful ones even after having found my memory!
But…
I wonder whether head of marimo found the memory…
[Marimo:marine animal of Japan]
What let us be made for Zoro if it is not the case?
Zoro!
And Luffy?
Was Luffy made kill by Zoro?
Not… It is impossible…
Where is the captain?
Whore of swashbuckler!
If you intend to make evil with these young ladies, I will be your adversary.
He says:“I have still a chart to play”.