RAIGOU
Angel Island…
was destroyed…
The ancestor of Papi Head-of-Diamond
was not a liar.
Then…
Then this Papi and monkeys in
low must know the truth!
The Gold City is in the sky!
I cannot let Eneru take it!
The sound of this enormous bell will be enough
powerful to be heard of anywhere!
It is for that I go
to make sound the Gold Bell!
Cut down Giant Jack!
The ultimate hope of escape
Even the door of the Paradise…
was destroyed instantaneously.
Isn't Angel Island there any more?
But where we will live?
For the moment, all that we can make, it is to join Cloud End and to flee towards the Blue Sea.
There are not an other choice.
But…
People are still
wedged on the Sea of Opal!
Nothing for them can!
Without Milky Road,
How could we go down
with the boats on the White Sea?
Then one will give up them?!
How is this possible?
Sea of Opal…
Skypiea disappears…
Then here.
Splendid!
Here what made the pride
large city of Shandora…
The Large Belfry!
Splendid!
That is appropriate to me perfectly,
with me Very Powerful God.
It is the bell which sounded it
beginning of these 400 years of war.
But…
They fought so much, then
that soon, all will disappear.
All their efforts will be vain.
Luffy, one cannot reach it!
The arch of Eneru floats close to this cloud.
Luffy…
Eneru had to find
Gold bell now.
Even by lengthening your arms,
you will not reach it from here.
If it seizes some,
I will take it again to him!
I borrow it to you!
It is too distant
top of bean.
What can we make?
How could one reach it?
The guy!
None among you will escape from it!
Neither you, nor those of which I
still perceive the bass voices!
It is that.
They are not yet escaped.
The others are still in bottom!
Made blunder!
Another trick is falling!
What?
With cover!
A sheet?
Hein?
There is something of writing above.
A message!
It is on behalf of Luffy and Nami!
Does that say what?
Cut down giant bean…
towards the West.
WHAT?!
And then…
to what that will be useful?
He.
Where is the West?
He, be serious for you?!
I think that the arch of Eneru
is in this direction.
All my objectives were achieved!
All that it remains…
it is to use this Raigou to destroy this country and Cumuloregalis then to leave for Fairy Vearth.
I am almost sad of me to separate some!
Eneru!
What a demon!
It is still…
larger than presently!
There is no more no means…
to escape from this island!
Good-bye, Skypiea!
It is even larger than the other!
Dumb!
You are right.
Considering it found the Gold Bell,
this country is not useful to him any more with nothing.
One sees clearly in his play.
If he believes that one goes
to let slip by with,
it will have a surprise!
Won't Nami, you flee?
How can you say that now?
You want to make sound the bell, not?
Ouais!
I will sound it!
Good, and as you do not know
not to lead Waver.
If I give up you there, you go
to continue to try to climb.
I can take you along with me
and to spin you a knack.
But!
You must promise to me
how I will remain in life!
Ok, not of problem!
Let us do it!
Ca will be played little.
And one will not be entitled to the error.
I hope that the others
will have had the message.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
They will run along bean…
and to cross while jumping towards the arch?!
I see that.
They lost the head.
Of agreement, then goes up to stop them.
How if I of be able!
In any event,
insane or not, it is our only chance!
Q-Q-what
?!
Length-nose-kun
!
They is good, I have it!
If one remains here, one goes
to fall into the ruins!
You move away from bean!
Will run towards the dry land!
I will do it!
I must just cut down
is the bean, it that?
He!
The only ones with being able to reach Eneru
before it launches this trick…
on all the celestial island…
He, Zoro!
it is them!
Even with two fingers of death,
you continue you
to discuss and to run.
You still did not include/understand?
While penetrating on these grounds
during the Play of Survival,
Your destinies are
dissipated like smoke.
II it goes
to make?!
Go!
You are the only one who can cut down it!
You ace finished with your whores of holes?!
Ouais, it cut out it!
Zoro!
Poor wretch maggot.
SHIT!!!!
Mr.-MR.-but, it
cut out!
It cut out it!
Oh not…
Look at!
It does not fall!
But it cut it!
This filth is solid!
It is really a plant?
It had only what it deserves.
Foreigners, you came to line
your nose in our business.
Wiper!
You cannot!
The calm one!
This bell incarnates the will of
Karugara and it is with us to sound it!
Why Straw hat
should make it sound?!
Let it make, Robin!
In any event, it will not be able
pas l' to stop with its wounds.
Now, all is owed
to make to cut down this bean!
Luffy and Nami count on us!
Zoro already cut out us half.
This entire trick must
to start to waver.
With the explosions mortals
of my Dance of Kayakuboshi,
This thing will howl of
pain while being crushed on the ground!
I am the showpiece
of this crew of pirates!
Robin, deals with
your comrades with ground!
[Note:Mochi:rice puddings]
With the attack!
400 years ago…
An explorer of the Blue Sea…
lied while affirming
to have seen the Gold City.
Its kingdom made fun of him.
But its descendants
believed in its words…
and continue to seek
Cité d'Or in the Blue Sea.
To sound the Gold Bell…
their will state that
Cité d'Or is in the sky.
Straw hat and it
boy divide this opinion.
[Note:Gunpowder star]
Don't a valid reason, you believe?
It is rather romantic.
In spite of the situation, using of its last
chance of survival, it does not give up.
It is as if it had lost the head.
hissatsu kayaku boshi
[Note:Star mortal
of gunpowder]
[Note:Rubber band]
dobikkuri kayaku boshi
[Note:Surprised star
of gunpowder]
And…
which is the name of its descendant?
Montblanc Cricket.
And its ancestor of 400 years ago…
Did this ancestor name himself…
Norland?
Wiper?
That there is,
This would be…
a miracle?
Large Karugara Warrior!
Good…
It is time to proclaim
until the fine bottom of the skies, Nora!
We will sound the bell
that you like so much to hear…
so that Norland can hear it!
It is what?
It was what?
Even this large tremor does not have
not succeeded in reversing it!
Blasted plant!
I will launch you one
triple shooting which goes…
Release.
Karugara…
The descendant of your friend…
always waits…
to intend to sound the Gold Bell.
These people are good!
Reject
But it was what that?!
Wiper!
What a madness!
Reject Dial!
NOW TOMB, GIANT JACK!
IT COLLAPSES!
It is reversed!
Go up, Luffy!
Give all that you ace!
To be honest,
I never led it
Jet Dial at full speed.
Because…
It is so powerful that
I have evil to control it.
Then it is the occasion to see that!
OK!
It left, Luffy!
Ouais!
It collapses!
Look at!
That it occurs
over there?
Go, Luffy!
Nami!
If the celestial island is destroyed,
We will not be able
to sound the Gold Bell!
It should be sounded so that Papi
Does cricket can hear it, hein?
Now, sink
towards the arch of Eneru!
GO!
ALL RESTS ON YOU!
Go!
Let us go, go…
Why they do not wait
what my Raigou is ready?
That these mortals are impertinent.
They do not leave me the choice.
A trick prepares!
Forget that!
I can divert all
what it launches us!
Even not badly! Be bad for you!
To try like that to reach me…
is of a stupidity without equal!
You will include/understand your silly thing.
MAMARAGAN
It tests…
to collapse bean
by destroying the base.
Do something, Nami!
You want that I do what?!
One is already climbing!
Without the ground which supports bean,
N will never go rather high!
One will not reach Eneru!
The flashes strike any Upper Yard!
Luffy!
Nami!
Even if my flashes
do not have any effect on you,
that is not used for nothing if you
donot can reach me!
Fall down and awaits the end of my Raigou,
Man rubber!