Don't run, you thief!
Give us back our map!
What?
Someone fell down.
Thank God I'm alive.
What a strange journey this is!
"Fear, Mysterious
Power! Pirate Clown Captain Buggy!"
"Kyoufu Nazo no Chikara!
Kaizoku Douke Buggy-Senchou!"
I am so hungry.
Boss, are you here to save me?
Yes?
Who are you?
You take it from here, boss!
Hey, that woman ran away!
Let her go, her boss is here anyway.
You are right.
Are you here to save your underling?
Do we have food here?
Damn it! Don't mess around with us!
Don't you dare hurt my baby.
Bastard!
Might that guy be killed?
GOMU GOMU NO PISTOLET!
You are so wonderful!
I got rid of them within 2 seconds.
Ah.. you are the one who just...
Who are you?
I steal pirates'
treasure. Nami's my name.
Hey, would you like to join me?
No, I don't want to.
Wait a second.
Hold on.
I almost forgot
I am starving!
Let me buy you dinner, ok?
Really?
Yes.
Haven't you caught the thief?
We are working hard on it.
Captain Buggy. Yes.
Why would the map be stolen so easily?
Don't you forget we are
sailing toward the "Grand Line."
But the keeper who had the key
left it on by accident, Captain.
What did you say?
I said he left it on.
Whose nose are you laughing at?
(In Japanese, "Left It On"
sounds similar to "Nose".)
(In Viz's English manga, the henchman
says, "And only the robber KNOWS...")
Do you think my round nose is funny?
No, you misunderstood me.
You think my nose is big and red?
("Misunderstood" and "Big Red Nose"
also sounds similar in Japanese.)
(In Viz's manga, "mistake" sounded like "steak",
another offending word for Buggy's nose.)
Help!
He will use his power!
"Devil Fruit" power!
Who am I?
Captain Buggy!
What will you end up
if you fight against me?
End up dead.
Please spare my life.
I won't say anything wrong again.
Please give me a chance.
I can spare you this time
for saying something wrong.
You have to get back the map.
If you fail, you know
what you will become.
Yes, Captain Buggy!
Delicious.
You live in such a
big house by yourself?
I don't live here.
The townspeople were so afraid
of Buggy, they all ran away.
So you broke in here?
You are so rude.
I am a thief who only
steals from pirates.
Don't compare me with
those degraded thieves!
You are thieves anyway, aren't you?
My goal is to earn 100 million Belly.
Why do you need so much money?
It's a secret.
As long as I have the map, it should
be easy to earn 100 million Belly.
Map? Are you a sailor?
I am better than a sailor.
That's great.
Would you like to
join us to be a sailor?
Really?
To be a part of our team.
No.
So you are a pirate, too.
Yes, I had a vow.
I told the one who gave me this hat
that I will find enough partners.
I hate pirates more than
anything else in the world!
But I love money! And tangerines!
Please be our sailor.
I said I don't want to!
No.
Hey, did you find it?
Where is that female thief hiding?
We'll be dead if we don't find the map!
Those guys... I have to
think of some methods.
If you agree with my deal,
I would think about it.
Really? I can give
you anything you want.
I want you to go to
Buggy the Clown with me.
Why would you tie me up?
It's just a rope. Got
a problem with that?
It doesn't matter.
It's not a bad thing to meet
the pirate leader. Let's go now!
Hey, wait for me.
What?
You let the thief run away!
We are very sorry, Captain!
What do I need you for?
Go hang yourselves now!
Captain Buggy!
What is it?
The thief comes to us now.
What did you say?
They are these two!
That woman stole our map!
I caught the real thief, Captain Buggy.
This is your map.
I am glad you return it to me.
What do you want for return?
I broke up with my boss. I
couldn't stand him any longer.
Please let me join you team.
Captain Buggy is getting angry.
The power of "Devil Fruit"
is coming out again. Devil?
You couldn't stand
him? This girl is funny.
I like it, so I'll let you in.
Infiltration succeeds!
Those pirates are so
stupid to be fooled.
Why did you put me in cage?
Because I am happy today.
Girl, what is your name?
Nami.
Alright, let's hold a
party to welcome Nami.
Everyone enjoy yourselves.
Yes!
What's wrong? This is your party.
Eat some more.
Yes, thank you captain.
I will steal the map
back when I have chance.
And all of Buggy's
treasure along the way.
I want some too.
Ohh...
I am in such a good mood.
Guys, get the Buggy Ball ready!
Yes!
It is ready!
What do we need that for?
Witness the power of
the Buggy Ball! Fire!
What the heck was that?
That is Master Buggy's Buggy Ball!
Buggy Ball?
It is so pretty.
With the Buggy Ball and the Devil
Fruit, I can rule the Grand Line!
Am I right, Nami?
Yes, of course.
Why?
I am the only ruler of the Grand Line!
What?
I want to be the pirate king.
You idiot!
Nami, now I know why
you can't stand him.
I told you.
This guy is too naive,
and lacks experience.
I can't follow him.
I can understand. I'll give you a Buggy
Ball. Then you can blow your former boss.
And show your loyalty to me, too. Ready!
I don't need it.
This is a great party!
Let's drink some more!
Do it now. This is the
rule of our welcome party.
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
I will be killed if I don't fire.
But if I do, I will
be part of the pirates!
OK! Fire now!
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
Nami, what are you waiting for?
What is wrong?
You hands are shaking.
You are not loyal enough
that's why you hesitate.
Loyal? Does killing
somebody mean loyalty?
No.
It is the loyalty
that you would die for.
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
Hey, newcomer, don't hesitate.
Let me teach you.
Damn. I couldn't help myself!
Nami, what the hell are you doing?
I am sorry.
What? Do you think apology is enough?
What's wrong with you?
Can't you save me earlier?
Shut up, idiot! I was
out of my mind then!
Besides, I don't want to be
a part of you vicious pirates.
You were out of your mind.
Pirates took someone dear to me!
I'll never become what I hate!
Ah, I see now.
Aagh! The fuse is lit!
Stinky girl, you fooled me.
Kill her now!
No way.
Go to hell.
Put it out! Put it out!
Am I finished?
You...
Behind you!
Die!
Hey, she is just a girl. You are not
hero enough to treat her so violently.
Zoro.
Did you get hurt?
What?
No, I am fine.
Ah, that is great.
You are marvelous. How
did you know we are here?
Get me out of here now.
What's the game you are playing?
First the bird took you;
now you are in the cage.
I found it quite interesting.
Zoro?
That kid called him "Zoro".
Is the other partner he mentioned...
the "bounty hunter" Zoro?
What is going on?
Are you Zoro?
Why are you here? To get my head?
No, I am not interested.
I quit being a bounty
hunter a long time ago.
I am interested in you.
I can be famous if I kill you.
Better not, or you'll die.
Oh, really?
Are you blind or deaf?
Come on, captain!
Captain Buggy!
Buggy, Buggy, Buggy, Buggy,
Buggy, Buggy, Buggy, Buggy, [etc.]
Go to hell!
This guy dies too fast.
Wow, he really sucks.
No. Huh?
Are those guys mad?
What is going on?
Their captain was just
killed, and they are laughing.
You.
What's so funny?
Zoro!
What's wrong with your hand?
What the hell...?
The Chop-Chop Fruit.
This is the name of the fruit I ate.
I am the die hard Chop-Chop man!
His body comes together again.
I thought "Devil
Fruit" is just a legend.
"Chop-Chop man"... this guy is a freak.
Though I didn't hit your vitals,
the wound is pretty deep, right?
Surrender.
Captain is so great.
Buggy, Buggy, Buggy, Buggy...
The situation turns around.
If it goes on like this,
those two and I will be dead.
It is too severe.
Buggy, Buggy, Buggy, Buggy...
Attack behind me! You are so nasty!
Big nose!
You idiot! You can't say that word!
Damn you...
Who is "big nose"?
Buggy!
I will kick you up to the sky.
Kick me to the sky? Are you joking?
The three of you will die here.
How can you hit me in such a situation?
Come on, come on, come on!
It's over. We're dead.
I'm not gonna die!
Run now, Zoro.
What?
You told your partner to
run? I am here to save you.
What should you do?
I got it.
What? I don't get it.
I told you I hate pirates most.
Stupid kid! You can't escape from me!
Stupid kid, your knave is not working.
Damn you! Let me finish!
The cannon is aiming toward us!
Light the fuse!
Why?
Hurry up! OK!
Wait, wait, wait!
The "Buggy Ball" is inside!
Nasty kid.
The fuse! It's over! We're dead!