Then now, where please go itself?
We have a boat, we cannot travel by the train…
We follow the log poses.
I see, therefore you move towards Water Seven?
Seven toilets?
Better of all, it is a city filled with shipyards.
The carpenters are most qualified there of the world.
Well! It is decided!
We will go over there and definitively recruit a carpenter for the crew!
Waouuuuh! It is what that?
Hummm… That should be a place on by here.
Wah, I will not have believed that.
Is Going Merry damaged as well as that?
Take this.
A chart?
This will be useful to us, thank you.
Excel. We can thus go to the shipyard after having made the exchange.
Yes. Finally, us will be able to repair Going Merry.
Well! Go, will yagara!
Return, and made attention!
Go, press towards the shipyard! Yahooooo!
The adventure in quotes of water!
Victoire for the giant shipyard
It is formidable.
Eh, I count on you.
These will yagaras are so convenient!
They are not balanced either, it is comfortable!
Course far, course!
It went by!
It comes by here.
Doge!
Idiot!
Cool!
This place resembles a residential district.
These channels are really the core of the city.
Eh Year-chan.
Ah Ossan!
Where go?
The tourist visit?
We move towards the shipyard to make repair our boat!
Then, first of all, direct towards the market in the open air.
Échec et mat.
Thank you!
The market in the open air…
Towards the line starting from this point.
Oh, my pretty Miss!
What would say to be dined with me this evening?
You do not occupy of him! It is right the manner of greeting certain men here!
Eh, darling, dispatch you to go to work.
I know, you are so strong…
In any event, this city is really liberal and excessively friendly with the foreigners.
Ehh! Length-nose!
Nothing, I just wanted to joke with you!
I will strike you, ossan!
Ah, they are the stiff ways.
The current is against us. Can they assemble that?
Bad way! It is on the right! ON THE RIGHT!
It is not card-indexed badly that the current is against us.
It is really strong!
Yihoo! There are channels above the roofs, too!
It is the bad way!  We must go to the market initially!
Would not be so in a hurry!
Since we came up to now, let us assemble this channel!
Eh… Eh! Look at… Look IN FRONT OF US!
Ah. .ah! It is well, we are all in top now!
That means…
Yihou!
It is amusing.
No… Not, that is not it.
Forgiveness
Us… We fly.
We are in the train of tomb… falling… to fall… Tom…
WE ARE IN THE TRAIN OF TOMBEEEERR!!
Do not believe to have made so well!
Oh! They is cheap!
In do you want?
Come there! Now!
It is rare to see a collection of pin's of this type.
It is now that starts the fair “All to 5”!
Wooo! It is very animated now!
Hein? We found the market.
Perhaps what it was a short cut?
Forgiveness! You are really very intelligent!
I never saw a market as animated as this one.
Eh! Look at!
Which enormous will yagara.
Ooo! It comes by here!
It is really alarming!
We could eat it.
Is this a form “King”?
Hein? Is qu. .qu' what it is?
Masks?
Ehh, it is pretty! They are splendid.
There is a festival?
What is what does not go?
Mizu-mizu:Toilet-toilets [Wet, full of water]
What delights! Yagara, goes over there!
What?! Eh, where do you go?
Eh Luffy! Where do you go?
Ask Yagara!
Welcome, which is what you will give pleasure?
I see, you are hungry.
Mizu Mizu:Toilet-toilets [Wet, full of water]
Mizu-mizu?! Put to me of ten!
The chiefs of the island of the gourmet come on this market to buy our dishes.
Do your body and your heart slacken, not?
Trooooooooooooop Cooooooooooool!
Delicious!
Euh? They is good? Oi, Luffy, give me of one!
It is with me! Will buy some to you!
Oi Nami! Let us go towards the stands!
Still one by here!
If one looks at around, there is everywhere!
Nami!
They are masked people…
Oi! Nami!
Oi! Pirates make grabuge with the Dock n° 1
It is true?
Ah! Allons-y quickly!
A room V.I.P? I do not include/understand.
Not, not, it is not that.
I thought of this.
Yes, you repaired our boat well but I think that the price is too high.
You obstruct our work.
I thus finally decided not to pay only one berry.
Thank you for these good repairs!
And for nothing, moreover!
Humm. Is Kalifa, it what that?
Ah, yes, Iceberg-san.
They are the customers of the Dock n° 1, they said to me that they refuse to pay.
It is an aggravating man.
Hum, an aggravating customer…
Customers, you would have cease making fun you of the carpenters.
Ca-captain!!
Captain!!
Aoh, sorry.
That is to say cursed! Look at what you did!
Ah…. Excuse me.
Do you want really to beat you against us?
Who do you think that we are?
Oi! Did you test if this gun works correctly?
Not, not yet.
Shit! Who you êtez?!
You will not draw any like that!
In the carpenters, the pirates cannot impose their rules.
We are here, then we will enter finally the island of naval construction
With the water elevator.
Water elevator?
I believe that it is this tower.
Please, enter!
The elevator leads to the island of naval construction
Where the shipyard so famous is that it is also the center of the districts of Seven Toilets!
Please, dispatch to enter itself the conveyer, one minute before the closing of the doors.
What T will it occur in it?
Oh! The conveyer closed himself.
We are going up, to go up in top!
I see.
We enter, the whole is closed and of water arrives and propels us in top.
Water Seven is so interesting!
They can do anything with water.
Oi!
It is which it alga?
Oi Zoro!
Where is Robin-chan? It is not there.
Ouais, it is not there. It went to visit the city with Chopper a small moment.
What?
They said that they wanted to make some purchases.
What a hell! Then you are only on the boat?
What a tedious situation!
I am of agreement…
Yosh! I also will make some races and will trott me.
Esseyes to keep the boat in good condition.
He sleeps all the time…
Okay!
I count on you.
We are there!!
They are high the districts of Seven Toilets, where is the best shipyard of the world?
As I suspected it, there is more ground by here.
All is so large!
I never saw such an enormous city!
The fountain which appeared tiny to us by far is so gigantic.
T why there it has an assembly?
Do they look at the shipyard?
Tokens an eye! Go will yagara!
Look at, it is to it Lucci-san! It is so marvellous!
Where is Paulee?
Excentric is there! He is super!
It is a true man among the men!
If you want speak about a man, it is Tyrestone!
Hey, Ossan.
What did it occur?
Yes… of the pirates still assembled themselves in the Dock n°1.
But, as everyone expected it, the pirates were made amocher by the carpenters.
The idiots did not finish their procession.
Thus these carpenters can beat pirates.
Ah! You must be a traveller.
This crowd is there to admire!
Those which do not live by here come to see the exploits of Galley it Compagnie.
They are strong, they are qualified.
They are the pride of Seven Toilets!
They is cool!
Hey, Luffy!
Let us dispatch to go itself to make the exchange.
We will be able to return later.
It is the market in the open air.
Not only it is animated, but that remains also a street.
There are malls too.
There are water and pretty streets.
Effrayannnnt!
A super beautiful woman!
In hundred years, it is the first time that I see if beautiful woman.
There are tons of Sanji.
It is what?
It is a shop of masks.
People around us carried from there.
Then they thus carried masks? I thought that they had odd heads.
In one of the cities where Umi Ressha passes, San Faldo.
They make a long dressed up carnival.
How do you know that?
Because people in the street were speaking about it.
How can you hear them?
A practice.
Since I am child, I learned has to read the expressions of people and to listen espièglement.
You are astonishing, Robin!
Doctor
There is a bookstore by here.
Really?
I can go there?!
Of course, go ahead.
Yatta!
CP9
Robin, you will join me.
Should that pass… in my human form?
My expensive, which beautiful disguise. Which kind of costume is this?
Human-reindeer.
How it is amusing!
Hein?
Robin?
Robin!
I thought that I attacked somebody of deadened…
Who do you etez, dumb?
Give me your names!