The attack of Eneru
continue with eagerness,
attacking the island of
Very whole Skypiea.
All this is only one affront!
People, trees and ground!
It is necessary that they turn over to their place!
They will become a rain which
will fall down on the Blue Sea!
Quickly!
Angel Island is on
the point to sink!
There is no shelter on this island!
During this time, Robin and Usopp
are still with the feet of Giant Jack.
It already took much altitude.
In little time, the arch
the summit of bean will have reached.
What can seek Eneru well up there?
He wants the Gold Bell hidden in top.
A bell?
This old Divine Sanctuary
is not useful to me any more with nothing.
Nor the city of Shandora in lower part!
There is from now on only one
thing which interests me in this country!
The Large Gold Belfry!
Luffy, with the continuation of Eneru,
sink towards the summit of Giant Jack.
Nami, I hope that you are well!
And I will not leave you
to take the Gold Bell, Eneru!
Destruction of Angel Island!
Terrifying descent of Raigou!!
The Gold Bell.
It is what you have just said, not?
Wiper…
Yes.
About what you do speak?
Just before it touches you with his electricity,
you spoke as if you knew what he wanted.
Isn't Eneru wants, it?
Where is it?
He, wait!
There are not time to speak about that!
You saw these flashes, not?!
If one does not draw
now, one died!
At the top of this giant bean.
How?
How do you know it?
He!
One promised in Nami to wait
its return on the boat!
It will bring back Luffy and us
to join in little time!
It rightly, Wiper.
Ruins of Shandora
are right in lower part.
This bean transpierced it
ground right in the middle of the city.
He, look at! He!
Ruins, finally I
do not know what it was,
but there remain only crumbs about it!
And it is exactly what
be likely to arrive to us!
The heart of the city…
it is there that drew up the Large one
Belfry, supporting the Gold Bell.
It was registered on a chart
that I found in the ruins.
You are unaware of me completely?
To make simple,
I believe that the force of
impact with bean…
the Bell high in the sky propelled.
It is just above us?
Song of the island!
He, Ho!
Then there is a large bell
in is the Gold City, it that?
Good, I reached it
top of Giant Jack.
Naturally, I never needed
to explore the sky above the Divine Sanctuary.
It has been there for 400 years.
Then, where is it?
The Gold Bell.
It is what this place?
Still him?
I did not expect that it there
arrive with this weight at the end of its arm.
Ah!
Te here!
Do not move!
Eneru!
Little runt.
Wiper, which do you make?
Do not say to me that you go
to climb on Giant Jack!
The guy, you move away from bean!
Something falls!
The top of bean!
That it is
passed up there?
He Ho!
I hope that Luffy and Nami
did not fall with!
Wiper!
Not! Wait!
You are too weak!
Look at yourself!
And even if you succeeded,
you could never
to reach Eneru because it flies!
It is…
It is just above us!
The Bell that the Large Warrior
Karugara wanted to sound!
Karugara?
Yes.
It is for that we are there!
Eneru…
I will not let to you take it!
Now, how you count
to go up up to now?
Puffiness!
Remainder one moment.
You will be likely to assist
with something the miraculous one.
It is what that?
Ah ouais…
I would do better
to benefit from its absence!
It is my only chance!
Gok35} driven {\ fs1 \ alpha&HFF& \ T (400,810,1, \ fs60 \ alpha&H00&) \ T (810,1310,1, \ fs60 \ alpha&H00&)} Go {\ fs1 \ alpha&HFF& \ T (610,1100,1, \ fs60 \ alpha&H00&) \ T (1100,1600,1, \ fs60 \ alpha&H00&)} driven
{\ fs1 \ alpha&HFF& \ T (900,3770,1, \ fs60 \ alpha&H00&) \ T (3770,4270,1, \ fs60 \ alpha&H00&)} No {\ fs1 \ alpha&HFF& \ T (3570,5800,1, \ fs60 \ alpha&H00&) \ T (5800,6300,1, \ fs60 \ alpha&H00&)} {\ fs1 \ alpha&HFF& \ T (5600,6620,1, \ fs60 \ alpha&H00&) \ T (6620,7120,1, \ fs60 \ alpha&H00&)} Yo {\ fs1 \ alpha&HFF& \ T (6420,8200,1, \ fs60 \ alpha&H00&) \ T (8200,8700,1, \ fs60 \ alpha&H00&)}yo
What it fout?
Brilliant, my plan went!
Now it is necessary that
I go up on this arch!
Luffy!
I finally found you!
Nami? What do you make there?
I came to seek you.
It is thanks to Sanji-kun and Usopp
that I am in life, they saved me.
It is true?
I see!
They is super!
More important…
Wait…
What is it?
The clouds of flashes change form.
Sky!
The Help!!
Oh not!
With the assistance!
Will run!
That
it passes?!
Embark!
Quickly, everyone on board!
A giant ball floats in the sky!
I have a bad presentiment.
Interior of this sphere
clouds of flashes…
is a concentrate of air
and of electricity!
It is just above Angel Island!
It gathered the clouds
flashes in a sphere.
It is a demon!
This trick is not natural!
But that…
seek it with
to make up there?
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
He, let pass to me!
Await me!
The sky belongs to me!
You for known as hold!
With my capacities and those
Maxim Arch, combined…
I have the power of a god!
It is what?
Ca will fall on Angel Island!
It is too late!
We did not succeed!
Flee!!
I am afraid!
[Note:spiritual guide of the thunder]
What? It is not true!
Did the White Berets flee?
The White Berets saved us.
Our island…
Our fatherland completely disappeared!
The island…
was disintegrated!
Which spectacular sight.
The sky should resemble that.
Was C-C' what this explosion?
And then…
continuous rain of flashes!
J I believe that one will not leave oneself there!
Angel Island…
was destroyed…
Which horror…
What a terrible cruelty, Eneru!
All trembles so violently.
I must wait.
I must help them with
to turn over on the Blue Sea.
Luffy, goes up!
We must go down again!
The others are already
turned over to the boat!
We must go there us too!
Not.
Not? What do you want to say?
What do you say?
Even if I should save you…
There remains to me a business to be regulated!
A business to be regulated? Can one know
what do you intend to make?
You do not have nevertheless the intention
to face Eneru again?
The Gold Bell is there, in the sky!
Gold? But…
our lives are more important!
Look at over there!
Even if its flashes
do not function on you,
it can nevertheless all destroy!
If it is the gold which you want, looks at!
You have some in quantity at the end of the arm!
Forget the Gold Bell!
You will die!
I will not die.
Ca is enough! Go…
You saw it you too!
About what you do speak?
The Gold City!
The Gold City exists indeed!
It was not a lie!
The ancestor of Papi
Head-of-diamond…
If it exists, it is so much better.
But if it does not exist,
it is so much better too.
My goal is not
to prove its innocence.
It is right a duel with
that which ruined my life.
… was not a liar.
Then this Papi and monkeys in
low must know the truth!
The Gold City is in the sky!
If I make sound the bell…
They will hear it.
Without that, this Papi and these guys…
will continue to explore it
ocean floor and to die about it!
Luffy…
I cannot let Eneru take it!
The sound of this enormous bell will be enough
powerful to be heard of anywhere!
It is for that I go…
to make sound the Gold Bell!
He, Ho!
Then there is a large bell
in is the Gold City, it that?
According to the newspaper of
edge of Norland, yes.
He wrote well that it existed.
What of other?
Why you requests?
I have a super idea!
What? It is what your idea?
If one makes sound this enormous bell…
Can be that Papi Head-of-Diamond
and the monkeys will hear it!
Ouais! They will hear it, not truth?
When he says that he will make
something, it does it.
You think that it goes…
Indeed he said it.
But under these conditions…
To sound.
To make sound the Bell?
Ouais.
Even if Nami tries to bring back it.
It will not follow it.
He wants the same thing as Eneru.
I have it!
Who gave you the permission
to go up on my Arch?
Eneru!
Luffy!
I said to you to drop!
This dumb!
Was this spectacular?
You saw this pathetic island
to disappear from the skies?
Gamine, if you always wish
to accompany me towards Fairy Vearth,
I would not show any leniency.
Rather to die!
When I obtain what I wish,
I would use second Raigou for
to destroy Skypiea very whole!
None among you will escape from it!
Neither you, nor those of which I
still perceive the bass voices!
Bass voices?
This country which does not have its
place here will be destroyed!
All will take again its legitimate place!
It is…
It is the mission of God! My mission!
I will leave you…
PAS FAIRE!!!
Good-bye, man-rubber!
Thus wisely death waits!
Luffy!
Nobody can stop me.
Brothel!
Listen, I promise you
to send on the celestial island!
Luffy…
I GO…
TO MAKE SOUND THIS BELL!