The world...
Yes!
Seek freedom,
And your world will stand stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides your spirits,
Conquer it!
Bear conviction behind your flag!
I began my search,With a blast of water,
Toward a boundless,everlasting world
With this overflowing passion in my chest, I'll go anywhere
Seeking the light l've never seen
When the summer-colored sun shakes the sall of my heart,
It's a sign the door to a new world has opened
Swaying between the waves, I can escape despair,
For the horize on the other side is what I aim for!
I began my search, With a blast of water,
Toward a boundless, everlasting world
With this overflowing passion in my chest, I'll go anywhere
Seeking the light I've never seen
Pirates' party
Alabasta escape strategy!
Quite a fascinating mixture you're making.
Quite original, and yet...
So superbly logical.
Wherever did you learn such exquisite medicinal skill?
Tony-kun is a doctor from Drum Island.
My word! I see!
A doctor from the Great Medical Country of Drum!
Ho-ho!
So they are still ahead of the rest of us!
I've been a doctor for 40 years now,
And I had no idea such medical techniques existed!
My, this is truly exquisite.
You're so young and I can't even help you in the slightest!
Shut up!
Quit starting at me! Moron!
Get the hell away from me, asshole!
Can I take that to mean:
"Please, have some tea and observe all you like"?
I think so!
Goodness! This is so extraordinary!
Shut up...
You are so talented!
I'm extremely impressed!
Shut up and get the hell away from me, asshole!
Oi!
There any spare timber around?
I need some too!
I've got plenty! Take it!
Ah! Thanks!
This is a strong country.
'Cause their Princess is so cute!
What does that have to do with it?
Everything!
Dammit!
Something broke through the walls between our houses!
What the HELL made these holes!?
It's like someone just kicked their way through!
There's no time to go around!
Shortcut!
Look at the damage...
Oi, Usopp! Look at that!
There's something happening over there.
Concentrate...
If I can't call forth that power at any point in time,
I will not have become stronger.
There are so many interesting books here!
Can I really have these?
Yes, of course.
I have read them all already.
Thank you!
I'll take you up on that.
Did you not hear me say that we know nothing?
Now leave!
Lying will serve no purpose to your country!
Harboring pirates is a serious crime!
Keep up the good work.
Ha, welcome back.
Given the state of the city,
We're lucky we were able to buy this much!
Yeah!
Do you have any proof that we are harboring pirates here?
Well... we...
I wonder if he's woken up yet.
If he had, we'd have heard him by now.
WHAT A GREAT NAP!
Where's Hat?
Hat! Where's my hat?
I'm hungry...
Where's breakfast? Hey, breakfast?
Hat? Breakfast? Hat?
You're noisy as hell when you wake up!
And it's not breakfast! It's already evening.
And your hat's over there.
A soldier found it in front of the Palace.
Phew, great!
I'm so glad, Luffy-san!
You've regained your strength!
Regained my strength?
But I'm always strong.
You idiot!
You were really sick with a temperature y'know!
Vivi and Chopper have been nursing you back to health this whole time!
Really?
Thanks!
Oh, Luffy, you're awake.
Oh, Zoro! Long time no see!
Long time no see?
Ah, HEY!
You better not have been out training again!
What? I can do what I want.
No means no!
I'm the ship's doctor! Don't take your bandages off!
They make it hard to move.
Then don't move!
Long time no see?
Well, it's no wonder you feel that way.
You've been sleeping for three days straight.
Three days!?
I was asleep for three days!?
Yeah.
I've missed 15 meals.
Why are you so fast at calculating that!?
And you counted five meals a day!
So the Captain is awake?
Dinner's in 30 minutes. Does he mind waiting?
WHA-!?
Oooh! The Chikuwa Ossan! You're alive!
I-I knew you were really into that kinda shit!
No, everyone!
This is Terracotta-san.
She's Igaram's wife and the Palace's top chef!
You all took care of Vivi-sama and my husband!
You're kidding me...
A couple can only be so much alike...
I've heard you eat a lot.
Do you think you could snack on this fruit until dinnertime?
Okay.
WAS THAT SOME TRICK!?
Obachan, I'm gonna eat three days worth of food!
I was hoping you'd say that!
I've been a chef for 30 years!
I won't lose to some youngster's stomach, so eat all you can!
Absolutely no manners...
The Grand Dinning Hall should be quieter than this!
He meant what he said, but I'm not done yet!
Eat fast or he'll-
Dammit Luffy! You just took that off my plate!
Don't stretch!
Oi, oi, you shouldn't eat that fast!
There's plenty more!
Take this, Luffy. My Super Tabasco Boshi!
Where did you come from!?
What do you call this dish?
This is Kenafa. You put the noodles in the oven and...
Kenafa - unsalted, soft cheese which melts easily
Yummy!
Here's the next course!
Osshan, youb da Kigh?
(Ossan, you're the King?)
Ho, yo mas he Bibiz fad.
(So, you must be Vivi's dad.)
Wight?
(Right?)
Well, we can just talk after dinner...
Ogei, sor.
(Okay, sure.)
Can I get some more beer here!?
We need some water over here!
What a boisterous meal...
I can't stand to watch. It's too disgusting!
I'm amazed Vivi-sama is able to laugh at all this...
This is the Palace's esteemed bathhouse.
We're only really able to use it when it rains.
Amazing! Gorgeous, gorgeous!
I'M GONNA BE FIRST!
NO, ME!
You guys having fun?
Well, that meal was certainly enjoyable.
I usually dine in a neat and tidy manner...
But it seems everything around you turns into a party.
Oi, Zoro, look at us!
We're training!
Training, training!
That's training!?
So? Where's the women's bath?
You ignoramus!
I would not tell someone like YOU!
Vivi-sama is in there!
Don't be so stingy!
It's right over that wall!
YOUR MAJESTY, YOU BASTARD!!
Ooh! I like your style!
This feels so good!
I wonder if any ships out there have baths this big on them!
I'm sure there are!
The sea is so vast!
We're seen Giants, Dinosaurs...
Sakura bloom in a land of snow...
The sea must contain so many more unimaginable things!
Um, that...
Switch.
Thank you.
Wait a minute, what are you all doing up there!?
Those guys...
Alright, it'll be 100,000 beri each.
「HAPPINESS PUNCH!」
NAMI-SAN!
Mellorine~!
I suppose you're wondering.
We're thinking of leaving tonight.
Really!?
There's no reason for us to be here anymore, is there? Our Captain is awake.
And the Marines are probably in the harbor.
Our ship's gonna be in danger.
Thank you.
Dirty old man.
Not for that!
For this country.
Oi, oi. You sure you should be doing that? A king doing that...
This is no small matter, Cobra-sama!
A king should not lower his head to others!
Igaram.
Power is something worn over clothing.
But... this is a bath.
There is no such thing as a naked king.
As a father, and as a man who lives on this land,
I wish to express my heartfelt gratitude.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Tonight?
Yep.
So we're leaving?
Well, I think we should too.
No reason to stick around here any longer.
Yeah, the Marines are starting to get bolder with their approaches.
Yosh! Luffy, you decide.
Yosh! We're leaving after one more Arabasta banquet!
We're leaving NOW, numbskull!
Bake! Ba-! Ba-!
What should we do, Igaram-san?
We must tell them immediately!
Yes, of course...
But... this is such a disastrous event...
I only hope they are able to leave the island safely.
This has happened all too fast!
Roronoa Zoro, Bounty: 60,000,000 beri
Monkey D. Luffy, Bounty: 100,000,000 beri
Igaram-san...
With this much on their heads,
Even the Marine Headquarters Admirals will move against them.
There's no turning back now, Luffy-kun...
You and your crew have taken down one of the Shichibukai!
TERRIBLE NEWS!
Vivi-sama!
Where are they?
What's wrong, Igaram?
You seem upset.
Where have Luffy-kun and the others gone?
To the sea.
They're pirates.
But...
Listen up you guys. Pirates really suck.
Marine Headquarters Private Recruit
Oi, oi, what're you saying?
Did you forget or something? You used to be... a pirate!
Crap!
Yeah, you're right!
Shall we dance, Baby!?
LET'S DANCE!
It seems the two of them have returned with a captured enemy ship.
Took them long enough.
What have they been doing?
I left them in charge of the ship in mid-attack, and this is how they repay me.
I'm unhappy. Hina unhappy.
Have all ships been deployed?
Yes, Ma'am! All of them!
All the docks in Arabasta have been blockaded by our 30-ship fleet with reinforcements!
But...
There is one thing that worries me.
What?
The vessel belonging to the Straw Hat Pirates that was sighted at Erumalu is gone.
You're telling me they've already fled the country?
No, that couldn't have happened, but-
Then find it!
Search coast to coast!
Yes Ma'am! At once!
Honestly...
Hina-jou!
We are late!
Please ask us why we are late.
Why are you late?
We picked flowers, just for you~!
I don't want them.
Return to your positions!
We're going after the Straw Hat Pirates!
S-STRAW HAT!?
I like this!
Farewell, oh country of sand!
Oi, Luffy, you still eating?
Arabasta food is the best!
Sanji, make some of this tomorrow!
Sure, I was interested in it too.
I got some recipes off Terracotta-san.
And I picked up some spices too.
Nami, are you feeling sick?
Nami, want a piece of meat?
But only one.
Nami-san, it's about Vivi-chan, isn't it?
I understand how you feel...
But if you keep thinking so much, you'll never get over it.
You two were good friends for so long...
But c'mon, look up.
I'm...
...giving it up.
For Vivi.
My 1,000,000,000 beri
OF COURSE YOU ARE!!
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT MONEY!!?
USOPP FELL OFF!
NAMI! Quit being so damn misleading!
Huh? What's your problem?
There's no point worrying about Vivi!
Oi! Usopp has FALLEN OFF!
That's his problem!
IT'S YOUR FAULT!
Carue!
Is Carue here!?
It won't work, Igaram.
Why?
They should at least know where they now stand in society!
I sent them on the Super Spot-billed Duck Squad.
Even Carue wouldn't be able to catch up now.
And it would only be the same.
What would?
Knowing that would just make them happier.
Nothing would change.
But-
You don't have to worry about them!
Now get out!
I'm going to sleep.
Early start tomorrow, right?
Oh yes, indeed!
Tomorrow you must deliver a speech to the country.
I know.
Come on, Carue. Let's sleep together.
Igaram-san...
Something is not right...
What do you mean?
She was too blithe about it...
Something is wrong...
Something is very wrong...
It's so quiet... Carue.
It's been so long since we've had a night this quiet.
No more refrigerator burglar and the fighting cook...
Or the swordsman doing his night training...
Or the half-awake, pillow-throwing navigator...
They're all gone.
A Den Den Mushi? From who?
From someone named "Bon-chan".
Bon-chan? Who's that?
We don't know him.
But he claims to be your friend, so...
Friend?
Hello, hello?
Hel-lo~!?
It's ME!
It. Is. ME!
WHAT IS IT!?
Oh, it's you.
What do you want with us?
Oh!?
Isn't that the voice of Straw-chan!?
You're so strooong~! I was so surprised~!
Oh, yes, yes! Don't go calling me Mr. 2!
If the Marines get wind of this conversation, I'll be in super big trouble!
He just said it himself!
Just spit it out.
Ah, right, right, right.
I took your little ship!
WHAT THE HELL!?
Asshole! That ain't funny! Where are you now!?
I'm on your boooaaat~!
Of all the annoying bastards in the world...
You've got it wrooong, all wrooong~!
Aren't you and I friends~?
He's upstream on the Sandora River.
Can we trust him?
We were friends with him before...
The idea of you becoming friends again scares me.
But... we don't really have a choice.
That's right. He's got our ship.
If he's trying anything funny, we'll just kick his ass.
Then let's get moving already.
Yosh, let's get going.
If the ship is taken, we gotta...
Hey, everyone...
Hey... everyone...
What should I do?
Listen carefully, Vivi.
We'll give you twelve hours to think.
Sandora River
Nanohana
Current Location
Eastern Harbor
After we take back our ship on the Sandora River,
Then exactly at noon tomorrow,
We'll swing the ship past the eastern harbor once.
I doubt we'll be able to drop anchor,
So if you want to keep adventuring with us,
That will be the last chance you'll have to jump on board.
If so, we'll celebrate! As pirates!
You're the Princess of the Kingdom, so this is the best invitation we can give you.
Come, Vivi!
You have to come! Come right now!
Stop it, Luffy!
Let's go!
What?
Don't you guys want her to come!?
It's not that!
Vivi has to decide this on her own!
Tomorrow at 12 noon...
The eastern harbor...
Carue can make it in four hours,
So I'll have to leave here at 8 o'clock to make it in time.
I've never considered becoming a pirate myself...
The chance to choose between two different lives...
...is something that will never be offered to me again.
I've never thought being a princess was boring.
And even with the rebellion over...
...the country is still in a terrible state.
If I went...
You'd come too, right?
Right, Carue?
What do... you want to do?
I WAS WAAAITING FOR YOU GUYS~!
HOW LOVELY TO SEE YOU AGAIN~!
Alright, we made it.
Unload our stuff!
Thanks a lot, guys.
This is farewell to you all as well!
Take care going home!
Send our regards to the King and the Chikuwa Ossan!
Stay well!
Some day...
Some day, let us meet again!
WHAT A BIG MINUTE!
What is it now?
What do you mean, "What is it now"!?
What kind of attitude is that towards your friend!?
What do you mean "friend"?
You're our enemy!
You tricked us.
I did NOT trick you!
I didn't know either!
But, really... That's all in the past now...
Baroque Works has crumbled.
We're not enemies anymore.
Shift over.
Oh, sorry.
If you're not our enemy, why the hell are you on our ship!?
You silly, silly man!
WHAT WAS THAT!?
Look!
If I wasn't on this ship right now,
What do you think would have happened to it!?
The Marine might have taken it.
Not "MIGHT" have!
It would have definitely been taken!
Do you knooow what's happening to this island right now!?
It's entirely blockaded by Marine ships!
Blockaded!
So then...
You protected the Going Merry from the Marines!?
Why!?
What for!?
Because we're friends!
Is there any more to bring on?
Nope! This is the last of it.
So then, Mr. 2...
With the Marine blockading the entire island, that would mean you couldn't escape either.
And so you're using us to escape safely?
BON-CHAN!
Yes!
Because we need each other!
IN THE NAME OF SACRED FRIENDSHIP,
LET US COMBINE OUR FORCES AND FIGHT TOGRTHER AS ONE!
Thanks for helping us out!
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN THERE!?
Hina-jou!
We've sighted them! It's the Straw Hat Pirates' vessel!
They are upstream on the Sandora River!
Prepare for battle.