The Utopia operation starts!
The Rebellion is moving
With the kingdom of the Oases.
Three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
Crocodile encourages with a civil war.
To stop this conspiracy,
Luffy and its crew entered the den of the enemy in Rainbase.
But they were made capture.
Crocodile revealed its final project.
Are the hopes of Vivi condemned to be buried by hot sands?
It is last midday.
The plan started.
Do not doubt him, Kohza.
You know the King me as well as.
Only the old men as continue to you to say that…
I did not come with you in Yuba by regard to the King.
They say that the rebellious army counts more than 100.000 men.
Ouais, I intended some to speak…
And there were deaths…
What?
When the rain falls, all these dreadful doubts will be unobtrusive.
It is true.
How this is possible?!
The channel of the village is dry!
Who could do that…?
We will not have any more water for the village!
It did not rain since more than one year…
Ca will be the end of Erumalu…
Do not doubt him, Kohza.
I do not want to doubt you but people die of hunger!
Even if you do not use it…
You must have some!
Not.
It is necessary to wait fallen from the true rain.
“Dance Powder” is a powder which brings misfortune.
Even more the minor amount will help!
So only it rained, the rebellion would cease!
That will give rise to only several disasters.
That cannot be repaired as easily as you believe it, Kohza.
I cannot any more…
TO SEE OTHER VILLAGES BEING DRAINED!!
You really did not change.
I changed.
I can fight.
I will return…
AND I WILL TAKE MT RAIN TO YOU.
Where does this country go?
Where we go?
Where is the answer?
Something of terrible has just arrived, Kohza.
It did without something terrible, Chaka-Sama!
The King has…!
What!?
About what do speak you!?
He disappeared.
It is absurd.
Did you seek it!?
Yes.
Everywhere since the palate to the gardens and with the warehouses.
During the night is party?
It is not possible.
The guards supervised the room of the King.
He did not can pass without it being seen.
If it is thus…
If it is thus, then why the King hide does the morning of the departure of the battle!?
Find it!
Seek in all the city and beyond!
Yes.
To find somebody is the strong point of Pell.
But for the moment, it is in location with Rainbase.
If something were to arrive…
But I cannot act of my own boss…
Shit…!
That…
...com ptes you to make with Arabasta?
Should I tell you the type of anybody whom I mistake more?
It is those which risk their life for the happiness of the others.
Hypocrites.
You intend to kill my father?
You will never arrive there!
Do not look at me thus.
I do not have the intention of it.
Of his death, I would not gain anything.
Cobra will know a humiliation much crueler than death.
Crueler than death?
A princess should not have the air if scorning.
I ask it once again to you.
What the “Utopia Operation”?
Explain me!
He He. Summers you sure to seize your situation well?
Answer my question!
Which courageous Princess…
Well, the plan being already started…
I think that I can speak to you about it.
The plan which will put an end to the existence of this poor wretch country…
… the Utopia Operation.
I have bad news, Chaka-Sama!
The King has…!
What is there?
You found it.
Yes. It is in Nanohana.
Ca was confirmed.
I see. Thank you my God.
But…
I am about to say something of incredible…
What you say?!
Kohza!
Kohza-San!
Wait!
We leave with you!
Why so suddenly?
You fell so low that!?
Do not doubt him, Kohza.
What is this they are, all these conneries!?
V-your Majesty…
What… do you have says…?
You have of course.
I must sincerely excuse myself.
I am that which stole the rain of this country.
King d' Arabasta, Cobra!
Cobra-Sama,
You joke?
In fact…
It is not a joke.
I used “Dance Powder” so that the rain falls exclusively on the town of Alubarna.
Me, the beloved King!
I want to say, a King such as me should not miss anything.
C this is not possible…
But because of that, much of people died for lack of water and food.
Your Majesty, you knew…
Of course that I knew.
I also know that many oases were drained because of that.
But some sacrifices are necessary to protect the kingdom.
It is not possible…
You were with the current of this terrible situation and you do not have…
It is too egoistic! Your Majesty!
Will you give an opinion of me, the King?
Therefore I am here to excuse me.
I came until Nanohana.
What would you wish moreover?
My little brother died in Yuba…!
There is another reason with my arrival in this city.
As you know it, “Dance Powder” is prohibited by the world government.
If somebody warned himself to speak about it,
the general headquarter of the Navy would send its troops and would try to reverse the kingdom.
We must prevent that.
But you remember that two years ago,
great quantities of “Dance Powder” were the subject of smuggling in the country.
This incident must be forgotten at any price.
It is included/understood?
What wants to say…
Completely.
To erase forever any trace of this incident…
I must destroy this city like his inhabitants!
What!?
Ca goes too far!
Because of the orders of the King, we go…!!
He, Majesty!
Thus it was really of your fault!
Because of you…
Because you stole the rain, all the villages are dry, cursed would be you!
I will avenge my friends…!
Ca is enough! Stop that!
Majesty…!
My soldiers!
Reduce this city rotted in dust!
Kohza!
Kohza-San!
Kohza.
I missed you.
What are you in the train of foutre?
Dumb…
Majesty…!
Not!
Isn't that seen?
I came to excuse me.
Stop your conneries!
Close it!
Do you know what you are saying!?
What a audacity!
That which used “Dance Powder” involving the dryness in this country…
I said to you to close it!
Why do you speak to me thus?
Kohza…
Remember that I am the King.
Majesty…
Close it! Close it! Close it!
It was nobody the other one than me…
Species of dumb!!!
People who died when the villages were dry…
Do you think of how they felt with their death!?
They were not hated or did not scorn themselves!
“It is not the fault of the King.”
“It is a marvellous person!”
Everyone believed in you until their death!
If you had not lied and had not said that you were innocent,
what would have become their feelings!?
Co… will bra…
Kohza-San!
Chief!
Kohza!
Well, we do not have any more time!
This country…
They all wanted to hear this answer…
This is why we fight.
At least…
… I made…
… what I could…
… to save it.
It is not possible…
They arrive.
A giant ship flies by here!!
Flee!
From where it leaves, this ship?!
Help me!!
Ca…
Ca cannot arrive!
All that for the final operation.
This mission is too easy.
Were there already difficult missions?
One succeeded!
Now, put fire and one draws from here!
Yes.
I do not feel at ease without this trick on my head!
Kohza!
Hold good, Kohza!
He!
The royal army left!
What?
How I was?
Was I quite royal!?
You were spectacular, Mr. 2, Bon Clay-Sama!
The fire should be extinguished!
The royal army put fire and east flees!
Quickly!
Extinguish this fire!
We must find Mr. 2 apart from the village.
We will finish in Alubarna.
Finally something of interesting.
Ambiguous!
It is the word which I prefer! Ambiguous!
Then, is the King of this country still King or not!?
Now, it is ambiguous!
The plan is a total success!
Where is Banchi!?
In the west of the city, Mr. 2, Good Clay-Sama!
What…
The King became a strange ballerina…
They is not good!
Ca does not die out!
Shit! Cursed either the King!
It was an impostor!
He misled us!
I must prevent everyone!
Which unpleasant boy.
Would you have seen something that you would not have had?
This moron showed himself.
Who are you?
To say to you to keep silent itself will probably not be used for large thing.
Water!
There is not enough water!
Wait, this water comes from my store!
You will have to pay!
Moron, at one similar moment!?
The city is in flames!
Extinguish fire!
Water!
Ca is not used for nothing.
We cannot contain fire.
We must flee.
Hold good, Kohza.
You are not those which die like that!
He!
Take Kohza!
Small, hold good.
They is dreadful…
To do that with a child…
My… My…
Your wounds?
We will look after them.
Do not speak any more.
But you are mistaken!
Everyone was made berner!
Hold good, small!
Kohza?
This country…
We will put an end to it.
Contact our other forces.
It is…
… the final fight.
It is well, but we do not have enough weapons!
Not, we have arm.
The ship which was crushed in the port…
It was a combat ship.
Really?
Yes, and it of it is full.
It is like a sign of the destiny…
Is this true?
Did a kid see me?
How it is damage!
Swan, Swan.
Frankly.
Now, it does not remain any more but with the pair of Mr. 4 to finish work…
The large one and the old hag can do it!
To kidnap the king was really not wizard!
Listen to, armed me rebel!
Arabasta that you know died!
It is our last battle!
We will crush Alubarna!
We all will put in this common attack!
No pity for the tyrant!
We will build a new kingdom!
Do not be ridiculous!
Cobra-Sama would never make a similar thing!
There must be an error!
But, Sir…
From the moment when the King disappeared and time to make the way, all coincides!
There cannot be of another explanation!
The news from what occurred to Nanohana is spread in any Arabasta!
And the rebellious armies of the other cities will be combined!
Moreover, people who still believed the king until now…
… came from there to hate it and take the weapons!
Their full number is unknown!
All the kingdom took the weapons and they will come here, in Alubarna!
They…
. .ne will not stop!
Which are your orders?
We will follow you.
How that could arrive…
Even the words of the King of yesterday become obscure…
What do I have to believe?
We will make our duty.
We are the royal guard of Arabasta!
We will not drop this country during the absence from the King!
Let us protect it in what we believe!
Let us protect this country!
We will fight against rebel!
Which démoniaque plan…
What do you think about it? You like my plan?
The plan to which you contributed is now moving.
If one listens attentively, I bet that one can hear the cries coming from Arabasta.
And only one thought:
“We will protect Arabasta…”
DECREE!
How can you be so inhuman!?
Doesn't that make you cry?
Love of the country…
… is what will destroy it.
This guy is an idiot.
Didn't he listen to what I said?
Of course, it is an idiot.
But…
This is why he is our Captain.
Crocodile…!
I will explode you the gueu…
I still remember all troubles that I had before arriving from there there.
My operations to incite the inhabitants to destroy their own villages…
To learn with my men how to make abuses all while being made pass for the royal army…
And do you know why I want of your kingdom very?
How could I include/understand what there is in your degenerated head!?
You are not really afraid of the words, Princesse.
Vivi!
He, He.
What do you make, Miss Wednesday?
I will stop them…
I will stop them…!
I can arrive still there in time!
Alubarna is in the East from here!
If I can go in Alubarna before the army rebels arrives there…
… then I will be able to stop them!
No matter what it costs some, I will make very to prevent your plan from succeeding!
Vivi.