Cherry trees of Hiluluk
The Heritage of its Will!
He! It is what your problem?!
What you can be dogged!
I want you in my crew!
You see, you still insist!
They is super to be a pirate!
Ca is enough!
Profit to be locked up here to put back you!
The wounds which you ace…
There is not what to joke, you know!
PF, what a cretin!
Eh?
How?!
Wait!
It is which this type?
How did it catch the keys?
Attends Attends Wait Wait Wait!
Wait!
This odor…
Wapol!
When he heard that Hiluluk had nothing any more but ten days to live…
… Chopper was very cut down.
It is normal after all.
But it had in heart to do everything to save it and it thus took the things in hands.
I am… dying?!
I will make flower of the cherry trees on this island.
You see, it is the symbol of my will…
… which defies the impossible one!
What does it occur?
Today, the frequency of the turns of round curiously decreased.
In fact, at the request of Isshi-20, the troops left to gather mushrooms.
Mushrooms?
They had the role of finding mushrooms likely to treat all kinds of diseases.
Imbecile, they could locate us!
Did doctor, about what speak?
I DO NOT WANT TO MAKE YOU OF EVIL!
Give the feet never again here!
What I have fact is wretched…
But at least, you will be the witness of my work.
My ultimate invention.
What?! Still missed!
Shit!
I do not have any more time.
For a man who raises the banner to tête de mort, nothing is impossible!
It is what I taught you!
I will fight!
How a pirate!
Over there!
Amiudake.
I found one of them.
But…
How I will cross?
Shit!
So close to the goal!
I am so close to the goal!
Doctor…
I am sorry…
Your preferred book…
I lost it.
What did it arrive to you?
This mushroom…
It is a drug.
It is Amiudake!
You… went to seek it for me?
It is necessary to live.
It is necessary to live, Doctor.
I want to become a doctor.
Teach me because I want to be a doctor like you.
I can also fight!
Like a pirate.
I do not know if a reindeer can arrive there.
Of course that if, you can!
You can!
You will be an eminent doctor!
Doctor, that hurt…
You have good heart so much!
Idiot…
Chess! Kuromarimo!
Does hunting for the doctors advance well?
We already exiled almost all the doctors.
Almost?!
There remain still two doctors to be captured.
Doctor Kureha and…
… this charlatan of Doctor Hiluluk.
What you say?!
Oh. I have just had an excellent idea.
Inform the people that Isshi-20…
… are in the incapacity to look after people.
The soup of Amiudake…
They is good?
Hurk! It is wretched!
Nobody can swallow that!
I see…
Do not make this head.
The best drugs always have a bad taste.
That proves that it is effective.
I thank you, Chopper.
What is it?
I succeeded!
I finally succeeded!
Ca is there.
Ca makes thirty years that I await this reaction.
I succeeded, Chopper!!
My research succeeded!
I knew that it would go!
I knew it! I knew it!
THE CHERRY TREES WILL BE ABLE TO FLOWER ON THIS SNOW-COVERED ISLAND!
Do not forget, during my absence, does not move and rests.
Included/understood.
I return quickly.
The Doctor was so content.
I… managed to cure somebody of patient.
You will be an eminent doctor.
I am sure.
You saw, all the country is invaded by panic.
I noticed.
They say that Isshi-20 are sick.
Imbeciles.
And by the way? What brings you here?
I wanted to ask you…
Not, it is out of the question.
But I still anything asked you!
It is what this dirtiness?
You see there, the thirty long year old fruit of research.
My panacea can cure the torn heart of a country!
Ca wants to say that you ace wasted thirty years of your life. I hope at least that you had fun?!
But then? Why do you give me that?
There is not enough of it. And I am with court of time.
I want that you make flower the cherry trees in my place.
Imbecile, why should I do that?
And still a thing.
Teach medicine with Chopper.
He wants to become doctor.
I heard some enough!
It is a reindeer!
Do not insist!
A monster would be said!
But it can become an eminent doctor!
It has good heart.
It risked its life to bring a drug to me!
I beseech you with knees! Make of him a doctor!
There are limits not to exceed!
You want that I deal with your absurd research as well as tone monster of company!
Even if you are dying, does not count on my compassion!
Maintaining outside!
Yes, I included/understood.
Ca makes a long time that I know you.
You will deal with all.
Ca does not resemble itself, Hiluluk.
To lower the arms like that.
I am with court of time.
The idiot does not go…!
What you known as?!
Isshi-20 are sick?!
But which will deal with the patients?
Please! Give us at least drugs!
One can nothing make for you!
Even the doctors can fall sick!
Release!
Hiluluk!
Release! Release! Release! Release!
The dumb!
Mets goes the TV-cable from there!
Lead me to the castle!
Where is Hiluluk?
You do not need to flee!
I know already who you are!
But where is this idiot of charlatan?!
The doctor was better and it went to the village.
“It was better”?
It could not better be.
There is currently no remedy which can cure it.
It is not true!
Look at that!
He ate some, it is for that he goes better now!
It is Amiudake!
It is a drug miracle!
Thus all is well!
The Doctor even said that it had found all his forces!
The Doctor said that I could become doctor!
What takes to you?!
Stupid reindeer!
This mushroom!
This mushroom…
is a mortal poison.
Once introduced, the victim has nothing any more but twelve hours to live.
It is thus that which he wanted to say, the imbecile.
It is impossible.
I looked in the book.
I lost the book…
But this mushroom can cure any disease!
This flag with the tête de mort enabled me to face all the diseases!
It is true!
On the photograph of Amiudake, there was a tête de mort!
The Doctor said that it was better!
He will not die!
YOU SUMMERS A LIAR!
Crush more quickly! Grouille!
I do not have a second to lose!
It was touched by your attention…
The sign of the tête de mort on the photograph wants to say that it is a poison.
It is a lie!
It is not a lie.
Now I listens!
There does not exist any drug in this world which can cure all the diseases!
Therefore there are doctors.
You lie…
Listen to me.
You cannot save the life of somebody, only with good will.
If you want to save a life, it is necessary you to have years of knowledge and practice.
You will never cure anybody in this way!
Poor imbecile…
Wapol-Sama.
Hiluluk moves towards the castle.
Perfect!
What a idiotic!
Did it lose the spirit?
Why does it come here?
It will not return in this house.
It decided that the castle would be its tomb.
Lead me near the patients!
I came to look after Isshi-20!
What?
Large cretin!
You still do not include/understand?
It is a trap!
Isshi-20 go very well, as you can note it!
You came here to die, Dr. Hiluluk.
Why did you come?
Guards, out of cheek!
What?
I am relieved.
Nobody is sick here.
I really thought that the country was in danger.
That to say if it is only…
I fell into the panel.
The best service than you can return to this country, it is to die!
Cut down it!
Ca is not used for nothing.
You cannot kill me.
Eh yes.
When do you believe that people die?
When a ball in full heart is drawn to them?
Not.
When they are reached of a terminal illness?
When they take a soup of champignons vénéneux?
Not!
They die when they… fall into the lapse of memory.
Even after my death, my dream will be carried out.
The ravaged heart of the people will be cured.
Why do you cry, Dalton?
You think… that it is the same thing for this country?
Will is needed.
Eh, eh, Dalton!
But good blood, why do you cry?
A monster soon will come here.
It is my son.
Made him not evil.
Do not worry you, Chopper.
Ca is not your mushroom which will be right of me…
It was really a formidable life!
So long, charlatan.
Thank you in you, Chopper!
He was made jump all alone!
What a cretin!
Good blood, what it is?!
A monster!
Cut down it!
DECREE!
Leave!
Leave from here immediately!
You cannot even beat me,
you do not have any chance against them!
If it is because he made fun of died of Hiluluk, I excuse myself some!
Your force will not be of any utility if you burst like a dog!
Would not be a sacrifice moreover for this country!
Please!
You it leashes to escape.
Silence!
You thus do not include/understand?!
The only man who tried to cure the evil which corroded this country has just died.
This doctor in the large heart which tried to save this country…
… whereas everyone had lowered the arms, died!
And which difference that can make that he died?
I saw the future of this country.
And it is chaos.
As long as we will remain here, the country will never be cured.
It does not matter where is the advance of our medical techniques!
It does not matter where are our research and our practice of medicine!
BECAUSE IT THERE NO REMEDY AGAINST STUPIDITY!
They is good, you finished?!
You really put to me in anger!
A doctor!
Teach to me medicine!
Please!
Made ego a doctor!
I want to cure people!
A doctor who can all cure!
A doctor who can even cure a country!
Because…
Because…!
There does not exist any disease in this world which doesnot can be cured!
Doctorine.
Call me like that.
I… will not die!
I must perpetuate his will!
And thus for six years, Tony-Kun has been at your sides.
Yes.
I taught him all that I knew.
Doctorine! Doctorine!
It is him!
I finally returned to the house!
Jamagushi = Large Ball
This dumb of Jamagushi!
And now, I will re-establish the kingdom of Drum!
Doctorine! Come quickly!
Wapol is of return!
I see.