OLD ICE
You made certainly well comprise you a such child.
You betrayed your partners and be been useful to you of them like toys.
To survive in a medium of shadies…
Was single only to serve your own interests.
Which blow schemes you in this new team?
All the organizations that Nico Robin could infiltrate all were destroyed…
Excluded it.
Your companions are very courageous…
But you remained the same one, Nico Robin!
You are mistaken! I am not any more…
Robin!
I am…
Robin-chan!
Rubber and of ice fights!
Luffy VS Ao Kiji
HE YOU!
Do not howl.
She will survive if you thaw out it delicately.
But its body is fragile, then would be careful.
She will die if she breaks.
For example…
What?!
If you break it like that!
Robin!
DECREE!
It was less one.
Yatta!
You are brilliant, Ussop!
It is what this brothel? He!
Ussop! Chopper!
Run to the boat!
You of it occupy and save it!
Included/understood!
Quickly! But prudently…
- It is cold!
- Baka! It is Robin who is cold!
Stop.
I advise you not to save this woman.
They is false.
Pirates need such a woman.
You seem to have very included/understood, Miss.
Could you shift?
Nami-san!
I will not allow myself…
To make as good seems you!
Wait, the guys!
You do not occupy of that.
I will undertake some all alone.
Let us stop…
You and me! With against one!
Ca is equal for me, but…
I gain nothing there to capture you…
I thus will kill you.
Does it breathe… Not it cannot…
It is probably choking itself.
Then it will die if one does not hurry?
But it will break if we heat it too quickly.
We must restore the internal temperature of the body.
Will it be left there while making like that?
I do not see other solutions.
How can you not be sure?!
The life of Robin is in danger!
But I was never confronted with human frozen before!
Ao Kiji said that it was still alive…
- But I have evil to believe in it!
- Does not despair!
If you can nothing make, nobody other can it!
You are the doctor of this ship!
I KNOW IT! A LITTLE SILENCE PLEASE!
Chopper!
What? You are only three?!
I will tell you later!
We will go back there!
But initially, do something for our arms and our legs cold!
Aah, of agreement.
Hum…
You must immediately dissolve the hardened zones!
But the shower is occupied by Robin.
Is Robin well?
I have doubts…
What?
Is they good like that?
Once all melted at low temperature, go up on the boat to mass you the members!
Nami, helps me for Robin!
What do you make there? Where are Luffy and Ao Kiji?!
They fight with against one.
Against one?! You left it all alone?!
It is an order of the captain.
You cannot do that, even if it is an order of the captain!
How can you be also cruel?! Luffy is…
Keep silent yourself!
It is a combat with against one! You do not include/understand?!
STOP NOW!
The moment is critical for us all.
If it is still one of its whims…
We must expect worst!
As I suspected it, you are not like the others.
GOMU GOMU NO…
STORM
ICE TIME!
Let us stop you and me, against one!
Good blood, I was made berner.
By accepting this combat with against one…
Only one gains, and it, isn't is finished?
If I put the hand on the others…
It would be dishonest person of my share. Isn't this Captain?
Or…
Did you really think of being able to beat me?
Let to me say a thing
In a near future…
This woman will become unverifiable.
You will be overpowered by the curse…
That Nico Robin carries since his birth.
Here what arrives when a woman such as it…
Go up on board a ship…
Monkey D. Luffy!
Ca does not pose any problem for me to explode to you now…
I have a debt towards you however.
From share your victory over Crocodile, I pass sponge.
And…
Heu. Forget that…
Still a connery of Smoker.
With more.
Here it is!
Luffy!
It is still whole!
It is a good thing.
Let us bring back it…
Quickly with the boat!
Stop repeating what I say!
According to this log book…
Their next destination will be…
Seven toilets…
The city of water.
Alalala!
They approach the general headquarter more and more.
Ooops, sorry!
Their heart…
Are…
Given to beat!
Yatta!
- Luffy!
- Robin-chan!
Not, not yet! If you return, you will make noise too much!
Ok, Dr. Chopper.
I can be useful to you?
But… you know… To call me Doctor does not return to me especially content!
Ah! When they awake, an hot drink would be ideal.
I will then install them in the room of rest.
Yes yes, Sir!
Nami, does one have to hoist the veils?
We will not leave with a captain in such a state.
The route is ready, but remain here for the night.
What is there, Ussop?
You are burst?
Of other guys as powerful as him…
Now will leave to our research?
All of which I was able was to run while shouting.
Lie down, baka.
You are just tired.
In order to grant a little respite to Luffy and Robin…
The Merry Vogue dropped anchor during four days.
A little later we hoisted the veils…
And we have sailed thus for three days.
The sky is blue, and one would believe oneself in spring.
And sometimes even in summer.
What a splendid weather!
Nami-swaaan!
I prepared you some potatoes in straw, Miss.
If you want it well.
Delicious!
I am happy!
Make less noise, I do not manage to sleep.
Yeah, yeah, afflicted, Mr. Cactus.
What you said ace, poor eyebrows!
How you called me?!
Poor eyebrows.
Lu-ffy there! Lu-ffy there! Lu-ffy there!
awaited we so much!
- Luffy!
Me, in intimidation….
Me, but frozen.
How can it still do that after having failed to die frozen?
- How was it?
- It was exactly like that, Luffy!
Clean to me all that, Luffy!
Hein? Do Nami, what you eat?
Straw. They are potatoes.
Potatos?
I am hungry, me too! He, Sanji!
How long do you have to sleep to be able to be satisfied?
Deal with your business! You want to fight?
Ok ok, that is enough!
Sanji-kun, the captain wants a little straw.
Ouuiiii, Nami-swaan!
Sanji, of potatos, potatos!
Even in convalescence, you remainders always the same one.
Ca is called “straw”, delicious.
Why “straw”?
(Actually, Paille refers to the straw hat. Potatoes in straw = fried)
I killed it. It made at least 100 meters length.
Hundred meters?!
It is giant, Ussop!
(Japanese Way to say “it was cake”)
Did you rise early to kill it?
Am Chopper, how I called?
- Ah yes, it is… Ca-captain…
- But of course! My name is Captain… Usso…
Robin.
Robin-chwan!
Robin!
How do you feel you? Do you have shivers?
I am well, thanks to you.
Thank you, Doctor.
You know… Even if you call me Doctor, that does not return to me more content!
It with the content air.
Yes.
Do not exhaust you, Robin.
Direction not guilty not to be itself as energetic as Luffy.
You can still rest.
Do not take that like a compliment!
Robin-chan.
Do I have to prepare you something of heat?
Did you find the appetite?
Then…
Do I can have a little coffee?
Ouuiii! With pleasure!
It is what that?
I cannot prevent myself from eating the straw of Sanji-kun.
Delicious!
With which temperature is cooking?
He, Luffy!
A frog which swims the crawl!
What?
Make the turn and come to see!
Really?
A frog? You want to say “this” frog?
He Luffy. Do you still believe what this stupid admiral says?
It is impossible that a frog which swims the crawl…
Can EXIST!
This frog swims the crawl!
Let us follow it!
Yes!
Tighten the veils! Leave the oars! Follow this small beast!
More quickly!
I do not know what it is, but I want to know!
Afflicted to have made you wait, Misses.
What was it?
What does it occur?
It would seem that the boat changes direction.
He, you!
Why we change direction?!
One located a large covered frog of scars!
What do you want to say?
One will make a barbecue of it!
You want to eat that?!
It is true…
Would this be a headlight?
Why this headlight over there?
Does Y' have somebody over there?
It is what, an island?
It is a headlight. This place was not envisaged on the Log Poses.
And the frog?! In which direction does go it?
Not question!
The frog moves towards the headlight.
Initially, to pass frog to the miller with white wine…
Then to coat it with flour and to fry it.
He, Sanji-kun!
If the captain said it, we, isn't this must go there?
Robin.
Yosha!
Any power!
Yes!
Why you pass all its whims to him?!
It flies!
Do not let it escape!
Row in its direction!
Something was run up against.
Are Nami-chan, Robin-chan, you well?
To some extent, yes.
I am well.
Pfiou, they is good.
It is what this noise?
What does it occur?
Did not say to me that it is…
What does this trick make here?
Half-turn, half-turn! Turn to 180 degrees!