Oh! What a nice day!
Keep going this way! We'll
see the navy base soon.
Koby! You are good!
We got here indeed!
Sure...
That's the basic skill of a sailor!
You're still in a good mood, Luffy.
I heard that he was caught there!
The famous bounty hunter Roronoa Zoro!
A bloody animal! Hunting down pirates!
He cuts them into pieces!
He's a man, known as "the demon".
(Episode 2) "The Great Swordsman!
Bounty Hunter Roronoa Zoro"
(Episode 2) "Daikengou Arawaru!
Kaizoku-kari Roronoa Zoro"
(Based on Manga ch.3: "Enter Zoro Pirate
Hunter", ch.4: "The Great Captain Morgan"...)
(...and ch.5: "The Pirate
King And The Master Swordsman")
We are finally here!
Hey Luffy,
Don't be stupid enough to see him!
I havn't decided yet
depends on whether he
is a good guy or not.
He is a bad guy! That's
why he was caught!
Uh, is Zoro captured at the base?
You can't mention that name here!
Let's go there first! Don't
you want to join the navy?
Um... I'm not quite ready.
I heard that there is
a captain named Morgan...
People in this town are so funny!
The people are scared
hearing the name "Zoro"...
...they are even so scared
hearing the name "Morgan"!
I'm not so sure now.
Sounds kind of fun.
How can it be?
OK! We're here!
We are here!
We have to say good-bye, Luffy!
In a such short time... Huh?
Yes!
Luffy! Why are you climbing that wall?
Where is the demon?
He can't be here! He must be isolated.
Yes! He's there! Alright!
See that guy?
How can it be?
Black bandanna... Haramaki sash...
He is Roronoa Zoro!
Very simple! Let's untie
him so he can leave!
Don't be stupid!
How can you let him go?
He might kill you!
Don't worry! I'm strong!
No!
Hey, you!
You're in the way...
Go away.
Luffy, if you want to have
him join you, you'll die!
It's very dangerous!
Luffy! Stop her! She will be killed!
What do you want?
You must be hungry...
...so I have some riceballs for you.
Kid! Do you want to die? Get out.
Big brother! You haven't eaten anything!
Here!
It's my first time.
I put my heart into it.
I'm not hungry.
I don't like them! Go away!
But...
I don't want it! I might kill you!
Don't take it so hard...
I didn't expect this, Roronoa Zoro.
That's another weird guy!
Wonderful! Must be a naval officer!
That kid will be safe!
Hey, it looks good!
Oh no!
Yech! It's sweet!
It has sugar!
Riceballs have salt! Salt!
It's good to me with sugar.
Tastes terrible! Completely inedible!
No! No!
This is going too far!
It took so long to make them...
Oh, didn't you see this notice?
"Anyone who helps
criminals will be hanged."
Signed, Captain Morgan.
Even a kid should know my daddy.
Daddy?
is he the son of Captain Morgan?
Hey! Throw this kid out!
I said throw him out!
Are you deaf?
I'll tell my daddy!
Yes! Right away!
No!
Sorry, missy... huddle yourself up.
Thank you.
Are you alright Luffy?
Were you hurt?
He's going too far!
Cretin!
I'm not sure that you can make it!
Uh... at least one month.
Then do your best!
I have ten days left!
I don't think you can make it!
He is going too far!
Luffy-san?
He's gone?
I heard that you're a bad egg.
You still here?
I'm looking for a crew member.
Are you really tough?
Mind your own business!
I'd be dead if I had
no food for three days!
I'm much different than you!
I'll survive!
I must!
Oh, what a weird guy!
Wait!
Could you get that?
You wanna eat that? It's all dirty.
Just give it to me!
Why didn't you listen?
It's good...
I'm stuffed.
Really?
Yes! He ate it all!
I'm so happy!
Is he really that bad?
Not at all!
He was imprisoned because of us.
Oh? What happened?
It was Helmeppo that caused it.
He is the son of Captain Morgan.
Move it! Move it! Give my pet some room!
Anyone in the way will be hanged!
Go away!
Hey! You really got
some nerve doing that!
Rika! Don't!
Something bad will happen if you do it!
I don't believe it!
He's dead!
Who are you?
Are you the bounty hunter, Roronoa Zoro?
What if I am?
Why would a bounty hunter
cross paths with the navy?
I'm trying to eat my food quietly.
Damn you!
You're too noisy...
...you... you and your pet.
Don't you know that...
if I tell my dad about this,
they will be hanged!
Well? Should we trade?
You can take their place and be tied up.
Yeah! For only one month!
If you can make it
through, I'll let you live.
Well?
Just one month.
Three weeks later...
...big brother has been
tortured by Helmeppo!
It's my fault! It's my fault!
I see.
I'm hungry! Give us free food!
Hey! We want some wine here!
Keep it coming! Toute de suite!
That's it! Yes!
I'm bored! Let's execute Zoro tomorrow!
I promise you'll have a good show!
What are you doing?
Luffy! Don't!
You liar!
You dare to do this?
I'm the son of Captain Morgan!
So what?
I'll tell my father and
you'll be executed too!
I dare you!
Luffy! Calm down!
Are you trying to be
the enemy of the navy?
I've decided! Koby!
I want Zoro to be my companion!
I'm the greatest!
Yes!
Correct, Captain Morgan!
Not many people are
paying tribute to me.
It is that... they no
longer have enough to give.
It's not how they pay, but
it's how much respect they have.
Am I right?
Father!
I want you to kill Zoro!
You are so useless, Zoro!
We had a deal...
I can't die here!
You again? Don't you
have anything to do?
Let me untie you! But
you must work with me!
What are you doing?
I'm looking for a
companion for a pirate.
Dream on!
I don't want to be your mate.
Don't waste your time.
What's wrong with being a pirate?
"Pirate" means "bad guy". Who
want to be a pirate anyway?
What's wrong with that?
You're practically a pirate to them!
I don't care what they think!
I've never done a thing
that I'll be sorry.
No matter what, I will survive!
I'll do what I want to do!
Oh... yeah.
I've made my decision.
With what?
Can you use a sword?
The stupid son of the
captain took my swords.
I'll get it back for you. What?
If you want it back,
you must work with me!
You're freaking nuts, you know that?
... trying to break in
the base by yourself?
it's on the other side, you idiot!
What?
GOMU GOMU NO! SPRING HAND!
Who is this guy?
1,2... 1,2... 1,2...
1,2... 1,2...
OK! Stop for a minute!
Make it stand up all the way!
Hey pop! You owe me a favor!
That kid hit me!
You never hit ME in the face!
Do you know why I haven't hit you?
Do you know why?
I do! I'm your...
It's because...
...you're so stupid,
you're not worth hitting!
Don't get me wrong!
I'm the greatest!
I am!
By the way... I've been told
that someone broke onto the base.
Yes! I gave her a little lesson...
Was she executed?
No she wasn't! She's just a little kid!
Hey you!
Go into town and kill her!
She's only a little girl!
Even an order from you...
I don't care!
Anyone who breaks the law must die!
But I can't do it!
Captain!
Why are you so angry?
It's what I do that makes me a captain!
Now hear this! I outrank all of you!
That means I'm the highest
commander of this base!
That means I'm the best!
I cannot be wrong in any way!
Do you agree?
Yes! That's right, sir!
We can take care of him later.
See here! It took a lot time to make it.
It stands for my power.
Come! Make it stand up!
1,2...1,2...1,2...1,2...1,2...
In the highest place of this base!
That's strange... no one here.
We must find him first to
get that sword back... huh?
1,2...1,2...1,2...1,2...
1,2...1,2...1,2...
Heave! Heave!
What was that?
Did you bump that?
There is something up there.
I'm very sorry! I didn't notice!
It's the statue of me.
If there are any
scratches, you are finished!
Let's go have a look.
GOMU GOMU NO!
ROCKET!
You're dead!
Overshot!
What's that?
Something's coming this way!
Got it!
Sorry!
Get that guy! I want him dead!
Yes! We'll get him!
Father! That's the guy who hit me!
Oh! It's you!
I've come looking for you!
Come with me! I want something from you!
Let go, Sir Helmeppo!
Chase him! Don't let him get away!
Captain! There is someone in here!
What?
Another one digging his own grave.
Come on! Come on!
There he is! Don't let him get away!
Oh! Somebody got in the way!
Where is Zoro's sword?
I'll tell you! don't hit me again!
OK! Tell me!
In my room we just passed by
What? Why didn't you say so?
You make me turn back!
Don't move!
Let him go!
Don't!
Shoot if you dare!
No! Don't shoot!
Get out of the way!
You can go now, Zoro-san!
You'll be executed if you cut me loose!
I don't like what they do...
I just want to... join the navy.
Stop it! I can't run away now!
Ten more days!
You'll be executed tomorrow!
What?
Helmeppo's not intending
on keeping his word...
That's why Luffy hit Helmeppo!
That guy!
The navy is chasing Luffy.
I won't force you to become a pirate,
but I'm asking this
only you can give him a hand.
And he can save you now, Zoro!
You're the only one...
...who can assist him!
Halt!
You commited a crime.
I'll execute you now!
Is it this room?
We got it!
But there are 3 swords.
Hey! Which one belongs to Zoro?
He is worthless and insensible.
Koby!
You dare to do this in my territory!
Trying to start a revolt with that kid!
I've been fighting alone.
It's quite different
with a man like you!
Roronoa Zoro,
don't get me wrong
no matter what you are,
you're nothing to me!
Ready!
I can not...
...die in a place like this!
You're still a coward, Zoro!
GOMU GOMU NO!
ROCKET!
Fire!
You! Luffy-san!
The man in the hat.
Liar!
They're useless!
Told you I was very strong!
Who the hell are you?
I'm Monkey D. Luffy...
...a man who wants to
be King of the Pirates!