Zoro!
And Luffy?
Was Luffy made kill by Zoro?
Not… It is impossible…
Where is the captain?
Whore of swashbuckler!
If you intend to make evil with these young ladies, I will be your adversary.
“I have still a chart to play”
The true robber of memory.
Counter-attack final!
Yes!!!
I am… me!
Me too!
Aren't you a customer normally?
Cavity how I am it!
Why am I equipped like that?
Owner, whom do you make?
Turn over to the reception!
Ah yes, it is true. I am the owner.
Mom, where were you all this time?
I excuses, you are well?
Yes! My memory… I found the memory!
Listen to me all! It is horrible!
Would this be Drim?
Am not afraid.
Drim! Drim!
Mom! Mom!
How are you?
Mom!
It would seem that everyone found its memory.
Thank you my God!
But what did it occur?
Listen to me all! It is horrible!
Those which stole our reports are in the forest!
How?
What is what he says?
“Deals with them, Rorornoa Zoro! ”…
He said.
But then…
He is really under his control!
He, ridges something!
Frankly!
This foutu swashbuckler causes us constantly problems!
Sanji, pay attention!
“I have time now!”
Do not interfere yourself that!
Stupid cook!
Oh, they are over there!
ZORO!
You are well?
Luffy! How is what you insane?!
Did Zoro, you say “Luffy”?
You found the memory?
Of course!
Your face was really alarming!
If you found the memory, you must smile, like that!
You will close it!
Who am I?
Hein!?
Do not make the things more difficult!
He, Zoro! You really hurt me!
Ridges as you want!
Thank you my God. Everyone returned to the normal.
Robin-chan, who discovered the true culprit, is really beautiful!
It was him?
You found your memory in first, why you in board you not returned account?!
They is false! I am better than Zoro!
And? Where is this bastard?
He fled?
Not.
One can see you through.
He. It becomes blue.
Why doesn't he flee?
Instead of hiding…
Rot!!! How you dared to make use of me!
I you will catch and you étriper!
“You humiliated me”.
“He! I catches if you can it!”
“He, wait!”
“Will not arrive to You there!”
“Yosh… It is what one will see!”
“I am too fast for you!”
“Eh? I do not believe myself!”
“If I am serious!”
“I hold you!”
“I will not release myself!”
You will be the next one, Usopp!
“I have still a chart to play!”
It is impossible!
Belmer-san?
Doctor!
Kaya!
You are cured?
How is that?
They all are…
The reflection of each one of their memory.
You want to fight?! I go you botter the bottom!
What is what it is?
Oh not!
What is what he says?
“Because of you, I lost all the memories of the inhabitants!”
“But if I recover all your invaluable memories, I would become one about it!”
To become what?
I do not know!
“I will not let pass this occasion!”
It is what this trick!?
And…
Who am I?
Who are you?
Who? Me? Ho!
Who am I? Hein?
He, a guy who drowns!
You know it?
ME EITHER!
[Sennenryu = 1000 years old dragon]
“Finally! I became Sennenryu!”
You!
Incredible! You include/understand what he says?
The tanuki speaks!
[Tanuki:left raccoon]
I am a tanuki?!
A speaking tanuki and Sennenryu…
A moron who drowns…
What is what occurs?
Although I see only one dragon…
I feel in anger! Why?!
Who? What? Where? When?
Strange! Why am I here?
Incredible!
A dragon? I will overlap it!
Baka! It is possible no to reach it from here…
You cannot say that without to have tested!
It is what that!?
What is what it is? My arms and my legs lengthen!
It is brilliant!
How it does that…
How is what arrives at its body?!
It is a monster!
Do not do that, they are dangerous!
Ca seems painful.
“Stops! I lose the memories!”
Memories?
How much time still…
You will steal us our reports!
Bastard!
How is what he says, Chopper!
“Chopper”?
Me?
Who of other?!
Hein?
“I finally became Sennenryu! Leave me quiet!”
What?!
The memories of people do not belong to you!
If you want to become Sennenryu, do it with your own memories!
“Keep silent yourself! Take that! It is finished for you!”
GOt (300,500, \ fs72)}DRIVEN  GO  DRIVEN  NO
WORSE (280,1350, \ fs72)}TOL
If you want to really fly, I will help you!
He…
You will catch cold.
I have boot to him the bottom!
But…
Isn't a sennenryu born in an egg normally?
If. It would not have changed just by swallowing memories.
It is true?
Yes. You probably do not know that, but we saw one of our own eyes of them while entering on Grand Line.
Well, in any case! I bet that the village is become again merry now!
We are the heroes who made find the memory with the villagers!
We without any doubt will be treated like heroes!
I will be able to perhaps drink at will?
Didn't Ca, you forget it?
The farm!
We can also await us full with rewards!
I want a bronze statue!
I will be able to take all that I want…
Robin?
If you could have all that you want, you would take what?
A book perhaps?
Yes, perhaps the historical book of this island, if possible.
Of course! Then I want full with books of medicine!
I see the houses.
Oyé Oyé, Mesdames and Sirs! Thank you for this cordial reception!
Why?
It is them!
With the attack everyone!
What it occurs?!
Usopp!
Aren't we of the heroes!?
I do not know! It is what I believed!
Nami-san, where is the waver?!
By there!
Wait, pirate! Wait!
Robbers of memory!
You will pay it!
How is what they have?!
They take to us for someone else!
He would seem yes.
My faith, we are pirates.
One can nothing make there.
Then we must act even as cause of despair!
He! Stop!
What would make a pirate in this kind of situation?!
He you!
I am glad to be of return.
When I think…
That I could have had a large statue.
Large and alarming…
But I did not think that amnesia could pose problems so much.
Yes.
There was of it one which tried to convince everyone to belong to its crew.
Sanji-kun, it was right to laugh…
There was also a cretin who completely left embobiner.
What?!
If you had not slept at the guardroom, all this could have been avoided!
Stupid marimo!
You close it! I try to sleep!
If you want to sleep so much, passes your life to sleep!
The calm one! Enough!
Want you to lose your memory again?!
Nami-san, do not say that!
My memories…
If I lost all my memories…
I…
What there is it, Robin?
All is well. I am just tired.
Yes. Robin-chan did not sleep because of all these events.
It is true.
Yosh! I will have a good meal this evening.
Meal! I had completely forgotten!
Sanji! Make me eat!
I will do it, then sit down and wait a little!
He, Luffy!
Why didn't you return with Zoro the other time?
And well, I was wedged under the rock that Zoro had split…
A rock?
Yes! It was so large that I could not raise it!