The green city Erumalu
And Kung Fu Dugong!
With the kingdom of the Oases.
Three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
In a howl of sadness, this desiccated ground sinks from now on in an enormous wave of agitation.
In Nanohana, port city of Arabasta, Luffy found his/her Ace brother…
… which made the demonstration of the talents acquired thanks to the fruit Mera Mera.
The crew goes up the Sandora river now with Ace to reach Yuba.
Halt! State the goal of your visit!
Please, let have an audience with His Majesty to us the King!
How long still will this civil war last?
Between it and the dryness, there remain to us nothing to eat!
Please, save my child!
I do not have any more milk to give him!
Wait! Do not push!
We cannot let to you pass!
Please, let speak to us with His Highness!
Will you let to us die thus!?
Hey, why you do not say anything?!
Do you intend to let to us die?
Ouais, known as something!
Dirty dogs!
How do you dare address yourselves thus to His Majesty!?
Is enough!
Guards!
Forgive me.
My incompetence caused the intolerable sufferings which you undergo.
Please, that those which want to speak to me enter and their problems expose me.
For the moment, all that I can make is to listen to your complaints and to think of it as if they were mine.
Hold out still a little bit, please.
I swear to restore peace in this kingdom.
Even at the price of my own life!
Father, it is a plot!
It is obvious that somebody seeks to destroy our kingdom!
Es you in life and good health?
Where are you now…?
Vivi…
The tea is been useful.
We are in the kitchen.
Thank you, Sanji-San.
Hello! I am the Onigiri-Usopp captain!
Oh, and which are you, without indiscretion?
Meshi = Food; Daru de Yukidaruma (bonhomme de neige)
I am Meshidaru-San!
DO NOT PLAY WITH FOOD!
If you are bored so much, thus will make the crockery!
Bento = cold Meal in a small box
Good blood! I try to finish our bentos before we do not unload!
Can I help for anything?
Not, you are a guest on this boat.
Thus remain sitted.
Heard.
YOU WASH THE PLATES WITH DIRTY SPONGES!!
Which pleasant breeze…
Nami-San.
Can we drop anchor here a small moment?
Why?
I will entrust to Karu an important mission.
In Karu?
Karu…
I want that you only go to the palate of Alubarna to give this letter to my father.
I wrote all that Igaram and me discovered on Crocodile and its bonds with Baroque Work…
I also say to him that I am always in life and that I return with very determined companions.
Can you do it?
You will have to cross the desert alone…
Listen well, does not forget to ration you out of water while you cross-pieces the desert, hein.
Well! Do of tone better!
And you will say to my father…
… how this kingdom is about to be saved!
I said to you to ration yourself!
Karu…
I count on you.
I knew that Shichibukai Crocodile was in this kingdom…
But which already heard of a pirate seeking to seize a kingdom?
Which dirty trick.
A pirate, to drop anchor for good and to confine themselves at only one place?
I cannot believe that he wants to take the place of the king.
Yosh! Ahead all!
He, I wait am not yet on board!
There could well be more behind this takeover that what he appears to with it with the first access.
More?
Ouais, a stronger, more important reason.
The kingdom of the desert, Arabasta.
Even with a history being spread out over thousands of years since its creation over these sands,
… the desert always been able death.
This country in the shade of was died since its beginnings.
We have just received a message:
Boats of the Billions stationed with Nanohana…
all were destroyed by an unknown force.
I have just had the confirmation of this news.
The Billions are easily replaceable.
It is not because a water drop falls into the desert…
that the plan is called into question.
However, if somebody, in one way or another, wants to be opposed to me…
Crush it.
As you want.
Erimaku = Lizard with flange.
I already sent the Erimaku messengers to carry this message.
Splendid.
We are there finally.
One finally will be able to walk in the desert!
It must be rather hot there…
I intended to say that the temperature could exceed the 50°C during the day.
What?
Be serious for you?
What You ES ARRIVES, NAMI-SAN?!
OR IS HELD MT OF DANCER?!
NOOOON! NOT VIVI-CHAN TOO!
WHY YOU CARRY CA?!
But we would be burned by the intense rays of the sun if we expose our skin.
Ah, misery…
My dear dancers…
Luffy-San, mets that, please.
Oh, thank you.
Prepare we to unload.
Ouais.
Go, everyone with ground.
What…?
Tortoises?
You want to say seals, not?
Of Kung Fu Dugong!
“If you want to unload here, it will be necessary for you to face me and beat me.”
“If you are frightened too much, thus accost on other bank, hens wet.”
Here what he said.
I cannot remain without anything to make after being treated of wet hen.
I ARRIVE!
Wait, Usopp-San!!
Kung Fu Dugong are very strong!
I gained!
It would seem that we have a winner here.
To gain is still worse!
What?
The code of Kung Fu Dugong obliges them to become the disciple of that which overcame them.
Truths fans of martial arts.
IT WAS MADE EVEN MORE DISCIPLES WHILE ONE SPOKE!
YOSH! MADE ALL LIKE ME!
IN POSITION!
THE FIST AHEAD!
The movement is done of before behind, go.
Well!
Go ahead!
STILL!
Yosh! On the way for Yuba!
Wait a little, there…
YOU WILL NOT TAKE THEM ALONG WITH YOU?!
You cannot, Luffy!
Dugongs cannot cross the desert.
Nice!                   Nice!
I have the impression to be petty towards them…
Me also…
What will we make?
I know!
What do you seek?
Here, I give you that if you remain here wisely, of agreement?
With the assistance!
Chopper!
BYE BYE!
Listen, Luffy!
You see well in which situation one is?
Is they said that they came with me, why it impossible?
One cannot go in a city with as much world!
Moron!
Frankly, one would have been in beautiful cloths if Chopper had not convinced them!
Ouais, they continued to say “follow We it!”
If one had not given them to eat, they would have really done it.
PF, thanks to you, our reserves dropped well.
It brings only troubles, hein?
Seriously.
It is what?
It is Yuba?
Not.
It is Erumalu.
It was called formerly the Green City.
The Green City?
To see this city, you can include/understand…
how much Baroque Works made of evil to this country.
And how much the people suffer from Arabasta.
Ouah, has there really nothing here.
Yes… But even if the city is today in ruin,
until its collapse, it was an alive city filled with luxuriant flowers.
This city, hein?
This area forever have much water, but…
by recovering water at the time of the rare downpours, the city had opened out.
However, these three last years…
not only one water drop did not fall into all the kingdom.
Three years?!
Also a long time?
But even without rain, you always have this river which we went up.
It is true, you could not simply draw from the water of this large river?
The answer is a little further.
An complete absence of precipitations is a misfortune which did not arrive in Arabasta since thousands of years.
But there was a place where there was always rain.
It was in the capital, Alubarna,
where the royal palace is.
People called that the royal miracle.
Until the day of this disastrous incident.
Discharge the boats!
It is reversed!
Caution!
Does He, that go?
You are wounded?
Oh, shit! One is badly there!
We were to make sure that the delivery with King Cobra in Alubarna was well made!
But it is what this powder with the Juste?
Euh, what?
Hum, we do not know!
We obey the orders of your King, it is all!
Not true?
We are right deliverymen.
Let us flee!
C it cannot be…
It was of Dance Powder?
What? You of ace heard speak?
Yes…
It is also called it “powder-which-fact-to rain”.
“Which-fact-to rain”?
It is only one hearsay, but…
it is said that she was invented by a scientist of a kingdom where it never rained.
Once burned, the powder releases a kind of fog which rises in the airs…
and which creates rain artificially.
Here what is Dance Powder.
Ah, included/understood!
You speak about the Magic Powder.
I ate some does not have a little there a long time.
It is really dégueu!
Isn't Ca eaten, you know?
In other words, that made rain, what.
What do you have, the guy?
You think that I lie, it is that?!
He!
Await a little, if this kind of trick exists,
I say the truth!
it is the ideal for this country, not?
It is what they believed, yes.
As its name implies it, the inhabitants of the kingdom danced initially of joy when this powder was invented.
But it has an enormous defect.
Indeed, it causes the dryness in the countries under the wind.
You include/understand?
Dance Powder is fixed on small clouds…
… which differently would have continued to travel to the liking of the winds while being gorged little by little with moisture
and the force to earlier reach the stage of cloud of rain so that it rains.
And then…
Ah of agreement.
Approximately, that steals the rain which should normally have fallen on another country.
Blow, a formidable war burst between two kingdoms.
The human losses were numerous.
The World Government since put a world interdict on the manufacture and the detention of Dance Powder.
A powder which brings at the same time happiness and misfortune, hein?
All this Dance Powder was conveyed in our port…
at one moment when it did not rain nowhere in safe Arabasta in the capital…
The reason for which it does not rain on our grounds is that the King uses this Dance Powder!
The rain with Alubarna is not due to a miracle!
We die of thirst and hunger right because of the King!
WHAT, VIVI!?
YOUR FATHER MALICIOUS EAST!!
MORON!
He was trapped!
How the father of Vivi-Chan it could ever have done something of similar?! Never!?
Never!
Never! Never!
Never! Never! Never!
Never! Never! Never! Never!!!
Of course, my father did not have any idea what did without.
And at the same moment,
great quantities of Dance Powder were discovered in the palate even.
Then, there were traitors even in the palate…
What is it that this road, Vivi-Chan?
It is there that the channel used by the city passed formerly to draw from the water of the Sandora river.
But one day, this channel was mysteriously destroyed.
Without him, the Green City did not can provide longer for its requirements out of water.
The inhabitants continued to wait with the energy of despair…
But the rain obstinately refused to fall.
And since the incident of Dance Powder, suspicion towards the King increased the every day regularly.
The plan of Crocodile went to the hair…
The confrontation was inevitable.
Exhausted, people left towards the other oases, to avoid the conflict and to obtain water.
The cities were abandoned.
And then…
The Green City fell in ruin.
What is it?
There is somebody?
It is the rebellious army?
They is perhaps assassins of Works Baroque!?
Nan.
It is right the wind.
Ca resembles voices.
They come from everywhere!
What do we have to make?
Hein, big brother!?
There is nothing to fear.
The wind crosses the city while passing between the buildings in ruin.
The city…
It is as if the town of Erumalu cried!
Ca arrives!
Was nutcase, what it that this wind?
There is somebody up there!
There would be still somebody of alive in this city…!?
Father…
What Father and the inhabitants of this kingdom made to deserve that?
To destroy the life of those which fought against Nature to live in this desert…
Why?
Of which right does do it that!?
It acts as if he were the saver of the people because he is Shichibukai…!
And nobody carries out that it takes part in the destruction of the kingdom!
Crocodile!
I…
I will never forgive him!
Good blood…
You are really kids.
Vivi!
It is necessary to go from the front one.
We remained here too a long time.
Allons-y, in Yuba.
It is well there that is the rebellious army, not?
Yes.
I will persuade the chief to stop the insurrection.
To persuade?
All misfortunes of Arabasta are the result of the schemes of Crocodile!
I will tell them the truth and will put a term at this useless bloodshed!
Included/understood.