When the Authority of the kingdom falls!
The flag of the will perdure for eternity
Where did it pass?
Who?
He!
He?
This person who is damned guy with the steel teeth!
What a jerk!
When I find it, I will regulate his account to him!
But what occurred here?
What did it make with my splendid castle?
Doctorine…
This guy, it said that I was…
his/her companion.
It is not the moment to remain with the bed.
I must eclipse before the return of Doctorine.
I have chance! The way is free.
Qu Which is?
Thus hold, you would not be a team member of Straw hat, by chance?
Its head does not inspire confidence to me.
Not, you make error.
I do not know at all what you speak.
What? It is an error?!
Really?
Completely! I am only one navigatrice of passage.
I see.
Good, I must go there now…
Of agreement!
LIAR!
Remain, small stupid there!
Does not approach you! Go away!
Would I have taken a little belly?
I know what it remains to me to do!
I car-will introduce myself.
What is it?
It was transformed into bucket.
Finished!
Miracles of the osseous rebuilding!
SLIMUP WAPOL
You will not go nowhere.
NOT!
I will begin my feast with you!
FIND!
Eh! I do not remember that it was also thin.
Luffy.
Why my jacket is very torn?!
Do you know how much it cost me?
28.000 Berry! And moreover, I had to haggle over to have it.
Afflicted! This guy drew me above with his guns.
I did not can anything make.
Frankly!
Go, it is not serious. I forgive you.
In any event, when I lent my jacket to you, I did not expect to find it in good state.
N the other hand, you will give me just small extra of three times his purchase price.
You thus owe me 100.000 Berry.
Ah! You had mijoté that since the beginning?!
Ca is enough, band of little runts!
But it is that it is solid!
LOOK AT!
It is arms manufacture!
And I have the key of it!
Of course, you can imagine the varied number of weapons in any kind which there can be inside!
After all to have consumed them,
my capacity Baku Baku will make an integral part of my body of it!
In front of your eyes, I will become a human weapon feared throughout the world!
You will be impressed! I will open it!
The key of the doors of the hell is…
WHAT?!
Well, that is not finished yet.
He flees!
Stop!
I still have a cord with my arc!
What… it is the key of arms manufacture?!
I hoped that it was the key of a trunk…
What a damage!
Nami-San!
I am relieved! You do not have anything!
What did it occur, Sanji-Kun?
Are you slopes… you well?
Nami-San! You are really anxious of my fate?!
If I could right being kissed by this soft heat…!
Ca is enough!
Nami… San…
Wait!
Wait! Wait!
Shit!
Even the upper floors are covered with snow!
I will kill them, I will kill them all for what they did!
I will show them with a whole a first impression of what is the power of the king!
The power of Drum… it is mine.
The supreme weapon of the Kingdom of Drum…
The Acier Canon with Seven Blows of the Crown of Drum!
You are made! Loan to take a beating?!
It is what you believe, Straw hat!
BURST!
A bird's nest?!
Of Snowbirds!
You make me pass for an imbecile…!
It is odd which there is a cable installed so far…
They are kids of the village who found it by chance!
Wouldn't Ca be the old house of Doctor Kureha?
There is a beautiful sight from here.
Yes, it is true.
Eh! You do not have the impression that one is too numerous on board?
One could not leave all alone Dalton-San, especially which it is wounded.
We there also will beat we.
I know, but one will not go well far with this train.
Pedal! There put more strength!
Dalton-San, you calm.
Wapol…
For which take you you, Dalton?
“There is no remedy against stupidity!”
You take to me for an idiot?
You think that you are a dispenser of justice who comes to save the widow and the orphan?
Did not dream, you are only one trusty servant!
Perhaps that a one week stay locked up in this cell will help you to become aware of your error of judgments.
Thus, your desires of rebellion will cease.
You are the chief of the guard in which populates it has a blind confidence.
Reflect there, Dalton.
You let yourself persuade by the stupid dream of this insane of Doctor Hiluluk.
To sacrifice your row and to destroy this country…
where is the merit in all that?
Look at me…
… I am the man who sat on the throne of this kingdom.
“I am sorry!”
Say these simple words and I release you, Dalton-Kun.
What a row?!
What a king?!
I am the king! Sovereign of the Kingdom of Drum!
I AM THE KING!
It is finished.
It does not matter.
That you would be a king… or that you would be a god…
How you would be tall… or that you would not be it, that does not count!
Because I am a pirate.
But of course that if, that counts, Straw hat!
The Kingdom of Drum is member of the World Government.
You measuring rods?
Ca wants to say that you are committing an international crime!
I said to you that did not have any importance.
It is my combat.
You… the snotty-nosed kid with the straw hat!
I will puff out you!
Try just to see!
I did not finish any with you!
Hein?! Its language was transformed into gun!
Burst!
Dalton-San! I beg you, hold out!
What do I have to make?
Dalton-San! Dalton-San!
Dalton-San!
I am well.
I… will finish some with this kingdom!
And this history!
Let us go, opens the eyes, Dalton!
Any country has its government!
You include/understand?
There are no feelings in policy!
It is true. The most important thing, it is the system.
Q- What you made?
Release me! Stop, please!
There are so many patients who need me!
Balance it with the sea.
If it resists, you can cut down it.
He. Leave me! I beg you!
There are patients who await me!
PLEASE!
What a way of controlling…?!
I am relieved. Nobody is sick here.
That is there of evil to control a country with its heart?!
D-Dalton-San!
Dalton-San!
What you…?
Dynamite!
Listen to me, everyone well.
Once arrived at the castle, I will infiltrate there and you will remain with cover.
You worry for him?
And why I would have?
It is a pirate!
Imbecile! You were made have!
Not, it is you!
What?
It left…
What? What do you make?
Eh, releases me!
Doctorine?
Yes.
It seems that one arrives at the outcome.
Ca will have taken time before putting a term at this kingdom.
It is the end…
This country is sick.
Its people too.
And the king and his government are it too.
The heart of people is ravaged.
One day, I will save this country with my medicine!
Break, charlatan!
Return never again!
Flee, Chopper!
If you are not ready to undergo the consequences of them…
… then does not approach you the flag to the tête de mort of another!
Doctor…
Wait!
I will give you a row… as well as a distinction!
Look at! There is somebody at the top of the castle!
Doctor…
The Kingdom…
The Kingdom of Drum has…
Of agreement, I will name you at the post of Vice King!
He… fell!
And thus the Kingdom of Drum was inclined vis-a-vis the flag with the tête de mort.
Agreement, I leave as a scout!
Ca goes! How everyone remains behind me!
Wait, Zoro!
It is the moment to show “my true power”!
Oh! Stop clutching you with me!
All is well, I am right behind you.
If you are afraid, why you remainders not in withdrawal?
J-J I am not afraid, C-it is that…
WHAT…?!
Luffy!
Eh! Zoro! Usopp!
BUT What TOOK to You TO MAKE CA?
He? It is you, the guy?
I did not recognize clothing of Zoro…
… then I thought that you were enemies.
Like did that, you climb the mountain?
Hadn't Usopp, you said that you could not climb?
It is ridiculous!
I am the kind of guy to be said:“If there is a mountain, it should be climbed”!
Although this rise was somewhat animated.
We came via the cable, Luffy-San.
It is unjust.
Nami-San and Sanji-San are well?
Ouais! They are well!
It is true that I was surprised when the giant condor attacked us.
They is marvellous!
Good news!
But obviously, I was there…
NOT!
I should rather say “I were there, like always”!
And what did you make at the top of the castle?
I knew what I had to do at the moment even where it came to strike me in the middle, I dodged it of a jump and…
… I circumvented it! Then I overlapped it!
I made the skin with a king.
And I was there! “Me” the captain, enfourchant the condor and flying through the skies!
Then that which was made dispatch in the airs a few moments ago…
… it was really Wapol?!
You beat it…?
Ouais, why?
“My name is Capitaine Usopp”!
And its two ministers?
It is the reindeer which put a beating to them.
Beaten… by a reindeer?
What do you say that? Impressing, hein?!
Ah ouais, Usopp! Listen to me!
As always…
I found us a new companion!
What?
A reindeer…
A reindeer?
A blue nose…
DECREE!
If it is because he made fun of died of Hiluluk, I excuse myself some!
Your force will not be of any utility if you die like a dog!
Would not be a sacrifice moreover for this country!
It was thus you… this day…
I see. You did not cease since then beating you.
Thank you.
Drum will be able…
To be able… to reappear!
Q - What is it? This odd creature!
One… a reindeer?
Not!
C-C' is a monstr- ***!
Eh, that is enough!
A MONSTER!
MONSTER DOES NOT TREAT IT!
It is him, the new companion whom I found!
What? This thing?
You frightened him!
Wait! The monster!
He!!
Eh, the reindeer!
He! The reindeer!!
But await me!
You are my companion!
Oh, Thundered-Chan!
You belong to my crew!
Doctor…
It of agreement, isn't this is?
Like that…
Wait! The reindeer!
I WILL NOT STOP!!