The world...
Yes!
Seek freedom,
And your world will stand stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides your spirits,
Conquer it!
Bear conviction behind your flag!
I began my search,With a blast of water,
Toward a boundless,everlasting world
With this overflowing passion in my chest, I'll go anywhere
Seeking the light l've never seen
When the summer-colored sun shakes the sall of my heart,
It's a sign the door to a new world has opened
Swaying between the waves, I can escape despair,
For the horize on the other side is what I aim for!
I began my search, With a blast of water,
Toward a boundless, everlasting world
With this overflowing passion in my chest, I'll go anywhere
Seeking the light I've never seen
1,867! 1,868! 1,869!
I got one!
Look it!
Nice!
Ah, I got one too!
It's a big one!
He's probably the big boss in these waters!
Really?
Whoa, cool!
GOT IT!
The big boss?
You can't even eat that.
Shut up!
Don't start dissing me when you haven't caught anything!
Yeah? Just watch me!
I'm gonna catch a huge one!
Will you really?
It'll work out somehow.
Nami-swan~!
To enhance stunning beauty such as yours with silky smooth skin, I have brought you a special tropical juice!
Thank you.
Hey now!
Give me some too!
Silky smooth!
Hold on... Why would guys want silky smooth skin?
So we'll be cute.
Winds are steady. Currents are favorable.
Looks like it's going to be another great day!
Got one!
What the hell is that?
It's huge!
Oi, Luffy!
What'd you reel in this time?
The navigator's mutiny!
For an unwavering dream!
That's a huge turban shell!
I don't believe that's a turban shell.
What do we do with this?
Think we can eat it?
Eat it!?
Maybe I could grill it in its shell...
You too!?
Ah, I thought I was about to die!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Who... are you?
Oh, forgive my rudeness!
With a single call, you can count on us to deliver all your material needs!
My name is Rice-Rice from Den Den Mushi Mail Order Services!
GEKIYASU - Super Deal!
Delighted to meet you.
Den Den Mushi Mail Order Service?
What the hell is that?
Oh!
While I was delivering some merchandise in my Escargot, I suddenly found myself amidst a storm!
It tossed me around quite viciously! This way! That way!
And before I knew it I was lost at sea!
Lost at sea?
"Sounan desu ka" - double meaning of "Lost at sea?" and "Is that so?"
Yes I was.
Oh my! That was a nice tsukkomi, Miss!
Tsukkomi - comedy exchange
Have, have some water.
I can't thank you enough for saving my life!
As a token of my appreciation, please take these catalogs.
Anything you desire will be delivered with a single call!
Hey, that's pretty convenient.
So you deliver all the way out at sea?
Actually we don't.
Oh...
I see...
Yes. Our motto is "Safety and low prices are our top priority".
And our company policy...
It's pretty spacious inside.
Ahh! What are you doing!?
Very well, allow me to introduce this fine product to you!
This is the well-known Buru-Buru Blade.
The Buru-Buru Blade happens to be our company's top product!
And this one I have with me today is the very newest model!
I gather many of you must already own the older version of the Buru-Buru Blade.
But that older model was not nearly as customizable.
It was just no good!
People were saying that it was fine for the elderly, but it was a little too dangerous for little children.
I don't really understand, but it sounds fun!
This newer model keeps going buru-buru-buru at a steady rhythm, and...
This is fun!
And this, I'm sure you all know, is the Ab-Ab Slider!
Our company's NUMBER ONE product!
It has returned, newer and better than before!
What's the difference between being the top and being number one?
Who knows.
And this is our best-selling product, the Golden Fish!
It's perfect for people who haven't been getting enough exercise.
And of these dieting products you've seen are available as a set!
And today only, I'll throw in 20 cartons of the famous West Blue ultra-sweet Mero-Mero Juice!
PLUS! A 26-volume encyclopedia which will surely come in handy!
And a handy pair of binoculars.
How much is all this, you ask?
You might think it would cost a fortune, but have no fear!
To show my gratitude for saving my life...
You're giving them to us!?
Just take it, you thieves! How does 23,800 beri sound?
You're selling it?
I WANT IT ALL!
You're buying it?
Oh, you have kitchen knives too?
Yes, you must mean these!
Each one was forged meticulously by the craftsmen of High Mountain!
Look at its flexibility! Its superior sharpness will last a lifetime!
A dozen of these table knives,
And I'll throw in the all-purpose, all-cutting kitchen scissors, a peeling knife, and an electric sharpener!
All together, it's 2,980 beri.
For you, Miss, I have this Silky Smooth Skin Soap to make your skin silky smooth!
You will become as silky smooth as an egg!
Oh, you seem to have everything.
Yes, there is nothing we don't have! From mineral water to cannonballs!
Do you have food?
No, we do not.
What, you don't?
We have nothing of what we don't have!
Hey, do you have any paper?
Paper?
Yeah.
Large, flexible, durable paper that won't get damaged by a little sea breeze.
If that is all, just leave it to us!
We, the Den Den Mushi Mail Order present our ulimate Thousand-Year Paper!
Thousand-Year Paper?
Thousand-Year Paper is made from the Thousand-Year Trees which grow on Eight Nine Island.
It does not attract bugs, and if left out in the sun, it is said that it will not fade for a thousand years!
It's perfect for documenting your family tree or for making treasure maps!
Paper airplanes too?
What?
That would be wasting it...
How much is it?
You're gonna buy it?
Of course!
I'm detecting the urge to buy!
I can sense she's willing to buy it at any price!
Therefore, I should offer her the highest possible price!
Even if you wish to purchase it, this is a very rare item.
If you place an order now, it might be five- no, ten years before you can actually receive it.
Do you think you could sell those to me?
Just name the price.
What!?
Nami, who loves counting money more than eating!?
Nami, the money-fiend!?
WILLING TO PAY ANY PRICE!?
That's going overboard, you guys.
Well, since you want it that badly...
A thousand-sheet set of the Thousand Year Paper.
Normally it sells for 60,000,000 beri, but I will offer it to you for the special low price of 48,000,000 beri!
48,000,000 beri!?
That means each sheet is 48,000 beri!
Can't you make it any cheaper?
You're killing me here. How about 47,500,000 beri?
2,000,000 beri!
4,800,000 beri!
Sounds fishy.
Down a little more?
I'll buy it!
Sanji-kun...
Do you have the money?
Nope.
If you hand this guy over to the Marines, you'll have plenty of change to spare.
WHAAAT!?
Forgive me, Luffy.
This is for Nami-san.
WAIT A SECOND!
Luffy?
Luffy!? You mean Monkey D. Luffy?
Yeah, that's me.
Sanji.
Come on and untie me!
Nope.
Monkey D. Luffy, a bounty of 100,000,000 beri... Leader of a bloodthirsty pirate crew...
Now that you mention it... That's a pirate flag!
How could I have overlooked such an important thing!?
Untie me already!
I said no.
I've just remembered a very important engagement. Please excuse me!
Thank you for your time!
Oi, you forgot your...
What's with him?
He was probably afraid of you.
The wanted man, Monkey D. Luffy.
Got it?
I'm going to do some work, and I don't want you guys bothering me.
What kind of work are you doing?
It's a secret!
That's not the least bit cute.
Leave it to me!
I won't let anyone near while you're working, Nami-san!
But what if the wind suddenly changes?
It'll be alright.
Those clouds...
As long as those clouds don't move, the weather will be fine all day.
Call me if you see those clounds change at all.
Now then...
Ever since we entered the Grand Line, things have been so busy that I haven't had much free time.
Little Garden.
Drum Island.
Arabasta.
I've managed to map out the entire route we've traveled.
And there's also the local maps I stole- er, I mean got from the towns we stopped at.
It's time to start drawing it.
The dream I've had since I was a kid!
My own map of the world!
Hey guys!
Let's clean this place up a bit while Nami-san's working.
Aye-aye!
Work hard!
YOU'RE WORKING TOO!
Cheater!
That's no fair, slacking off by yourself!
Yeah, yeah!
Then what about her?
Don't be an idiot.
She's a lady.
That's stupid!
What's the difference between being a man or a woman?
Just help out , you monster Marimo.
That's funny coming from you, you love-love machine demon!
Just help out or I'll kick your ass!
Why don't you try it? Think you can beat a monster?
You only talk like that 'cause you haven't witnessed my demonic powers.
I'll cut you to pieces!
You're askin' to be filleted!
I'll mince you first!
Yeah! Yeah! Go! Go!
Come on, stop it guys!
Usopp! Don't just stand there! Stop them!
Are you kidding?
What am I gonna do?
Nothing can stop those two.
Oh.
Comin' right up!
Didn't I tell you to be quiet!?
Mellorine...
A-A single blow!
Damn, that hurt...
Bellemere-san!
Bellemere-san, listen!
Bellemere-san? I wanna know where the wind blows from.
From the sea.
The sea?
Yup.
The wind is born from the sea and blows over Kokoyashi Village, bringing us blessings.
And it's not just the wind.
Rain, clouds, and rainbows all come from the sea.
Oh!
Then... where does the sea come from?
Nami! Don't bother Bellemere-san so much!
But, Nojiko!
Nami, you really are a curious one.
Nami!
I heard you did it again.
The bookstore lady came barking at me.
Okay, let's go home.
Dinner's ready.
Hey, Bellemere-san...
What's beyond that sea?
Who knows?
I don't know a thing about what lies beyond the Grand Line.
Even though you were a Marine?
I was, but the sea is just too big.
I want to see what lies beyond the sea.
Nami...
Do you think I can make it?
Beyond the sea?
You're a strong girl, Nami.
If you set your mind to it, you'll be able to go anywhere you want.
Then I've decided!
I'm going to travel the world's seas with my navigation skills!
And I'll make a world map of everything I see!
I'll do it!
Yes.
Someday... I will complete a map of the world.
Hey, Luffy!
Watch this!
Wow!
That's so cool!
Geez!
You must be tired. Have you finished your work?
No...
What's all this?
Oi, what are you guys doing?
Cleaning.
It's kinda fun.
Wanna try it out, Nami?
What's all the noise?
What? The Silky Smooth Skin Soap?
Hey, that's dangerous!
Don't worry! We're fine!
Luffy!
That idiot!
GOMU GOMU NO...
BUNGEE!
Look out!
Nami-san, look out!
Are you alright, Nami-san?
My map!
Oh, you were drawing maps?
What? A map?
So that's what you were up to?
That's right.
It is a one of a kind map recording our travels on the Grand Line.
That's all I wanted!
My dream is to complete my own map of the world.
Get out!
But...
Just...
Nami!
What?
Sorry.
If sorry was all it took, the Marines wouldn't be after us!
Just get out!
If you don't leave, I'll fine you 100,000 beri!
It's your fault.
Why me?
Geez, they'll just be in my way if they stay in here.
Luffy, cheer up!
Why do I smell rain?
This is bad!
Luffy!
We've got trouble! The clouds...!
Oh, a spider has ten legs.
Kumo can mean either cloud or spider
No, they have eight.
Wait, that's not the point! Wake up!
A hundred arms...
Usopp!
Sanji, wake up!
Zoro!
Flower lady!
Help!
Nami!
I'll fine you 100,000 beri!
W-What should I do?
It's done!
Humm, Prefect!
Am I a genius or what?
What was that?
Hey, what's going on!?
Nami!
Hey, what are you doing?
Why didn't you tell me about this!?
But, the 100,000 beri fine...
Don't be stupid.
Hey, you guys!
How long do you plan on sleeping?
Wow, what the hell is that?
IT'S A CYCLONE!
We can tell.
I said...!
Luffy, Zoro! Hoist the sails!
Aye!
Usopp, Chopper! Tie down everything on deck with the ropes!
Got it!
Sanji-kun, hard to starboard!
Turn the bow away from the cyclone. Or else we'll be pulled in!
Oi, oi.
Listen up!
If that map I worked so hard on falls victim to the high waves...
Not one of you...
...will escape.
She really is scary!
Atmospheric pressure rising, rain's stopped...
Nice work!
You can all take a rest now!
Oh.
I'm going to continue with my maps, so keep watching the clouds, okay?
You're still working on it?
Of course! My goal is to draw a map of the world.
I've only finished my first page. The real task is still ahead.
Impressive resolve you've got.
I love this Nami-san too~!
You think there's gonna be a 100,000 beri fine again?
Yeah.
Have you been reading the whole time?
Okay, full sail!
Full speed ahead!
AYE!
So now, you guys have the helm.
Oi!
What course can I set that will lead me to a better tomorrow?
Taking the helm, I spread out the map of miracles I had shut in my heart
Aiming for the sky, searching for a dream, there were times when I lost my way
But this isn't a dream, I found a wonderful part of myself when I met you
With a small bit of courage, I gained something large
So now is the time to change my dreams into vows.
Shining Ray! Find your brand new way.
Let's paint a story of the future
And put all of our thoughts into this new wind
Shining Ray! Find your brand new way.
A never ending journey to be together.
I'll chase it anywhere, this Shining Ray!