(The following episode is based
on Manga ch.5: "The Pirate King")
(...and "the Master Swordsman", ch.6:
"Number One" and ch.7: "Friends".)
Fire!
Luffy-san!
The one with the straw hat!
They're useless!
Told you I was very strong!
Who the hell are you?
I am Luffy...
...a man who become the Pirates king!
"Morgan vs. Luffy!
Who's This Beautiful Young Girl?"
"Morgan VS Luffy!
Nazo no Bishoujo wa Dare?"
What? You want to be a Pirate King?
Hey, do you know what it
means to be a pirate king?
A pirate king is a pirate king.
What else is it?
I was frightened when I heard that.
But Luffy is serious.
That is him.
He said he wants to be a pirate
king, and find the world's treasures.
That means he has to
get the "One Piece."
Take it it's your baby.
Which one? I don't know,
so I brought them all.
They're all mine I
am a three-swordsman.
If you cooperate with me,
you will become the evil
party against the government.
So, are you game?
Are you getting yourself killed?
You are the son of the devil.
Forget it, it can't be worse.
I promise... I'll be a pirate!
Wonderful! So you will be my partner!
Alright! Fantastic!
I haven't any choice! Now untie me!
That guy... it's so magic.
He lets the bullets bounce back!
That straw-hat man is
not an ordinary person!
He must have eaten the "Devil Fruit".
"Devil Fruit?"
He ate the treasure of the ocean?
Devil Fruit.
If you ate it, you will have the
greatest power beyond imagination.
Like the ability to spit fire...
...or the power to
cause the tidal waves.
I have heard many legends,
but they are so many,
it's hard to comprehend.
I heard this treasure is sunken on
the ocean floor of the "Grand Line".
The power of that straw-hat
man must be from the devil.
Quick, hurry up!
These knots are too tight!
Hey, stop whining.
No matter who he is,
I will kill anyone who is against me!
If the bullets can't
do, kill him with swords!
Strange, it's getting tighter.
Give me the swords!
Luffy-san!
Roronoa Zoro!
Oh, cool!
Don't move or you'll die.
He's so scary!
I promise I will be a pirate.
I've fought the navy;
therefore, I am now an outlaw.
But remember this
I have to carry out my ambition.
Ambition?
I want to become the best
swordsman in the world.
If you deter me from
achieving this dream,
I will make you commit Hara-Kiri!
The best swordsman, cool!
The pirate king's partner
must have this title.
You are so arrogant.
From now, I will be famous
even if it means notorious.
What are you doing here?
Kill them now!
Crouch down, Zoro.
GOMU GOMU NO!
WHIP!
You did it! Wonderful!
What is that?
Because I ate the rubber fruit.
Rubber fruit?
He is a rubber man.
He is the powerful man
who ate the "Devil Fruit."
Captain, they're too much for us!
That guy is too strong!
We can't even fight Zoro!
Captain's orders!
Those who do not fight
must kill themselves!
I don't need cowards!
This troop got some problems.
Luffy-san!
I will vanquish this navy.
You guys have no identity or title!
You are not qualified to fight with me!
I am Naval Captain Morgan!
I am Luffy, nice to meet you.
Go to hell!
Captain!
Kid!
Die!
I don't want to.
Captain Morgan...
We can never win.
What a crab navy. It
shatters Koby's dream.
Damn!
Stop, straw-hat man, look over here!
Stop it, you moron.
Don't you see I got a hostage?
Master Helmeppo!
Hey!
If you want him to live, don't move!
I'll shoot him if you move!
Luffy-san, don't let him win!
I am easy with death.
Yes, I know that.
Give up, stupid son.
Koby is ready.
Don't move! I told you not to move!
I am going to shoot!
Behind you!
GOMU GOMU NO!
I am the Naval Captain Morgan!
Papa, kill that boy.
Pistol!
Fantastic.
Zoro.
No big deal Captain!
Captain Morgan is knocked down!
I can't believe it!
Who dare to catch us,
declare your name first.
Wonderful, wonderful!
Freedom... Viva la Navy!
What is going on? The Captain is
defeated and they seem to be happy.
Actually they are afraid of Morgan.
Zoro, what's wrong? Are you hurt?
I am starving.
Sorry, please stand still.
It is not here.
I found it! The map of "Grand Line"!
It is here.
"I have the map. Captain Buggy"
It is not a sail map. What is this sign?
Captain Buggy!
Buggy is called "the immortal body".
Ah, I am so full.
I think this is my limit. I
haven't eaten for three weeks.
You can't eat no more?
Why did you eat more than me?
It's too delicious, isn't it, Koby?
I am sorry, I ate some too.
It's OK, you saved this town.
Old brother is really something.
Of course.
I can be even better, because
I will be the pirate king.
And I got my partner now!
Tell me, who else did
you find besides me?
Didn't you say you are
looking for partners?
Since you are the pirate king,
you must have a lot of followers.
No, you are the only one.
You mean...?
Yes, just the two of us.
You call you and me are the pirate team?
What's wrong with it? We are both good.
And the Ship? Where is the pirate ship?
That one!
That one?
We will have a ship
bigger than that one!
How could it be possible?
I want a pirate flag!
Mm, it is cool!
Maybe Luffy isn't such a good planner.
And I called this man "captain"?
We will find more
partners sooner or later.
Hey you!
Big brother, what are you going to next?
Believe it or not, we are
going to the "Grand Line"!
But you have only two people!
It is impossible! Even if you are god!
Impossible! Impossible!
Is the "Grand Line"
such a terrible place?
Of course it is terrible.
You should know that there are
two big oceans in the world.
The land that divides the two
oceans is the giant "Red Line".
There is a town on the Red Line.
Go through that town, and sail around
the land in a vertical direction.
You will find the greatest
route, the "Grand Line."
It is said that the pirate king
"Gold Roger" had all the treasures.
He put the priceless
treasures on the "Grand Line".
It is the called the "One Piece."
So all the pirates wish
to go to the "Grand Line."
Now it is a terrible battle field. People
even called it "The Pirates'Graveyard".
I have heard some deaths mentioned.
Once you enter the "Grand Line",
you will never leave alive.
But "One Piece" is on the "Grand Line"!
We have to be there!
Then I can't help you.
Zoro, even you would say so!
You are not going anyway.
I'm not going, but I get worried, too!
Can we not go?
Though Luffy and I don't
know each other very long,
we are friends after all.
Aren't we?
We're going our separate ways,
but we'll always be friends!
I didn't have many
friends since childhood.
Nobody would fight for me.
Because I don't have
any strength myself.
But you two let me know that
I have to live by my faith.
I finally have the courage
to realize my childhood dream.
I will join the navy!
You were worrying about us just
now. Are you OK with you future?
What?
I was only a cabin boy on the ship.
You have stayed on the ship
for two years, that's true.
Don't give the navy
too much information.
If they know your past,
they won't let you in.
You are right...
Excuse me.
I heard that you are
pirates. Is that true?
Yes, I found a partner.
We are now a pirate team.
You saved our base and the
whole town from tyranny.
We all appreciate it.
But you are pirates.
For the reputation of
navy, you can't stay.
Please leave town.
For being just and moral, we
won't report this to the base.
Navy, what rubbish is that?
Aren't you afraid to be subjected
to the tyranny of Morgan?
Those people saved our lives!
That's right!
Ok, let's go.
Thank you, ma'am.
Big brother, are you leaving?
Yes.
Aren't you their partner?
What? I..I am...
Wait, what's the matter with you?
I know this guy did some bad things.
Luffy, you are not...
There was a really fat woman pirate,
Her name is Alvida, I guess.
Luffy-san!
If they find out that I've
been on the pirate ship,
they won't let me join the navy.
The woman pirate always carries an
iron mace and she is old and ugly!
That guy has worked for the
woman pirate for two years.
Stop it! Stop it!
Luffy-san!
Hear me, you stinky boy.
Damn! Damn! Damn!
Stop!
You can't mess around in this town!
Hey, you are too serious! Stop it now!
Now I know you are not on the same side.
Please leave now!
Hmm...
He did it on purpose...
He did it purpose!
He did it for me!
He gets me angry, and have me beat him.
I counted on his help, even at last!
I haven't changed at all.
I am a idiot...
Please let me...
Please let me... join the navy.
Even if I'll only be a cabin
boy, I will be glad to serve.
As long as I can be in the navy.
Objection, Captain!
I can't trust this guy.
We had pirates spy in the navy before.
We have to investigate you first.
I am determined to be in the navy.
Many of my friends
were killed by pirates.
Don't look down on the navy.
Then...
You are in.
Yes!
"I have the map. Captain Buggy"
You are too crazy!
It won't be strange
if we were discovered.
Koby will think of his own way.
Our sail has a nice start.
We can't look back, this
is the style of pirates.
You are right.
Luffy-san!
Thank you!
I will never forget your help!
I never heard a navy
would salute a pirate.
Goodbye, Koby!
Luffy-san.
Goodbye, big brother!
Sa-lute!
Goodbye!
I have made a good friend.
Yes.
We just saluted to the pirates.
We have broken the navy law.
All the soldiers are not allowed
to eat dinner for three days.
Did you hear me?
Yes!
One day...
One day we will reunite, Luffy.
Even though we will be pirate and navy.
One day we will reunite!
The pirate ship is going to set out.
There seem to be a great
adventure waiting for us.
I am determined to be the pirate king.
Do you have any reason for the
determination of being a pirate king?
No, no reason.
Just that I have vowed before.
I vowed to someone.
I will find the greatest partners,
and find the most treasures,
to be a pirate king.
This straw-hat knows it all.
Really?
Ok, let's go!
We are sailing to the "Grand Line"!