Do you know what the difference
Is between you and me?
Nose...
Chin...
Oh, the webs!
It's our very race!
That idiot, he'll bite off his own tongue!
His teeth must be...
He bit that column to pieces!
BURSTING OUT! MERMAN ARLONG
FEARSOME ATTACK FROM THE SEA!
See now?
This is the true power we mermen are born with!
The Heavens only gave you humans
enough strength to exist below us.
You are inferior creatures!
From the very moment we were
born, everything was different!
Allow me to show you just
how different we really are.
Sure, show me.
But I won't lose to the likes of you.
'Coz I'm the man who'll become the Pirate King!
Pirate King?
Don't make me laugh.
You think a mere human like you
can become someone like that?
Can you bite through that column with your power?
To simply bite through a solid stone column
like he did... no human could do that.
Those teeth... wouldn't just leave
scars if he got bitten...
It'd go through and break his bones, too!
So what?!
Don't try showing off... with things that don't matter!
I can break that column without having to bite it.
Oh! Well said, Luffy-aniki!
You got it! In the end, the results the same!
You're so stupid!
The whole human race is pathetic!
You can't even save yourself in the ocean.
You can't do anything!
And when I can't do anything,
I have others to help me!
Huh? He can use swords, too?
Take that, and that, and that!
What the hell are you doing now?
You're just waving them around.
I'm not interested in fooling around with you.
This is boring.
Then eat this!!
Arlong's teeth broke!
Of course I don't know a damn thing
about swords, you dumbass!
Wha... what's he talking about?
I don't know how to navigate, either.
I can't cook.
I can't even lie!
Hey.
I know that I need others to HELP
me if I want to keep on living!
You sure are useless... How pitiful.
And such a pathetic guy is their captain?
They must really resent you.
Why should they risk their lives
to save someone like you?
Someone they can't be proud of,
why should you be their captain?
What can you do?
I can beat the crap out of ya!
That goes without saying, piece of shit...
If you get yourself killed, I'll kill you.
Yeah! I'll back you up!
Yeah! All right!
Kick his ass, rubberman!
Go Luffy-aniki!
Go get him!
SHUT UP! You've got to be joking, weaklings!
Eh? His teeth grew back!
Because I'm a shark.
My teeth will grow back over and over...
with stronger ones everytime!
However many times...
As many times as I need.
This is a trait that the Heavens have given to me.
COOL!
Are you beginning to understand
just how superior I am?
TWIST GUM!
Whoa, stop that!
Luffy-aniki!
A-Arlong-san... it hurts...
M-my kinsman!
Why you, rubber bastard...
How dare you use one of my kinsmen as a shield!
What're you talking about?
You're the one who attacked him.
You had me worried there.
Stand still, rubber bastard!
Heh, I just thought of a good idea.
An idea?
What could it be?
Does he have some kind of special attack?
TWIST GUM!
They came out!
Idiot, I told you that it doesn't matter
how many times you break my teeth.
Don't you get it yet?!
Luffy-aniki, could your idea have to do with..?
Look! Now I have 'em, too!
I-It wasn't a special attack?!
I figured he'd do something stupid like that.
How long do you intend to keep fooling around?
Ah! I was bit by a shark!
'COZ YOU'RE FOOLING AROUND!
Who's fooling around? I'm dead serious!
TWIST GUM!
Bitten again!
How's that? Getting bit by your own teeth?
Sha-hahaha!
Even if they are mine...
Your jaw's far too weak!
Listen, sharks tear flesh and limbs
from the body of its prey.
That's what a shark's true power is!
No! Aniki's bones will be broken!
Luffy!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
I-Is his arm alright?
He was one step away from being eaten!
I can't imagine what it feels like to
be bitten by that beast's fangs.
Aniki's elbow, you think it's okay?
Huh? Where is he?
Luffy! In the water!
The water?
Oh! A shark!
That's ARLONG, dummy!
Huh? He dove down.
This is bad.
They grow more powerful in the water!
No one can surpass my speed in the water.
This is a special trait that only we mermen have.
Is he running away?
SHARK ON DARTS!!
What the!
A torpedo?
Something shot out from the sea!
Oh?
You dodged that well.
But dodging is just dodging, the
next one will send you to hell!
SHARK ON DARTS!!
W-What's that shark freak made of?
He even crushed the floor!
SHARK ON DARTS!!
Hey, Luffy! Hide!
He went back into the water!
Aniki, hurry and hide!
He's gonna attack again!
RUN!!
No.
What are you saying, you moron?!
You wanna just stand there and
be an easy target? Go and hide!
No!
I'm gonna break that nose of his!
Bring it on!
Sharky!
Heh. You've got guts!
Or, maybe you've finally realized
that you have no escape?
What part of ''hiding'' do you not understand, Luffy?
You just got lucky before and barely dodged it!
But if he hits you this time, you're doomed!
GOMU GOMU NO...
What's that stance?
Does he really think that'll stop him?
I have twice the distance to accelerate.
I'll pierce your heart this time!
SHARK ON DARTS!!
Stabbed!
What? Is he dead?
No, he got away in time!
I stopped your li'l trick, so I guess
you can't use it anymore!
SHARK ON DARTS!!
You dork, haven't you used enough of that?
You're finished!
Take this!
GOMU GOMU NO
Fishing! Let's fish!
And now...
YARI!
He did it!!
Good job!
Oh? Is he dead?
Arlong's eyes have changed!
That's what people said happened to the ''Sea
King's'' eyes when they were attacked...
...that he changed and went berserk!
Arlong... with those eyes... I've
never seen him like this!
You inferior human!
How did you do this to me, a merman!?
Man, that shook me up.
I don't think he's hurt, but he sure is angry.
What's that?
Kiribachi!
With huge teeth!
Luffy-aniki! Run! Watch out!
He won't stop. There,s no way out of this!
It's dangerous!!
They went inside.
Top floor... left window.
That room is...
That was close.
Now you have no where to run.
This is the top floor of Arlong Park.
Looks like your last moments have come.
What's with this room?
It's full of paper.
Not just any ordinary paper!
This is the map room.
The room for that girl to draw her maps.
The cartography room!
Nami's room?
All of them are sea maps that Nami drew for me.
It's impressive, isn't it?
Her eight years of work. My treasure.
We know the sea like the back of our hands,
but it's hard for us to make maps.
We needed a skilled cartographer.
Then I found that girl, with her talented eye!
That girl's a genius.
You won't find anyone who can
draw more accurately...
She's too good to serve you humans!
Her talent exists to serve us mermen forever!
Nami is our nakama.
Nakama?
Just stay out of our way!
You rubber bastard!
What? What's with that look?!
She's...
Nami is...
OUR NAVIGATOR!