The crowned creature!
The secrecy of Apis and the legendary island!
Is Humm… it what?
He! I see a band of birds with starboard!
Included/understood!
Wait a little…
He, come to see…
It is a young girl…
The wind arrives. A strong wind…
Since presently,
the boat does not have advanced of a hair.
Oh not… We entered Calm Belt!
Charm Belt?
It is what?
Calm Belt! It is an area where water is calm!
Nagi No kaiiki = area where water is calm
Nami No Kairiki = the superhuman force of Nami
The superhuman force of Nami?
Cretin!!
Eh? An earthquake?
An earthquake?
In the ocean?
The guy, dispatch you stop speaking to lower the veils and start to row!
Bring back we where we were!
Immediately, Nami-San!
Why one must row?
It is a bateau à voiles.
It rightly! Why one should return whereas one has just moved away from the Navy?
Listen to me, we will have
big problems if we remain here!
But the sea is so calm…
Well! I will explain you!
Listen! We summons parties with haste and we landed much more in the south that envisaged!
Therefore, we are on Grand Line?
If it were so easy to enter there, everyone would go!
Look at, Grand Line is located between two bands of ocean, Ok?
These two areas are called Calm Belt.
Nobody knows why but these two oceans have neither wind, nor current sailors.
It is simply an area CALMS permanently.
For the bateaux à voile, it is an area extremely dangerous to cross!
Luffy! You include/understand?
Yes! Just that they is not good…
I am happy that you seized!
Then, here what wanted to say the old man by saying that they was dangerous…
Therefore there is no wind.
There is nothing to make not?
We have only to wait until the wind begins again!
As I said, one will wait in vain it will not have there more the least wind!
And it is not all… It is not the only reason which makes that this zone is dangerous.
This place is…
What does it occur?
Something arrives!
Here they are!!
What is it?
Wahou! They are enormous!
ENORMOUS!!
Calm Belt is a ground of breeding of monstres marins!
And only for the large ones moreover…
This is why one cannot cross Calm Belt!
What will one make now?
For the moment, nobody moves!
We will be soon again in water…
And then… one will row thoroughly!
You pleasant!!
Why?
The frog arrives!!
Qu… Qu… What??
Caution!
Your arm is stretched!
Luffy, did you eat a Fruit of the Demon?
Ouais.
Luffy!
Drawn bar to the bottom still!
He He, Luffy!
What you insane?
I do not know!
Apis!
Pay attention!
Ok, now…
What did it make?
To tear off a hair of nose!
Wait one second…
If you do that,
this thing will sneeze!
It is an enormous hair of nose!!
Ok! One goes there!
What???
How can you be also unconscious?
Incredible! It is as if one flew!
One really flies!!
It would be said that one returned where one was.
And no sign of the Navy.
I thought that I was going to die…
Well.
Thank you!
Ok! All sails!
Our destination?
Of course,
the Gunkan island!
I do not see anything the whole.
You can see the fog!
Apis, are you sure that it is in the corner?
I do not know!
How can you say that?
That should be some share by here…
You are so strong, Nami-San!
I really do not include myself/understand…
Oh… Over there!!
Ooh, a boat
Go approach!
There is something which you do not find enormous?
Therefore, should I say that it is super méga enormous?
Not!
It is the Gunkan island!
It resembles a battleship,
this is why it is called Gunkan!
He, cool!
This boat…
Pirates!
Pirates! The pirates are there!
Pirates?
Return!
Cuckoo! I am of return!
Apis?
Why are you… on a pirate boat?
What does it occur?
He, you over there!
What do you want?
Is there a restaurant of Yakiniku on this island?
Yakiniku = roasted Meat
Hein?
Who are these guys?
Look at… Even if they are pirates,
they are good pirates.
Does that exist a pirate good?
But you had not been made remove by the Navy?
Yes! But I am flee and then
Did Luffy and its crew save me, not true?
Apis, which did you make?
I do not know why,
but the Navy sought you.
But you should not return at home.
They still trail in the corner.
Oh not…
We would like to help you but…
these guy are pirates!
Which embarrassment…
But, she said that we were good pirates.
Apis!
Come here immediately!
Who is this?
Do not know!
Bokuden grandfather!
I am content that you are well!
Thank you to have saved Apis!
I would like to accommodate you
cordially at home!
Is this… a restaurant with Yakiniku?
It is not a restaurant with Yakiniku but
Grand-père Bokuden makes best Butaman of the island!
Butaman = Sandwich with the pig
Brilliant! Allons-y!
Sure, allons-y!
It is it!
Eriiiiik!
I am with your humble service!
This girl was trapped in Calm Belt
and left itself there alive.
Impossible! This little girl?
Now, you…
Now, you will turn over on the Gunkan island!
Again capture it by all the means!
Then, they succeeded in passing Calm belt?
All is ready!
All is not prepared, we do not have any more but to wait.
Super!
That feels good!
Oh, it is sure that it is an old dish.
Will grandpa, how long that take?
Hmmm, about… 4 or 5 hours I think…
Aahh… I have if hunger!
Was Bokuden-San, why Apis kidnapped by the Navy? You know?
Do Apis, you have an idea?
At all!
But you had said to us that there was a reason of which you could not speak!
Oh, I lied!
Eh well… there is a reason.
It has just said the opposite!
There are not large thing on this island but that
could be due to our old legend.
A legend?
The inhabitants of this island are known like
descendants of Lost Island which ran it there
is 1000 years old with the height of its prosperity.
Lost Island was the country of dragons called Sennenryu.
Sennenryu = thousand-year-old Dragons
The bones of these dragons are called Ryukotsu and are supposed to give an elixir bringing the eternal life.
I include/understand…
But this legend is not a reason with the implication of the Navy.
Yes. Which is the interest of the Navy?
I do not include/understand either.
There would not be a kind of allusion in this legend?
Initially, first king de Lost Island was Iskandaq…
Ca is there! It set out again!
Now Pokepo had 3 wire.
The first wire was Bokehontasu,
the second was Bokebonbon,
and the third was Bokebokepon.
One day, the king says this to them:
“Listen to three, will seek the tree of which them
fruits are stars in the valley of the dragons. “
And thus, Bokehontasu, bokebonbon and bokebokepon left courageously to research the valley…
When it starts, one cannot any more stop it.
And then, with the 317ème generation, Yugrimori,
wire of Ingrimori III, became a large leader.
Will He, how long continue?
I do not know!
It had 18 wire. These 18 wire…
As a king, it engaged a great revolution.
I am hungry…
But this king had full children…
Highly that it finished its history!
When will one eat these Butaman?
With time, these grandchildren were born and it finished its life with 65 heirs!
Butaman…
They said that if one sent a stone on the kingdom, the princes would be wounded! He He!
Luffy?
I will piss!
Butaman…
Hold good, Ryuji.
Oh not!
It arrives! What do I make?
Please, do not come by here!
Butaman… that feels so good…
It is not true?
I did not even strike it yet!
Butaman…
And then, with the 1111ème generation, not it was
with the 1121ème, there was Hokehontasu.
A little afterwards, Nemenemetasu entered the army and thought:
“how can I protect this man?”
Oh, where do you thus go?
I worry just about knowing why
Luffy is so long! I will check.
Before the countries donot can attack, it ordered the beginning of the preparations in the kingdom.
Not just…
Nami-San is so splendid when it is furtive!
Ouf… what a relief!
Luffy!!
They have all disappeared!!
They is good!
You us did not even leave one of them!
What do you have to say for your defense?
About what you do speak?
Hein? What is it?
Where does that go?
Did that disappear?
What does it occur?
He Do Luffy, what you make?
A hole!
It seems that crossed…
Luffy?
Of course!
Ryuji?
We are behind the mountain.
Where that does it carry out us?
Ah… What is it?
Yes, I am well.
Strange pirates saved me.
Not, they are not malicious.
I have some Butaman of Bokuden grandfather for you!
Here! He, does not swallow them at the same time all!
I am afflicted, I still do not know.
I try to find of all my forces,
but I always do not have any index.
Apis… With which speaks it?
Yo Apis! With which speak you?
Do not shout abruptly like that!
Not, remain behind!
Luffy, that there is…
Hein??
Wahou! Too much cool!!
Stop! please stop!
Wait, Luffy!
It is a truth! It is alive!
Stop! Leave it quiet!
Incredible… They exist!
I believed that the dragons were right legendary animals!
Enormous! You come from where?
I see… You want to turn over at home?
Ryuji says that he is your friend Luffy.
It knows that you are somebody of nice.
Luffy, how do you include/understand Ryuji?
How that!
Like that?
You can also include/understand it not?
Not, in fact… I…
Would this be a Fruit of the Demon?
You the capacity of a Fruit of the Demon, isn't this has?
Yes, I ate the fruit Hiso Hiso!
Fruit of the whisper
Afterwards, I could listen to the heart of any animal.
It is for that you had guessed for the wind presently.
Yes! The gulls said it to me.
I also met Ryuji thanks to the fruit Hiso Hiso.
Who is this?
A so sad voice…
Ever understood anything tel.
Await me, I come to help you!
Therefore, it is you who called me?
Ryuji lost all its force and
was separated from his/her companions.
He sought only the place called
the nest of the dragons, Lost Island.
Lost Island? The island which ran 1000 years ago?
Ryuji says that the island will remake surface.
“That should be now” says it, but it
does not remember the localization of the island.
It lost all its force and its capacity to be flown but it continues to say that it wants to turn over at his place.
I want to help it but I do not have any idea
place where can be the island.
There are no indices in the old legend…
Then by chance, I asked the Navy which passed in the corner.
But I made an error.
They seek the ryukotsu.
Ryukotsu? To have eternal youth?
It kidnapped you for that, isn't this Apis?
Yes… They said to me that I were all to tell and they kidnapped me,
surely because I carried the claw into pendentive that Ryuji had given me.
Therefore you were outside in full storm.
You are caught too the head!
I know, it is for that I do not speak about it to the villagers nor with Bokuden-San.
I do not want to torment them with that.
But I want to bring back Ryuji on his lieu de naissance to any price!
Ryuji, you always say that.
If you turn over to the nest of the dragons,
you will find surely your force.
What imports time that will take,
I will find it for you!
It is sure! No matter what it arrives,
Good! In this case, I bring you to it!
Did Luffy, you listen?
She said that lost Island had run in the ocean.
But legendary Sennenryu said it.
Lost Island must be some share!
An island which isn't on any chart?
Yes! Therefore let us go there we!
An island which is not on any chart…
If you say it… Allons-y!
It is true? You are serious?
Yes!
Thank you!
Now how it is decided, take more!
Luffy! I forgot to say it to you front but…
Ryuji is a little senile!
This girl has pendentive made with a claw of Sennenryu.
Without any doubt, she knows the position of Lost Island.
Little girl who maintains the secrecy of the ryukotsu,
this time I will have you!