Ace and Luffy!
Fraternal memories and bonds
With the kingdom of the Oases,
three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
In a howl of sadness, this desiccated ground sinks from now on in an enormous wave of agitation.
After being arrived at Arabasta, Luffy and its crew…
… found themselves vis-a-vis Colonel Smoker.
But Luffy was saved just in time by…
… a man handling fire, Ace with the burning fists.
Ace is… the brother of Luffy.
Release.
Ca would astonish me.
Ace with the burning fists…
Who could have thought that somebody as would be to you the brother of Straw hat…
Is Qu- what it?
A fire!?
Not, it is not ordinary fire!
What can occur well?
A battle opposing fire and smoke?
He said to have eaten the fruit Mera Mera.
But is Luffy, it true?
Is this guy really your brother?
Ouais!
It is Ace!
I am not really surprised that you have a brother…
But what does it make on Grand Line?
Ace is a pirate.
It left our island three years before me, to launch out in the search of One Piece.
Of in any event, dispatch we to turn over to the boat.
One should leave this place before they launch out to our continuation.
You are right, Nami-San!
But I would never have thought that I would see Ace in a place like that one.
Eh, the road separates into two!
Usopp, on the left!
Included/understood everyone?
Yes! I am with you, whatever the way which you will take, Nami-San!
Ero - (Erotic):Pervert, Cook:Cook.
I have some enough of your remarks, Ero-Cook!
Brilliant!
The columns continue to grow!
A combat between fire and smoke is thus vain.
But you, isn't this knew it?
Where are the pirates of Straw hat?
They left!
And Ace too!
We lost sight of the fact them!
It is the first time that I catch up with Straw hat since I am on Grand Line.
Portgas D. Ace.
You become awkward.
Charge the provisions!
One from goes away now!
Let us dispatch!
VEIL DEPLIEE!
Eh, we finally arrived on your island.
You are sure that one should not remain here longer?
Yes, one stopped here just to get the provisions necessary.
One from now on will sail upstream of the river from here.
Then, one will put the course on Arabasta.
Our next stage is the Green City, Erumalu.
Erumalu?
Quickly!
Yes!
Do not slow down!
All is avoided!
It left!
But…
Hum!?
It is as… if we missed somebody.
It is what I think too.
And that which misses… is most important.
This… MORON!
It is odd…
Why am I only here?
Where are parties?
Eh well, you do not have the air of somebody who seeks to escape.
Yo!
Ace!
Ca made a long time, Luffy.
Yes, that made a lease, Ace.
Does Ca make how much years?
No idea.
But Luffy, you are to me always with the trace.
You did not change since you were a kid.
You either, Ace.
Ca has surprised me to see that you had eaten a fruit of the demon, but if not, you did not change.
You remember this time when you had stolen a hundred water melons to the farmer…
… and that you had spit the pips with the figure to him before fleeing!
It was not me!
It was you!
Same as you crowned one bump on the head!
It was you also, that!
I did not stop laughing.
One really did not change, both.
Ouais.
That good memories!
But…
Your crew is surely seeking you.
Ouais.
But, Ace…
What do you make here?
Hein?
What? You did not have my message with Drum?
In Drum?
Bah, drops.
It was not too important.
I have some small businesses to regulate here.
I thought that one could see oneself.
Small businesses?
I am with the Pirates of
White beard, now.
Pirates of White Beard?
It is the mark of the Pirates of White Beard.
My greater pride.
Luffy.
Does Ca say to you to join us?
Your crew is also welcome.
Not.
I was sure. It was by courtesy.
Barbe Blanche is the largest pirate whom I know.
I decided to help it to become the Lord of the Pirates.
I hope that you include/understand, Luffy.
And then? Ca will make me a person moreover fight.
I will become the Lord of the Pirates.
Eh, wood not all, Luffy!
He had to occur something downtown.
If not, all the soldiers would not have left their station…
Ca well will help me to escape to me.
Mr. 11.
To know my code name, you must work for Baroque Works.
You are “Million”?
Dispatch you to detach me!
One works well for Baroque Works, but…
One is “Billions”.
Ca wants to say that one is candidates to be of “Number Agents”.
Mr. 11.
An Agent of low level should not be much stronger than us.
Oh, I see.
I excuse myself, Billions.
Could you detach me before they return?
Would not be stupid.
If you die, one of us will become perhaps “Number Agent”.
Let us release a place “Number Agent”.
NOT!
He!!!!
Ace with the burning fists is downtown!
What?
Ace with the burning fists?
The Commander of the Second Division of the Pirates of White Beard?
If we deal with him,
one will be ensured to be of “Number Agents”!
Let us seek your friends.
If the Navy finds them, that is likely to be dangerous.
They are perhaps turned over to the boat.
In which port it is moored?
I know anything the whole of it.
What does one make then?
When you are Captain of a pirate boat,
to know where is your boat is necessary.
It does not matter, does not worry you for that.
You exchanges not.
Say to me, your crew…
How is it?
A epeist who wants to become best world in his discipline.
Haramaki:Girdle protection
It always carries a haramaki.
Our navigatrice adores the charts, the tangerines and the money.
And our cook makes us super flat goods.
There is also a liar.
And… a reindeer!
Ca does not miss diversity in this team.
In this moment, there is also a princess and a duck which has the mottled nozzle.
They are really incredible!
Me, I would bet that you are most incredible of all.
However,
that does not astonish me that you direct a small crew of pirates.
We miss just a musician.
Do not move any more, Ace with the burning fists.
As you can see it, you cannot escape.
Ace with the burning fists, your head is with us.
Prepare to die!
One should await Luffy before leaving, not?
The Navy soon will invade the port.
One must hide the boat some share.
There should be a split a little further in which we will be able to hide.
One will wait until the things are calmed.
We then will seek Luffy.
It is not true, it is necessary always that one runs to him afterwards.
You speak about a Captain…
Ace with the burning fists.
Your chance stops here.
Eh, you do not only believe…
this other type, it is… Straw hat, Luffy?
Now that you speak about it…
Its premium is of 30.000.000 Berrys!
One crowned one bowl, today!
Ace with the burning fists and Luffy with the straw hat!
When one has your heads, our chances to be promoted will be three times larger!
Let us leave to research your boat.
One should go to the beach.
Ouais.
Eh! You two!
You stop!
Us to take for imbeciles…!
KILL them!
OUAIS!
Jerk!
It is finished!
Exterminate it!
Come and test!
Attack it on all the sides!
Qu-Quoi?
Its arms lengthened!
He had to eat a fruit of the demon!
It is for you, band of dumbs!
Ca burns!
AL GO AHEAD!
The promotion of Number Agent is with us!
ALL ON THEM!
Ah, sea!
You see your boat?
You will not leave!
You donot can stop you.
Ah, it is over there!
Eh, I am there!
The guy!
Eh, Luffy. Go ahead…
He does not listen to me.
Ah, it is there!
It is Luffy!
I see it!
Be sure for you?
Ouais, it is well him.
With this air of moron…
Me… here!
Sanji-San! Tony-Kun!
And now…
There has enough.
Afflicted, Sanji, Chopper.
Jerk…!
You do not know your own force!?
I will throw you over edge!
It rightly! You caused us not badly problems!
Behave a little more like one captain.
Afflicted.
Ah I forgot Ace!
Ace?
Was your brother with you?
One should not await it?
Eh well, it will be well.
Ace is strong.
It is really strong?
Ouais, it was it already before eating the fruit Mera Mera.
I never gained when one fought!
Ace is really very strong.
You never gained? Against human normal?
The big brother of a monster could be only one super monster.
I did not stop losing…
But, if one fought today, I would gain!
Still an assertion without base.
Who is this…
You could beat me?
Eh, Ace!
Here my companions.
Oh, I am magic to meet you.
It is you who take care of my little brother.
Yes, it is that.
He does not have any manner and he must tire you per moments…
You have all my recognition.
You must surely have much things to tell us.
Come inside.
I will prepare tea.
Not, thank you. But I appreciate the invitation.
It is very surprising.
It is clear…
I thought that, according to what Luffy had said to us, this guy was going to be sure of him, arrogant…
It is a lie.
Somebody of also polished cannot be the brother of Luffy.
He was so much better than his brother!
Fraternity is a marvellous thing!
That does not have any direction.
The ocean is a place full with surprises.
Eh, eh, everyone…
Then? They are not incredible?
Works baroque!
It is the fleet of the Billions!
Ace with the burning fists and Luffy Straw hat!
One will have to you!
One will show you the power of the Billions of Works Baroque!
Still them?
Luffy.
I occupy myself some.
What will it make?
With a so small boat…
One finally will have an outline…
… of the force of the Commander of the Second Division of the Pirates of White Beard.
Bring yourself, Ace with the burning fists!
If you believe capacity to beat us, bring yourself and test!
It jumped!
FIRE!
Make fall it into water!
GE… NIAL!
Colonel Smoker!
We found neither Luffy Straw hat, nor its crew.
Tashigi, that do you think about it?
Vivi was with these pirates.
Vivi!?
Was the Princess Nefertari Vivi with the pirates of Straw hat?
Is it them hostage?
Would they have kidnapped it while hoping to make use of it later on?
Not, Vivi seemed to be free, as if it belonged to their crew.
The Princess…?
One their friends…?
As I thought it, it is woven something in this country.
Colonel Smoker!
Forgive our incompetence. The suspect,
Mr. 11, who was prisoner on our boat…
… was killed by a not identified person.
And we still did not find the pirates of Straw hat…
Do not panic.
I have my little idea on the place towards which Straw hat moves.
They have some after Crocodile.
Crocodile!?
A pirate approved by the Government…
It is one of Shichibukai, not?
I hate Shichibukai.
Especially that one.
But, it is an ally of the Government and Navy, not?
He was an extremely intelligent pirate.
It is not the kind of man to be subjected to a government, whatever it is!
It done it forever!
Tashigi, you point out that:
It does not matter how a pirate evolves/moves, it will remain always similar!
Straw hat will find Crocodile.
If we find them, the things will be cleared up.
And, when time comes, we will capture Straw hat!
They is super! Ace belongs to the crew!
KAMPAI!
Who said that?
With this delicious drink…
KAMPAI!
Do not make any you.
With food…
They always find a reason to clink glasses.
KAMPAI!
And for sand?
They are not good!
Will Ace, you really remain with us?
I am in the search of a man.
He is called Black Barbe.
Black beard?
The pirate who devastated the Kingdom of Drum?
It belonged to the Second Division of the Pirates of White Beard.
One of my men.
Until it makes the irrevocable one, for a pirate:
He killed all his team-members and fled with the boat…
As a Commander, I must find it and finish some with him.
This is why you have some after him.
The only reason which made me come in this country is that he was seen in Yuba.
One thus goes in the same city.
One is on the Sandora river.
Initially, one stops in Erumalu.
Then, one crosses the grounds of Arabasta to go here, in Yuba.
The chief of the rebels is there.
I included/understood.
You also go in Yuba.
I will go everywhere where Nami-San and Vivi-Chan will go!
Drop, Love Cook.
What you said ace, jerk?
IN ANY EVENT.
It would be said that you will travel with us for a small moment.
With you at our sides, one will be in safety.
In our voyage, Ace!
OUAIS!