Two blows per front and three by behind.
I do not know what it occurred in this room, but it is horrible.
Breaking news!
All fresh!
Anyone, I will never forgive him!
Get stuffed, Luffy with the Straw hat!
Is this your answer to have taken to you your 200 million?
Unforgivable!
Do not be timid, listen to all!?
Acclaim me!
Show yourself, Straw hat!
The man Gomu Gomu VS
The cyborg with the breath of fire
Show yourself, Straw hat!
You are inevitably in the corner, Luffy with the Straw hat!
What? This degenerate knows my name.
Haven't people not just called it “Franky”?
Then it is of its fault…
It is of its fault if Usopp is…
This money is with us maintaining.
RETURN the-ME!
It is…
Luffy.
Oi! The puppet in slipway!
He, Luffy.
Hein?
It is me, Luffy!
Still not of news?
How is it?
You all.
Kalifa.
Made not noise while entering.
Then…
Iceberg-san returned to him.
Brilliant!
They is marvellous!
Iceberg-san!
Maaa, sorry to have caused you concern.
It does not matter, they are good to re-examine you alive.
You rest a little.
One deals with the building site while waiting.
In connection with…
Those which returned in my room…
The investigation is in hand.
Not, I remember.
They were two.
A giant with a mask, and the other…
Was a woman with the long brown hair.
No doubts…
This glance sinks…
Begun again knowledge
Iceberg-san…
Iceberg-san regained consciousness!
Really?!
Thank you my God!
Brilliant!
Youpi!
Es you Luffy with the Straw hat?
You did not go there with hand died during my absence, small.
I did not believe my eyes of them while returning.
My house was not any more in the same state as with my departure.
And you put my men in a sorry state.
Pay to.
I am unchained this week!
And a thing is sure…
This anger will not be calmed as much as I will not have reduced to you in dust!
He!
, Where is to you our money? The 200 million berrys.
Return it to us!
Hein? The 200 million berrys?
I very spent, I am dry.
Do not make any you for the dough…
Since it was dirty money, pirate!
Nothing with foutre!
It is about OUR money!
In any event, I will not be able to calm myself…
As long as I will not have you boot the bottom!
It is me which will not calm me, merdeux!
Oi! Go down immediately!
It is foutu, Franky will break out!
With the shelter! All with the shelter!
Flee!
What it fout?
It spits of fire!
How it does that?
You ace never considering a guy to spit of fire?
Perhaps it has the capacities of a fruit?
Which fruit?
What?! This dumb jumped to water!
He is stupid?!
If it has the capacities of a fruit of the demon, it will drown.
It had to slip.
It has the capacities of a fruit which makes spit fire.
It is which this guy?!
He can swim?!
I did not eat any fruit of the demon!
GOMU GOMU NO…
I heard of tone capacity.
STRONG RIGHT!
What?
Luffy!
What? It was what that?
You do not know?
Then I will explain you…
I am a man-robot…
A cyborg.
The crew of Straw hat?
It is true?
Yes.
I carried out my survey.
I asked Lucci confirmation near the government.
Then…
Ouais, when I contacted the government…
They affirmed me that it belonged to the crew of Straw hat.
They are thus them them guilty…
The crew of Straw hat.
Why? By vengance that one doesnot can repair their boat?!
Nobody knows.
It does not matter the reason, one is sure that it is them.
We will be able to ask them after having caught them.
I wonder which excuse they we will give…
One will return to you what you merits, Straw hat!
Continue to seek Robin-chan, Chopper.
Sanji, say to me…
Aqua Laguna must be terrifying.
Yes, all the city will be submerged.
I know somebody who is perhaps not with the current which the high tide arrives.
Perhaps…
Then, of the horrible things could arrive at its boat.
Not, then…
He Sanji…
Chopper.
With the fact, didn't you say to have forgotten something on Merry?
Not?
Then it is foutu.
Await us! One returns to seek you!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
OOOIIII!! It IS HORRIBLE!!
YOU DO TOO MUCH NOISE, TILESTON!
Bandage insolents! Remain quiet please!
ICEBERG-SAN! GOD THANK YOU, YOU ARE AWAKED!
You do too much noise.
You do nothing but worsen his state.
It IS TRUE!! I AM SORRY!!
I HAD FORGOTTEN! It IS HORRIBLE! LISTEN TO me!
Do not return. Tell here.
The PIRATE WITH the STRAW HAT SE BEATS WITH FRANKY WITH the N°1 DOCK!!
It IS the BROTHEL WITH the BUILDING SITE!
Straw hat…
Iceberg-san!
It has base to be shown over there.
You, Iceberg-san rest.
I remain near you.
GUN!
Made blunder! Ca collapses!
The boat will fall in ruins!
Stop! Why you made that?!
Luffy! Boot me the bottom of this puppet in slipway!
Aniki!
You beat!
No matter what it arrives…
I will botterai you the bottom!
Test! Your attacks do not have any effect on me!
WEAPONS LEFT!
GOMU GOMU NO…
MUCHI!
What?! What did it occur?
Ah, it is…
It is which?
It is what this behavior?
What tests you to make, Straw hat?
Do Galley it, what you foutez there?
Engineers of the Dock n°1!
Youpi! The engineers finally arrived!
It was time, a little more and the building site was in ruin.
Brilliant, they are the carpenters of yesterday.
They are on our side.
Oh oh! The small ones of Galley it!
It is not well to mix with the businesses of the others!
You are likely to hurt you!
How oses you to speak to us on this tone?
When our building site is damaged like that…
One is obliged to intervene.
OUAIS, FRANKY!
HOW HOPE YOU TO PAY FOR ALL THAT??!
Wait, Tileston.
One will see that later.
For the moment, there are more important things.
He, Luffy with the straw hat.
You us, isn't this remembers?
How oses you still to show you here?
What? One learned the news for Ossan and…
Doesn't my house have is enough to you, you also muddled itself with Galley it?
In full crisis of adolescence to muddle you with all people that you are to you meetings?!
I SAY to YOU THAT I MADE AI NOTHING!
You can play the innocent one as much as you will want!
ROTATION HALF KNOT
Ca hurts!
Badly…
AIR DRIVE
SPECIES Of DUMBS!
YOU DO NOT HAVE TO INTERFERE YOU THAT?!
It IS ME WHICH MUST REGULATE ITS ACCOUNT to HIM!
Show them, Galley it Company!
Five stronger from the docks go battrent themselves!
He?! Why the carpenters are our enemies?
Oh! Oh!
Oi, wait!
I do not have any reason to fight against you!
This guy…
With capacities.
He, guy! You does listenings not when one speak to you?
I said…
He is with me!
There are not time to lose with you, Franky!
What, it is what this species of monkey?!
YOU DISTURB US, FRANKY!
Tileston is too strong!
It is the montrueuse force of Tileston!
Stop!
They are really strong.
Shit.
You made what? Say to me at least why!
Straw hat, it is we who would like to know.
The criminals who entered the office and who attacked Iceberg-san…
It was you, hein?
Never!
Such a thing…
These guys interfere in my combat…
This person, it was Nico Robin.
Was the giant one of them?
Initially, why would they have attacked me?
I cannot believe that it is by vangeance.
They are probably in the search of this thing which I hold.
Would there be a bond between the government and these pirates?
Or do they seek it for them-even?
Straw hat…
Scoop… The last scoop!
The name of the culprit appears in the deposition of Iceberg-san!
Really?!
We must inform the city and put them of it out of state to harm!
Do not let them escape from Toilets 7!
Catch the culprits!
The persons in charge of the aggression of Iceberg-san are…
Pirates of Straw hat.