And on my line…
Originating in East-Blue, it is the captain
of small but frightening crew…
Its head is worth 100 million berrys…
Called the Straw hat!
MONKEY D. LUFFY!!
And to crown the whole, Luffy covered
the Afro cut to enter on the scene!
Go ahead Luffy!
It is which him?
The gong sounded!
Here me is!
Y' has that my hand which is slowed down!
I would not do that in your place!
That one either.
I had warned you…
Luffy…
It is not possible…
NORO NORO BEAM WITH FULL THROTTLE
VS LUFFY the INVULNERABLE one
Oh! What a impressive explosion!
When it is thought that the boat is
become the battle field by chance…
And that these Foxy Face Bombs have
summer left there by sheer coincidence!
“By chance”? It is prohibited what they did!
Dirty cheaters!
Hey Luffy! How is what occurred?!
calm you…
The bombs were judiciously
used by our Oyabin…
to trap Luffy with the Straw hat
in an enormous explosion!
Thin… Luffy is…
Would this be the end?
I do not see it any more…
Waaa… it was less one!
Yes, it was really a dangerous attack.
What you ace you? The farm!
One would say that Luffy to the Hat
of Straw is always in life!
Serious?
Frightening…
It had to escape right before the explosion!
What a incredible speed!
It is thus that, the force of a man of which
is the head worth 100 million berrys?
Of course how it is that!
Hurry to finish it!
Wait! It would be said that Oyabin
prepare one second offensive!
That made cold in the back, the voice of Oyabin resounds
through the smoke of the explosion…
By where it will attack?
Which Foxy plan the Silver fox
it has scheme against its adversary?!
His shade is seen!
Then? You ace fear now hein?
You exploded yourself all alone?!
OF COURSE THAT NOT!
BA-KA!!
LIAR!!
Dumb! I will not let myself leave this alive boat!
I will break you the arm so that
you donot can use this ray any more!
It is turned over in this smoke…
Be to you thus there!!
It is what this trick?
Then? Where am I?
From where the ray will leave?
How I would know it?
They have all of the heads of morons!
Head of moron…
I found you!!
DUMB!!
You ACE NOT OF HEART OR WHAT?!
I will never forgive myself it! Look at up there!
Shit! A trap door!
You do not should have looked at elsewhere!
It IS YOU WHO Me ACE KNOWN AS TO LOOK IN TOP!
You would make better remain on your guards…
Hum? Hein? What…
Ah! But the ground moves!!
Hey, it is Luffy!
What does it make over there?
Oh not! If it falls to water it is foutu!
You do not believe nevertheless who I will fall so easily!
It was right!
The spectacle would have been wasted
if that had finished like that!
Go ahead thoroughly, Straw hat!
But it is what this boat?! Fact of shitting!
Where you hide, salts fox?!
Oh! While Luffy with the Straw hat
was not there, Foxy addressed an invitation to him!
It is there!
Oyabin will succeed in it cramming Luffy
with the Straw hat towards the interior?
Luffy, does not go there! It is surely a lure!
There are other traps inside!
What a dumb! I go him botter the bottom!
Luffy seems to accept the invitation.
They are now inside the boat!
I cannot return there, therefore we will not know
not what occurs! It is pure combat!
The true combat with death will be able to start!
Move! Move, Luffy!
Do not forget your intensive drives!
Close and sit down it, you see more anything.
The room of the guns?
It is really large…
Usopp would have liked to see that.
Where you cushy jobs?
Ah! Over there!
Yosh, they is good it will come…
It will insert the door at full speed…
And then, it will be cooked!!
It will be made transpierce in this room filled with peaks!
Then, you will come or N
Ah. You stays there.
It is what this room?
HEALTHY PEOPLE Of SPIRIT DO NOT DRAW
PAS AU CANON DANS UN BATEAU!!
Ah. It returns.
You will pay it expensive to me!
You will see of what a wood I heat yourself!
Ah! He flees!
Wait!!
Well, it will come here and I will be able to finish some!
Well… “Foxy Shichihenge”…
[Shichihenge:Disguise]
Wait, fox!
A lady?
Ma~! What is there?
You have some share badly?
Where do you have badly? With the head?
Does your head hurt you?
What… did you see somebody passing?
Not, not really. But more important…
Where do you have badly?
With the face?
Really odd… I was sure…
He, wait a little…
This lady resembled to him bloody!
Not possible!
HE YOU!! TU SERAIS PAS SA SISTER?!!
Imbecile!!
But it is what that?!
It is super odd!
Then it had really entered this room…
He wants to fight or not!?
Oh! Kitchen!
Cut bienz the poiz-zon, cut it, cut to it bienz…
Make-Zen of the carpazzio… vinegar and zucre…
And eat morzeau by morzeau…
Huh? You zavez hunger?
You would not have seen large weak with
a head of puzzle by chance?
It is too for me…
It IS YOU!!
The nurse, it was me too!
PAS POSSIBLE!!
Et~ merde~!
Do not imagine that I made you come up to now without reason.
You know what there is in this room?
I you will show it… it is not alive, however.
It would be contrary with the rules, is not this step?
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
MUGIWARA-TEAM
When the effects of Noro Noro Beam stop…
the energy accumulated by my fists will create an explosion.
Go, go away.
It is here that your voyage is completed.
The 30 seconds are past.
It left…
If it is me whom you seek, I am just there!
Luffy.
It is what this odd behavior?
I am Foxy the pilot!
Let to me present itself…
“Gorilla Puncher N 13”.
This ultimate “Gorilla Puncher” is the result
of long series of improvements.
And it is you the mug of gorilla!?
ronche of gorilla L Mug of gorilla L
Mug of gorilla L
You had me!
The farm!
Deal with your business!
Ahead, “Gorilla Puncher N 13”!!
How it makes to advance this trick?
This machine is excellent!
It must sweat like an ox.
Buckle it!
You undoubtedly believe yourself able
to dodge its punches, not truth?
You aim who, there?
Look behind you!
The dumb! A mirror!
Eh yes! My rays are reflected in the mirrors!
I hold you!
I touched you? I touched you?!
I forgot to say to you that the fists
of this machine could ignite.
Even a monstre marin would be made cramer!
It was right a heating!
This time it left!
Admire Noro Noro Coach Training!
I see! It is like that the other
man-fish deviated the rays.
Fact of shitting… if I could approach me…
Always try to avoid it,
you will nevertheless finish flaring or crushed!
Yes!
I NEVER HAD THINK HAS THAT!!
WHAT?!
Species of imbecile!
It is the final combat of
return match of Davy Back Fight…
and we do not have any idea of
what occurs inside.
But it is certain that a duel without pity proceeds there!
The spectators encourage our Oyabin!
It cannot lose.
Obviously! Luffy carries a Afro cut…
Even all alone, Luffy can finish some with this asshole.
What does it have of so special, this Afro cut?
It returns it really more extremely?
That takes more time than usually.
It is because it is out of rubber.
It is out of rubber and with a Afro cut.
What does it have of so special this Afro cut?
Luffy will recover us, I am sure…
Cavity… It carries a Afro cut.
Even Robin…?
Oh! There is agitation on the bridge!
Where is the combat?
Is there already a winner?
I see two shades!
That of Oyabin is upright!
OYABIN!!
Straw hat on the other hand is burned with sharp.
It had to box serious punches.
Luffy!
Impossible…
How punches did can burn it?
What did it occur?
Luffy!
Look at…
Luffy with the Straw hat was raised!
Whereas everyone believed it K.O. !
You hold hardly upright, Straw hat.
Drunk Brother… A Afro truth…
Put it at the carpet, Oyabin!
Here my Noro Noro Beam Sword!
Now, you cannot any more
to move neither your arms nor your legs!
Thus try to see…
If you can it…
Thirty seconds…
This time it is finished…
Not, not yet!
Luffy!
Luffy with the straw hat is raised!
This type is incredible…
It is Afro! The capacity of Afro made it wild!
Which embarrassment…
Take that!
It is unjust! This ray should be prohibited!
Usopp…
This time…
It is tiring to strike like that, you know…
It is more one combat, it is torture!
Still?
Still…
Luffy!
I…
will beat me…
for my companions…
UNTIL DEATH!!!
It is… It was still raised!
LUFFY WITH THE STRAW HAT!!