It is…
A trap! The Navy their tightened a trap!
The guy!
Usopp!
Ahead!
What?!
Does a boat pirate which goes down from the mountain?
Ossan!
Where the treasure of the island is!
Pirates of Zenny, With the attack!
It is him.
Played well, Ossan!
Oi, Oi, do not exaggerate.
Its heart probably stopped from now on.
Hey, how can you say a similar thing?
Jii-san! Is all well?
I finally left at sea.
I really became a pirate!
It is that! It is not my coffin!
It is an authentic pirate boat, Zenny!
It is not true?
It is that, Ossan!
Does not encourage it!
It is sick!
What is it that, Zenny the praetor on pledges?
It is not your work to take the money of these pirates?
I stopped being a praetor on pledges years ago.
Now I am Zenny the Pirate!
Do not laugh in front of the Navy, species of insane old man!
Jii-san, made attention!
It has some after your treasure!
Oh? Thus now instead of catching pirates,
Was the Navy put at hunting for the part-time treasures?
What assiduous men!
Nami, brings back the boat.
Of agreement! That everyone follows me.
Species of bastard! Do not give orders to Nami-san!
Minche sergeant! The crew of the straw hat prepares to do something!
Call the fleet of the Moore Captain in reinforcement!
Your mouth!
Didn't I say you that I was going to give you a share of the treasure?
You, isn't this includes/understands?
The Captain should not know about what occurs here.
Let us see seeing.
Thus for a part-time work, you would kill your subordinate.
You must be done full of money, Mister the Sergeant.
Species of old waste.
Do not believe that you will leave yourself there alive!
Your mouth, kid!
You have base to try to steal the treasure of a pirate!
Take it if you can!
Quite known as, Ossan!
Show him how the pirates fight!
Yosh!
IDIOT!
It was what the goal of that?
Bastard…
If you are a pirate, in this case that will not be done anything to be killed by the Navy!
Does Hey, this old man have weapons?
I of insane who you are Navy!
I will show you competences of a counting frame 10th daN!
With the attack!
A counting frame and…
… goats!
What?! It has problems!
Ossan!
What a stunned!
Luffy!
Bandage cretins! What did you aim?
You should not waste your ammunition!
I am just there! And here me is!
What you make?!
They are goats! GOATS!
We have a problem because precisely they are goats, Sergent.
Hey! The combat already started!
Why not descend and take a little pleasure?
Quickly! Quickly! Quickly!
I know. Move just a little.
Calm you, Chopper!
But…
Jii-san is not in good condition for this type of things!
Fire!
Do not draw!
As soon as my guy are irritated, one cannot any more stop them!
With the attack!
Oi, Oi, look at them!
They were put in position!
They are only awaiting us!
Odd… They do not seem to move.
We must think of a plan as long as we still can it.
Good, what does one make?
Do we have to attack in first?
That is to say not insane!
We must go to help Jii-san immediately!
Does Hey, one have not just run up against something against the moment?
Good Ah?
You dispatch!
Moore captain! There is no answer on behalf of the boat of the Minche Sergeant.
Which was this shot?
Do we have to advance?
Not, not yet.
Await the report/ratio of Minche.
Where are you all gone?
Bandage vermins! I have enough you of it!
It is enough!
Yosha!
What did it arrive at your bravery, Zenny the Pirate?
Lacks breath?
Thus you are finally descended, species of hooligan.
What a large mouth!
Why one would not finish any immediately.
Where is the treasure, Zenny the Pirate?
What did you say, Caporal-chef?
Why didn't you finish yet of it?
Yes!
I am terribly sorry, Capitaine Moore.
This small dumb.
He thus had some after that.
Why cowards you not the piece?
You do not want to die immediately, not?
Of course that I want to live.
I really want it.
But I said it to you. I do not have a round.
What am I to suppose to release?
I am too poor to spit.
Well.
In any event, the island is rather small.
Ca will not take much time to turn over each centimetre of ground.
You are not to me any more any utility now.
Species of small…
It is the end!
I broke your counting frame.
Afflicted.
What you insane brothel?!
Do you think that you can flee easily after being gone against the Navy?!
Jii-san!
You are late the guy!
I was about to die!
We were so anxious on your subject.
KE \ko72}SHI
[Note:Star of smoke]
Ca will be enough amply.
Was Robin, you there?
You do not worry Jii-san!
Capitaine Usopp is there!
What occurred? You have a large bump!
He does not have pulse!
Calm you, Chopper.
It is by here.
I know!
You put at ease! You sleep!
Will not die, Jii-san!
I am not dying.
How do you feel, Jii-san?
I feel very well.
I finally became a pirate.
I feel more alive than ever.
We came on this island only because the Sergeant had given the order of it.
I see. I suppose that the subordinates must obey the orders.
Our Captain is also very egoistic.
Really?
You are not supposed to make you friends.
Oi, Ossan. You are well?
Are YOU well?
Frankly Luffy, you are really useless!
The attacks grew blurred. You should be well for the moment.
Thank you, Dr. Chopper.
Afflicted.
Ossan. It was advantageous?
Not too badly.
Now…
Then Ojii-chan, can you speak to us now about the treasure?
Hey! Do not make start my patient!
Jii-san, hold good!
I think that you had me.
Well.
You all enormously helped me.
I suppose that I can speak to you about it.
It is what I wanted to hear!
Ca must be really a very large treasure so even the Navy know it.
I had a treasure.
I had a mountain of treasures which I had taken to the pirates of compensation.
Then I thought that it was time to repurchase my pirate boat and to start to gather a complete crew.
Thus, I changed it into argent liquide.
Argent liquide!
While reconsidering there, I suppose that to flee with was my destiny.
Last night, I said to you how I had failed on this island…
… after having escaped with some pirates to which I had recovered the money, isn't this?
Of course, I took the money with me.
This money was for my dream and I risked my life to reach it.
But when I awoke after being swept on the beach…
They ate it?!
Really?
All?! All money?!
Ouais.
Some tickets have being saved.
It is for that which I say that they represent my treasure.
My fortune flew away, but now I have a crew.
They will never disappoint me nor will not put a stab in the back to me.
They help me without never thinking of the profit, and they will be always with my with dimensions.
I would like to return the similar one in kindness to them.
I now have the most beautiful treasure of the world.
It is brilliant, Ossan!
Ouais, it is brilliant.
Even when I stumble, I am never raised the empty handeds.
Rubbish!
Hey, Straw hat!
This combat is not finished yet!
An unscathed fleet waits just there low!
You will not flee easily!
Is not so proud whereas you from go away while rolling.
Is he cretin?
It is you the cretins!
Do you think of having a small chance against a fleet of nine boats?
I will not flee.
Will say to them that they come, if they want to fight!
GOMU GOMU NO!
Hey Luffy, aims at very small little higher.
Of agreement!
GUN!
Straight towards the target.
You…
You are the shame of the Navy!
Take it along!
Well!
I am the Moore Captain of the Navy.
I do not may find it beneficial any to capture this man, Zenny, which lives on this island.
My only goal is to catch you, in the name of justice.
However, to thank you for having given to us the vermin of our body,
I will let to you decide place of battle.
Now, put the veils!
We were precisely thinking of leaving.
We will go soon towards you.
And here is, Jii-san. I repaired that for you.
Thank you very much.
You do not worry for that.
I prepared your meal.
All that it remains you to do, it is to cook it.
Ah. Thank you.
But you them will guy, that go?
You nine boats, isn't this will fight?
You do not worry for us.
I am not only strong. I am also very lucky.
I suppose that I am not size against you, Nii-chan.
Jii-san, I have make a large package of drugs.
Do not forget to take them.
Do not forget!
Well, well.
I will take them, do not worry you.
It was amusing, Ojii-chan.
Take care of you!
Hey the guy! Take care of the old man!
With later on the seas!
Ouais!
I take the sea as soon as I repair the boat!
We will await you, the Pirates of Zenny!
Ok, let us turn over on the island.
We need to repair the boat.
Well, everyone. Go down, we return to the house.
If I want to be a pirate, that does not disturb the age which I have, not?
They really know how to excite an old man.
And this Chopper works really hard.
How much years that T it will take to me to finish these drugs?
Thank you. Thank you very much, everyone.
I think that I could be able to live a little longer.
I want to say, my life of pirate have just started.
Us to take along in the corner of the rocks covered by the fog?
It is an good idea, Luffy.
You your brain occasionally, isn't this uses?
Really?
“Really?” I ask you!
It is the fleet of Moore!
Any boat of the Navy, answer!
Ask an immediate assistance!
What a idiotic!
I am afflicted, I made you a compliment! Return it to me!
To return what?
It is impossible that it planned as much.
It was right chance, it is that?
It just showed any direction.
Moreover, Mr. Doctor.
Without lying, that do you think of the condition of the old man?
These drugs can only anticipate the attacks.
They will not look after its disease.
First of all, its heart is weak, and it is rather old.
It should not travel on board a boat, nor to become a pirate alone.
About what you do speak?
If Ossan wants to become a pirate, us should let it make.
And if it goes at sea,
It will be able to perhaps find a remedy for its disease.
You think?
Of made you not as much.
This old man will not die so easily.
Even by knowing that it is weak, it is rather energetic.
It is true, Chopper.
We will still re-examine it.
Yes, it is true.
We will wait!
Pirates of Zenny!
www.rival-spirits.com
http://www.zento.fr
www.saiyajin-team.com
www.kyubi-wolf.net
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/rival-spirits
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/zento
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/saiyajin
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/Kyubi-Wolf
CYB3RFR34K-ISO