GOMU GOMU NO...
BAZOOKA!!!
No problem, 'coz my hands and feet are still free!
What!?
This time...
It's all over!
You still can't do anything about that kid's 'spear'.
I know a fool,
Who got attached to that 'spear'
for his own stupid reasons.
All Blue!
I'm the strongest!
Don Krieg...
We've lost.
Commander!
Thanks for everything, Sanji-san.
Give him this message for me when he gets up...
I may only have a few hours left in me.
It's kinda weird for me declaring this,
just because I'm running out of time,
but this time, I'm going to do what I want to do.
Trusting my instincts.
Then I won't have anywhere to run anymore.
When your mind's made up, you eventually
pay less attention to things like,
Being scared of a strong enemy,
or how not to hurt yourself.
That's what he taught me.
See ya.
I'll be taking this.
I don't have to return it, do I?
Nope.
Try if you dare, small fry.
Hey! Drive this into your head!
This is the fighting sea restaurant, Baratie!
A strange restaurant indeed...
DEPARTURE!
SEA CHEF AND LUFFY TRAVEL TOGETHER
Ah! My hat?!
Where's my straw hat?!
Isn't it right there?
Oh yeah.
Feel all better now?
Eh? Where'd they go?
They're gone.
Thanks to you.
Me?
''We might meet again at the Grand
Line,'' was what Gin said.
Gin, eh?
He told you that?
He meant you!
Oh yeah!
Since I kicked 'em out,
guess I'm off the hook with all the work here?
Congratulations.
But, about you...
I'm not going.
I don't want to be a pirate.
I'm staying here to continue being a cook,
until that old fart acknowledges my cooking skills.
I see.. I'll give up then.
Your hand isn't giving up!!
I can't go.
They're all unreliable around here.
But I'll go there someday.
...Grand Line.
Then, let's go now!
Not now.
Hey!
Have you ever heard of ''All Blue''?
Nope.
What? You haven't?!
It's a mystical sea!
In that sea,
fish from all over - East Blue, West Blue, North
Blue and South Blue, can all be found there!
It's like a wonderland for cooks like us!
And it's in the Grand Line!
So, have you heard of it?
He looks so damn happy.
Fool.
Lunch time, boys!
Finally, some grub!
Food, food, food!
Hey, where are we sitting?
Where's the food?
We didn't save a seat for you.
Eat on the floor, the floor.
No seat?
How can that be?
This is a restaurant for crying out loud!
Oh well...
They're acting weird.
It's what they always do.
Hey!! Who in the world made the soup this morning?
It's me! Me!
Pretty good, eh?
Today's is even more exceptional.
I could hardly swallow this piece of crap!
It's only fit for pigs!
Hey. You never tasted 'human'
food before, crappy cook?
You're turning this awful cooking into an art form.
I'm about to puke!
Excuse me, but I'm very confident
with what I made today.
Is something wrong with your tongue?
It's disgusting!!!
i can't take this at all!
Right, everyone?!
How can we eat this?
The soup's super horrible!
We can't drink up this crap!
This is just awful. Can somebody
get me some water?
What're you bastards up to?
You're just a phony chef assistant.
You've just been around a while, that's all.
We're tired of your violent behavior!
It tastes so bad, we just had to say it aloud.
What did you say?!
We're cooks of the sea.
We can't afford to waste even a single drop of soup.
Owner!!
Old man?!
What's up with this disgusting soup of yours?
Do you intend to shut this restaurant
down or something?
Stop kidding around, old fart!
Tell me what makes your soup
and mine any different!
Tell me!
Between mine and yours?
Don't be so conceited!
The boss didn't kick him, but punched him!
You're a hundred years too young
to compare to me, lil' eggplant!
For I am the man who has cooked on
all of the seas, all over the world.
Damn it!
Damn old fart.
I... I...
i'm no li'l eggplant no more!!
This soup's great!
I know so.
Sanji's cooking is revered by everyone here.
It doesn't taste bad at all.
Yeah, it's well made.
Man, that was scary, he seemed pretty mad.
Yeah, he was.
But, if we didn't pull this off, he'd never leave,
That stupid brat.
Hey kid!
You mentioned that you needed
a cook on your ship, right?
I'm not trying to force you or anything,
but that li'l eggplant of ours,
Care to take him with you?
To the Grand Line.
The Grand Line is what he's always dreamed about.
You see, the boss is a real troublemaker.
I was worried for a sec with your crappy acting.
Not to mention yours.
Another helping of soup please!
Me too! Me too!
I can hear everything, you damn bastards.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
How 'bout it, kid?
No.
What?!
Didn't you say you need a cook on your ship?
Or do you not like the guy?
It's nothing like that. I want to take him with me,
But he said that he wanted to stay here as a cook.
I can't take him along even if you guys insist.
So you're saying that you can't do anything
about it unless he says ''Yes''?
Exactly. Seconds please!
Yeah, that's obviously best.
But that peculiar kid, would he just
admit that he wants to go?
Not a chance.
He's a stubborn son of a gun.
Seconds please!
Damnit...
Sanji?
Who's he?
A merman?
He came all the way from a
merman island to eat here!?
Idiot!
It's just somebody in a shark's jaw!
Hm? What's going on?
Eh, Yosaku?
Oh, Luffy-aniki!
Why are you the only one here?
Where's everybody else?
Where's Nami?
We didn't catch up with her.
But from the direction she was headed,
we roughly knew her destination.
Humm... Why didn't you bring her back then?
Well, about that...
If her destination really is...
where we calculated,
it'd be a dangerous place.
Anyways, we need your help.
Please come with me!
Yosh!
I don't really get it... but I get it!
Let's go!
Wait.
All of us hold on to foolish dreams.
I'm gonna do this for my own dream, for All Blue.
Sanji?
As you wanted, I'll go with you.
On this ''Road to the Pirate King''
Allow me take up the position
of cook aboard your ship.
You got a problem with that or what?
YEESS!!!
Great!
Isn't this great, Luffy-aniki?
Yay! Yay! We got our cook!
We'll always have something to eat now!
So that's it, people.
I gave you a lot of trouble, didn't I?
Man, you piss me off.
I wanted to throw you out of here myself,
But now things turn out to be easy.
Well, I'm sorry...
That's what you get for putting on
such an appalling performance.
Wha- you figured us out?!
You couldn't be any more transparent.
You're all morons.
What?
So you guys really want me outta here, eh?
Eh, old fart?
What's with that foul-mouth of yours?!
That's right, you li'l eggplant.
I hate kids!
I regret every passing day that
I let you live, ungrateful kid.
That's just nice, old fart.
Now you can sit back and relax
for the rest of your life.
Oh! Nice ship there!
You sure we can use this?
It's Sanji's, so of course you can.
Aren't you done yet?
Nope, more meat please.
How many days are you gonna be sailing?
Dunno.
Kid!
Oh, old man.
You want this?
It's my journal during the year
i ventured the Grand Line.
Don't need it!
Thought so.
I want that frozen beef up there!
Can't you cut it out!?
Awesome!
Old fart, so this is our floating restaurant?
Hey, Sanji...
Eh? What?
No matter what kind of bad guy,
even if he's a fugitive,
as long as they're bastards who come here to eat,
Then our struggle here would be meaningful.
We'll be very busy from now on.
No problem, 'coz I'm here!
Gimme a break...
The peel's still too thick! Li'l eggplant!
That hurts!
You should watch quietly when people are focused on their cooking!
Who do you think you are?
You li'l eggplant!
I'm no li'l eggplant, you old fart!
Try it!
Did you make this yourself?
And?
Man, this tastes awful, li'l eggplant!
Why... you old fart!
Cook-aniki's rather slow, isn't he?
This is the fury I've accumulated for years!
Prepare yourself, Sanji!
You can never beat him.
Let's go.
You sure? No goodbyes?
Nah.
Sanji!
Don't catch cold now...
OWNER ZEFF!
All this time,
I owe you a hell of a lot!
What you've done for me,
I shall never forget!
You damn bastard!
I'm gonna miss you, damnit!
Gonna miss you alright!
This is so sad!
I'm so sad, damnit!
You morons!
Men should just leave without saying a word.
Let's go!
'Til we meet again, you freakin' bastards!
With the belief and refusal to die,
They will find All Blue.
Alright men! Customers will be flooding in soon!
Get back to work!