As usual, your reputation's pretty bad.
No surprise. I am pirate after all.
But Arlong understands me...
Just a little bit more and I can
fulfill my part of the bargain.
No matter what, I'll collect that 100 million beli...
...and buy the village!
USOPP'S DEATH?!
LUFFY YET TO LAND?
Go! To Arlong Park!
Wait for me! Nami!
Let go! Let me go!
Not yet? You still haven't caught
that long nosed guy?
A common human!? Dares
to challenge us mermen!?
We're returning. To Arlong Park...
Damn! I can't outrun them?
Where'd he go?
Anyone who thinks Usopp-sama shouldn't
die yet, should raise their hands now!
Yes!
Idiot! What is he thinking?
You people think so too eh?
Me too!
What?
Killing move!!
TAMAGOBOSHI!
It stinks! This sucks!
How's that!? Mermen aren't that great.
No matter what Captain Usopp will always escape!
Crap...
I wasn't aware I'd reached the beach already!
Come this way! We've got him!
There's nothing here.
Were we mistaken?
That guy does run really fast.
Lets look elsewhere.
Thank god...
I don't know!
Telling lies won't do you any good.
Huh? What? What the?
Thanks for cheering me on!
As you can see I'm fine...
Perhaps a little too fine?
That's true...
Too slow.
When's Luffy gonna come?
If he doesn't come in the next 5 minutes,
I'm going to die of boredom!
Oooh oooh oh! This one's awesome!
Even I, a member of Arlong's elite,
Hachi-Hatchan can't pull it up.
It must be a super great fish!
I don't know from where you've come
but your gusto is East Blue's best...
Wh..What the? What?
Oh it was myself.
Truly, my gusto is East Blue's best.
Truly, my gusto is East BIue's best.
Anything strange?
Definitely strange.
Huh? Who the heck are you?
M-Me?
I'm Hatchan. Call me Hachi.
Are you a merman too?
Of course! Of course!
I'm a charming octopus merman.
Do I look like a human?
I guess not...
Are you with the Marines or just a guest?
Guest?
Yeah, I'm a guest.
But you know, Arlong-san's
not here right now, right?
Yeah. Where'd he go?
I heard that there was a long nosed stranger
that was trying to run away.
They say another one was caught
and held here though.
He went to Cocoyashi Village to catch him.
Usopp, huh?
I guess I'd better go save him...
That Cocoyashi Village, how do I get there?
Get in.
Guest, right? I'll take you there, swordsman.
What's happened here?
What exactly?
My comrades!
Roronoa...
What? What did you just say?
Roronoa Zoro.
What?
The Pirate Hunter?
He's come for my head huh?
N-No. He didn't 'come'.
That guy, turned out to be Zoro.
What?
The man with the stomach band
that we caught was Roronoa...
I caught him Arlong-san.
W-What's... all this..?
Took you long enough Chew.
Don't teII me, Zoro...!
We've arrived.
Cocoyashi Village.
Arlong-san should be here, in this village.
Yeah, thanks.
Don't mention it, later.
Oh! I didn't ask you your name!
Me? You want to hear my name again?
It's Hatchan. Come again!
Strange guy...
This puny thing won't even fill half of my stomach.
You're right! So let me go!
That was just a greeting. In my village that's
the common way...to greet people.
But you're one of Zoro's group members right?
Well...it's normal to be targeted by a bounty hunter.
Save me! I'm not connected with that Zoro!
Chu! Stop telling such pathetic lies.
You attacked Arlong-san didn't you?
Either way there's no saving you.
Oy! What are you insinuating?
Me and Zoro are b-buddies!
That means, if you lay a finger
on me Zoro won't stand for it.
Oh? So you're saying if you are
killed Zoro will come right?
No that isn't right! Killing me is definitely bad.
If you keep me alive Zoro will appear.
If you don't keep me alive Zoro won't come.
But how did Zoro...
get out of the prison?
What are you saying?
I'm saying someone helped him escape.
Arlong-san, isn't it possible to think,
In order to get your head, Nami invited Zoro?
Come to think of it lately Nami's
behavior has been strange.
Yeah, she jumped in the water and saved Zoro.
Could it be that from the start, along with
Zoro, she planned on deceiving us?
Betrayal is that woman's forte.
That's enough!
Don't end the matter simply
by jumping to conclusions.
Nami?
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Watch your mouth.
I'm a traitor?
It's been 8 years since I joined the group.
I swore on this tattoo.
Sorry. Sorry.
Nami, it's only natural that you would be angry.
But don't worry. I never suspected you at all.
You and I have known each other for 8 years.
We just got a little worked
up, isn't that right? Nami?
That one that should be killed is
Roronoa Zoro and his partners.
Hey Nami...
Say something! Nami!
Damn Zoro. Doing stupid things.
What's wrong Nami?
You don't look well.
Long nose here, even you can't save him,
because he attacked Arlong-san.
How far?
How far do you intend to go on suspecting me?
It's because you're too intelligent.
The amount I promised to Arlong will soon be ready.
Why would I betray you now?
The amount promised?
I know.
The promise from 8 years ago to buy Cocoyashi
village from Arlong for 100 million beli.
But I just don't understand.
Betray the villagers, your family.
You would do anything for money.
Why are you so concerned with Cocoyashi Village?
Why for such a puny village?
Actually, I found this in your room.
That's...mine!
What was that?
Usopp got caught?
He was just taken to Arlong Park.
That man was brave enough to go against Arlong.
I'm sure he's been killed already!
Shit.
So in other words, he was caught
while I was killing time.
Usopp! Stay alive!
Isn't this a treasure map?
Cocoyashi village seems to be marked.
A treasure in Cocoyashi village?
That map is one of my personal belongings.
It has nothing to do with you at all!
Oh! What's wrong? Getting so excited.
W-What is this?
What exactly happened here?
It's the work of Pirate Hunter Zoro.
More over, where did you go Hachi?
If you had been here this wouldn't have happened.
Of course! If I had been here such
a thing wouldn't have happened.
This is beyond forgiveness.
So in other words you don't know
where Zoro disappeared to?
Huh? If you mean someone I saw... I did
see a kind of weird swordsman alone.
It was him!?
So you did see him you idiot!
So where did Zoro go?
Since he said he wanted to see Arlong-san
I took him to Cocoyashi Village.
That means there's nothing to get worked up about.
He is also searching for me.
Well... He said he was Arlong-san's guest.
I didn't think Arlong-san would
come back so quickly.
Zoro is...
That means if I can just buy
myself some more time..!
Why are they interferning?
Everything was going to be resoIved soon.
Really soon!
You... want to fight?
You're an obstacle.
It's your fault,
for having attacked Arlong.
Nami, you really disappoint me.
Luffy didn't doubt you one little bit!
Even after you stole the ship!
Even now he trusts you completely!
How can you so calmly deceive someone like him!?
The only thing I trust is money.
He's an idiot for being fooled.
What was that!?
The deal was supposed to have worked out
perfectly without anyone's involvement.
I can't let you ruin my 8 years of business.
So I wilI at least let you die by my hand.
In the little time I haven't seen you,
you've become quite the pirate!
Kill?
You...Me... Don't make me laugh.
You'd better not...
underestimate me.
Damn.
There's no 100% way of escaping from here.
Killing move!
KEMURIBOSHI!
Damn! Its smoke! Don't let him escape!
Right now!
This is the kind of thing only you would think up.
Stop...
For my business,
this is the only thing I can do.
Nami... you...
Just die.
Great! You avenged us!
Truly a member of the Arlong group!
Usopp-aniki has been killed... by Nami-aneki!
It was your wish... to die at sea.
Nami, sorry for suspecting you.
You truly are our comrade.
Comrades?
I don't have any comrades.
The only reason I joined this group,
is to buy Cocoyashi Village.
Keep your promise.
The 100 million beli will come soon.
Of course.
I would rather kill myself...
Than break a promise over money.
That's the kind of man I am.
Just like Arlong. You understand.
Eerie woman.
She's become a really good woman!
Witch...
That woman's a witch!
I can see it!
Arlong Park!
Hey! Don't get tired, you bull!
It has to be.
Sanji-aniki's kick is affecting it.
Hey! That's wrong! More to the left!
That's Arlong base over there!
Finally... I've come to this point.
For 8 years I've endured...
Come. From today onwards, this is your room.
Your desk. Your pen.
Everything you need is here.
I've endured for so long.
There's only one thing left to do...
It's just like flying in the sky!
It's not 'Iike'!!
It's REALLY flying, you...!
We're falling!!
Landing complete!
Yo! Zoro!
We've arrived. We've arrived.
You bastard... What the heck are you doing???
What do you mean?
We've come to take Nami back.
Still haven't found her?
Oh yeah. Where are Usopp and Johnny?
Usopp?
That's right! This isn't the time to be idling around.
What happened?
That guy was caught by Arlong.
If we don't hurry he'll get killed.
He's dead.
What?
It's too late.
Usopp-aniki is dead.
He was killed!
By Nami-aneki!
Am I...
A ghost..?