The isolated island at sea remote!
Legendary Lost Island
It uses Kamaitachi!
Over there!
They are ready!
On the way!
I will find you.
Well! On the way for Lost Island!
Ahead!!
Send messages to the chiefs of each unit!
How everyone repairs the bridge of the vessel-mother!
Where is the officer of maintenance?
Opposite the deposit!
Not, on the right on the right!
Use boards of another boat for repairs!
The team of repair!
Dispatch you to repair the vessel-mother!
These blasted pirates…
They gave up more quickly than envisaged.
It is not serious.
For the moment, let us let sail them with their ease.
What?
They are flee in a very clever way.
For which reason?
You forgot that this island contains a legend,
in connection with the localization of a nest of Dragons, the history of Lost Island.
What? Thus they…
It is only one presentiment.
Draw! Draw!
If I am right, they will carry out us directly over there.
A report/ratio with the Admiral Nelson?
That is not necessary.
But, Mister! I…
I sought during very a long time this Ryuukotsu.
Elixir of youth.
I will not leave this feeling reluctant Nelson Royale to put the hand above.
I will only keep it for me.
And Erik the Tornado will become invincible.
Where is it?
Your meat? Here!
The farm!
It is not that which I want!
Admiral Nelson Royal!
Oh, it is that until I waited!
You have the report/ratio of Erik?
Not, it is a report/ratio of the one of the soldiers in station in the Gunkan island.
Erik found one of legendary Sennenryu.
And, because of the damage on their ship, the whole fleet is occupied repairing it.
Erik…
Why didn't you say me that you had found Sennenryu?
You intend to only keep Ryuukotsu for you?
It is a mercenary after all.
That the principal fleet immediately puts the course on the Gunkan island.
How all the vessels install!
Lost Island?
To see the chart,
there do not seem to be other islands in the vicinity only that of Gunkan.
He… Ryuji-San!
By where must one go?
He…
It would be said that he still calmed down.
Afflicted to have made you wait!
The meal is ready!
Still of its kitchen?
I did not wait for that…
Oh oh, Sanji!
Excel!
You made the meal today?
Ryuji!
To eat…
It is the hour of the meal!
It is hot!
Cretin!!
It is extreme!
Ryuji!
Apis!
Ryuji…
You are well?
Which misfortune,
you wasted the food which I had especially prepared for him.
You ace that with in repréparer.
What did I say to you on the wasting?
What y' has?
Lost Island…
The nest of the Dragons… is in the east of the Gunkan island.
It is there that Lost Island is?
Ryuji remembered some!
One succeeded!
Lost Island is in the east of the Gunkan island!
Ryuji has just said it!
It is perfect!
Usopp, come to help me!
Ok!
Well, on the way for Lost Island!!
Full sail!!
Cretin, you would do better all to eat!
Ouais! Worry you!
They changed course?
Yes!
The pirate vessel seems to have deviated its course towards the east of the Gunkan island.
They pass to the action.
How all the ships put the course at the east!
Maximum speed!
We must decrease the distance between us and the pirates of Straw hat.
How the artillerists arm the guns!
How the heads of unit prepare to order their units!
Our destination is…
Lost Island.
All vessels, ahead!!
Hold, Zoro.
Zoro…
, You are not obliged to you to say it each time know…
Some share in this immense ocean,
Lost Island awaits us.
I ask for myself which kind of place it east.
Do Usopp, you see something?
Nothing, nothing the whole!
I see.
You know what?
If the island ran, it is not by enchantment that it will appear in front of us.
You do not believe?
I hope that Ryuji will test
to remember a little more.
Ohhh, perhaps with that!
Let us give a blow on the head of Ryuji with that.
Perhaps that the shock will awake its hidden memories.
Do you want to release me well that?
He Ryuji! It is not far now!
Soon we will arrive at Lost Island!
It over there isn't this is?
The nest of the Dragons!
If you go on the nest of the Dragons, you will feel better!
What is there?
What a idiotic, he says already thank you!
One did not arrive yet!
Then they followed us…
It is what that? Smoke?
Eh well, I will know it is what when one is there.
Al!!
I am sure that are not idiotic for you!
What doesn't go?
He Ryuji you me listenings?
It would be said that Apis disputes.
They is not good for you to remain without anything to make! Say something!
It is as if Apis were put in all alone anger.
You believe that one should stop it?
A boat?
There is something of strange…
It is certain…
They is cool, Nami!
Come to see that!
I am… already looking at!
Where I passed?
The pirate vessel!
Where is it?
It disappeared!
How is this possible?
He, that did occur?
How did they disappear?
We do not know anything of it,
nothing the whole!
Stop the fleet!
Yes!
Say to them not to advance before to have had the order to do it!
Continue in this direction.
Known as step of connery!
We do not know to only reserves this hidden side of the ocean us!
Nothing of nothing!
Still that?
Very well, give me a boat.
Wait… You…
It is exact.
I will only go.
What, of the fog?
I thought that it was more important so that Nami-San starts to shout.
What does it occur?
It is what this bazaar?
I saw the right boat in front of us and then…
we entered inside.
I see that flagstone!
It was almost… like a mirage.
A mirage?
Of course! I read it once in a book.
When the cold and hot sea water meet,
mirages appear on the sea!
And… it is also a mirage that?
What doesn't go with this ocean?
Dumb, looks at what you do!
I do not like that either, face of fart!
Sanji-Kun! Zoro!
I will return the sail!
Loosen the cords!
Yes, San!
You should remain in cabin!
Out of the question!
I must remain with Ryuji!
Cretin!
Remain with him will not help it at all!
Ryuji sat there without any help!
I must be with him!
You want to listen to me well good blood?
Quickly!
We will be in danger also if we remain on the bridge!
Which odd ocean…
It would be said that he wants to run the boat.
Ryuji!
Am not afraid, the storm will not stop us!
Not!
Zoro!
Ryuji!
Not, do not say that!
We will still fight!
You cannot give up now!
Didn't we promise to find the nest of the Dragons together?
Nami-San! I see light in front right!
It is the eye of the Typhoon!
He, I see an island under this light!
We must direct the boat over there!
Luffy!
They is good!
I promised to bring you to the nest of the Dragons, not truth?
Yes!
Then this storm surrounds the whole island,
like preventing people from returning.
To now anybody had not succeeded in finding this place.
It is surely due to this storm.
You know what? One would say more one floating castle on the sea that an island.
He! Look at that!
You do not find that with the shape of a dragon?
That must surely be the island of Sennenryu.
These dragons were to be very malignant!
Cretin!
They are the human ones which built these buildings.
Ben, it does not matter which did them…
We arrived! Lost Island!
In any case, I wonder since when there is no more life by here.
It seems that the jungle very covered for a long time.
Is Ah yes, according to you where the nest of the Dragons?
He!
Ryuji! Go, Ryuji!
We are on the island where the nest of the Dragons is!
Go, upright!
He says what?
He does not know.
Perhaps that it is not Lost Island.
What?
You laugh?
We had to cross a frightening storm to arrive up to now!
Apis!
Throw an eye at the top!
If we climb until there, one will be able to see the whole island!
It is true!
One gains nothing to remain here.
You want to go to see?
Yes!
Well! On the way!
That arranges Nami well,
they is the guys who make all the job!
Why it would not push a little bit?
He you over there!
Stop discussing and pushes a little more!
Stop of you foutre us, species of…
I will stop chattering and I will push more!
Ah, this charming
Close it!
A village?
All is in ruin.
As so people had really lived by here.
You can see it only by looking at the houses.
But why there is nobody any more here?
Who knows…
Perhaps that they found better elsewhere.
A Sennenryu toy.
Perhaps
that Sennenryu and the children of this island played with unit.
He! You are also friends of Sennenryu?
He Apis?
Do not remain behind.
You know what?
These birds said to me
that up there, there was a building with a drawing of dragon above.
Be serious for you?
Quickly, it is surely the nest of the Dragons!
Nami!
Hurry!
Await me!
One finally arrived!
I can about it more!
Thank you to have shown the way to us!
We surely took the longest way.
Thank you for your assistance friends.
Yes, good job!
This drawing it is Sennenryu?
Yes, one would say.
It is this building the nest of the Dragons?
This place?
Do He wait one minute, where is the door?
How will one return?
The door is just there!
What a cretin!
We do not even have the key.
How will it be opened?
Apis… Its pendentive…
It may be
what it is the key of the nest of the Dragons?
I cannot reach it!
You are too small, Apis!
How that?
Well! Let make me!
One is alive?
Ouais, one would say well.
By the way, which had the idea to use a key up there?
Hold!
Well that does not have any more importance, one is inside now.
The result is the same one!
But… which is this place?
And do that… you think what of it?
What… is it?