He, Sir, we want to go on the celestial island!
Do you know something?
If it is the case…
The celestial island?!
But… the Log Poses point very right towards the sky!
Luffy!
Zoro! Wait one minute!
The farm!
This guy seeks the brawl and I will give it to him!
Luffy!
Bar you, band of larvae!
Luffy! Zoro!
This promise is forgotten! Put to them a beating!
We will not beat we.
A large pirate! The man who
speak about the dreams and the King about the Sonar
Look at! It holds always upright!
Clean the floor with this species of good-for-nothing!
This city does not need these cretins of dreamers!
It is what this din?
Bellamy and its band make a lynching as a public.
Luffy, Zoro!
What you foutez?! You can burst them!
Burst them!
Smash them! Foutez them a beating! It does not matter!
It is useless, young girl.
They are not insane.
When they are not size, they know it.
Never they would resist more extremely only them.
It is really pitiful.
I see that your Captain
really no dignity has.
The navy is too generous these times.
30 Million reward for a shit like him.
Zoro! We will not beat we.
Why do you do that?
Pacifism…
Ca must sound well with your ears.
In addition to being weaklings, you do not have any pride!
Even not able to take up a challenge…
And your heads are faggots of dreams!
That vers de terre!
You said it!
Enough, enough.
This kid seemed so weak, but with a premium of 30 Million on his head…
I wondered which kind of the type it was.
Then I was really disappointed, it is not worth a nail.
I ever saw a similar coward.
He, foutez to me these guys outside.
They are ugly.
Luffy!
Zoro!
He, my nice.
You will not survive
New Era while remaining with them.
I will buy to you.
Tell me your price!
I ask you for forgiveness?
You want to buy to me?
Ouais!
Come with us.
You will not be bored.
Unfortunately…
I am too well…
for a band of queers like you.
It is really expensive!
It is really a crew filled of morons!
Y' does not have any to catch up with the other!
Collect these deux-là and disappear from my sight!
While you are still in life.
Weaklings!
And do not return!
The celestial island exists.
They are really
famous these tarts with cherries!
You are still there, you?
You make the head, soeurette?
They are your friends who gained this combat.
Do Oh, you think of becoming stronger than us?
Our next meeting will be done
in the high layers of piracy.
And counterpart that you have to them
impetus was not badly either.
You do not miss a notch, young girl!
Zoro!
Luffy!
This “New Era” of which they speak, it is shit.
The time when pirates
dreamed is completed?! Hein?!
Oi!
What…
PEOPLE…
DREAMS WILL ALWAYS HAVE!
PAS VRAI?
He, Ho!
He the nut, why you mouths like that?
Is it is what this delirious on the dreams?
To exceed the others is not easy matter to achieve!
He lost the ball or what?!
What still? Ca becomes noisy outside.
Drop.
These goods with nothing surely must
to pass their frustration on the inhabitants.
Ouais!
Let us let laugh them!
On the road of the tops, there is
battles that one does not gain with the fists!
Follow-there!
Allons-y!
Ok…
Luffy.
Luffy!
Oh, one would say that I delayed you.
I see that you are in a hurry.
I hope that you will reach it.
The celestial island!
He, it surely knew some
thing about the celestial island.
It was which this type?
'Do not know.
It is not “this funny of type”.
What? Not “this funny of type”?
And… why?
They was “these funny types”.
A priori.
What do you want to say?
You want to say that this type has nakama?
Where that?
He, answer me!
Rum is particularly goûteux today!
Board!
Here!
Nail!
Board!
Here!
[Note:Ita = at the same time means “board” and “IEA”]
IEA!
Here!
Here…
Whore…
I do not stop saying it to them.
I am not carpenter, me.
But you are so skilful with your hands, Usopp!
It is true?!
It is my best asset!
One would make better buy a new boat.
PAS QUESTION!
YOU DO NOT ONLY KNOW
REPRESENT THIS BOAT!
But if, but yes.
You already said it to me hundred times.
It is a pretty girl of your village which it gave you, it is that?
But that will become dangerous
to sail under these conditions.
It is for that I repair it!
Come to help!
Spin to us a knack!
Repair? Ca?
It is right patching up.
THE FARM!
He, not badly this head, Usopp!
What, that?
THE FEEEERME!
With the fact, you want what to dine…
THE FARM!
I see that we are not hungry.
I will make the crystallized one of gulls.
One wants some!
Sanji-kun!
Please! one wants some!
[Note:Sarubeji (ang. Salvage) = fishing out]
Sarubeji! Saru-Be-ji!
What is it that this boat?
Salvage!
This song…
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
L-L-Luffy, Zoro!
In what a state you are?!
How it occurred?!
Nami-san!
You do not have anything, Nami-san?!
A DOCTOR!
It is you! Will help them!
Oh!
Thus? How much monsters did you face?
Just a pirate.
It is nothing, the business is regulated.
Ouais.
Ca, it is you who it known as. Me I am in bad temper.
NOT BUT!! You could you
to defend nevertheless, I do not know me!
Not! You would have to shave this
whole city me to have mad!
It is not what you said at the beginning…
The MASTER KEY It IS the MASTER KEY!
Then does not bring back it! I strike you, me!
Is He, why so furious whereas it was not even wounded?
Good question.
With the fact!
You learned from the things on the celestial island?
The island
The island-C
The island-C them
Island-C-The-Te?
I do not want to intend some any more to speak!
Everyone burst to laugh
when I evoked the celestial island!
WHAT CA HAS OF SO FUNNY?!
Brothel, what that has of if…
Hissatsu Ketchup Boshi!
Guard Not…
And well, there is stir!
With what rhyme all this row?
Oh!
Welcome, Robin-chan!
Are you hungry?
Want you to take a bath?!
What is nine, Robin?
You went some share?
Yes, to buy clothing, vivres and to find infos on the celestial island.
It IS CA, ALL IS OF MT FAULT, ROBIN!
It is you who started with
us to speak about the celestial island!
Jumping Not!
If it does not exist, I balance you over edge!
He, Chopper!
Would be careful if you approach it for the moment…
In the final analysis, does not at all even approach it!
Nami had a hard day.
And here is, Captain.
Oh, a chart with the treasure!
He, a chart with the treasure.
It is where?
On the left, you can see the site of Mock Town, it is there that we are.
And on is the opposed side, there X, you see?
It would seem that one bet of Jaya lives over there.
Did one bet?
Its name is Montblanc Cricket.
It was exiled of Mock Town because it spoke about absurd dreams.
Which coincidence, you don't find?
Ok, let us see that!
Have-await a little, Luffy!
One cannot move for the moment!
Because these types…
He Chopper, you saw them you also,…
You foutez what, both?
I believed well that it was the end!
Shit, because of you I am exhausted.
But it is Nami which was…
WHAT?!
HOW I was?!
You will treat me too of moron me?!
Big Boss!
The plungers are ready with the action!
Avoided microphone!
OK!
Then it left for the Sonar!
Here the plunger Outang number 27!
Confirmed echo!
A fish bench is detected with 9:00!
According to their speed, they are herrings!
Perfect, this evening it is barbecue!
Plunger Outang number 24! Confirmed echo!
Sailing ship of small size in approach!
What? A sailing ship?
Which is its position?
Euh… it is with 12:00!
They are right in front of us!
Stop research!
Outangs plungers! Regain the ship!
Still funny of boat that here.
But it is not that which you believed, Usopp.
Remain more than to see whether it is better or worse.
However, they were indeed seen!
Not true?
Yes.
The type of the fishing out must
to really live on this island!
One saw them returning!
Bah, that does not disturb me to meet them again.
He, Ho! Frèrot, frèrot!
You would reduce well from up there!
Zut then, I wondered who you
were and my heart was beating wildly.
You ace a dirty mouth!
Be to you of which race?
I am human, head of anvil!
Cretins!
You never heard of Big Boss of Shoujou Pirates,
The King of the Sonar, Shoujou-sama?!
Do not irritate Big Boss!
The calm one, the calm one.
You seem to be pirates.
Do you know that Crocodile, one
from did the Seven Powerful Corsairs, fall?
And its place among them could return to me very well.
My heart beats at any speed when I think of it!
Did Ah ouais? You would like to belong to the Captains Corsairs?
And well, you want to know what I have of so incredible?
In 25 years of existence, I never cut myself the hair!
Then? Surprised Es you?
Be to you idiot.
Oh, I am surprised!
Dumb, our Big Boss is…
The calm one, the calm one.
Your answer makes beat my heart at any speed.
Listen to me well!
If you master keys by the tunnel of my
anger, you will find a sea of blood.
Ouais, it is well…
But one does not have that to make.
Then moves from there!
CRETIN INSOLATE!
THIS SEA EAST MY TERRITORY!
IF YOU WANT TO PASS, PAY THE TAX!
Its territory?
He tells the same thing as Masira.
What? He said that?
How?
Masira?
I have Masira of course?
Ouais, one released it.
But…
D-DEGAGE?!
You… released it?!
Big Boss!
FOR MY BROTHER…
He!
It was released, but…
He did not die!
SOUND WAVE!
[Note:Havoc = Devastator]
The boat, it…!
And then?
What it fout?
You should not do that on the bridge!
I do not know.
But it is hefty man, he destroys the boat with his voice.
It is too late! The boat leaves in crumbs!
Go, the guy!
There remain not planted, one draws!
YES!
, You hold are not more furious?
It rightly!
He, it emits sound waves.
A-A-A… Wait!
Oh!
There are troubles!
The sound waves also attack our boat!
They destroy all my repairs!
The hull was already of pieces!
ONE WILL LEAVE IN CRUMBS IF ONE REMAINS HERE!
Ahead all!
It is necessary to be put out of reach its voice!
And Ben, there I fell on the bottom!
This woman asked me,
“Where I can find this Cricket?”
She did not have cold with the eyes, this pullet!
You astonish me, it was really hefty man!
It was not natural!
It had arms which pushed everywhere!
It seized the whole bar! It was not the joy!
But what it can
to want well with the old Cricket?
This sea is the territory of the brothers simiens.
With his place, I would attend
not this damaged old man of too close…
Perhaps how its madness is contagious!
She surely does not want that!
She must have some after her gold.
Gold?
Ouaip, it appears that it found some.
Did Ah ouais, where that?
He, the guy!
Bellamy!
It is what this gold history?
This man, this Cricket…
I would like to meet it.
Look at this mop!
The island where we are.