It…
It is not God only
people fear.
It is the terror which it incarnates.
Zoro!
30.000.000 VOLT
The drum…
HINO
Why remainders you upright?
For my ancestors!
I am to you!
I cannot?
He, Zoro!
You insane what?!
WIPER!
Skypiea will be destroyed.
It will turn over to surface.
Our village too?
All.
Here the Arch, Maxim!
I hear them.
It must be Nami and Eneru.
Take me along
over there!
The Last Confrontation!
The Pirate Luffy VS Eneru God!!
I see Angel Island.
[Note:Heso = navel]
Pagaya and his/her daughter, heretics having
clerk of the sacrileges towards God…
like their accomplice, the old one
God Gan Fall, are escaped!
Please remain on your guards!
If one of you sees these fugitive,
please, inform me,
McKinley, immediately!
Contact please
McKinley for any information!
In the name of Eneru God,
us, White Berets, us
will defend the peace of Skypiea!
Heso!
Ah, they is good to know
that one can count on them.
But that does not reassure me.
And if the fugitive ones
hid among us?
Let us be us subjected
with the Judgment of God?
Report/ratio! Report/ratio!
That there
does it have?
Dear Sir, we have just been informed…
What?!
The girl of Pagaya
bring closer to the quays?!
The heretic entered
by the door number 1!
Why?
Why it returns,
knowing what will it be captured?
Do not let it escape
! Capture it at all costs!
Bring yourself, fugitive!
LET PASS TO ME, PLEASE!
What you make?!
You draw aside!
WHAT?!
CAPTAIN!
CAPTAIN!!
NR… Not.
McKinley captain!
It is the fugitive one!
It is the girl who
was opposed to God!
Does not approach you!
The Judgment approaches!!
Which quantity of incredible gold.
While listening on Angel Beach,
it would be said that the girl causes
much agitation on Angel Island.
Conis?
But how?
Conis should be on our boat.
There is much noise outside.
What? It is only one
small complication.
Then, this capacity of Mantra
that you have all…
Ca enables you to find
a person in particular?
He well, I would not say
not that it is perfect.
I am an exception.
In addition to my powerful Mantra,
my capacities of the lightning enable me to create electric waves and to hear the conversations.
When I intend somebody to say a thing which it would not have owed, I inflict my Judgment to him.
The extent of my hearing is sufficiently
large to cover all the country.
It is thus like that.
It is an aptitude which
God must have.
Will run as much as you
will want, people of the sky!
It is the ultimate song of Skypiea!
Festivities of
dancing angels of the sky!
You over there, you already saw the expression of one
mortal who loses balance suddenly?
It is what its problem?
It is what its problem? It is what
its problem? It is what its problem?
What do I have to make?
I must flee from here, if not…
Not. Even if I flee,
the celestial island is on
the point to be destroyed.
There is not only
I can make?
Hein? I…
Doesn't something go?
Who is this?
Not, it is nothing.
Please! I you
in requests, listen to me!
Goes you in! Does not approach you!
You all! Listen to me, I request from you!
We have little time!
Please!
You calm and
listen to me!
Close it! Goes you in!
Leave this island, species of plague!
Yes! If you remainders here, us
all will be subjected to the Judgment!
Heretic!
Ouais!
Goes you in from here!
Release!!
Not. Pity, listen to me… I…
You do not approach more.
It is a bazooka-flame.
I will draw!
You all, please! You must
to join Cloud End on bank of the cloud…
and to flee towards
Blue sea immediately!
This country is to two
fingers to be destroyed!
A minute ago to lose!
Please, use all the boats
that you will find and leave Angel Island!
Which is this madness?
Eneru God with the intention
to destroy this country!
While remaining here, NONE
will not survive us!
Hah! It is anything!
You try to swindle us?!
It is to avenge you?!
There are certain things on
which one cannot joke!
You take to us for imbeciles?!
Do not miss a respect
towards Eneru God!
Forgiveness…
What?
It released its weapon?
He! Stop it!
Yes.
I…
I DO NOT WANT a ENERU LIKE GOD!
Father…
It became insane?!
You put at the shelter!
Reprocess! Reprocess!
You move away from it!
Judgment of God approaches!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
Hein?
It is odd.
The Judgment does not arrive.
Why?
After all these sacrileges towards God…
That
does it pass?
Because there is no more
reason that it only kills to me.
“Skypiea will be destroyed.”
A Soldier who is
flee of Upper Yard…
its life sacrificed to inform us.
He…
He and my father underwent
the Judgment together.
Did God do what?
That
does it pass?
Isn't God supposed to help us?
What says this woman?
We do not have time.
You all, please go
towards bank of the cloud, Cloud End.
How is this possible?
Wait a little!
It is impossible!
We have need of time!
We all are born here and
we grew in the sky!
To give up that now is… (that would be ptet to better put:all to give up it now is…)
Yes! It rightly!
Moreover, one is never
gone on the Blue Sea!
How we could
to live over there?
Then you count
to wait here and die?!
You have all considering the kind of man who is
Eneru during this incident six years ago!
After such a declaration, it
will put its words at execution!
If that continues…!
It east cannot be not so serious.
A miracle will arrive can be…
and the celestial island will be saved.
Yes.
God goes can be to change opinion.
Yes, it is that.
Then can be…
Over all, us
always knew…
that it has the capacity of us
to bring despair!
And this time, it is for soon!
What good is it to await a miracle?!
We know all that our country
does not have God in this moment!
Before requesting,
before closing the eyes on reality,
we must initially make
what is in our capacity!
We cannot hide us
behind its victims to survive!
If we do not do anything,
it does not matter with which it fault,
we will have lost our lives!
Now,
you must be solved
to leave this country!
Will run towards the Blue Sea!
To gather your business!
All worms the bank of the cloud, Cloud End!
Made what she says!
Quickly!
Time ago to lose!
He, Miss!
You know what are
become Soldiers?
My husband is one of them!
I want to flee with him!
My son is too!
Are the Soldiers well?
My single son too!
He is always over there!
Hum, I…
The Soldiers are surely already…
I do not know.
Then, that the Soldiers make over there?
Where are they?
You can nothing say to us?
Please, one deals with
Soldiers, us them White Berets!
We will bring back them for you
healthy and safe!
Please, leave! You
must benefit from it to flee!
McKinley captain!
You dispatch please!
Captain…
I have my little idea on the subject
fate reserved to the Soldiers.
Eneru is this kind of man.
I always knew it.
But now, it is imperative that the citizens of this island find a refuge quickly.
I will not only allow this
island becomes another Bilka.
Bilka?
A celestial island far in South-east.
Eneru was born and grew on this island.
Me was told that it had disappeared
without leaving traces six years ago.
Six years…
Ca wants to say that…
Yes.
Eneru destroyed its own country
native and settled here.
It was said that Bilka lodged
many powerful warriors,
But before Eneru, they
did not have any capacity.
God without equal.
It east can be true.
I am sure that you are already conscious…
that we all were members of
Soldiers with the service of Gan Fall-sama.
While betraying the Soldiers, us
lent oath towards Eneru.
We thought that while remaining on the island,
we could protect the citizens.
But in the final analysis, even that…
was a poor wretch failure!
We tried to prevent all it
world to cause the anger of God.
We hoped that if
nobody disobeyed to him…
It was all that
we could make!
Failure!
A failure!
A failure!!
Only a failure!!
Ca was not a failure.
I am content with
you to intend to say that.
There is not to have shame.
You did what you
thought of being best for all,
then would owe us
rather to thank you.
Captain.
Can I leave you
you to occupy of all that?
Yes, of course.
Where do you go?
In fact, there are some people
who do not know how to flee from here.
They are my friends.
I must join them!
Take care of you!
Of course! Blue sailors!
Heso!
I will not be able all
to move at the same time.
We must at least reach
higher layers.
In any case, we must flee.
Aisa!
Be sure that it is to you by there, hein?!
Yes!
One is there almost!
I am sure that it is by there!
Well!
It is that, Luffy!
The hole on your left!
Ca! Over there!
It is over there that they are?!
WELL!
It is what I thought, they were not
not among the five survivors.
Did brothel, where hide?
This would be…
What a poor unbearable!
Ca wants to say that my
prediction was false.
It IS YOU…
THAT ONE CALLS ENERU?!
Luffy!!!
But what you made ace…
with my companions?
About which waste do speak you?
Do not move!
I will assemble to you botter the bottom!
You should moderate your words!
I am God.
In what you are God?!
He causes Eneru deliberately…
Will Ca go, Luffy?
Wait, Luffy!
Pay to!
I hear the festivities of the angels!
It would be said that the citizens of Skypiea
took note of their destiny.
I wonder until where they will be able to run before the ground does not collapse right under their feet.
I You AI REQUESTED IN WHAT YOU WERE GOD?!
You go soon the knowledge.
I see.
You are not human ordinary.
But a paramécia type.
You are not size vis-a-vis me!
Nothing can resist to me…
because I am God!
EL THOR
[Note:God norse of the thunder]
LUFFY!!
Luffy… Not…
I am impressed that
you could dodge that.
60.000.000 VOLT
What? He dodged?
[Note:God of the thunder
aboriginals of Arnhem]
100.000.000 VOLT VARI
It is that!
In there reflective, I would have
had to think of it earlier!
The lightning does not have any effect on Luffy!
It is out of rubber!
STOP YOUR TOMFOOLERIES!!
The calm one!
Physical attacks
will not affect my body!
From there, it
monkey of the Blue Sea…
It completely inhibited
its capacities of the lightning!
Eneru probably never has
imagined that somebody on ground…
could not be
affected by the lightning.
Luffy east can be only on
ground with being able to beat Eneru…
Its natural enemy!