SANJI THE COOK!
ART CULINAIRE MARINERE!
It is true that these pirates
fell from the sky?
Incredible.
But Navarone is
the surest fortress.
Besides this boat which
has just fallen from the sky,
it would seem that he there
nobody on his board has…
It is as if it were
arrived all alone!
How…
coffee was drunk here
little time ago.
L was to have somebody on board there…
And there was also…
MUCH GOLD!
I heard of a gold relic.
L says things
appalling about it.
Is this one… ghost ship?
This boat east can be cursed
by this old relic
He will certainly wander until
to disappear with this world.
“Order of the commander Drake,”
“The council must meet in the station of
as fast as possible order No 1 of the tower! “
I do not know if it is
the ghost ship or not.
But seeks he to defy
the Navarone fortress?
One goes there!
“Contact 4th, 6th and 9th units!”
These units, which are?
“You in the station Join together
of ordering of the tower! “
Navarone?
I see, it is thus that.
Then like that, we fell pile…
in one of the fortresses of
Navy protected.
You intend to react, Mister the captain?
L of fout completely…
L is necessary to hurry,
it is a state of emergency!
The boat was moored with the quay No 88,
and excavated basic in roof.
General.
Stanberry with the report/ratio.
Although I said to them…
Forgiveness?
that we are in state of emergency…
Our losses were enormous
because of C storm.
It is a cas de force majeure.
Do not lose a second. Make us
to enter, we need care.
L is true that you were
detached from the base. But…
there are great chances that there is one
crew of pirates infiltrated in the base.
We cannot accept.
So of other boats enter,
there will be an useless chaos…
Open to them…
I accept their request.
Find to them a medical team.
Yes!
Commander!
On Large Line, people taken
in a storm are in danger.
You would owe the knowledge.
It is true but…
If…
we remain inactive too a long time,
Which will be the fastest means
to leave the fortress…?
But why come here, in Navarone?
Monkey D. Luffy.
The boat is in sight.
Pass in level 1 of alarm.
The bridge is ready.
Which large fortress…
It is the first time queje come here.
Gigantic!
What it is
large this fortress!
It is difficult to be found here…
We must leave from there.
The more time passes, the more it will be difficult.
Where are the different ones?
Oh not.
What is it?
It is really gigantic.
Where is Merry?
Merry disappeared!
Wait!
Where is Merry?
Where is my gold?
However… However… However…
It was so hard to obtain such an amount of gold…
A boat.
It is a warship.
The 31eme unit.
Go to the building B of the 7th zone.
The boat can enter this fortress.
That wants to say that it is not a lake.
L must have a passage there towards outside.
Perfect.
Let us join together the others and
let us find Merry together.
We must benefit from this chaos.
We can flee disguise as sailors.
And perhaps to obtain information.
Where?
They know the faces of Zoro and Luffy…
But not mine.
It is here?
Zut!
It is what this whore of fortress?
A labyrinth would be said.
Do you know where is the kitchen?
Kitchen?
Yes, yes, I know where it is…
We are boat which
has just arrived.
Can you help us?
We lost our way.
You are lost…
Me also I often lost
my way five years ago.
That made five years that you are here?
Bring us to the kitchen, please.
As a chief-cook one cannot
not to waste more time.
I in taken to you…
Do I have the choice?
We are of Maryjor.
Ca does not cost you anything to help us.
Ca does not bring back anything to me…
Ok, casserole.
That pleases to me.
Do you know something about this fortress?
Not, we are only of the chief-cook.
We are recognized by the navy.
Oh, you are famous…
It is the Master of the restaurant which sends to us.
We cooked put delicious
for the soldiers in front Maryjor.
We are better than…
finally let us let be to them the only judges about it.
I have anything of it to beat…
Initially I must absolutely find the others…
will espéront that they have of advantage of information.
Waouh! You seem to be gifted chief-cooks.
Then, turn right to the first intersection.
Then on the left with the intersection
following, You will find the kitchen.
This way?
Yes.
Goodbye.
Is this the first intersection?
Hein?
Hein…?
It is well that.
Roronoa Zoro
L would seem that the boat pirates is
that of Luffy to the Straw hat…
Jonasan, the commander orders to us…
However I am convinced that our unit has
all capacities necessary to capture them.
And…
The most important enemy must be…
Roronoa Zoro.
L was formerly called “hunter of pirates”.
L is famous for one
technique called “Santo Ryu”
Let us capture it, a point it is all.
And let us make regret having put a foot to him here.
What do they tell, them?
Hein?
What I can well
to make here now?
How you can remain
quiet with so much of arrogance?
Ouch be to you that a snotty-nosed kid.
Oh? It is you.
You ballades with your swords.
You are easy to locate.
Hein?
In any event, we hide initially.
Brothel, my katanas!
It is time to eat.
I am hungry.
They left?
Stop worrying you…
If there is not an other choice, we will batrons ourselves.
Daaa!
One cannot do that.
Did we envisage to join the others?
Of course.
But I do not know yet where is Merry.
Would not be so anxious.
Benefit from the landscape.
We cannot appreciate it of night.
It is beautiful here.
He Nami, finds the others, which they see that.
Not thank you!
In any event, it is that where to remain here.
All that one would gain there they are troubles.
He brothel! My katanas!
You do what with my swords?
Whore…
Acknowledge that one is lost.
I leave to seek the others then I
return to seek itself.
But before…
He, snotty-nosed kid…
What do you make?
One was made have.
lmpossible.
How can you remain nothing there to make?
With the job and that jumps.
With your orders.
The crew of the ghost ship
is decided with remain to hide.
In any event aborrd should be eaten.
A ghost ship?
Did you hear spoken about puffs out?
Restaurant?
TO EAT, WHAT!!
Wait!
What, what takes to you?
Quiet remainder.
Am not afraid, will seek to eat.
To eat…
Be to you shitting.
Do not move.
More one gesture.
Strange.
It is a hallucination?
Perhaps let us be us too gone far…
One is tired too much.
In any event, it is initially necessary to eat.
Moron!
One failed to be made have.
That at the right moment.
One will pass unperceived like that, not?
That feels good.
It is the kitchen here?
Funny of sight.
There are recruits which arrived.
What? Already? This type which speaks extremely?
It had not been said to you that this type was to arrive?
They are foreigners.
Let us not be malicious.
Yes!
Meat, it is… the odor of the meat!!
You cannot calm yourself?
All of which I want it is of…
to eat meat…
In eating much…
It is all?
Luffy!
MEAT!
“ART CULINAIRE MARINERE!”
It is you?
Alleged brothers of Mary.
Marry…
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Hello!
You are the chief-cooks
who came from Maryjor?
Hein?
How you can say that our
fortress is a campaign.
And to say that we are cooks of low level.
Show us what you can do.
What? You are mistaken on us.
Nothing to make, I want to eat! Give me
meat to be eaten!
It is you…
The imbeciles who cook for graded of Maryjor…
and which waste a million Berrys per week?
It does not matter which you are.
Here the holiest place in Navarone.
It is the kitchen.
If we decide it, you will not be able
to put one foot more here.
It is true.
Quite known as Jessica-san.
L has there thousand courageous soldiers in this fortress.
Our cooks make of their better for the soldiers…
To make them strong…
That they can fight for their fatherland.
Each day they make of their better.
They are better than the chief-cooks…
who can only praise themselves.
Astonishing what you ridges.
Do not forget it.
The meal is made…
with the heart.
Do you want to learn how to me to cook?
I am not so pretentious.
I want just to say that it is our pride.
Who who you are…
and what imports your talent,
you are likely to annoy you here.
That it is clear,
if I decide not to admit you…
you could never be a chief-cook with Navarone.
I see…
You are caught well too much with the serious one,
Miss.
What, it is what this to foutoir?
L would seem that the chiefs want
to make a duel of kitchen.
Let see me.
Are these types the chiefs who arrive of the base?
Use what you want.
The rule is simple,
Prepare a meal percent soldiers.
The soldiers will decide who is the winner.
I include/understand anything, but they is enthralling.
One starts when you want.
We will give best ourselves
to the last breath.
Let us do our better.
Hein?
If you do not finish, you lose.
That is there.
Percent soldiers.
And you?
Cool, really fast.
That with the good air.
Do not touch.
Of course, usually we cook
for thousand people.
Incredible, you do not find?
It is the secrecy of the chief-cooks of Navarone.
Hein?
Which wasting…
What does he want to make?
C this standard…
Impossible!
Perhaps that he wants to use remainders…
The head and edges,
as well as the intestines must be crushed…
then mixed with vegetables.
After make fry them in oil…
until it bubbles.
Sprinkle with the fish juice.
The bitterness can stimulate the appetite.
The spiced taste can stimulate the tired body.
In this case, fresh vegetables are necessary.
The potato is good.
For a soldier, it is the best food.
The broccoli cream is sonctueuse.
Hop!
Look at this full food
of love and vitamins.
In period of war,
it is not necessary that is tasty.
But rather to save each ingredient.
It does not matter… Ten thousand or one million Berrys…
We should not waste an ingredient.
It does not matter food, you
must make it cook with love.
It is like the love of a woman.
You all must like it.
I have never to eat food if
tasty. But of what I lime pits…
Incredible!
Shit, one does not have the right to lose.
But I do too much of it.
I can just use the best ingredients.
That changes luxurious food
eaten by the rich person.
It is the food of the courageous soldiers.
It is the faith of Jessica-san.
But I forgot it.
And right fact of the wasting.
94… 95… 96… 97… 98… Hmmm…
Iccroyable!
Nobody Na ever eaten as much!
94… 95… 96… 97… 98… Hmmm…
99…
100!
Oh!
What doesn't go?
You are well?
Say something.
It is too boooooooon!
I am more hungry.
I am happy.
Allons-y.
They was really good.
Thank you, Miss.
If possible, I will not fight
with you. A so pretty girl…
You include/understand.
Miss.
Wait.
does L remain food?
You want that I remain dishonoured forever?
I like you.
Your kindness and your eloquence.
You are ours now.
Really? Jessica-san!
They are not easy to find.
Obviously, Commander.
They are pirates.
They will not come in a so dangerous place.
We control all here.
I reflected much there… It must
there to have somebody of hidden.
Probably one or two stupid pirates.
Really?
Perhaps that we will not miss them today.
Hein?
Shit, navigatrice with nut.
What took to him to balance them,
bloody hell…?
Whore…
Whore, stone with the idiot.
Welcome with Navarone.
Hein?
And of one…
What doesn't go?
Who knows.
Dirtiness of head of lawn!
What is this you ace say, brothel?
You ace of the chance that one is still alive!
Good…
You will remain a small moment here.
Where it is the different one?
These types should reflect one
little themselves with if ation.
Chopper!
What you insane still with the infirmary?
Soon in One Part
The urgent operation of Zoro and Chopper!
I will become… the lord of the pirates.
The URGENT OPERATION
ZORO AND CHOPPER!