You knew at the end of the ocean there was a fabulous treasure?
That which will find it will become the Lord of the Pirates.
Es you as excited as me?
There are incredible adventures which await nothing any more but us!
Uncle fortress, with the next one!
He, it is me!
Lock up it!
You should thank Robin.
I see, all will be well with Zoro to my sides.
It would be preferable not to carry out of investigation by here.
There is only one exit.
The desperate decision of Luffy and Sanji!
The army maneuvers of rescue!
Parmis the members of the crew of Straw hat who were located,
Some infiltrated and claim to be members of the marine.
Listen! You can act as good seems to you.
If you notice somebody of suspect, apprehend it.
Yes!
You ace heard Ca? The type with the long conk… made party of the crew of Straw hat.
Ouais. But why this type did come here in particular?
Indeed. the gulf conceals much better boats.
It could have subtilized any of them.
They are like that the pirates, they have the eccentric ideas.
It is quite true!
What does it arrive to you? You do not work today?
I get old from now on.
It is old.
But it pète the form.
Species of large cretin! Test to be more discrete.
D-sorry.
Nothing to make. This fortress is a true hell.
Where can be Zoro and Ussop well?
They are without any doubt in prison.
Well! Then direction the prison.
You know at least or is the prison?
Do Sanji, you know or it is?
I know anything of it
perhaps that it is on the suspect island.
What makes you say Ca?
Intuition.
It is a well kept place, that does not make the shade of a doubt.
The zone is taken out of clipper by the sea.
The only means of fleeing, it is to take the bridge.
Even if it is shitting, will throw a glance.
Included/understood.
Shit. One cannot go into reverse any more now.
Yes, here the zone F N°4 building. Nothing to announce.
Remain vigilant.
Yes.
They are informed of the situation in one nothing time with their apparatuses.
It is without exit.
With the Sanji fact.
Hein?
I am too excited.
Continue to advance, cretin of monkey!
Where am…
Do not move any more.
It is bizzare… The entry and the exit of the ships were chamboulées.
why?
I am supervised.
He, what you foutez?!
For which take to me you?!
They say all the same thing…
You claim to be the special inspector, lieutenant Shepard, not?
If you know it then let me leave!
I wish entretenie with the commander Jonasan.
lieutenant Shepard?
I see. Robin usurped his identity to him.
The navy regards it as one as of ours.
I am brilliant!
Go gives up, that is not used for nothing.
In tan that man you must know to recognize your defeat.
It is not worthwhile to be efferayé.
Coéquipié Konteriano.
Kon… Konteriano?
It is what Ca?!
And then be to you which?
Stop your conneries.
How may it be that you can forget your own name and my face?
Break! I do not see what you speak!
I do not know this type!
What does it take to you?
Impossible, would you have lost the memory during your fall of the bridge?
It is… It is too sad.
He, please! Take it along elsewhere.
This type is not any more as of ours, dear Konteriano!
I am not able to decide to me.
I include/understand better why it was made pass for the inspector.
I said anything, me.
Wait, what you will make ego?!
Wait, wait, you do not include/understand?!
Konteriano!
Is Konteriano, it which?
Mets out of silencing device!
Played well, Zoro!
They fell into the panel…! Of thanking me Robin will be necessary to think.
Exaggerate you a little too much, Ussop.
Commander. We did not succeed in yet locating Straw hat.
What do we have to make now, commander?
Did they find the site of the prison?
If it is not the case let reach that point.
hein?
Penetrate there and hide you over there.
And have patience until their arrival.
Now, let us leave the their initiative of the offensive.
What you insane, Sanji?
Shit.
I have the impression that one will have to pass in force.
How is it made that nobody supervises on this side?
Allons-y Luffy, by here.
Hello?
I am with the report/ratio.
Us venos to apprehend a suspect.
We think that it makes party of the crew of Straw hat, under the name of Konteriano.
Konteriano?
Yes.
It tried to be made pass for lieutenant Shepard
But I was right not to believe it.
Hum… Good job.
Two Shepard?
It left…
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
He Zoro, you ace not the impression which it is woven something of strange?
Ouais, there is like funny amtmosphére.
Hein? But it is…
You are…
The old mechanic-san?
What you factories here?
Nothing the whole… Arrange your… your
Arrange your sabers!
I see.
What you ace at the head?
Ca is not looked at. I seek the type with the long nose.
Wait. Ca is not made go to discuss pépère with a criminal.
Ca will not be long, look at.
Yo!
Ah, you are…
To does the fact Going Merry go well?
Do not worry you. Your boat is well.
At least until now.
I am relieved.
It is you who had rafistolé the boat?
Hein? Heu… Exact.
I do not like too your way of the bidouiller.
How can you plan to make good repairs without cup?
It could break in thousand pieces at the time of a storm.
A cup?
You do not know what it is?
In fact I am not naval engineer.
I am unaware of who repaired it this night there.
Nobody would be able to give it in state in only one night.
It was when we were on the celestial island to 10 km with the top of the ground.
To 10 km?
Ouais, ouais, nobody does not want to believe us.
What means that this boat fell from the sky.
Wah, you believe us?!
I was there at the time of your arrival, it is for Ca that I believe you
If the angle of fall is taken, I can affirm
that it comes from a place located in height.
It is true.
I saw full with incredible things on the celestial island.
A god, angels and full with other things.
A god and angels?
You already tasted with death?
I tested full with tricks but not yet death.
Well, let us return to our sheep.
Did that which repaired it appear… right in the middle of the fog?
It, how do you know it is exact?
In fact do, you know who it act?
If what you say is true, then it acts…
What do you foutez?
Ca is enough, old man.
We still have bread on the board.
Take it along.
He, He!
Have-await, I want to know!
It is which this person?
I forgot a very important thing.
Listen, length-conk.
When you repair your ship, you must pay the attention to least the details…
in order to know the site exact of repairs to be carried out there.
If you like your ship… Then does not forget my councils.
They is good, you ace included/understood?!
Ouais, it is well included/understood, Ossan! Thank you!
Somebody has just left there.
Voice thus the exact site.
Good, one sinks.
Wait, wait, there is a trick which bell.
While taking this way, nobody followed us.
And finally we arrived here.
It is too easy.
I included/understood.
Uncle fortress is in fact a nice uncle.
It is an ambush I say to you.
Your sympathetic uncle, it wants to make us fall into a trap by involving us towards the prison.
But it is not a bad thing.
And then if one does not go there, how one will make to release Zoro and Ussop?
Imbecile! Did not fall so niaisement into the trap from the enemy.
notice, it would be better that one infiltrates directly instead of turning around the pot.
And then I am worried too much by the state of Nami-san and Robin-chan.
Are Sanji, to you reflecting?
Not!
You reflect.
I said to you that not!
It is what this place?
Go ahead, dispatch you and enters.
Ouais.
He, Zoro, Ussop! You are where?
It was the voice of Luffy at the moment.
Ooooé!
It is well Luffy.
He, Luffy by here!
You think that will go? We are disarmed I you signal.
Do not come, not, do not come by there!
What should I say to him?
Will know, I do not have the least idea of it.
Reconsider your steps!
From which did the voice come?
By here!
They came.
Pay Luffy to.
They are there, wait I will draw you from there.
Ca must be Ca Kairoseki!
Lastly, you were awaited.
You would make well return to you, Straw hat.
You underestimate us.
You think that it will be sufficient to have to us?
Ca will be useless.
Thin. It is the same thing bandages cretins.
What will one well be able to make now?
Above all…
What is this that it makes?
It is not worthwhile.
It is impossible to come to end from these bars even with a gun.
Fact of shitting. It is what these bars?
Canon… I see.
Sanji, come by here.
The trick at the bottom of my pocket catches.
Your pocket?
Impact-Dial.
Use it to destroy the bars.
Impact-Dial? The type which uses it finds wounded then…
Would not be stupid.
Go quickly, take it.
What do they still manigancent?
Appointment!
Wait a little, the gorilla. I will show you something of very special.
A shell?
With this shell there, be remotely held hearth of impact.
step back…
It left.
You speak about the flexible snake.
Large idiot.
It is what? Is this your secret weapon there?
If you add a word I kill you.
Frightening! It is really opposed.
Ah, Sanji-kun, forgiveness! It is the other pocket.
It is here… here… here.
How that drives back!
Shit!
C-Ca…
Whip too much…
Who pété in my dial?
E-excuse me.
Why you ace pété elsewhere?
Good blood, Ca will jump. With cover.
Explosion announced in the prison!
You gather, quickly!
Does He, Ca go?
Did the escape… succeed…?
Ca has all the air of it.
I have too badly.
Putin, too be to you shitting.
There are not any more time to lose.
We from here of speed draw.
Thank you.
One goes there, Luffy.
Very well!
One mets veils immediately!
Wait, wait.
Do not let Zoro guide us, or pommer is risked.
Ussop… Dumb.
Is everyone well?
O-Oui, Ca could better be.
Well, all the soldiers still in state, follow me.
One leaves to the continuation Straw hat.
Imbeciles, Ca grouille soldiers outside
This time I will send to you in prison for good.
What?
One lost oneself.
It is what this place?
It is deceived it does not have any direction of the orientation!
Your mouths!
Commander, I am sorry!
Straw hat succeeded in escaping to us.
And where is the remainder of dryness companions?
Is Roronoa with them?
Yes. Heu…
The guards said that only Konteriano did not succeed in being withdrawn.
I see. Major, take care to reinforce the guard on the bridge.
O-Oui.
Of made you not. There are still several opportunities of putting the hand above to them.
The others finally reacted.
Rat-trap?
Do not import, it perhaps will do without something funny.
To think of something of shitting, it is shitting.
Let us see what it is like trap.
Do you think of being able to escape to you from Navarone?
And of Jonasan?
One will not be made take because we are pirates.
Prochaienement in One part:
Participation of the special unit in the war. The offensive battle of the bridge!
I will become the lord of the pirates!