Run! Run! Run!!!
Have-HAVE-await me!!!
Where can be Going Merry well?!
PARTICIPATION OF THE SPECIAL UNIT!
BATTAILLE ON THE BRIDGE!
L remains one as of theirs.
Members of the crew of Straw hat
one their companions gave up.
Anything!
I am Sheperd, an inspector of
general headquarter of the Navy!
Release me…
Inspector?
Warn your superior of it immediately.
The pirates are escaping from Navarone.
Insane steps of us, Konteriano!
Do not try to deceive us, that will not take.
Go there!
Konteriano?
How that?
Slacken me!
I am not Konteriano.
I am Sheperd! Inspector of
general headquarter of the Navy!
What there is?!
Navy!
On this side too!
That fears, that fears!
One is made like rats!
It is very interesting all that.
The Uncle Fortress had prevented me…
that it was impossible to escape from this place.
L would seem…
that there is more than one thousand of soldiers.
What do you find of interesting in it?
One will see whether it is veracious.
I do not see the interest of it!
They is good, Usopp.
You know well that nobody can
to stop when he wants to fight.
Avoided unit 37!
Unit 44 avoided too!
Capture the crew of Straw hat!
Quickly! Catch them!
Wait, Straw hat!
But it is…
the crew of Straw hat.
It is a dead end?
Not, one could go along the wall…
Straw hat, you revoilà.
It is the Commander de Navarone.
L is called Jonasan.
Then, Uncle Fortress, where you stays?
In my personal room.
Charge the guns!
Yes, but…
if one draws with the right in the middle…
Do not discuss!!!
Ah, Lu-Luffy, Luffy!
I had left to lend strong hand to my companions.
As I said it to you, Tonton Fortress,
I will put the veils from here when I would like it.
And how?
Because you do not wish any more to escape from here?
Do not make any you, one will go soon there.
You will have opportunity of leaving Navarone…
or to distort me company?
One will not be made trap by you…
because one is pirates!!
WILL RUN!!!
They slipped by.
Commander!
At present, units 7 and 2l
are posted side by side in ambush,
close to the building site naval.
It is the ideal moment to demolish them.
Point out the troops of unit 7.
It would be likely to weaken us.
Wouldn't it be preferable that they remain in position?
An ordinary strategy is not likely any to go.
Its head is not put at price for
100 million Berry for nothing.
Our manpower would be likely to undergo heavy losses.
I do not want to make useless sacrifice.
We must remain vigilant.
Yes!
They will go to the shipyard
in order to recover their ship.
We will concentrate our forces with the building site
naval, in order to put the hand on these pirates.
Decree, Straw hat!
Drake?
Yes!?
Appointment with the shipyard by the short cut.
There lead also the crew of Straw hat.
All the blows are allowed.
YES!
If Drake goes to the building site
unit 88. That risks dêtre long.
Indeed.
To go to the shipyard of unit 88,
they will have inevitably to pass by the bridge.
We will keep an eye on that one…
while supervising them with the accesses of the bridge.
Moreover, as long as we will keep the control of the bridge…
In spite of their power, it will be delicate for them to cross it.
We can thus take all our time.
I see.
Remain to be seen which unit will be in charge of their capture…
I see only one of them…
We are the elite of Navarone!
We will show them our
relentless direction of the capture!
Of course!
Please, leave unit 55
to deal with the guard of the bridge.
And we will put in Mugiwara failure,
while guaranteeing the safety of the bridge!
I count on you.
Euhh… Excuse me…
What thus?
What does it occur?
Pirates are in escape.
It is about Mugiwara.
They are infamous beings.
Several of them infiltrated the base.
What does one have to make?
Luffy seems to be last with the action.
They surely will go to the building site
naval to recover Going Merry.
Ca wants to say that Luffy already helped Zoro.
One is not drawn from business for as much.
They are unaware of this place very.
Moreover one worked out no plan of escape.
To act thus could be to us fatal!
But…
maintaining our single solution,
it is to return to us to the shipyard.
Yes, then dispatch we to leave
from here and let us join Luffy.
The ball is in their camp
Kobato-san?
Did you know? One of the pirates is
infiltrated as a doctor.
You must finish some with this operation.
Let throw an eye inside to us.
Kobato-san?!
Kobato-san, open immediately!
They is not good… Not good of the whole…
He you!
Doctor Kobato…
Afflicted, we misled you.
Indeed, we are pirates.
Please, made attention.
They said to me that pirates
ground in the base.
It is terrible.
They as said me as they were equipped as a doctor.
You are probably in danger.
Eh… Euh. Eh… Well…
To be frank, pirates in question…
it is us two.
As I say it to you,
we are pirates!
But I know that you are somebody
of good, then I count on you.
Say we where is the shipyard?
We do not have time.
PIRATES!
This cry at the moment, it was…
Kobato san!
That it occurs?!
Kobato-san?!
It occurred something.
Good, one goes there!
Kobato-san!
You are well?!
Kobato-san?
It is there…
You are well?!
He, hold good!
Where can they be well?
They are flee by there, isn't this?
O-Oui!
Dispatch you to catch them!
You are finally awaked, Doctor Kobato.
Afflicted!
I include/understand your reaction.
But can you keep your calm?
Nami.
Quickly, it is necessary to benefit from it to slip by.
Yes, I remember…
You are…
Hein? Me? I am…
I ate a fruit of the demon which me
allows to metamorphose me.
This type resulting from funny from is ligée…
Then you see, Doctor Kobato.
I know, it is a history out of the commun run.
But we really do not have
time to tell it to you.
They is good, I will not cause you more concern.
We will leave now.
The soldiers can return constantly.
Euh! Wait one minute!
Mister the stag.
You summers a large doctor, even if you are a pirate.
You made me become aware
true role of a doctor.
I would like to do something to thank you.
Keep your fine wordss for you.
And then I am not a stag,
I am a reindeer!
Forgive me.
Yes, therefore you are with research
is shipyard, it that?
Hein?
I will lead you to it.
You really can it?
But…
Kobato-san would be likely to have troubles
with the soldiers of the base of Navarone.
It is true but…
If I am discovered, you will not have
that to say that I am your hostage.
Excel.
I hope to be useful to you.
The perimeter is entirely buckled.
Ouais, will be necessary to play it discrete.
Uncle Fortress, it is frightening.
Discretion question, do not be to you the good person.
We will be able to rejoin zone 88,
while passing by here.
Going Merry must be moored in the neighborhoods.
But it would seem that grouille
parasites in the corner.
And if one passed by there?
One can take this way.
That seems to me equivocal.
Y' has anybody.
One will be made roast while passing by there.
It is a trap.
A trap?!
It does not matter the way to be taken…
one will leave from here.
To think of something of shitting, nothing more shitting.
The trap will not work with us.
He Luffy, S-Sanji. Zoro, wait!
Ah… I do not want…
And then even if I sometimes happen to escape from it
I do not know if that will be the case for you!
And if I do not save you, you could die!
You want to always pass by there?
But if I am in danger,
I count on you to help itself!
Answer me!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
The place of which you spoke,
towards where it is?
There are several shipyards here.
I think that it is about the building site
naval underground located at the East.
The boat is probably moored
with the quay Is naval base.
In the East? I hope that it acts
of that of zone 88.
Why thus, Kobato-San?
Yes!
Although it is about a shipyard of weak width…
it is always empty…
and my father is over there.
It would be although your ship is over there.
What does one make, Nami?
Where does one go?
I precisely put the question.
We do not know anything of this endroi
best, it is to remain on the alert.
But we will follow Doctor Kobato.
Nobody in the neighborhoods.
Ouais.
Y' does not have a cat,
quickly, allons-y!
Oi!
Wait, cretin of Luffy!
It is irremediable.
It is super high! I have too the giddiness!
Woho, here they are!
Wohoho, here they are!
It was a bad idea!
I see…
One will be entitled to a little exercise.
One will leave from here costs whom costs!
We are the elite of Navarone in
capture, and we are in load of the bridge.
We will not let to you pass,
do not even think of it!
Do not pay attention to me.
You can continue your mise en scene,
I have a cigarette to have patience.
Do not take to us with the light one.
We are the elite of the Navy based with Navarone!
You will see our relentless direction of the capture!
Ooh, that with the air amusing all that!
Go ahead!!!
Zoro!!!
Put yourself at the shelter!
Yes!
Played well, Zoro!
Fight like a brave man!
Prepare well, Straw hat.
It is too funny that.
Now.
I had studied your technique of combat
Co-how?
You always disturb me at the bad time.
Fact of shitting.
It is finished by it of you, now.
Navy of shit.
But what you manufacture?!
Put to them a good beating!
This time, I will cut out you out of discs.
It is what?
However I struck of all my forces.
It is the Dial Impact
That does not finish any.
Listen well, pirate of shoddy goods.
This warping is the proof of my
membership of the elite of Navarone.
I will fight that with dead if it is needed.
I will not let any pirate cross the bridge.
It is what, this whore of nonsense?
That burns!
He, He, put it a little out of night light.
This funny of play is really sympathetic.
It is the moment!
Seize it by the arms!
I will not let myself make this time.
They are tough.
And shit…
'
Fact of shitting…
You never think of the consequences of your acts.
Afflicted…
Good, one goes there.
By where?
By there…
Commander!
Part of the bridge was destroyed.
The crew of Mugiwara is in the lake.
There was no death,
nobody knows their current location.
Eh well, they are really coriaces.
But, there remain to us still 22 minutes.
Unit 55, the direction relentless
capture, hein?
Commander!
Here unit 88.
Their strategy of capture is based
on the optimal effectiveness.
Be sure that we will capture Straw hat.
Well, they have just crossed the bridge.
They are very close to you.
You hold ready!
Especially do not neglect any detail.
Be on it is to you by there, Usopp?
Do not worry you, they are good, it is very right.
They arrive.
Operation captures! It left!
It is an urgency!
You push, please!
Nami-san as a nurse!
It is what any Ca?
Lu-Luffy!
It is not with the smoke-producing ones
that I will close the eyes.
I did not expect from it less my “head of algae”!
Thank you “pretty eyebrow”!
You will have wanted it.
Vien not there!
Head of algae!
It is not the moment to dispute!
You will never arrive at
to reach your boat!
I still do not have a fooorce….
Soon in One Part…
Smash the barricade!
Going Merry is recovered!
I will become the lord of the pirates!