Collect these deux-là and
disappear from my sight!
While you are
still in life, weaklings!
The celestial island exists.
Zoro!
Luffy!
This “New Era” of which they
speak, it is shit.
The time when pirates
dreamed is completed?
Hein?!
Oi!
PEOPLE…
DREAMS WILL ALWAYS HAVE!
The legendary family!
Norland the king of the liars
Zut.
It…
macaque…
The boat is dilapidated even more…
It is true that the hull
is in a dirty state.
Would not be necessary to change it?
I AI NOT REQUEST YOUR OPINION, DUMB!
DUMB!
You remember how one
had this boat, not true?!
PAS VRAI?!
It is known, Usopp.
But that is used for nothing râler.
The Vogue-Merry is a member
of the crew him too.
DUMB!
ENF! ENF!
Then, let us give it in
state all units!
INCLUDED/UNDERSTOOD!
Luffy… be to you really one…
COM! COM! INCLUDED/UNDERSTOOD!
Oups.
… DUMB!!
YOU WANT TO REPAIR IT OR DESTROY IT?!
Ben, I want really to repair it…
Oh, still…
LUFFY!!
After our departure of Mock
Town, we took towards the East.
One should reach soon
this point of the chart.
And this type which one seeks…
Which is its name already?
Montblanc Cricket.
This man who speaks about dreams
saw here, it is well that?
IN-INCROYABLE!
It is its house?!
It is a palate!
This Montblanc Cricket is
super rich person, or what?!
Imbeciles, look at more attentively.
Isn't a dreamer?
It is right
slap-with-l'oeil.
How that?
It was that a decoration?!
WHAT?!
It has only one half of house.
The remainder it is patching up.
Then it is a skinflint.
Which kind of dreams it could well
to tell to be driven out of Mock Town?
I do not know the details, but…
It seems to have spoken about a gold mountain
being some share on the island of Jaya.
Gold?!
The hidden treasure of a pirate?!
Who knows.
GOLD!
DIG, CHOPPER!
One will find gold!
It is enough that I
digs to find some?
He only saw, without companions, hein?
Hello.
There is somebody?
HE, YOU WILL NOT RETURN?!
Hum?
Y' has anybody.
HELLO!
No the answer.
Wait, cretin!
And if this type were insane dangerous?
He, the guy!
He is not there!
Look at that…
A book of tales.
It does not have the very young air.
“Norland, the Liar”
It is a super title!
Ca sounds well!
“Norland, the Liar”?
You know, Sanji-kun?
However, it is a book
published in North Blue.
Ben, I was born in North Blue.
I had ever said it to you?
I did not know.
I thought that you were
originating in East, like us all.
I grew there.
Silence, Chopper!
What you insane, brothel?!
Usotuski Nourando (Norland, the Liar)
This history is very
celebrate in North.
It is that a tale for children, but it
appears that this Norland really existed.
It was once, it there
has very, very a long time…
Perhaps more than four centuries…
In a kingdom some share in the seas of
North, lived a man named Montblanc Norland.
Norland was an explorer
who liked to make the account…
so fantastic adventures, that
one believed in lies.
People of its village never knew
if he told the truth or if he lied.
One day, while returning of a forwarding,
Norland went to present his report/ratio to the King.
“I saw a gold mountain
on an island of the Large Sea. “
The courageous King, wanting
to see that of its eyes…
embarked for the Large Sea
accompanied by two thousand men.
They faced enormous storms and
horrible monsters fought.
Only Norland, the King and a hundred
men arrived to the famous island.
But all that the King and his men
discovered was a simple jungle.
Norland was condemned to
died to have lied.
And here which were
its last words:
“I know! The gold mountain has
summer absorbed by the floods! “
The King and his subjects did not believe it.
Nobody any more would believe
Norland now.
But Norland continued to lie
to its last breath.
Tales of the North Sea,
“Norland, the Liar”.
This Montblanc Cricket is it
descendant of Montblanc Norland?
I often heard this
history when I was kid.
In North Blue, there is not
not a kid who escapes from it.
One comes from North Blue.
Obviously that it is known.
Always same the rengaine, “does not tell
lies if you do not want to finish like Norland! “
It is more and more amusing!
I would never have believed but Jaya
had been the theater of all that!
And the descendant of Norland, the Liar,
is four hundreds always there
years later, to seek gold.
All that to wash the name of sound
ancestor, died as a wretched liar.
What a family of damaged!
He thinks that some gold nuggets
will be able to repurchase four centuries of shame?!
Not but what a simpleton!
And thus the poor liar…
… died…
… without never becoming one
honest warrior of the seas.
DO NOT LOOK AT ME LIKE CA!
AND THIS DRAMATIC TONE DOES NOT ADD!
Luffy fell to water!
What you insane?!
WHO SUMMERS YOU?!
You are quite shameless of
to penetrate at the others like that?!
This end of sea is MY territory.
He, Usopp! Will seek Luffy!
OK!
You want gold, it is that?
YOU WILL BURST!
SANJI!
Sanji-kun!
No panic! It has me magnifying glass!
Have-await one second!
Cretin, that will learn to you
to have underestimated it.
Drop!
I occupy myself some!
He, but what you foutez?!
Y' had bubbles…
… at water surface!
I was observing them, and
then a sweet chestnut left water!
But makes some, the sweet chestnut,
it was an old man…!
And it drew me with the fleet…!
Papi!
Bring to me of the cold towels!
Open all the windows!
Aeroembolism?
Is the old man sick?
Yes.
They are symptoms
that the plungers have sometimes.
It is only momentary.
The problem comes from decompression
when one goes back to surface…
… a gradient of pressure
develop and forms bubbles.
The nitrogen bubbles deform the veins and
the fabrics and block the blood-vessels.
Ouais, a dirty disease.
It had to plunge the every day without leaving time to these bubbles to dissolve in its organization.
But why?
I do not know…
But they is bad for its health.
In certain cases, aeroembolism…
can be fatal.
Oh! If that it is not Masira!
Be alive for you?
Did Ben ouais, why?
Not, nothing.
You ace heard the shot, you too?
Yes, my brother!
He had to arrive something to the Boss!
Quickly! My heart is beating wildly!
BOSS, ALL IS WELL?!
THEY COME TO KILL US!
What you made here?!
What you made with our Boss?!
About what you do speak?
One deals with him. Brushes!
MORON!
You really think
that they will listen to you?!
They are mad monkeys!
Mad!
You do not see?!
These guys are formidable…
Let us flee by the windows!
THEY HAVE You LISTENING.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
You live here also, you two?
In fact, the house of the Boss is also it
general headquarter of the Allied Forces Saruyama.
[Note: Saruyama = Mountain of the Monkey]
But one lives nevertheless on
our boats, in general.
This house is too
small to contain us.
You are too large, the guy!
But, compared to the giants, you
be that droppings of nose!
How they can
to get along so well?
Birds of a feather flock together.
Ca astonishes me that a dwarf as could you, of one
kick, to send in the air this large bacon!
Really?
You also you can do it.
Good Ah?
Of course. Be to you a monkey after all.
Luffy! It regained consciousness!
Did Ah ouais?
Oh! It is true that it flies well.
Papi Head of Diamond!
One needs small information!
Afflicted for presently.
I thought that you had some
after my gold like these idiots.
Hein?!
You have gold?!
Stop that immediately!
Then in what do I can be useful to you?
Papi, one wants to go on the celestial island!
Say how to make us!
The celestial island?
You really believe in this dream?!
The calm one! It is sick!
You want to say that it
do not exist, papi?!
And well…
I know somebody who
its existence affirmed, but…
it was famous to have been
largest of the liars.
And since, its descendants
are risée of everyone.
It IS NOT ME!
It is an old history which all
people of North Blue know.
“Norland, the Liar.”
Since I say to you that it is not me!
The name is different, you see well?!
Now that you say it, I remember that
its complete name was Montblanc Norland…
Do you have a bond with Norland…?
You are his downward?!
It is here that was held
this famous history?
It is my back-back-arrear…
grandfather, something like that.
A very old ancestor.
Its history me because many troubles.
Even a mosquito would not find
not a drop of its blood in me.
At the time, All the line of Montblanc has
summer condemned to the exile and to live in shame.
And this disgrace us
continues still today.
However, nobody in
family him in forever desired.
Why?
Because Norland was honest
man like one makes some more.
But, the book of tales…
In this book, the last
words of Norland are:
“I know! The gold mountain has
summer absorbed by the floods! “
It is represented with one
to smile idiotic on the drawing.
But it is said that actually, he cried
all tears of its body.
The island where they accosted was well Jaya,
that where Norland had discovered the Gold City.
It was certainly not
a turn of its imagination.
Norland affirmed that the city had finished at the bottom of water following the movement of the tectonic plates.
But everyone believed that it
just sought to save its skin.
Norland was carried out in the middle of
sarcastic laughter of the assistance.
Only the “Lying” word
remained in the spirits.
I see! It is thus to wash the honor of
Montblanc that you research this absorbed city!
DO NOT SAY ANYTHING!
USOPP!
Oh shit.
That my ancestor was one
honest man or not…
Or that it was large
explorer… I have anything with foutre of it!
You imagine what
can feel a kid…
who undergoes the ceaseless mocking remarks of all it
world under pretext which its ancestor was an idiot?!
I have grows by enduring all that!
Finally…
It is right. During these
four hundred centuries,
many are them
members of my family…
to have taken sea in the hope of
to restore the honor of our line.
But none returned alive.
I was ashamed of my family.
I thus fled all that
and I became pirate.
Then be to you a pirate, papi?
It stays not really a vocation.
I just sought to escape
with the curse of Norland.
Very quickly, I formed
my own crew.
As soon as I entered on Grand
Line, my life was full with adventures.
But ten years ago, the chance wanted
that my ship leads me on this island.
Which irony, whereas it is me which
disavowed Norland and the Montblanc family,
I am the only one to have failed here.
And while I pressed the ground of this island deprived of very Gold Cité, as in the book, I thought:
“It is the destiny.”
I could not escape to him.
Let us stop, Norland!
You joke!
Captain! Your stories of
families, it is not our problem!
If you want to seek this Cité
of Gold, you clear up all alone!
It is here that our ways separate.
Good-bye, Captain.
If it exists, it is well.
But if it does not exist
not, it is well too.
My goal is not
to prove its innocence.
It is right a duel with
that which ruined my life.
I want just to regulate
that, before clamser.
Q-which man!
Then, which report/ratio
with these two monkeys?
What do they make here?
It is surely another
poignant history men…
facing the depths of
the ocean, tightening the elbows!
It is right fans of the book.
FANS?!
Ca breaks a little the history, that…
They was there are five or six years.
They came to find me afterwards
to have heard rumors on me.
They said, “We are convinced
how the gold of Norland exists! “
SHOUJOU!
Prepare to die
to have done that to me!
Pay attention so that you say, Masira!
Do not cause me!
The sea is deep in the corner.
These great dark and frozen sea-beds
nothing has to go up you the moral one.
Especially when one plunges without
stop alone, day after day.
These deux-là is
encrusted in my life,
without asking my opinion, and they have
issued that I would be their chief.
To look at these two
stupid large unbalances…
honestly, they saved me the life.
You see what I want to say?
Oh yes! Then it is that.
It is so important for a man
to have friendly truths like that.
Good, that is enough for the monkeys!
THEN DOES NOT SPEAK about IT IF It EAST
CA! It IS YOU WHO HAS REQUEST!
How I said!
One wants to go on the celestial island, papi!
You ace really no patience.
You did not listen to me presently?
Only testimony on the celestial island
is that of Norland, the Liar.
Follow its way, and you risk
to become the rized public one, like him.
Hein? It went on
the celestial island too?
If it is the case, it does not have it
written in its book of edge…
A log book?
It is that of Norland?
Exact.
Lily thus this passage!
Incredible. A newspaper of
four centuries old edge…
“Maritime Calendar of the year
1120, on June 21st, a clear sky. “
“Have just left it
merry wearing of Villa. “
“Followed the direction
The North-East, indicated by the Log Poses. “
“Acquired of an object
extraordinary coming from a navire marchand. “
“It is about a small boat
single-seater assembled on ski called Waver. “
“It moves with its own wind, even
when this one does not blow on water. “
“I did not can well control it because
that requires a remarkable skill. “
“It became the pastime
favorites of all the crew. “
Ouaah! I want one of them!
GO! LILY THE CONTINUATION!
“It is told that the energy source of Waver
seem to exist only on the celestial island. “
“It would seem that it has there up there
other objects quite as strange. “
“In connection with the celestial island, a fellow-member
explorer has me one day shown a flying fish. “
“I can say to you that it is
a quite strange creature. “
A flying fish?
“The celestial seas remained
inaccessible to our ship,
but as a sailor, I hope
a day to foam them well. “
“Montblanc Norland.”
Celestial seas!
Robin was right!
And it would seem that at the time, nobody
did not doubt the existence of the celestial island!
Then, it really exists!
Eh, Boss! Is Ca better?
With the hair!
Good news.
Boss… this type, it has…
Listen to me, both!
You like them?
Why you requests that?
It would be said that they are well
decided to reach the celestial island.
The celestial island?
But there is one
means of going up there.
And only, they in
will not escape, Boss!
This is why I ask you the question.
What would say you of their
to give a small knack?