Wow, thanks!
l thought I was a flashy goner there!
It's no big deal.
You're Clown Buggy, aren't you?
How do you know that?
Just who are you?
I'm searching for a certain man...
What do you think? Will you cooperate with me?
YOU'VE BEEN WAITING FOR IT!
THE RETURN OF CAPTAIN BUGGY!
Where is it that you're headed, Buggy?
WHAT?
You wanna get rid of me ALREADY?
THAT'S NOT IT!
Well first, I need to find my crew.
Where are they and what are
they doing now, I wonder?
GOMU GOMU NO...
BAZOOKA!!
SHIIIIIIT!!
Dammit! We're in danger!
EVERYONE! Run for your lives
ls everyone here?
If you made it onto the ship, say you're here!
I'm here.
Here...
Captain Buggy is...
Captain Buggy isn't here!
CAPTAIN BUGGY!
How long has it been since that day?
Who knows what could've happened
to Captain Buggy...
We should start thinking about
the future of the Buggy Pirates.
AUUUGH!!
This is obviously all that thief girl Nami's fault!
Roronoa Zoro.
I will take your head off, you fiend!
Zoro. If you always sleep outside on the deck,
you're gonna catch a cold you know?
I get battle wounds, but I never get sick.
Come to think of it...
I never get stuff like headaches, either.
Someone must be talking about
how great a swordsman I am.
I see...
Hey.
Oh, someone must be talking
about me behind my back.
Really... it's hard, being this beautiful.
I wonder who it is that's talking about me?
Captain Buggy...
Before he died...
I thought he was such a cruel and terrible Captain...
But now, I realize what an honorable,
wonderful pirate he was!
Everything we are now, we owe it all to,
Captain Buggy's loving help and example!
We will pay our respects to Captain Buggy,
and dedicate this day to his memory!
Captain... Rest in peace...
And from now on, trust your faithful Number 2,
this humble Chief of Staff Cabaji, to lead
the Buggy Pirates in your place.
Huh?
I will rebuild the Buggy Pirates, and
restore them to their former glory.
Wait a minute!
Cabaji!
What is it?
I should be leading the Buggy Pirates
after Captain Buggy should be ME!
Vice Captain Beast-Tamer MOHJI-sama!
Heh!
I'm the Captain!
My natural Captain-ish abilities are obvious.
Well, everyone!
This should be decided by a challenge of strength!
I was hoping you'd say that.
Mohji! Mohji! Mohji!
Cabaji! Cabaji! Cabaji!
Mohji! Mohji!
Cabaji! Cabaji!
Shoutogi!
CABAAAJI!
This will put an end to the matter!
Yukemuri, Satsujin Jiken!
DIE!!
MOHJI!!
Bring it on!
I see, so you want to challenge me bare-handed.
Yeah. A man-to-man fight.
I'll finish you with these two fists.
Mohji! Mohji!
Cabaji! Cabaji!
All right! Get him!
Yeah! Whoo!
Ready to quit... I bet, aren't you?
Quit talkin' about yourself!
The one who will be the captain... is MEEEEE!
Shuuuut uuuuup!
Yeah!
Our awesome Cap'n Richie!
CAPTAIN RICHIE!!!
Cap'n Richie! Cap'n Richie!
Our awesome Captain!
After the death of Captain Buggy...
the one who is best suited to
lead us, is Captain Richie!
Cap'n Richie, Cap'n Richie,
Our awesome Captain!
Cap'n Richie, Cap'n Richie
Cap'n richie, Cap'n Richie
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
You there!
Who the hell are you?
Who let you onto these shores?
You should know,
that this island belongs to the Kumate Tribe!
Oh! Captain!
Oh? So you're their Captain.
Interesting. Gonna fight?
U-Uncle.
Wha--?
HEEEY!
HEEEY!!
What is it?
You don't need to yell so loud...
Did you find something good?
Yeah.
That's...
That's my great...
Grand Flashy Flagship of the Buggy Pirates!
What is this?
This big grave?
W-What?
Did you say, big nose?
Who's got a big nose?
ME?
The grave! The grave!
RED? YOU SAY IT'S RED TOO?
You think my nose is big AND red!?
Wait, this is my grave?
You're so slow.
But who would have done this?
It's such bad luck.
And they used such an old picture of me...
Huh? There's someone lying
on the ground over there.
WHAAAA?
Mohji! Cabaji!
What the hell happened to you?
Oh... oh, Captain Buggy...
Oh...
How I've longed for this moment...
You survived!
I'm so happy to see you again!
I'm so happy too!
But...
What the hell is going on here?
Who did this?
Oh...
I was beaten up all of a sudden...
It's strange, but...
I really can't remember a thing!
I think the ones who did this...
must have been the Kumate Tribe.
Kumate Tribe?
Yeah...
If you want to save them, you'd better hurry.
The Kumate Tribe are famous for having
a very special taste in food...
Captain says that lion meat is not very tasty to eat!
And neither are we!
I'm sooo not delicious!!
He's got better flavor than me!
No, no, he's lying! He tastes much better than I do!
I-I-I'm far too skinny!
It's okay! The Kumate's are excellent cooks.
We'll just add some wine and
marinate for a great flavor!
What should we do about these ingredients?
What is it?
I've never seen such ingredients before.
Shall we all try some?
I hope it's still fresh.
BARA BARA BARA
BARA BARA BARA BARA
L-LOOK, IT'S...!
BARA BARA BARA BARA BARA BARA...
FLASHY REASSEMBLE!
REVIVED!
CAPTAIN BUGGY!!!
Sorry to keep you waiting, boys!
Show them the Buggy Bombs, and make it flashy!
Go-go-go-go!
Richie!
Shoutogi, Yukemuri, Satsujin Jiken!
Here comes the animal show!
You thought you could take on the
Great Buggy-sama did you?
I need to thank you for watching
over my crew for me.
HERE I GO WITH FLASH!!
BARA BARA KICK!
BARA BARA PUNCH!
Die flashily!
BARA BARA DIE!
BARA BARA FESTIVAL!
BARA BARA PUNCH!
BARA BARA CARNIVAL!
All for us...!
Our Captain is...!
CAPTAIN BUGGY!
We're so blessed to see you alive!
I'm so sorry for troubling you, my dear men.
Oh please don't worry about us!
Yaaaaah!
Who are you calling a freak?
Ooohhh!
We've been through such difficulties...
All because of that shitty Straw Hat guy!
By the way...
Who is this lovely young lady?
She's sooo cute!
Oh yes, I was curious, too.
This is the wonderful person
who saved my great life!
Uh...
This...
Um, excuse me...
May I have your name, please?
Alright, guys! The Buggy Pirates have returned!
Captain!
What are we after now?
MONKEY D. LUFFY'S... HEAD!
YEAHHHH!!
Hey, I can kinda make out an island.
Eh? Really?
What island is that?
Didn't we go over that already?
Ah?
So that's the island where Loguetown is.
It's a pretty big city.
Yes, I've heard that, too.
They should have lots of good
places to get fresh food.
I need to go to a weapon store.
San tou ryu with only one sword just won't work.
Yeah, I wanna check it out, too.
On that island, Gold Roger was born...
and also executed.
Oh? So you do remember.
The city where the Pirate King died.
A place called, ''The Town of
the Beginning and the End''.