They are really strong.
Shit. You made what? Say to me at least why!
It is we who would like to know.
Those which entered the office and which have to attack Iceberg-san…
It was you, hein?
You speak about Iceberg?
What does it occur?
You joke?! Why one would have done that?!
You intend to play the innocent one still a long time?
But one did nothing!
There were two people…
Iceberg-san remembered…
In its deposition with its alarm clock.
One was a masked giant.
The other a large woman.
We asked the government…
They said to us that it belonged to your crew.
Nico Robin, whose head is put at price!
Robin?!
Had you come on the island with an aim of killing Iceberg-san?
Or did you make this decision after having met it?
I do not know the practices of the pirates.
But now, we know that you are guilty, this is why you will not go further.
It is him the culprit?
Unforgivable! Absolutely unforgivable!
Impossible!
Oi! Oi! Then like that, Iceberg died?!
It would not have been made kill so easily by snotty-nosed kid!
Since it would seem that you want some with the life of Iceberg-san…
One will finish some with you maintaining!
“Dead or sharp”
Living or not…
Do you include/understand this poster?
Though we make you, nobody will help you.
The laws do not protect you.
Yes.
One is of the outlaws.
I am with the current.
But…
You do not know anything Robin, then do not speak like that about it!
Is the crew of Straw hat guilty?
Guards of Toilets 7
Luffy.
Let meet Ice-Ossan to me!
It is surely an error!
It is impossible that it is Robin!
One will not let a traitor approach Iceberg-san!
It rightly! Let us capture them!
They tried to kill our héro!
Let us catch them!
He! What it occurs?!
You!
Oi, Miss. You spoke with Straw hat presently!
You belong to the crew, you too!
Really?
Ouais, me also I saw it!
I will not let myself escape to you!
Do not move any more!
He, stop!
Nami!
Release me! Release me, I said!
What one made?!
Do not make the innocent one!
Bandage assassins, how have you to dare to draw on Iceberg-san?!
You will not escape!
Oi! Stop!
I said to you that one had done nothing!
Yes, it is true. Robin did not have any reason to attack Iceberg-san!
Speak as far as you want.
In any event, it is finished by it for you two.
To wound this man, it is…
To do of Galley it Company, its enemy…
As well as the very whole city of Toilets 7!
Why one would have made a similar thing?!
Let speak to me in Ice-Ossan!
Drop, pirate!
The new one already made it tower of the city.
You cannot hide any more.
We will massacre all your crew!
Galley it Company! Find to them all!
What is there, Straw hat?
You intend to dodge still a long time?
I said it to you, I do not have any reason to fight against you!
It is known that the firearms do not have any effect on you…
Shit. They do not seem to make seeming!
Aimed well!
Not, it is to escape!
It was less one.
Oh not! I cannot move any more!
Luffy!
Yosha! They had it!
Ouais! One recognizes the pride of Galley well it Company!
One feels well.
Ouais, they do not have the right to finish some with him.
Not, not, not.
This merdeux of Straw hat is the worst enemy of Franky Family.
I at the origin of this combat, isn't this is?
Then how much time should I repeat you…
NOT TO TOUCH WITH MY ENEMY?!
GALLEY it!
Wait a little!
One will deal with you when one finishes some with him!
But why try you to catch my enemy?!
Not, that is not used for nothing. You do not include/understand anything.
Paulie, pay attention!
Galley it, flee!
Franky prepares a dirty blow!
Connector set. [Established Connection]
It destroyed the large crane like that presently!
The crane?
It is a gun?
Flee, Galley it!
In you to play, Aniki!
Oh not, it is not a boulet de canon.
I will send a ball of air to you.
But even faster than the wind.
Air?
They is dangerous! Flee!
What?
STRONG GALE
Oh, it was what?!
One was made reverse by the power of the wind!
Another crane is reversed!
Will run! It will crumble here!
Quickly!
Caution!
Ouais, and here!
The stolen dock n°1 in glares!
It is which this guy?
From where does this technology cyborg come to him?
It was what this odd gun?
But…
Thanks to that, I could escape to me.
Nami, course!
LUFFY!
Does Ca go?
It is necessary some more to beat me.
In any event, I do not include/understand anything.
One must found Ice-Ossan.
What? Be serious for you?
One will never arrive there in all this row!
Oi, look at!
Straw hat escapes!
One is badly.
One is encircled.
Nami.
Cling well to me!
Wait!
Do not let them flee!
They escape!
Let us follow them!
I do not see it.
It cannot surely still not move.
There but one can remain without nothing to make.
Are Chopper, you ready?
Oi! Oi! The high tide Aqua Laguna is in way!
Ouais, ouais! This evening to midnight, the city will be submerged not water!
The shore also will be found completely submerged!
It is horrible! One cannot remain there!
Ouais! Ouais! One cannot remain there!
We must find a refuge in height!
Ouais! Ouais!
Let us find a refuge, quickly!
Refuge! Refuge!
One breaks!
It was what this din?
You must find a refuge.
Find a refuge, Usopp!
A high tide or a trick like that…
Moreover, the wind blows extremely…
Aniki…
They flee. You do not continue them?
Ah, after such a Strong gale, I am exhausted.
Look at my hairstyle!
One would say the branches of a tree, floating with the wind
If these guys had also not stopped me…
When I take again forces, I will eliminate it.
This reward of 100 million does not astonish me. It is very strong.
Good! I do not manage to believe that this dumb of Franky did that!
Which day.
At all events, we should not let them escape.
Aqua Laguna arrives this evening.
With share two remaining trains of the sea….
It is possible no to escape from the island.
Because they cannot use their boat.
Let us find them.
Let us divide the craftsmen of Galley it through all the island.
And all will be arranged before laying down it sun.
Grandmother! Grandmother! It is Water 7.
Made attention not fall into the ocean.
Here offices of Galley it Company.
Connected directly to the Dock n°1.
Look at.
the place is faggot of journalist.
The carpenters also gathered.
Iceberg-san is inside this fortress.
You want to go really there?
Of course.
I will ask directly Ice-ossan why he shows Robin.
Do not forget that we are pursued in all the island.
We must seek in which room Iceberg is.
Then we will have to find an opening and discreetly…
Then, I go there.
Wait!
He is untraceable.
It is which?!
It is…
It was what that?!
The window broke!
What did it occur?
Us are attacked!
It is Luffy with the straw hat!
It penetrated the offices!
What? In full day?!
Me known as step which it still tackles the offices!
Where is it?
Take the staircases to the third stage!
Where are the engineers?
They seek on the island with the craftsmen.
They left all!
It has a red jacket and a straw hat!
Protect Iceberg-san!
It is Straw hat!
By where it went?!
Where? Where is it?
Baka! No firearms!
Do not draw!
You disturb Iceberg-san!
Please excuse me. It is bruillant outside.
Is Naaa, it what?
Luffy with the straw hat penetrated the fortress.
Kalifa, I have a thing to ask you.
Here it is!
Whore!
Y' has too much of it!
It jumped on the second building! Go ahead!
Straw hat!
You are…
Did Kalifa-san, the pirate come by here?
Not, it did not come.
On this subject, continue it in silence please.
Iceberg-san still rests.
Excuse us.
Straw hat did not arrive yet.
Let us protect this zone.
It does not move inevitably there!
Did Naaa, you want to speak to me, pirate young person?
Yes. Thanks for having made me come.
You nevertheless did not come to kill me?
I came to know the truth!
Last night, I saw Nico Robin of my own eyes.
And it is a member of your crew. Here is the truth.
It is impossible… It was really Robin?!
Keep silent yourself.
You do not inspire confidence to me.
If I made you call, it is because I have a thing to ask you.
Let meet Nico Robin once again to me.
Breaking news!
Culprits in the attack of Iceberg-san…
is the crew of Straw hat!
Soon in the Mizu-Mizu newspaper, the accounts of eyewitnesses!
The culprits are on this island!
Find the crew, and hang them!