What do you make!? One must bring all these tricks to them!
I know!
What they are noisy these horrible brats.
He, why are you so in a hurry?
Somebody is able to help us.
One will return in Ruluka.
Does Qu-Quelqu ' one arrive!?
Pa-do not leave!
Wait!
Let leave to me!
Hurry!
IF you like it, wait!
Take to me with you!
Will you leave me all alone there?
It is as if you killed me!
Return, please…
Open the cell.
Do not give up me.
Of agreement.
Thank you!
I owe you a proud candle.
Frantic fight!
Plans of Whetton and the Tower of the Rainbow
GOMU GOMU NO!
ROCKET!!
Release me, whore! Release me!
Stop that, Lapanui!
It would be a large error.
Henzo would never have become a dog of Whetton.
You believe that I will listen to a similar connery?
Whetton at burnt our city until there remain nothing any more!
Burn!
Burn! How all disappears!
This pain… This sadness…
If you had not forgotten them…
You would never have knelt in front of Whetton, even if your life depended on it!
In only 50 years, did you forget all that?
Even if that made 50 years for you,
For us it was right a few days!
Wait, Lapanui!
You say that because you do not know what it occurred!
Do you know at which point it suffered during these 50 years!?
What?
They called it the dog of Whetton.
All people showed it finger…
But it endured all that and continued its research on the Rainbow of the Fogs!
Why?
Isn't this obvious?
It was to save you!
It is not that.
Ca had nothing to do with them.
Strike me, Lapanui!
Forget shame and the pride.
Since the day when Whetton arrived, I lived my life under his orders…
Tighten your fist and strikes me!
Strike me! Go ahead!
Fact of shitting!
How 50 years they could pass!
With this face, I could not strike you even if I wanted it!
And well, here is a beautiful bouquet of imbeciles.
Ok, it and good you is again comrades.
Even if 50 years passed,
You can always entrust one to you to the other.
Henzo!
Lapanui…
Afflicted!
Luffy!
What a idiotic!
They will be left there.
Inside the Fog, space is deformed.
They will return.
Or perhaps not…
One does what now?
One must find them!
One does not know what can arrive to them in the Fog.
This guy, it is really gifted for foutre the brothel.
Lapanui…
Where are we?
Raise me, immediately!
Eh oh, not of jokes hein?
Moved away, Nami!
He, made something!
This rate/rhythm, Nami will be made devour…
Sanji!
And what should that make me?
It is its punishment to have tried to be opposed to us.
But, Grandfather…
With a monster in water,
We cannot go either in Ape' S Concert.
I know it well!
But we can nothing make against this monster.
I WILL DIE!!!
I have just had an idea, Miss!
Use the device of help!
Device of help?
It is professor Henzo who invented it!
I am sure that it was in preparation for situations like this one!
Professor Henzo?
No idea of which it is, but please, made that saves me!
A life line?
Nami-san!
Nami!
Not, remains with the variation!
What?
It was what… that?
Chopper, please!
Ah…! What do I have to make?
They is good, I have it!
I go in the Fog.
When I give the signal, draws on the cord.
Received!
It is impetuous, hein?
From all those which entered the Rainbow of the Fogs, nobody is come out from it alive.
It will return.
After all, Nami-san is the best navigatrice of the world.
Chopper, as long as Nami-san did not return,
Prevent whoever from touching this cord.
Included/understood well.
Interesting.
I think there that we will let it go.
We will keep an eye on it, to see whether it returns in life or not.
Qu
What?
The Mayor now will change behavior.
What does it make?
Combination of fire.
Reload elements started.
Interior pressure in increase.
Devices of ready helps!
I will burn you to the bones.
Hey, await me.
Where one goes?
You ace not of brain or what? Our companions were joined.
Serious?
Do you can how turn over close to the others?
Not, no idea.
Hein? What doesn't go?
Then you run simply because you feel it like that?
Of course that not!
It is my instinct!
It is the same thing!
All is of your fault, you returned to me inside!
Afflicted.
To excuse itself will not change anything.
I had finally reconciled myself with Henzo…
And I did not even can benefit from it.
And we will perhaps never re-examine Rulaka…
Fact of shitting!
I will finish like my father,
Dying in this rotten fog!
Your father?
My father was a naval officer.
When I was still small, it left on a journey to research a sea rainbow.
And I remained only, while waiting for that it returns.
I thought that it was some share on the ocean, living great adventures.
But…
Father!
I excavated all the ship,
But there was no sign of my father.
We really will be blocked here the remainder nowadays.
Prisoners in this fog for always.
He! Where do you go?
Reflected… I turn over near the others.
How!?
One does not even know where we are!
Do you hope to continue to advance in the Fog?
If one remains there, one, isn't this will never return?
You ace found something?
Nothing. I do not have anything considering.
In the worst of the cases, they perhaps were sent to the fine bottom Fog.
What does that want to say?
Isn't Lapanui here any more?
It is possible…
Not…
It is… 200 years an old galleon.
And I never saw such a ship.
What can occur if time is deformed in Ape' S Concert?
He! The guy!
Oh, it is Nami.
I have right that to a “Oh”?
I came to save you, you know?
Which morons.
Do not be able to you already to run away itself all alone, I am mistaken?
Oh hoists.
Forget that, forgets that.
He, which is these kids?
And where is Luffy?
Why you have all this gloomy air?
It arrived something?
They went at the fine bottom of the Fog.
Hein?
I have just said it, they disappeared.
They are not there any more.
About what you do speak?
It is as he said.
One cannot explain you if you did not see what occurred.
OK…
Allons-y!
Wait!
And for Luffy?
I do not include/understand exactly what it occurs,
But it, isn't this will not die?
It can only manage.
Go, one returns!
Do you have a means to leave?
It is possible.
It is only one cord!
Then you are those which come from Ruluka?
Ian…
It is which him?
One of the companions of Whetton.
What does it make there?
Why is it here?
Now give me this cord.
Why?
If you want to leave the Fog,
You have to only come with us.
Do you hold with this boy?
Not really.
What!?
It is which this kid?
I am not enough nice to help from perfect abroad.
Well, I see that.
Wait, it was what that?
I will draw to him above! I swear that I will do it!
Loophole!
Please, listen to it!
You are too naive.
It is right…
He, stops!
I do not want to lose other comrades yet!
Please listen to it!
Well, Isoka-chan!
Now the life line to the boat goes down.
Do Isoka-chan, you want to come with me?
With all these treasures will have us what to amuse us all our life.
Do not mistake!
Our only chief is Lapanui!
We will never follow a coward like you!
What?
Course, Isoka!
Shit!
Longo!
Te insane step of me…
Stop!
Fact of shitting! Leave, leaves me me!
He! What is there?
Kairouseki.
What?
Shit!
Take that, poor idiot!
Does not let it leave!
Hurry and draws!
Wait
Dispatch! Dispatch! Dispatch!
I test, I test!
Dispatch!
I cannot draw!
Burn…
Burn!
Ca is used for nothing.
I will never avoid them like that.
Rumble!
Are Reik, you ready?
Electric combination, maximum power!
Not so quickly!
Spark dragon!
Chopper!
You should not let you distract!
It is what that?
Silver Barbecue!
Barbec…!?
You speak much for somebody about also pitiful.
You need to learn where is your place.
Grandfather!
Ca draws! Ca draws!
Does this girl really return from the Fog?
He, brings back this cord up to now.
Well!
Not yet!
What!?
I promised!
As long as Nami did not return,
You will not pose a finger on this cord!
Do not make me laugh.
Which promise?
What a joke!
Do you want the treasures at this point?
We do not want any of it.
Nami-san will return.
We must just leave him a sure place where to return.
PLAY
[kick with the cheek]
It is nauseating to see at which point you want to adapt my treasure.
Mr. Mayor, the boat arrives!
Well, draw the cord.
One will direct it by here.
These stupid kids!
They can pass the remainder of their days in the Fog!
Ah, that shown of the good again the blue sky!
Ah, I see it, I see it.
The town of Ruluka.
The standard CEC…
It is not Nami…?
T…
Afflicted to have made you wait!
Ian, with the report/ratio!
You seem in good health, Capitaine Whetton!
Me?
Yes, I am in good health. Thank you.
Ian?
Es you Ian of my crew?
Does captain, what it want me this old nut?
And… And well…
I am the Captain.
I am Whetton.
Hein? Then it is which him?
My grandson, Reik.
I am his son, Philippe.
Not possible!
The Philippe who pissed of the half pints to the bed!?
You ace have a son?
It is too funny!
Stop laughing, stop!
Now me tells what there is in the Fog.
Have-IEA.
Here, drink.
Thank you!
Well?
No the chance, I do not collect anything.
The last transmission which passed…
Was probably due to a particular circumstance.
Which terrible bad luck.
These jewels are decorated with Kairouseki…
Kairouseki?
It is a crystallized substance of the ocean.
Ca with the capacity to destroy the capacities of the people having eaten a Fruit of the Demon.
Oh, there are so many treasures here…
But that does not have any interest if one cannot leave!
Be to you a navigatrice, nan? Find a solution.
I already tested.
I never sailed on a so chaotic sea.
Then, one can nothing make?
Not, they will return.
Why?
Whetton, can imports the means démoniaques which it will have to use, it will come to seek the treasure of Ape' S Concert.
Now that Ian, his/her companion of crew returned,
It will bring a garrison with him to invade us.
It is not funny!
One will fight!
I will not let anybody touch with my treasures!
And here…
So only Lapanui was there…
He! Remain with me!
He!
Fact of shitting!
Ca is not used for nothing!
One will row in vain of all our forces, one will not be able to return!
It is useless.
One cannot leave this fog any more now.
It is not serious.
We are only here.
One can sing when one wants, and play as much as one wants!
It is our paradise! A ground of freedom!
Neverland!
Lapanui!
We will never return!
We will create our country of our own hands.
I want to return in our city…
I want to return in Ruluka.
Father?
Father…
Father!
This light!
Is He, what it?
It is an exit?
Lastly, after 50 years, my dream will be raised.
The world inside the Rainbow of the Fogs…
Will be connected outside for always!
Q-Qu-what!?
Ahh! The sea breaks out!
You with something hang!
Is Qu-Qu'est-ce-que it?
The Tower of the Rainbow!
It was right!
Your hat.
Thank you.
With is the fact, it what this trick?
They envisage to invade Ape' S Concert.
Hein? Who?
We must hurry.
These guy there are dangerous!
Whetton…
I knew that you would come.
Go ahead, the guy!
Bring back the least parts of the treasure of Ape' S Concert!
www.rival-spirits.com
http://www.zento.fr
www.saiyajin-team.com
www.kyubi-wolf.net
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/rival-spirits
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/zento
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/saiyajin
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/Kyubi-Wolf
CYB3RFR34K-ISO