You committed all these crimes and
transformed the world into a true hell.
Eyes fixing reality
You are protected!
You knew that at the end of the ocean, there is a fabulous treasure?
That which will find it will become the Lord of the Pirates!
It is really exciting!
More the great adventure of all times is in front of us.
Good voyage!
Do not lose confidence.
And you will see the way towards
future to trace itself in front of you.
The tern horizon that everyone described.
You will be able to see it in your telescope.
The compass which scatters your life and your heart.
Now you it controls easily.
Good voyage!
Give up handicap them and the past.
So that we all can laugh together.
Stinginess not on the tears
that you make run for your dreams.
It is the most invaluable thing of my life.
And you will see the way towards
future to trace itself in front of you.
The last representation!
can nothing see, with share the dreams.
Extraordinary poursuiveurs of dreams
do not see the power.
The affection is not necessary…
Go from before with the smile.
The significance of the family I believe that looks at you!
Whether you are hungry or that you cry,
I will always give you a knack.
The best friend is always the best.
Not only knowledge, not only friends.
We are a family.
Not only our close relations or our brothers.
It is unforgivable.
I will not save to you.
I will put my life concerned until you,
dirty pirates, be destroyed.
It is unforgivable.
I will never forgive you.
I will put my life concerned, leaves to die about it. Until you…
I will never forgive you!
I will put my life concerned until you,
dirty pirates, be destroyed!
Until you,
Go, go, you all!
The most popular drama played by the troop of Randolph.
Combatant, Hero of the seas,
it saves the innocent ones
immondes vicious gredins.
I am sure that you will adore.
Welcome with all those which like the dramatic adventures.
Go, celebrates it heroic actor Randolph soon will leave the scene.
It is its last representation!
Randolph?
You do not know Randolph?
It will stop its career.
It is him?
Randolph is the best.
I am impatient, that must make 8 or 10 years
that it did not come on this island.
Me too.
I am so content.
Super! Randolph!
All that with the very interesting air.
Which part?
The whole ship will be used as theater.
It is not common!
He! Which part?
There remains to us still time before taking again the sea.
Some tickets, that is not so much expensive.
I require of you of which part it acts?
He. Do not make any you, Chopper.
You will see well. Allons-y.
Super. Here!
Wait!
It is not started yet.
You listen to me?
, You all wait!!
This place with the really interesting air.
He. There is something here.
Qu… What?
He, you!
Where you go? The entry is not here!
It is…
, You wait…
Its name is Usopp and a day it will save the world!
Its heroic history will start!
Ah. Finally… You could to at least say something them, Sanji-Kun.
Ah yes, it is true.
I should say something.
It is what the problem?
Even you…
Kill it! Kill it!
What is there?
What? Wouldn't it be to better go to help it?
Silence! The part started.
Finally you will pay for what you did!
It is finished for you!
You have committed all these crimes and
transformed the world into a true hell.
It is unforgivable!
I will not save to you!
I will put my life concerned until you,
dirty pirates, be destroyed!
Well, well. It is finished, it is finished.
Which is all this stir whereas
didn't the part start yet?
That is enough like that.
Let us make a small pause.
Yes!
We will put at it all our heart for your last representation, Randolph-San.
Let us make so that it is most unforgettable of the representations for Randolph-San!
Ouais!
Made as usual.
Even if I take my retirement today,
you must continue the representations.
From tomorrow… will make we the representations without you, Randolph-San.
Do not make this head!
It is not the face of a large pirate.
Afflicted, it is a coincidence.
I decided to leave the boat.
I drop the role from heroin.
I have enough of it.
Qu… What? You leashes to fall?
To be the heroin of a poor troop,
that does not bring back anything.
To make representations on the open sea stormy…
Why a famous actress as me should do it?
You… You pleasant, not?
The representation begins in 30 minutes.
Without you, the representation of today will be…
I am not the only one to have remonstrances in connection with this troop with the reduction.
You…
Goodbye, Randolph.
Att… Wait… Listen to me… Return…
Leave, that often arrives them this starting kind.
Why are you so indifferent? What will become the troop with 3 people in less?
Without actress, who will play the part of the Princess?
The representation will be a fiasco if they do not return.
Let take his place to me.
But I want wages of 100.000 Berrys.
What do you say some? It is given, not?
You do not need an actress?
100.000 Berrys. Is that appropriate to you?
Absolutely. No problem.
Ah! Me too! Me too!
Let play to me!
You need 3 people, not?
Then, me too.
I want to be an actor since my childhood.
I want a chance.
Who are you and from which you come?
Of made you not.
They are my friends.
Who asked you to answer you??
Throw an eye with script if you have a trou de mémoire.
It is script?
Yes, I must rewrite appearances on stage and the dialogs for you.
From today, you belonged to the troop.
Thank you very much for your assistance.
In this case, add my lines.
Mine too!
The null ones…
I do not want to give me in spectacle.
Here are which is very interesting.
Do you… you also want…
Ouais! I am a too good actress.
It is a joke?
Robin-Chan!!
Then me also I want! Give me a role!
How you will want!
Ball…
A long time ago… very very a long time…
in a South Sea remote, very remote,
a calm small island and without history was.
He! Dispatch you to return after having said your text.
… a calm small island and without history was.
Here!
… an small island cal was…
Let turn over to me on scene!
The public claims me!
Is necessary that I await the signal before making it turn.
It is what?
Oh! The Princess. The Princess arrives.
Princess!
It is very heavy.
Hello with all!
We summons charm to accommodate you.
Wahou! The Princess is delightful!
The sun of the morning seems quite pale beside its splendor.
But it is what this play of actor, Robin?
It does what?
He, He!
Princess, I am the Captain of this island.
Ah not not,
I am not prestigious.
The farm!
Pirates! The pirates arrive!!
It is the truth!
The pirates attack the island in this moment!
It is soon to the large Baran pirate to enter in scene.
He, hurries!
Ah, euh… Red… Red.
The large pirate responsible for all these misdeeds,
it is me Baran!
I will strip you of all your treasures
and all to massacre you!
Pirates!
The pirates arrive!
… on the princess, by holding up the sword.
Princess. Die!
Princess… You are wounded?
What you made?
Ah. the Help!!
Stop!!
He! What you factories?
To kill! To kill!
What does it occur? Did I die?
Why the scenario changed as much?
Species of dumb! What you made ace with Nami-San?
Ah! This world…
Wait! You of made too much.
I play the comedy, not?
You believe yourselves in an opera?
Oh? I was wrong?
It is panic in all the village
when the pirates make rage.
Is there something of worse than that in this world?
Ah. My God…
That is used for nothing if it is a tragedy like the others.
Excuse me.
But… Wait. Now…
It is not my role.
But, what you cards?
Euh…
There is a monkey in the scenario?
Ah! The costume was in the slides.
Do not play anyhow.
It is interesting?
Well. Still a little.
I want to say…
It is the signal?
What does it occur?
It is what this brothel?
Deaths are running.
The village sank in darkness as in a tragedy.
What a waste!
The calm one.
You calm all.
I am the Major of the Marly Marine.
That made a long time that we wait.
Randolph.
Species of dirty refuse of pirates.
You transformed this splendid island into a cruel abyssal zone.
It is unforgivable.
Upright, villager!
You whose family and friends were killed,
you must continue to live!
No pirate can take our thirst for living to us!
Let beat this refuse in the name of Justice to me.
Wahou! This Randolph…
By looking at it, I feel courageous.
It is soon the second act.
It is its best performance.
Ouais.
What is there?
It is what these boats?
That it was spectacle!
I feel really happy.
Why my role is finished?
Then, it is the second act. What will it occur?
Randolph-San beats the pirates at the end.
It is the end when the pirates are overcome?
What? Is the Navy there only to return justice?
This end is really null!
It is shitting!
Nothing there can.
In any event, Randolph-San was Major in the Navy.
Major in the Navy?
When one thinks of it, it joined the Navy because its family was killed by pirates.
By pirates?
Randolph-San comes from a family of actors, but they were attacked by pirates
and they were massacred.
All except Randolph-San which fled.
He joined the Navy.
After the capture of the pirates who killed his family, it was promoted Major.
Then, it is become again actor in order to encourage all those of which
the family had been killed by pirates just like him.
From one island to another, he encouraged many people.
Those whose moral one was with lowest began again
courage after having seen our representations.
It is what Randolph-San always said us, then we remain with him.
We are not afraid
even if the sea is unchained.
But… Irony of fate,
Randolph-San was seriously wounded when
it was attacked by these pirates.
That becomes increasingly hard for him to speak. And that worsens with time.
In spite of that, it satisfies so much the spectators whom they notice nothing.
It reached its limit.
There is not any doubt that one day he will not be able to produce the least sound any more.
And it is for that it must take its retirement.
Randolph. Great news!
They are pirates!
What?
The crew of the pirate to the Straw hat, Monkey D. Luffy.
Does Pépé, it remain still bento?
They is very good.
What do you want? Blasted pirates!
The pirates kill people like animals!
They betray their companions,
and make them lose any hope!
In fact refuse of the worst species does not deserve to live!
Refuse?
The pirates are not all like that.
In what concerns us,
we are adventurers of the sea.
The refuse does not have the right to speak about the ocean.
What?
Wait!
I undertake this old wreck.
You want to fight?
I will burst you.
Randolph, stops. You will die.
There is a reward of 100 million Berrys for this type.
100… 100 million Berrys?
Hum… The amount of the reward
no relationship with the force has.
It left!!
It does not manage too badly, the old man.
Then it is a former Major of the Navy…
But it is not in good health, not?
Which is this force?
Completely different from that from before…
Go, Randolph-San!!
Go!
Randolph-San!
You scratched me. Do not make the malignant one!
Not my kind.
But I cannot fight thoroughly against you.
Here me is!
Ah. Of the bento!
Doesn't that go, not?
What a blow salts!
You gained ace, I am irritated now.
He ate a Fruit of the Demon?
It is not my fault…
Do not be to you well?
Randolph!
Randolph-San!
That goes. It is nothing.
You can nevertheless go up on scene?
Not. It is not the moment for that.
It is the hour of the lever de rideau.
Ouais, the spectators wait.
Kid, remains here until the end of the representation.
Our combat was not finished.
One will finish it after the representation.
Very well.
Why you remainders planted there?
Repair the scene, quickly.
It is soon the hour of the lever de rideau…
Randolph-San!
All is well, it is right small a giddiness.
All is well.
Doesn't He, why that start?
It is the hour.
You are sure that goes, Randolph-San?
Not possible. Do we have to cancel the representation?
Impossible! Today, it is the last
representation of Randolph-San.
All is of your fault!
It cannot go up on scene for the representation. Luffy, it is your fault with 250%!!
Species of dumb.
Are Nami, why to you on their side whereas he threatens the pirates?
The pirates are refuse.
It is also what I thought front.
The pirates betray even their companions.
They make them lose any hope.
It is unforgivable.
I always thought that.
Just like Randolph whose family was killed by pirates.
But, there is a difference.
Randolph forever met the crew
of the pirate to the Straw hat.
What a bad counterparts!
You are caught for the first feminine role?
What?
Nami-San is perfect.
You can nothing say of other that?
Love! Love! Love!
The farm!
Navy!
Navy?
That is enough for the warnings.
Here is finally so much awaited moment.
You are Randolph?
Yes.
We are there to stop you.
To stop?
That made of the years that you resell with the pirates
weapons flights with the Navy,
whereas you claim to travel of share the world
for your representations.
About what you do speak?
It is true? You have evidence?
We found that in the reserve.
There are many weapons flights by pirates.
Impossible. How did this arrive there?
Pass to him the shackles.
What does it occur?
He, await Lieutenant.
Prepare you to excavate the places.
It is impossible.
What does one make for the representation?
It is the last!
What do you manufacture?
We do not have anything to see in it.
He! Wait, Officiers!
Do not take along the old man.
The representation is not finished!
And then one must finish our baston afterwards!
Who are you?
I am a pirate.
Would not be so frank!!!
One pi… pirate?
Not not!!
He plays the part of a pirate.
What? It is anything.
Hein? Pay to or I burst you!
Interfere yourself your business.
I return after me to be explained with the Lieutenant.
The spectacle must continue, for the public which awaits me.
Take it along.
You really believe that you will return?
Nobody has the right to show innocent.
Randolph.
We all know it,
you did not do anything of evil!
Return quickly, please!
I want to see the end of the spectacle.
Especially the scene where Randolph re-silvers the malicious ones.
I feel extremely and courageous by looking at you playing on scene.
Me too.
We all here think we it.
I count on you. Return, Randolph!!
Randolph!!
That made a lease, Randolph,
former Major of the Navy.
Gabana, then it is you.
Your former subordinate,
it is what I was front.
But as you can note it,
I am Major now.
At all events, I exceeded you.
At all events… At all events.
Incredible, Gabana, you are incredible.
One day, I will exceed this man
and I will obtain all the honors.
I will reach the top and I will become leading dazzling.
It is for that I must save,
to use my brain
and money.
To use the money to bribe an officer in order to obtain more to be able.
The money can all buy.
It is the rule in the world.
Gabana.
What do you say?
Major Randolph…
Your friend disappeared.
And then?
Did Gabana, you kill it?
You flew our arm, and you resold them with our enemies, the pirates.
It was a good lucky find!
And not that once.
You have evidence?
We did not can anything find in spite of our excavations.
You really played very well.
However…
Isn't your attitude now a proof in itself?
I will send to you in cour martiale.
You believe that will be accepted?
Without evidence?
I have nothing to do with Randolph.
Nobody can declare me guilty.
I will be avenged one day.
One day I will be avenged.
I will send to you in hell.
I will do it.
30 years ago, I passed in cour martiale.
After a very long lawsuit, I was declared innocent for lack of evidence.
In same time, that very strongly slowed down my career.
Otherwise, I will have assembled the levels much more quickly.
I arrived there thanks to my intelligence,
stage by stage… How it was long!
Because of you, that took 30 years to me to arrive at the rank of Major.
In this case, how long is it necessary to reach the top?
Randolph. All is of your fault.
You very wasted.
It is not rather because of your incompetence?
Who are you? From which do you come?
You take to me for whom?
I am Major in the Navy.
You resemble an idiot.
An idiot?
Species of dumb!
I have sufficient evidence this time.
You…
Exactly.
Randolph-San secretly resells weapons flights since years.
It ordered to us to do it as a Colonel, us did not can refuse.
You very prepared since the beginning.
It is you who placed these weapons on board boat.
How will you prove your innocence?
You planned all that by resentment towards me.
I had warned you that I will have my revenge.
Well, Randolph.
One clinks glasses with your health?
You should not leave in retirement today?
It is one day important for you, not?
You…
You this date purposely, isn't this chose?
Exactly. At the end of your career of devoted actor,
in order to beat you on all the line.
Allow me to be sent in cour martiale as former Major of the Navy.
As you would say it yourself:all is ready.
You do not like to look at tragedies?
Will you think of me when you will be carried out?
Will you curse me by pushing your last sigh?
Here are which will put an end to my revenge.
I must turn over aboard ship.
I must go up on scene.
I do not have time to lose with remains.
Public, my companions
await me!
I must go back there now!
You…
Turn over on board near your companions!
I do not want of the assistance of a pirate.
I can count only on myself this time.
You…
What do you want?
Kid… Leave me.
They escape! They escape!
Release! Release! Release!
What does it occur?
Here it is.
Exact.
Why does it always do anything?
What does it still make us, there?
It is all him.
What does one have to make?
It would be said that one does not have the choice.
Ah, I will help it.
You are very courageous you!
What you ace known as?
Did Randolph flee?
What do they make?
Catch it! You dispatch!
Ah… The enemy is too powerful.
The farm! If you let it escape,
I send all to you in cour martiale!
You cannot act with more delicacy?
Draw! Draw!
Run the boat of Randolph and this type consequently occasion!
Use all the guns!
Or it is you who will go in cour martiale!
Take again the representation!
Try to go until the end of the part!
We will protect the scene!
Fire!
Danger!!!
Luffy!
You believe that this kind of filths is able to kill me?
I will become the Lord of the Pirates!
I will not let any of these balls touch the ship!
Concentrate on the representation, pépé.
Do many people await this last representation, not?
Believe me!
Once I decided something, I am ready to risk my life!
It is that… a pirate!
Kid!
You do not brag a little?
The spectacle will begin again!
All with Randolph-San!
Well! One begins again!
I all will put in this last representation!
Well!
Run the boats of the pirates and Randolph!
But there are civilians in this boat.
It is Randolph which of it will be responsible.
Attack and one will see the remainder afterwards.
But…
It is likely to flee. If you do not run the boat of Randolph,
you all will be responsible!
All the ships start to attack.
That all the ships start to bombard.
Zoro and Sanji-Kun, you of these boats occupy!
Well!
I occupy myself some.
One will let pass no ball!
The balls arrive!
Fire!!
It is which this type?
That rebounded.
He, does not let you go.
I did not can anything make…
Why do you say that?
You are not responsible.
It is the fault of Baran the pirate.
He wants to have all the treasures.
All beautiful princesses and islands too.
Begin again yourself. Do not die!!
We must use the same weapons as them.
Fire!!!
Look at!
Qu… What?
Fire! Fire! Fire!
With 15° by starboard.
Here me is!
Dispatch you to run the ship of Randolph!
Let us attack the pirates together.
Which ball this type.
Second round!
Fire!
We do not have the advantage by defend us.
It is interminable.
It is necessary that they approach so that the advantage is taken again.
Robin, do something with these gunners.
Even if it is a little far, I will test.
Take that.
Super!
Well!
One approaches them!
Do not be afraid.
Ahead!
The flagship is attacked!
Included/understood. Go in reinforcement.
Not. You do not occupy of them.
It is the reserve of ammunition.
A cigarette can start an explosion.
They is bad to throw cigarettes anywhere.
Caution.
What did it occur?
It is this type there?
At all events,
attack the ship of Randolph.
Call reinforcement!
Ok!
It is what the problem?
This type cannot…
What does he want?
It is the famous hunter of pirates,
Roronoa Zoro d' East Blue.
Guessed well.
More one gesture!
Ah… Great news!
It is my last representation.
If I cannot pronounce a word,
all will have been vain.
You! Marly, Lieutenant of the Navy!
That made 100 years that I await you!
Your time is counted!
Wait…
Save to us, please.
We do not have anything against you.
Stop attacking us.
If we do not listen to the orders of Major Gabana,
we will be…
Gabana?
But which is these types, good blood?
It is obvious that it is truth
Luffy with the Straw hat.
Who that?
A type which is worth 100 million Berrys.
You… How can you not know
this formidable adversary?
I submitted a report/ratio.
It could be that it is the crew of the Luffy pirate to the Straw hat. You inform.
Which are the evidence?
I must send to you in cour martiale.
Very well.
I will tell you the truth now.
All that counts for you, it is your promotion.
To stop the pirates does not interest you at all.
You do not fulfill your role of Major.
Moreover…
Now, you will pay for all that.
It is finished for you!
You have committed all these crimes and transformed
the world in a true hell!
It is unforgivable!
I will not save to you.
I will put my life concerned, leaves to die about it.
Until you, dirty pirates…
What is there?
You forgot your text?
“Until you, dirty pirates, are destroyed!”
It does not arrive any more at speaking?
Is it the end? Now?
Randolph, that does occur? “Until you, dirty pirates, are destroyed!”
I must fight thoroughly against you,
scorning characters!
Yes. Our enemies
are not the pirates.
We were wrong.
Our enemies are these types whose heart dirty and is rotted,
filled up of a disgusting lust.
During too a long time, this island was dominated by the Baran pirate who had established his base here.
What you known as?
It is not in the scenario!
My friends.
My very dear friends.
Even if you lost the hope or those which you like,
please, continue to believe that the force
who pushes us with living is more powerful.
Believe there firmly and
create your future in this direction!
It is true.
How them!!!
Return! Return quickly!
Return to protect me!
For this type? But which would do it?
All the time, we fought for
that this type can appease its ambitions!
To become Major of the Navy… It remains to him still much of way to traverse.
As long as I am in life,
I will be able to do all that I want.
I will not let myself make, it is with me.
Yo!
I will burst you.
Go, leave with your companions…
It is that the good spirit.
Carry out your dreams!
With the pride of the sea,
continue your dreams.
We are…
Companions.
The last representation of Randolph comes to a end.
It was brilliant!
Thank you thousand times, everyone.
It is the end one would say, pépé.
It is finished.
I wanted to see his last representation.
I will have had at least to say goodbye or something…
Does not cause them any more troubles.
And Navy…
To bind friendship with pirates is not easy.
The pirates are pirates.
It is impossible for them to borrow the same way as normal people.
But at least, it will be necessary to remember it the happy heart.
The formidable last representation.
He, pépé!!
Do not forget that one must finish our baston!!
Do not forget!!
Similar for you, kid!