(Based on Manga ch.14: 'Reckless", ch.15:
"Gong", ch.16: "Versus Buggy's Crew"...)
(ch.17: "High Level, Low Level", ch.18: "The
Pirate Buggy The Clown" and ch.19: Devil Fruit)
I will chew up his head this time.
GOMU GOMU NO!...
Gavel!
Be my partner, Nami.
Let's do it for our own
purpose. Let's do it together.
OK. Fire!
Here it comes... ack!
(Episode 7) "Grand Duel! Zoro the
Swordsman vs. Cabaji the Acrobat!"
(Episode 7) "Souzetsukettou!
Kengou Zoro VS Kyokugei no Cabaji!"
I kept my promise...
to come here to clobber you.
Straw-hat kid!
How dare you come back again...
to be here facing me!
Listen!
I just want the map and
the treasure. Nothing else!
Whatever.
You three kids.
What are you doing
here? Stay out of this.
This is my fight.
I am protecting my home town.
You guys stay out of this!
How could you do that?
How could you
do that to the mayor?
He's in the way!
Good idea.
If you hadn't punched him, he
would've got himself killed.
He's better off unconscious.
Don't be stupid!
There must be some other way!
Here goes!
Super big nose!
Don't ever say it!
Damn idiot!
How dare you say that to me!
Give him the Buggy Ball!
Don't you know when to shut up?
Luffy! Watch out!
That little bomb...
Blow him up!
...not gonna work on me!
GOMU GOMU NO!...
Balloon!
Who he hell is that guy?
He is not trying to bounce the bomb...
back to us, is he?
Why didn't you tell us earlier?
That evens the odds the little!
Who the hell are you?
What a showoff.
Since you fought with the lion,
I had a strange feeling about you!
You're not a normal human thing!
Explain yourself!
The air balloon belly
thing! How did you do that?
It's like my belly is made of rubber.
That's what I'm talking about!
Are you a monster or something?
You got some nerve.
He's using his crewmen as human shields.
I am so stuffed.
What happened?
You are...
Hi.
It's the hat kid!
Captain Buggy. Watch out for this guy.
He has the devil fruit power too.
He is a rubber man.
What?
Rubber man? >> Right.
He ate the devil fruit, too.
No wonder he could bounce back the bomb.
This is the most embarassing time
ever in the history of piracy.
Captain.
It's too humiliating.
I am too angry to talk.
Cabaji! What have you done to Richie?
The kitty?
I was afraid my clothes would get
dirty, so I used him as a shield.
Richie!
Hang on, Richie. Are you alright?
Why you little...
Get away!
You get away!
Captain Buggy.
What, Cabaji?
Let me handle this.
Show them how bad we are.
I am Second Mate, Cabaji.
I will get you back...
for our captain!
If it's a sword flight, I will take it.
It's my honor, Roronoa Zoro.
I can chop up a famous
swordman like you.
Zoro, you get some
rest. I will handle it.
Keep out of this.
Hurt by the captain, right? Stupid.
The Breath Of Death!
What's up?
I didn't think I kicked that hard.
That mean guy! He aimed for his wound!
Murder At The Steam Bath!
What kind of circus trick is that?
You're just kicking up dust!
He did it again!
What?
You are a man. Don't act like a wuss.
Now you know how scary I am, huh?
It's too stupid of you to be against us.
Is he out of his mind?
He is wounded seriously.
It's a miracle for him to
be alive with that wound.
What are you doing here?
He is going to be killed!
Roronoa Zoro...
Go to hell!
Damn you!
You like to attack my wound?
Then you're gonna love this!
Why didn't you avoid him?
That's enough. Stop
hitting below the belt.
Now I'll show you some real swordsplay.
Cool!
So, Roronoa Zoro...
I underestimated you.
My ambition is to be the
greatest swordfighter.
I will never lose to anyone.
I got it.
It's you dream and
you are trying so hard.
But don't worry.
You are severely wounded
and I am your enemy.
It's reasonable for you to lose.
It's the other way around
If I lose just because of a small wound,
I might as well give up on my dream.
You scurvy dog!
Go, Zoro.
I am out of here.
I don't care. Do
whatever you want.
What you do is none of my business.
I'm gonna get the treasure now.
Let's be partners next time.
Bye, good luck on the fight.
Thank you.
Let me show you my circus trick.
The Dance of a Hundred Kamakaze Tops!
Luffy and Zoro are both freaks.
It's always bad luck being around them.
Here it is.
I will take the map and
treasure and sneak away.
And now...
A Hike In The Mountains!
And now, Fireworks In
The Cool Summer Breeze.
Wow! He's way up there!
Sting Of The Unicycle!
Chop Chop, Low
Flying Cannon!
Cabaji! I will trap Zoro!
Thanks.
Why you...
Luffy.
Damn you!
When Zoro is fighting...
keep your hands off.
Look at all that treasure!
They are all mine.
What are you doing to my treasure?
Soneone found me!
Buggy said, anyone
who comes near here...
It's empty.
It hurts!
What's wrong?
My chest hurts!
What chest?
Checkmate!
The map of the Grand Line!
I don't need the
Captain's help to kill you.
Enough. I am tired.
You finally gave up.
It's amazing for you to hang on
for so long with a serious wound.
I am tired... of your
stupid circus tricks.
No more tricks I'll finish you now...
...with real swordsmanship!
Go to hell!
Oni-giri!
"Onigiri" = Demon Slash
Cabaji!
I can't believe we pirates...
...lost to these thieves!
We are not thieves.
We are pirates!
I'm going to sleep, Luffy.
Ok, leave the rest to me.
It's so much treasure. No
wonder they are notorious.
It's making me tired.
But with so much treasure...
We gotta get out here!
You said you are pirates.
Yes. We are going to the Grand Line!
It's not a place idiots like you
can just go because you want to go.
Why do you want to go to the Grand Line?
And don't tell me for sightseeing.
I wanna be the pirate king!
Don't be a fool!
If you were pirate king,
would I be God of the pirates?
Only I can be the pirate king and
get all the treasure in the world.
So forget it!
Shut up.
Come on! Show me what you got!
Seeing your hat reminds me
of that man. It's annoying.
That stupid red hair man
is a real pain in the butt.
Red hair?
You said "red hair"?
You mean you know Shanks?
So? So what if I now him?
Where is he now?
Well, If I know where he
is, I know where he is...
But if I don't know where he is,
so I don't know where he is...
What are you talking
about? Are you a moron?
Hey! Watch your mouth!
I am not a good man and
don't think I will tell you.
Then I will make you tell me.
You'll be dead before I tell you.
Rubber won't bounce back a razor blade!
It sure can't.
Chop Chop
Buzz Saw!
You can't escape in the air...
Now you can't get away.
Sure I can.
This is getting interesting!
Same here.
GOMU GOMU NO! PISTOLET!
What an interesting skill.
It's not quite perfect.
I will chop you up!
GOMU GOMU NO!...
Chop Chop Quick Dodge!
...Sickle!
You underestimate me, Gummy Boy!
Damn, you're no fun.
What kind of fight is this?
I am like dreaming.
Hey, did you see that?
Shut up and stay still!
If we get involved, we're mincemeat!
Chop Chop Harpoon!
Separate!
Now you know how good I am, kid. Huh?
You bastard!
What? You're upset
because I hurt your face?
You hellspawn! How dare you ruin my hat!
So?
This is my treasure!
I will never forgive
anyone who ruins my hat!
I swore to the man who gave me the hat.
I told him I would become a pirate.
I thought nothing fazed this guy...
...but he looks pretty mad.
That hat must be important to you.
Yes.
That hat is very precious?
Since it's your treasure...
...then protect it well!
Shanks.
Your arm!
Keep my hat with you.
It's my best hat. Please
take good care of it.
You must return my hat someday...
...when you become a pirate king.
Promise, Luffy?
What kind of "treasure"
is this ugly hat?
A treasure is supposed to
be like gold or something.
It should be valuable to
represent the owner's reputation.
You said this beat up
old thing is "treasure".
Don't be ridiculous.
That hat represents
my promise with Shanks!
What?
It's Shanks's hat?
That's why it looks familiar.
He always wears the
hat when I was with him.
You used to sail on the same boat?
Yes. When I was an apprentice pirate.
We were pals.
That damn red hair guy!
Shanks is a great man!
You were pals?
Don't flatter yourself!
Chop Chop Quick Escape!
Don't say you are Shanks's pal!
It's none of your business.
Tell me what happened
between you and Shanks!
Damn.
What have you done to my treasure?
You really wanna know?
I will never forgive him.
I will curse him to death.
I will never forgive him!