Just let to me say a thing…
NORO NORO BEAM!
Remember of that, Straw hat,
I am a man who obtains
always what he wants!
Foxy, the silver fox!
I will empocherai the 160
million and all your gold!
This time, I you
inform with certainty…
That Foxy Pirates are
the most powerful crew.
This guy would it be invincible?
The most dangerous man!
They fell, all the five.
Oyabin, that we go
to make now?
It is simple!
We will crush Straw hat and will make them pay what one underwent in Davy Back Fight!
Porch! Hamburger!
One passes in the plan D!
They seem to make
celebrates on the other boat.
They would be still in
train making a banquet?
Doctor, you can go to see whether you want.
I can remain alone to keep the boat.
I remain with you, and I continue my studies.
I do not want absolutely to go there.
Good blood, to make me berner like that!
Show yourself, Tête of Puzzle.
Calm you Luffy.
You are furious because of your cut afro.
In fact, this wig you
give more class, you know.
Yes, but why afro?
We saved it but it
always think of being avenged.
But one should not forget too
that it intends to steal our gold!
But it is too negligent.
If we really want it,
we can destroy this place.
With us five!
With us four…
In any case, if we do not escape
quickly from here, this Oyabin still will act as coward.
We can escape by here.
It is what this part?
Choppy!
Where is… Choppy?
Where did it pass?
If you do not show yourself
not, I will punish you!
Doesn't something go, Doctor?
Not… nothing…
Whore! It is the kind
of joke that I…
Wait, Sanji!
Luffy!
He, you!
Yes?
Where is Tête of Puzzle?
Haa?!
Porch does not know!
What? You do not know?
- Perpetual Stupidity…
- At all!
- It does not include/understand?
- It is incredible.
“If you do not know, I will have to seek.”
It would seem that he is not there.
Luffy!
Qu… What?
Luffy, looks at its face well!
What is that there is?
You are…
The little sister of Head of Puzzle?!
They is enough, low the masks!
YOU ES Head of Puzzle! I
to me am still made berner!
I really hallucinate.
Take that,
Hat-of-straw!
NORO NORO BEAM!
You thus do not include/understand?!
Nobody escapes Noronoro Beam!
This guy starts to aggravate me.
Really?
NORO NORO BEAM!
Nami!
He, you!
Imbecile, draws aside you!
Sanji-kun! Zoro!
Ho not, it had them!
Avoided Hat well of
straw! Species of coward!
Stop, bastard!
He knows really it
direction of the “loose” word?
He, Nami! Allons-y!
Yes!
You two, remain thirty seconds there!
What?
Wait a little!
Na… Nami-swan…
What?
There is something of writing!
Look at.
“No woman can enter. Entry
authorized with the men only. “
What does that want to say?
Humm, would be careful then.
Doesn't something go, Doctor?
Nothing…
It is terrible.
I am of agreement.
It is only one banal corridor.
It is what that!?
What do they have?
I see. It is a prison.
They were surely imprisoned
here to have been stupid.
Ca… Ca is likely to be
difficult to cross.
U… A girl.
Hurrah!
After all this time.
Not, I do not have courage of it.
I occupy myself some, Nami.
Usopp.
They are imprisoned in this place sinks for a long time, they are not accustomed to the light.
If I use this flashbang, they
will be plugged during one moment.
And thus us
let us precipitate, it is that?
Exactly.
Firm the Nami eyes!
Yosh, now Nami!
- Na… Nami! Nami!
- Yosh, I hold it!
Usopp!
- Does not leave me! …
- Lets I touch too!
Very well! Ca wants to say that I
must continue, is not this?!
- He, wait! That what you are…
- They is really soft.
- After all this time…
- So soft.
Doesn't something go, Doctor?
Heu, nothing…
It was less one!
Which is this place?
Yo, Nami!
Luffy!
You spent time of them.
What you make here?!
What? I eat sembei and I drink it
tea. [Sembei:Japanese rice cookie]
I SEE IT WELL!
Played well. To do all
this way, I admire you.
But…
Heu, but to occupy Straw hat and
to attract to you here belonged to my plans.
Why me!?
Because you are navigatrice,
and expert in strategy.
If I remove you both…
The crew of Hat
of straw will not be any more!
I see.
Very well.
Let us start.
You in redemandes, small!
Iya, we go finally in
to finish with Straw hat!
It is what?
I do not know that one, but
that one, it is Gorilla Panties.
Not “Panties”! It is
Gorilla Puncher n°13!
It left,
Hat-of-straw!
GORILLA PUNCH
Hide Nami.
GOMU GOMU NO…
GUN!
You did not forget, is not this
does pas Chapeau- strip of straw?
If your punch touches me, it…
Ignite.
You forgot!
Luffy!
Remainder attentive!
You are now the prey
of Roboton Kick n°18!
He, Nami!
Water! Give me water!
Ok! I included/understood!
Hope you to beat Oyabin
by using the magic?
Ca arrives Luffy!
The storm brings the rain!
THUNDER STORM TEMPO
Imbecile! Believe you to be able to destroy
Gorilla Puncher n°13 with a flash?
You did not really include/understand anything.
Neither flashes, nor rain
will not damage this machine!
One noticed.
Didn't you still seize?
Your punches
do not have any effect here.
GORILLA PUNCH GOLDEN DELICIOUS KICK
Fire is extinguished by the rain!
Iya, which do you make?
GOMU GOMU NO…
CORE
Oyabin, not by there!
Oh my God!
What did it occur?
It is Oyabin!
Oyabin gained!
He guys!
I lost!
We did not can anything
to make because of your slowness
AND WHY You ACE NOT BULGE, YOU!
He Straw hat! Since
I lost this combat, I incline myself!
Be useful yourself… do what it you like!
No problems.
Then leaves them
to become again your companions.
What? Those which wounded
my pride of pirate?
You do not want?
Straw hat… you are…
Yosh, OK!
Such is the will of Hat
from straw, you are discharged!
Oyabin.
Look at them. See them.
Afflicted, Straw hat.
Would you like to work again for me?
Oyabin!
It is charismatic at least.
Ca tends to irritate me.
Oyabin!
What you
make, Sanji-kun?
It was right for
to joke, to joke.
Take care of you, Straw hat!
You too!
Ho, Yeah!
Stop that!
Is Ca better, Usopp?
I see. Why am I here?
Nami, how did you dare to give up me!?
They is false, Usopp.
In fact…
Ha, then that occurred like that.
Impressing, the enemy is
gone beyond my forecasts.
Oyabin, which one goes
to make now?
We go sought new
taking part in Davy Back Fight?
Of course!
Oyabin has a new terrifying idea.
Listen to me all.
As long as we will not have beaten them,
we will have to support this scar.
There is thus only one
direction to be followed, theirs!
I will not leave myself
to escape to you, Straw hat.
Guys! I see an island!
This island seems uninhabited.
You prepare, we drop anchor!
Well, then. That each one leaves
to find food.
Yeah!
No rats, nor frogs, OK?!
You are only one weakling!
It is the same thing one
time in your stomach…
He, Sanji! We have full with
fish, of vegetables and fruits!
Thank you, I appreciate.
Health!
Delicious.
He, Luffy. Do not make the goinfre.
He said that he had a hunger of wolf, but
although he already ate, he is still hungry.
It there of forever enough!
With such an appetite, one
will have any more quickly nothing to eat.
Robin, eats quickly front
that there is nothing any more.
I almost finished this book.
But if you continuous with reading all it
time like that, you will become a zombie.
And this book must be made for that.
I found you
Hat-of-straw.
You all are ready?
All is OK, Oyabin.
We are ready.
Oyabin, they look at
all in our direction.
Do not make any you. They believe
all that it is a crab.
A false crab, of course.
It is them?
They thus give up never.
If they could stop…
Ok, let us destroy their boat.
How is what it is?!
Ca with the delicious air!
It does not have…
Yes, it did not include/understand.
Release us, Straw hat!
It test to escape!
Shit! Take that!
Now!
KANIGANI PUNCH
Thus Straw hat died.
He you!
It is not poor small
crab which will resist to me!!
Takes that!
Ah, what? You were
facts of eating by crab?
I am too naive.
It is now that you it remarks!
You do not occupy of them,
the barbecue awaits us.
All this stir gave me hunger.
Ah, that did not finish cooking.
Not, it is better like that.
Oyabin, I am hungry!
Baka! You are hungry?!
You forgot that you made
part of Foxy Pirates…
Afflicted to have made you
to wait, Miss!
Here the dish of the day.
Iya, that with the delicious air!
Eat, please.
Iya, it is excellent,
you could have knocked me down with a feather!
Cook, come on our
boat please.
Iya, when Porch-san speaks
how that, that gives me desire!
Please go ahead, I ask it to you.
Hello, here the station of communication.
Oyabin is KB, then
join us please.
Ah not they is good, it
is always alive.
Then, ciao.
Cook-san, goodbye. They was delicious.
Porch is impressed.
Take care of you Porch-chan!
You do not want to really go there?
Imbecile, who will deal with the meals
of Nami-san and Robin-chan afterwards?
Is not this step Nami-san?
Sanji-kun! Zoro! Let us leave to find
more food for our reserves!
Ouuuiiiii, Nami-swan!
He Chopper. You found
plantes médicinales?
I found much of it. This
island is filled with rare plants.
There is a thing which me
disturb since one moment,…
Which is this strange line?
It is true, which this is
what that can be well?
It would seem that one
cyclist passed by there.
He He, this island is
uninhabited, isn't this?
Impossible that it is a trace of
bicycle if nobody lives this island.
It is true.
We leave the jungle.
We found a zone cleared.
What does it have, Chopper?
It runs towards this rock.
What is there over there?
Chopper reserves this large
mushroom for him all alone!
Wait!
How is what there is, Chopper?!
It occurs something, allons-y!
How is what it is?!
An raccoon?
I am a reindeer! Look at my horns!
You are well, Chopper?!
Who it is this guy?
What did it occur?
Doesn't something go, Luffy?
Who are you?
Who you are?!
It is which this giant?
Who is this man?
Robin!
That it occurs
Robin-chan?
Robin!
Why do you tremble?
Robin.
Alalala?
Let us go, go, are not
if not frightened Miss.
I am not on mission.
The weather is splendid,
then I trott myself.
On mission? For what a organization?!
It is a navy, one of more
great powers of the government.
He?!
The admiral of the Navy, Ao Kiji.
Alalala! You became one
very beautiful woman, Nico Robin.