Meeting of the powerful ones!
Its name is Ace with the burning fists
With the kingdom of the Oases.
Three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
In a howl of sadness, this desiccated ground sinks from now on in an enormous wave of agitation.
Princess Vivi, accompanied by Luffy and her crew, finally arrived at the Kingdom of Arabasta.
They accosted with the port of the town of Nanohana.
While hiding Works Baroque,
they prepared in order to cross the desert and to stop the rebellion.
However, Luffy left before the others…
… and found itself, only, far from the city.
Year-Chan = Traveller
Oh! Anchan, I never saw you in the corner.
Is it the first time that you come in Arabasta?
What do you think about it?
Throw a glance there!
It is a gold apple!
Wait one minute!
I have something to say to you into private.
I found this extraordinary treasure when I explored old ruins!
If you eat a piece of this mysterious gold apple, you will be able to live during thousand years!
Afflicted, but to live during thousand years does not interest me.
It will be already well if I survive today.
A gold apple!?
To live during thousand years!?
Really? Really? Really?
You known as to have found it in old ruins!?
Yes, of course!
It is a legendary treasure inherited unmemorable times.
When one eats a piece of it, one can live during thousand years!?
Yes, I never lie.
Brilliant!
Dear customers, you seem to be experts.
Let us see seeing…
If you buy it now, I go down the price to 1000 Berry!
1000 Berry!? Really!?
It is taken! It is taken!
Good blood…
But of what do you think!?
Do not believe all that one tells you.
He, they is good! Leave us quiet!
One can live during thousand years right for 1000 Berry! You do not include/understand!?
Stop with that.
One must find Luffy.
The purchases were finished. At once that one will have found Luffy, one will leave for the next city!
Moreover, I wonder well where is Luffy.
It is enough!
This type…
I would like to ask you something.
Did you already see this man?
Hum? Monkey D. Luffy?
There are chances so that it is in this city.
I seek it here for some time already.
I never saw it.
Oh yes, if you seek somebody,
you should return to you to the restaurant which is a little low.
The owner is with the current of all that occurs in this city.
Thank you.
A restaurant, hum?
I in any event start to be hungry.
Who is it? It with the really strong air.
And why does he seek Luffy?
An bargain hunter?
Not.
It is not one.
This mark…
As an old hunter of pirates,
I will be able to never forget this mark.
But it is…?
I do not believe in it…
What a shame!
To sell this katana 200.000 Berry…
It is swindle!
Do you have at least a license of sale?
Oh, shit!
Roronoa Zoro, you are thus a pirate.
I…
You lied me!
A good-for-nothing like handling you such a splendid saber!
It is unforgivable!
Your Meitou, Wadou Ichimonji…
… will have to be seized!
This woman…
Why is it here?
Please, remade more never a thing also dishonest person.
Was I well made include/understand?
What do you make, Zoro?
Do you hide?
With each time I meet this woman, the troubles are never far.
Shit!
Eh, Tashigi.
Colonel Smoker!
A band of the large pirates playing hard ones.
They started to insult me while dancing in front of me.
I stopped their spectacle.
Even if we are in this place moved away,
your vigilance towards the pirates is always also relentless.
If you have time to lose in words,
why don't you call the royal army of this country so that it removes us from this refuse?
Yes!
We do not have yet any news of the arrival of Luffy to the straw hat in this city.
But remain vigilant!
It will be shown well early or late.
Smoker…
It is well the Colonel of the Navy of Logue Town?
That would like to say that…!
What it could be well with our cases since we left Logue Town?
Look by there.
And there is also this other type which we saw… that becomes dangerous.
But where is thus this… idiotic?
I…
I am hungry…
Thank you well. Afflicted to take your lunch, Ossan.
I ate it too quickly. It is as if I had not eaten anything…
OR IS THE CITY!?
OR IS FOOD!?
To eat!
TO EAT!
Does Hey, what occur?
What did it arrive?
It seems that a customer died suddenly in it.
Died suddenly?
It would seem that he died while discussing with the owner the restaurant.
It is a traveller.
Everyone says that he undoubtedly ate a Strawberry of the Desert.
A Strawberry of the Desert?
It is a poisoned egg of spider which resembles a strawberry.
If one eats one of them, one dies suddenly a few days later.
Then, a few hours later, a contagious poison escapes from the body and is propagated in the air.
It is for that nobody approaches him.
In the desert, which one does not know can kill us.
Look at how that arrived:it was going to take another mouthful…
… and it solidified, like that!
That shows well the power of the poison of the Strawberry of the Desert…
IT IS RESSUSCITE!
is this E-that goes?
Sea…
Shit…
I fell asleep.
YOU DEADENED ES!?
This is not possible!
Right in the middle of a meal and a conversation!?
And it continues its meal as so nothing was…
And you, what you made here?
WE WORRIED FOR YOU!
You engaged of comic or a trick in the kind?
Eh well, not… but, if you are well, I am happy.
HEY!
YOU RENDORS NOT!
What? Then he had not died?
Which waste of time.
Ah, I am more hungry!
In the fact, Oya-San.
Oya = Landlord
What?
This type downtown, isn't this is not?
A pirate wearing a straw hat…
I suppose that to eat in public no difficulty arises.
Ordering the Second Division of the pirates of White Beard.
Portgas D. Ace.
Does bar Beard White!?
Pirates of White Beard!?
Does this imbecile belong to the pirates of White Beard!?
I knew well that I had already seen this tattooing…!
It is well the mark of the pirates of White Beard!
Why is it here?
What can attract well an infamous pirate like you in this country?
I am with research…
… of my little brother.
TO EAT!
Is qu What it?
There is a strange odor which comes from this place.
There!
A restaurant!
Then…
What should I make?
Sitted remainder and lets stop you to me.
Rejected.
Ca does not say to me.
Eh well, I expected it.
In any event, I am here in the search of another pirate.
Your head really does not interest me.
Then lets leave to me.
I cannot do that…
Because I am Navy…
… and you, a pirate.
Which reason idiot…
We thus will amuse we a little. Not?
A restaurant!
I finally found one of them!
Now I can eat! I am too hungry!
Ossan! To eat, eat, eat!
I am really hungry!
Quickly, quickly, quickly.
To eat, eat, eat!
Super!!!!!
Ca, it is a restoring good!
O-oui…
Thank you, but you…
You would make better of you be from there very far from here.
Why?
Do you know those which you have just sent in the air?
To send in the air? Who did that?
You.
I did that? With which?
A hole has why there here?
This restaurant is odd.
To make is holes your pastime?
It IS YOU WHO ACE MADE CA!
Me? When?
Jerk…
But which it was? Brothel…!
To be caught some with me…
It is what this idea? To do that with me to me…
Accept my excuses to have stopped your meal.
Who is this prehistoric imbecile who did that? Brothel!
Lu…
Eh, Lu!
STRAW HAT!!
I sought you, Straw hat.
I knew that you would come here, in Arabasta.
DECREE TO EAT!
Is it…
Finally there?
Luffy with the straw hat.
I said it to you:if you do not beat me, you will never go on Grand Line.
What, what, what…?
I ate the fruit Moku Moku.
My body can be transformed into smoke as soon as I want of it!
You include/understand now?
You will never go on Grand Line.
How I said it to you!
It is smoked out! What do you make there!?
Dumb…
Wait a little!
Thank you for the meal.
WAIT!
Wait, Luffy! It is me!
Eh, wait!
Eh! Luffy!
He eats while running…
Shit, my Gomu Gomu does not go on him!
Is better than I leave while running!
TASHIGI!
Yes, that is there Colonel Smoker?
Do you want a towel?
It is really hot here!
Catch it! It is Straw hat!
Straw hat!
I will cut it into two!
Tashigi!
Call all the Navy available urgently!
Seek his/her companions in all the recesses of this city!
Yes!
A fruit eater of the demon!
Incredible!
Pirates of Straw hat…
That wants to say…
Roronoa Zoro is in this city.
Straw hat, why did you come in this country?
What do you seek?
What? I am here for botter the bottom of Crocodile!
What? Crocodile?
What does Crocodile have to see with you?
It disappeared!
Dumb! Played well!
Straw hat!
I wonder where is Luffy-San…
It is shitting.
It is a Captain who always should be supervised.
Oh, Nami-San!
Oh, oh, I have bad news.
One would make better leave now.
This place is badly attended.
Badly attended?
The Navy is there.
Navy!?
And an odd guy too.
Let us find as quickly Luffy as possible and leave this city.
Eh, with ground!
What?
What occurs?
Navy.
One hears them since there.
They must have some after somebody.
Do not let it escape!
Do not lose it!
They are surely idiots of pirates who run on the place.
Idiots of pirates!?
Stop, Straw hat!
It IS YOU!?
Eh, Zoro!
Whoa, everyone is here!
Imbecile! Do not come!
They are still with your cases!
They are the pirates of Straw hat! They are seen!
Does Eh, what one make?
Our only option, it is the escape.
One must turn over to the boat!
You dispatch! Allons-y!
IMBECILE!
Halt! You will not escape!
Behind everyone!
Colonel!
Straw hat is with me!
Ah, it will have me!
You will not escape to me!
Still you…
Drop.
You are smoke, but I am fire.
Our capacities make a combat useless.
This guy has the capacities of a fruit of the demon?
But which is it?
Why does it help us?
Ace!
You did not change, Luffy.
Ace…
It is Ace!
You ace eaten a fruit of the demon!?
Ouais, the fruit Mera Mera.
Colonel Smoker! Which are your orders!?
We cannot speak now!
I find you later! Let us go away!
I deal with these guy!
Go ahead!
Allons-y!
But, Luffy…
Who it is this guy?
I do not include/understand.
Why did you help Straw hat?
A big brother always worries for his little brother when this one has troubles.
What do you want to say by “little brother”?
That wants to say that…
Release!
Portgas D. Ace!
Ca would astonish me.
Wait, Luffy. Say to us just who it was!
Do you know it, Luffy-San?
Ouais!
It is my brother!
BROTHER!?