It seems to me that it was by here.
Found!
If all occurs as envisaged…
Luffy and the others must be on the way towards the dock with gold.
Forgiveness.
I had really forgotten.
I was worried so much at this time.
But one can use this Waver even on the sea blue.
Yosh! We dispatch! One turns over over there!
Sanji-kun, is clutched with me.
Good idea!
I am happy to be in life!
God, Buddha, I am grateful to you!
Ah… Yes, yes…
It does not matter, hurries to climb!
In this case, I will not deprive myself!
MORON!!
How you want that I lead like that?!
The demonstration of the love of Nami-san is so much… dynamic!
I cannot that to fall under the charm!
Go, one goes there!
Catch to them all in only one net!
The secret plan of Jonathon
It would be said well that one was made berner.
They dared all the same…
Me also, I would like to catch a fish as large as that one!
Stop your remarks without interest!
One opened this trunk with the danger of our life!
Since this flight of the chart, the Commander guessed that you would appear here undoubtedly.
Which person crafty one.
Now there is no more loophole.
Whore…!
Even if Zoro and Luffy are strong…
One would have can be to await Sanji and the others to force these doors to open outside…
Not.
Our presence must be announced.
All the reinforcements must hurry.
It is nothing any more but one matter of time.
Useless to wait longer.
Hein? If our gold is not there,
one has only to seek it elsewhere.
As if it were easy to make.
One must fight all these types…
and to make jump all these armor-plated doors if one wants to flee from here!
And then?
It is true!
One will not deflate!
On the honor of Navarone,
we will demolish you!
Usopp Pinch!
[Pinch:Bad Posture]
They will launch the offensive….
It is the end, pirates of Straw hat.
Hein?
Konteriano?
As I expected it, you finally came in the chambre forte.
Who be you, good blood?!
What it takes to you to open the doors as good seems to you?!
You conceal!
I am the special inspector of the General headquarter.
The Lieutenant of Sheppard frigate!
With the authorization of the Commander, I direct the special regiment of the General headquarter.
I do not need you.
Do not intervene!
Hein? Euh….
I already saw it some share….
Ah! It is the type which was in the same cell as Usopp and Zoro!
What is this you ace to make the malignant one?
Yo, Konteriano! You ace successful to escape to you!
You have the air in form.
I owe you all a proud candle…
Be sure…
that I will return the similar one to you…
for all the services that you returned to me until now with the interests in premium!
Lieutenant Sheppard.
What y' has, just when that became interesting…
With if military low power,
it is useless to try to apprehend them.
Do not underestimate them…
Close it! Close it! Close it! Close it!!
Mets not soldiers of the HQ and soldiers of the fortress of Navarone in the same bag!
We go éradiquer the pirates of Straw hat.
You have only to admire the spectacle.
Included/understood?
Yes…
You finished ace?
Would be patient! I will crush to you now!
Give it to me…
Yes!
It is what?
It is the last model of portable bazooka developed by the General headquarter of the Navy!
Greenhouses of the marine eagle baptized “Eagle launcher”!
Its fire power is equal to that of a battleship.
[Battleship:Navire de guerre]
WHAT?!
It was still brought back with a frightening machine.
And then?
Approaches!
If such is your request, I cannot refuse it to you!
Burst!
What?
Played well, Konteriano!
Lieutenant, it is with back, back!
Hum?
Is Ah, it thus that?
Oi!!
Close it! This time, I will arrive there!
Not, not! Not at this place!
Crowned Konteriano.
What did it come to make, this imbecile?
I am amazed by this special army at the General headquarter.
Go, on the way.
Yosh! Gold, gold!
He! Have-HAVE-await! He!
Dumbs of pirates of Straw hat!
This time, I…
CUSE Konteriano!
Do not let them escape!
Continue them!
Is He, where gold?
Me it of mande not to me!
The monitoring is narrower than I thought it.
Only with Nami-san in front of the sea in this romantic night…
It is the whore of better, Nami-san!
Sanji-kun…
Whore of cheer, Nami-san!
Sanji-kun!
It is a whore of fantastic, Nami-san!
That has the candy taste!
Whore, Nami-s.
Sanji-kun! Close it with your “whores”.
It would be said that they know that we are still in bay,
but then, why do they remain motionless?
That intrigues me.
Let us find a place sure to re-examine our plan.
You believe that there exists a sure place in Navarone?
Of course!
With the canteen where I was with Sanji for example!
But it is there that all the Navy puffs out!
Nobody would go in a so dangerous place!
But wait a little…
it is what our enemies must also think…
Yosh! It is decided!
Let us eat!
It is not the moment!!
I am a true pirate from now on.
I progressed well.
I will protect this ship costs which costs.
I am a guy on whom one can count.
Chopper!
Nami, Sanji!
You are healthy and safe!
I did not at all only feel, the guy…!
Isn't Luffy and the others yet there?
Not, I assemble the guard all alone.
It is strange.
It perhaps arrived to them something…
And thus with our gold too?
Yes…
I will seek them!
It is the second part of our exit with Nami-san!
Again only!
Sanji, you also will keep the boat.
I have a favor to ask you…
It seems to me that the chambre forte is in this direction.
It is….
These foutus pirate of Straw hat fled in direction of the mountain.
Towards the mountain!
You dispatch!
Do not trail!
Is all well, Lieutenant Sheppard?
Shit!
I was with two fingers to have them…
But it is not because they found a trunk empty which they will throw the sponge for as much.
We still have a chance!
Hein! Vacuum?!
Lastly, I knew well that something as that would arrive, I thus already worked out a plan of help if.
I never make errors!
The chambre forte was only one trap,
but then, where gold can be well?
GomuGomuNo Fansub
Gomu Gomu No
I thought that it was some share in the corner…
He, He… a little serious!
I believe that I gourré myself!
You stays nevertheless over there presently.
The refectory is located further, here one is with the infirmary.
Chut!
There is somebody!
Dad, please do what I ask you.
Even if it is a request of my daughter,
who would like to swallow such a disgusting trick?
But let us see it is a drug!
This voice…
It is the doctor who was used to us as hostage…
And its papounet!
Wasn't gold any more aboard ship?
Nor in the trunk.
All the same, which surprise
to learn that you were parents.
Doesn't Ossan, then that go extremely?
What? I have only to drink a mouthful of that, then to sleep and I will be immediately cured!
That always has was an effective remedy for me.
Out of the question! No drink is authorized in a private clinic!
Go, just a p' tite mouthful…
Not!
You are not very reconciling…
Ossan, you would make well listen to your daughter… finally the doctor!
How? Thus you show me your gratitude?
I helped you, and despite everything, you have the base to return to line the nose in my business!
You make a point so much of recovering your gold, species of long nose!
Of course, Ossan of the dock.
One is pirates!
It is true that, you worked hard to obtain this gold.
, Be held you quiet, Kobato!
One wants to make economies of them…
Economies?
It was decided all together, that once this gold converted into money, we would renovate our Merry.
Peuh! How if I were going to accept the words of a pirate!
I of insane that you believe in it or not!
It is what one decided between us.
That is not looked at!
What?!
Me, I believe you.
Because he said… ur house.
Their house, hein?
It is there.
It is a small turning.
But there are no soldiers and this way will carry out you towards the mountain without encumber.
It is not a way… it is straightforwardly a cliff!
Well!
One will seek our gold, Ossan!
Thank you for all!
Of nothing!
To take the way…
Lastly, still sorry for the disturbance, Ossan!
Hello!
Wait!
What is there?
Our Commander adores fishing.
One would say well, it has just shown us his technique of door-fitting!
Gold is undoubtedly used as soft food of first choice to fish you.
In this case, it must have highlighted it well in a place.
A place well in obviousness…
A soft food?
Hurry to come!
O-Oui!
Dêpêche to join them.
Ouais…
Hello!
He, wait! Oh!
If these young people succeed in taking again their gold and escaping from here…
Navarone will be in a really annoying situation.
What took to me to help them…?
Finally, there were not time to revise our plan.
Shit!
Will one have to seek all the time while grinding like that?
What is there Zoro?
Not…
I believed to have heard something.
Is this an insect?
Probably my imagination…
Not, it is not your imagination.
That arrives by here.
Waver?
It is Nami!
Thus you re-examined Doctor Kobato.
We do not have any index of the place where gold is.
I want of ronquer…
One should not trail, the sun will not be long in rising.
And it will be then more difficult to move.
Say, has it another chambre forte there?
Even if there were one of them, it would be probably again a trap to attract us inside.
With the fact, presently Ossan said something to me on this subject…
A soft food history…
Hein? About what is it?
I did not seize well but, approximately, he said that…
Here, it is that, Usopp!
Hein?
It is that what?
A soft food to fish us.
In other words, gold is with one
clearly visible place for us.
Visible?
I wonder whether a quite visible place is in fact a place which one can provide.
Ah! I see.
What does that mean?
However in your opinion, which tries “to fish us” by hanging a soft food there?
The Commander de Navarone…
Exact, the fisherman is not other than the Commander de Navarone.
Then the soft food must be near the fisherman,
what brings us to a quite precise place.
Not! Impossible…!
Completely!
What does it take to you?
If I remember well, you said that you knew where was the room of the Commander.
Lead me over there!
Hein?
Yes.
Ok, I go there with Luffy.
Robin and the others, you direct towards bay,
Chopper and Sanji will come to seek you.
Will that go?
One can go up only to two on Waver…
Bah… obviously one will be made locate.
Such an amount of worse.
One goes there to full power!
Be ready for you?
Ouais! When you want!
One goes there!
I they appeared.
It is where?
Quickly, shows to me the way, Luffy!
It is in top! In top!
Where that in top?
Do not loupez them!
It is there!
Included/understood!
But what a good surprise!
Which is this machine?
It is him the Commander?
Ouais, it is Tonton Fortress!
I had not even imagined that you will use this alternative.
It is impressive!
It is a vehicle used in the sky.
There is only Nami which can lead it.
DO NOT SAY THAT TO HIM!!
Yes, sorry.
Young girl, it is the first time that I see you.
Welcome!
In connection with our coarse manners, if you were not pirates, I would have reserved warm welcome to you.
In fact, it is well damage.
You have the fine spirit and a certain notch.
However, even if you are daring, perhaps should think to you of anticipating a little.
This time, no soldier will be able to eat or disturb us…
Luffy with the Straw hat.
But before that, one cannot bite with the hook without soft food…
Hein?
Where is gold?
You some share in this part, isn't this hides it?
You could to at least show it us, not?
Ah, just there.
Right under our eyes!!?
Oh! Gold was found!
Nami, one finally found it!
It is not fake I hope…
I can affirm you that they are gold bels and goods.
You can check it…
Ouais, included/understood!
Luffy!
They is truths!
No the doubt, it is well our gold!
Yosh!
I take the whole!
Uncle Fortress, sorry for the disturbance!
Oh there! Not question of letting escape a catch which bites with the hook.
Do not be violent one with the young girl.
Thank you for this attention.
Initially with the turn of Straw hat.
I all will burst you the mug!
Still this odd net!?
I have more fo-but this.
Hein? Kairouseki!
Straw hat captured!
It is perfect.
And now…
That fears, that fears! That to make,
what to make? Does Y' have a means?
If these types are armed, there must well be a means!
It is cold.
It is hot.
Succeeded!
Is C-C' what?
A cloud?!
Today time is with the good shape.
The risks of downpour are of 0%.
But in certain areas,
an enormous cumulonimbus will be formed!
Take guard with the loves at first sight!
What do play you, young girl?
Luffy!
Hold good!
Afflicted, Nami!
Dispatch, take our gold and goes up!
I have as a practice never not to let my catch slip by once I caught it…
I will catch them all in my net.
Then, Luffy?
You see the ship?
The weather is so dark that I have evil to see there.
Make blunder, Nami!
It is a ship of the Navy.
While looking at there more closely, it does not resemble a battleship…
Ah, they are there!
By here, Luffy!
Nami!!
Nami-swan!! You are healthy and safe!
You thus have just let escape the pirates from Straw hat who had been introduced on your premise.
They have even catch gold moreover…
You made a dishonourable error…
I will not let these individuals escape my influence so easily…
Lieutenant Sheppard.
Here that you start to play the bad losers.
Ah forgiveness!
What do you say some, Commander?
Remain quiet while I take the control of the operations.
Oh, I thought that you had of it already enough!
Presently it was only one negligible error.
And I already prepared a unit of destruction which will crush these pirates.
Oh, in this case, I am in a hurry that you make me a demonstration of your skill.
They is well you, the captain of the Painpiku ship?
The pirates certainly will appear in the neighborhoods of the gate.
Act according to the plan and wait until they are sufficiently close to run them!
Included/understood?
With your orders!
Captain!
We reached the place of ambush.
Yosh! Ensure you not to let pass the boat of the pirates!
We will launch a great offensive as soon as you locate it!
The preparations are perfectly in place.
Do we have to move towards a place raised to admire the spectacle?
If us profi…
Please not touch with that!
Do I can ask you a question?
If it is in connection with the manner of capturing the pirates, I can explain it to you without problem.
The unit of destruction of which you did speak is well Painpiku, hein?
It would be said well that there is another boat here…
What you known as? Is C-C' impossible!?
This battleship does not belong to Navarone.
Lastly, one cannot really regard it as a man-of-war.
C-C' is what this brothel?!
Captain!
A man-of-war… finally which resembles a navire de guerre approaches the back!
A ship of Navarone?
What do you want to say by “which resembles”?
How to say…
If that continues one will strike itself!
Stop! You stop!
Merry! Ahead!!
What! What…!?
Thank you to have opened the way to us!
One thus could arrive up to now in all peace.
All my gratitude!
Thank you well!
Do not let them escape!
Continue them!
It is not most alarming for the moment!
What!?
Im-impossible!
They sent Painpiku by the bottom…!
Dirtinesses of pirates of Straw hat!
If be not agitated!
They were made take, undoubtedly, in the net…
The net?
This evening with 9:00, sea of
Navarone will reveal its hooks.
There will be no loophole.
It will be the opening of curtain of the last trap!
Yosh!
This time, it is the exit!
And our gold was recovered!
It was done, one did it!
Go, one sinks illico towards the gate!
Ouais!
In Luffy with the Straw hat and its crew…
You fought well until now vis-a-vis the fortress of the Navy, G-8 division.
You had an iron will, but that finishes here.
Good, drop, pirate of Straw hat.
It y' still has a means!
Soon in One Part:
Good-bye, the fortress of the Navy!
The final battle towards the escape.
I will become the Lord of the Pirates!
Good-bye, the fortress of the Navy!
The final battle towards the escape