We're not gonna abandon Bellemere!
Damn, why does this have to happen?
Don't give in to them, Bellemere!
Delicious! Truly a Bellemere orange sauce original!
The duck in the oven needs another 10 minutes, gotta add the vegatables
Stew's about ready too. So it's just the egg rice left.
This is going to hit the budget pretty hard.
Oh, they're home now?
SURVIVE!
BELLEMERE, THE MOTHER, AND NAMI'S FAMILY!
It's open! Come in!
Don't mind if I do...
Too bad for you, I'm a former marine.
Now what would a pirate all the way from the
Grand Line want with Cocoyashi village?
What's so funny?!
Useless!
You inferior being that was absolutely useless!
We'll use the backdoor to let her escape!
But the pirates might be in there already!
It's okey
Stop !
Doctor!
You can't go home!
Get out of the way! We have
to rescue Bellemere-san!
Nojiko , Nami !
You two listen up.
It's times like these... Well, because
of a situation like this,
I'm forced to tell you something
that may sound a little cruel.
Doctor !
Bellemere-san!!
It's no use... These guys are real monsters!
We're gonna get killed! Nojiko... Nami!
Bellemere!
Don't waste your life on something trivial.
There are fights without meaning, too!
This can be solved with money!
Gen-San !
That's right, marine girl.
Adults are 100,000. Kids are 50,000.
If you pay for the family's worth, I'll let
you live... As a divine mercy on you.
My family's worth?
That's 200,000 total.
How much do you have in all
Even with everything...
A little over 100,000.
Hey! There's food for three here!
Oh? A three-person family, eh?
It must've slipped my mind...
Today, me and a good friend of mine
were invited over for dinner.
Come to Bellemere, pay up for Your self, the food gonna get cold
Gen-San....
She seems to have the 100,000.
Good thing we all have enough.
Now everyone will be safe.
The census shows that she's never
been married nor had any kids.
She's always been single.
Understand?
There's no proof that you two
and Bellemere are a family.
Leave this island before they find out!
Cross the sea and escape!
There's no other way we can afford
to save all three of you.
I know it's unreasonable for you two
youngsters to venture the sea.
Something could go wrong...
But even if there's the slightest chance...
No.
I don't want to! Why do we have to leave?
They're the ones who invaded us.
I want to stay in this village.
Is it because we're poor, that we can't
be Bellemere-san's daughters?
Why...? Why does it have to be this way?
Thank god. That I could save...
Fine, we'll leave this island.
Nojiko!
We're leaving! That way, Bellemere-san will be safe.
Hold up! Who said that was my share?
That 100,000 is for my two daughters.
I'm short on mine.
Bellemere, You....
Sorry, Gen-san.
I can't deny I don't have a family...
Even if it means sacrificing my life.
That's absurd!
We may not be blood-related,
but we're still a family.
I wish I could be a mother by simply saying it.
Those two... are my daughters, right?
Bellemere-san!!
Hay, You two...
If i was to be adopted, then I'd rather have been taken in By a rich family
I was lying!!
It was a lie!! Bellemere-san!
I really wanted to buy you more stuff,
like books and new clothes.
I'm sorry that I couldn't more
of a mother to you guys.
thats not true !
We don't want anything, just don't die!
Just stay with us!
You need to see the map I'm
gonna draw of the world!
Map, that's right...
Make sure you fulfill your dreams.
Live on' eh?
Bellemere-san!!
These are your daughters, eh?
Yeah, that's right.
You have to promise to leave these girls alone.
Of course! As long as you die.
Help !!
Eh... they've become bloodthirsty.
Don't kill them. Just show them what we're made of.
You'll set a perfect example.
You'll die for your pathetic love.
Nojiko, Nami!
I love you.
You are helpless, you little fox
Let go of me! I'll pay next time...
with My Body!
You made another Boy cry?
Coz they made me mad
Its Ok, Its just a child's fight
They said Bellemeres Orange taste bad!
what did you say?!
Bellemere?
Don't lose to anyone.
Girls have to be strong too.
It doesn't matter if you're not complimented.
Don't hate the era you were born into.
And always remember the strength
to continue laughing.
BELLEMERE-SAN!!
During my reign, people who
don't have money will die!
Do you inferiors understand?
What's this?
A map?
Stop!
That's a special map that I drew! Give that back!
You drew this?
Give it back!
Stop it Nami!
Oh, this is rather good.
She could be useful, bring her with us.
Yes, capt'
Stop! Let go, let go of me! I don't wanna go!
Let go of Nami! Let her go!
Wait! You got your money!
Wasn't the deal to leave them alone?
Yeah, we won't hurt her. We're
just gonna ''borrow'' her.
Gen-san, help me!
Don't you dare hurt those children!
Kuroobi.
Gen-san!
Gen-san!!
Gen-san!!!
I'll save you, Nami...
I won't let you go.
It's okay! Enough already! You don't
have to save me, please just-!
Stubborn fool.
I'll save you...
I don't want anyone else to die!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
All the village's ships have been sunk.
Our plan of letting Nojiko and Nami go to sea was...
Naive.
The marines won't even bother with us.
This island will be taken over.
Bellemere knew...
From her experience as a marine, she knew
instinctively what they would do.
There was no way anyone could escape this fate.
They've taken Nami.
What am I supposed to do now?
Bellemere-san.
We know where Arlong and his gang are!
Looks like they're gonna settle down on this island!
It's time to decide!
Whether we fight to our death,
or gamble our lives and wait for the
day the government saves us.
Knowing that we may die at any moment!
One of these two!
The only ones that can stand up to them are those
people from the ''Marine Headquarters''.
But the Headquarters have their
hands full with the Grand Line.
Chances of them coming out here
to save us are close to zero.
But I can't just ignore Nami.
Let us fight!
Im in too!
I can't abandon a child and think of my own survival.
We're all a family!
Even if we trade blows with them,
we're gonna save Na-chan!
Bellemere traded her life to save those girls!
We'll fight again!
Even if only one of us fought, we'd
all still get blamed anyway!
Yeah! Let's go! Fight!
as long as you continue living, lots of good things will come your way
Nami!
Na-chan!
You're okay!
Nami! Nami!
Are you hurt? Did they make you cry?
Nami ?
I'm... joining...
Huh?
I'm... gonna join Arlong's crew.
I'm gonna be a map-drawer
and draw maps for them!
What are you talking about, Nami?
Are you for real?
Did they make you do this?
That's what happened right?
No
They threatened you to, right?
NO!!
Tell the truth!
Let go of me
Nami!
T-That's Arlong's tattoo!
You !
Look at this! I got all this money!
They're gonna buy me whatever I want!
Nami!
I won't forgive you, I won't!
You're becoming a pirate? I'll never forgive you!
Do you even know who they are?
So what?!
If you live properly and die like Bellemere-san did,
then I don't wanna live properly!
What a thing to say...
Bellemere-san...
Bellemere-san was killed for us!
That's enough, Nojiko.
Listen to me, Nami!
Never step foot in this village ever again!
Nami!
Such a foolish thing to have done...
Wasn't Bellemere like a mother to her?
That wasn't the case.
Nami loved Bellemere-san.
Hey, didn't Bellemere-san always say...
''As long as you continue living, good
things will come your way.''
" lots of good things.''
Yes...
After being captured by Arlong,
I saw him sink five marine ships easily.
The government probably won't
help this island anymore.
I realized that I had to act on my own.
made a deal with Arlong.
I'm going to buy Cocoyashi Village from him.
Buy the village ?
For 100 million beli.
If I buy the town, we'll be free.
No one has to die.
As long as I join that crew and make maps for them.
But 100 million beli.
Even if you worked your entire life for it...
I'll make it! No matter how!
Everyone's having a hard enough
time just paying the tribute.
I have to do this alone.
I ask for their help, they'll just get hurt.
Won't it be hard?
To be with the person who killed Bellemere-san,
I'm fine. I'll just smile whenever I see his face.
I've decided I'll never cry again.
I've decided I'm gonna fight on my own!
For a 10 year old girl to decide to fight
alone and struggle
Do you understand how hard it must've been?
For a deal that would free the village.
That girl...
Whoever makes Nami san suffer I'm gonna..!
Why...one sama..?
Because, I'm telling you not to interfere.
If you guys keep claiming that you're her partners,
the pirates are gonna doubt her loyalty.
And all her hard work these eight
years will be all for naught!
Don't make it any harder than it already is.
She is fighting on her own.
Knowing there are people who call her a
''friend'' is the most painful thing for her.
Stop! Stop it right there!
A Pirate Thief!?
That's right!
I'm gonna make use of this era, where there
are plenty of pirates to steal from!
I'm gonna get them back!
Aren't those cuts all over you?
Yeah, I screwed up a little.
But look at this, 1 million beli!
Who cares about that! We gotta tend to those cuts!
It's nothing, these cuts are nothing!
No one will find it here.
I'll save up little by little.
By the time this fills up, I'll have 100 million beli!
Still a long way to go.
100 million beli...
It took me a while, but it's only 7 million to go.
With my skills now, I can earn
that much in just a single trip.
Only one more trip and everything will be all over.
Everyone in Cocoyashi Village including me...
We'll be free from Arlong's reign. Then...
Then I can finally...
I can finally laugh from the bottom of my heart.
Bellemere-san...
What business do the marines have with Nami?
You should remain quiet and escort us.
Why does he have a pinwheel on his head?
That's TOO cool!
One final stealing spree... Shall I get on with it?
Marines?
And why is Gen-san with them?
Are you the female thief Nami?
you seem to have stashed the stolen
treasure in this very orange farm.
According to our investigations,
you seem to have stashed the stolen
treasure in this very orange farm.
Well, since you stole from pirates, we
have no intention of arresting you.
But theft is still theft.
Therefore all the treasure that you have stolen
will now become government property!
Now then hand it all over!
Confiscate it!