The world… Yes!
It is the research of freedom,
the ideal world being right in front of you.
If this dream without end is your guide,
then passes in addition to the symbol of the Faith!
Well, this should bring happiness to you.
It is all that I can do for you.
Forgive me.
Frankly, Zap Captain,
this mission is really easy.
One was just to capture these kids.
They are perhaps kids,
but they have value.
Now one can announce the good news with the owner.
The dumbs, they have fun the festival.
I can of it more this job.
Is necessary to resign.
What do you tell?
One is able to be made money,
then why one would drop?
It is true…
He! You two!
You are still awaked?
Is necessary to sleep!
Tomorrow, one will see the owner.
You take us along with you?
I will not let to you do that for nothing.
I will reveal you a secrecy.
You want money, not?
If one is able to draw from here into soft,
I show you the hiding-place of a large treasure.
It is a good arrangement.
The kids slipped by!
It is Bonny and Marcus!
These incompetents!!
How do they dare to betray us?
Find them quickly! Find them!
We must bring back them!!!
To explore the ocean!
The great dream of my father!
The weather is good.
Really?
The ocean is very calm,
we are perhaps in spring.
It is not a reason.
It is too easy, you do not believe?
Captain?
He Luffy, do not make fall fishing cane.
Luffy! I had warned you!!
Will seek it!
Immediately!!!
Well.
You want my death?
He sleeps really anywhere.
With this time, it is normal.
Leave it quiet.
In the event of problem, it is always there.
I am not sure…
The weather is splendid!
An island?
What is there?
Amanda!
I am sure that they are pirates.
But it is not Zap.
What does one make?
One can nothing make
as long as the treasure was not found.
You are only one idiot.
A treasure… or life.
Which is most important?
It is…
Listen, if it is not to me Zap,
one will be able to perhaps find a solution.
Listen to, made what I say to you.
This island is really splendid.
There is nobody here, one would say.
One will be able to rest.
Would not be so sure.
Perhaps that people hide in the forest.
There are perhaps aboriginals on this island.
What?
Who are you?
You identify!
One did nothing of evil!
We are only one small family which comes to make camp-site here.
A family?
Holly!
That made one month that one camps here.
Yes.
My parents wanted to take holidays before it is too hot.
Holidays?
What have you made for one month?
One fishes and one catches butterflies.
You have fun with the play of survival?
And your dad?
What does it make?
Us?
A treasure is sought.
That hurt!
A treasure?
He wants to say something of edible,
to survive this play of survival.
Food, it is a true treasure.
What…
You are called Milia?
It is funny the camp-site?
Eh…
Yes…
Heu…
You are pirates?
Yes. You are afraid?
Not really…
We are adventurous pirates.
We are different from the other pirates.
If that interests you,
I can tell you a heap of adventures
that we lived.
Stop!
Afflicted, I…
I am sorry…
It is in full puberty.
Yes.
Stop!
I am not edible!
Wait, panda!!
I am a reindeer!
Amanda.
I want to leave to the adventure.
Dad will find a treasure which will be worth a fortune.
You will see!
I do not need any treasure,
I want simply to remain with you.
Dad!!
Which kind of adventures?
Captain, awakes!
The enemy is of exit.
It is Robin, something arrived.
Captain… I caught it.
We found the kid.
Well. Return quickly.
Big sister!
Wait… lets make me.
Slacken me.
Wait…
I discovered a strange ship of pirates.
I had never yet seen it.
Take guard!
Well, it is noted.
Who are devil?
They are the malicious ones?
I know anything of it, but they do not have
the intention to leave well nicely.
Chopper!
Awake Luffy.
It is a super urgency!
Included/understood!
I hold you, band of dumbs!
What you insane, moron?
Zoro!!!
What you cards here?
I lost myself while walking me.
I walked along the coast.
But what do you tell?
I was mistaken by your fault!
Shit!
All is of your fault…
What?
Wait… They remove the young girl!
He! Luffy is odd,
not average to awake it!
What do you make?
I am too nice or what?
One brought back it to edge.
Prepare the guns!
Something bell.
They will attack.
Qu… which can one make?
No… our plan fall to water.
Let us drop the treasure,
and we draw from here.
It is too late now.
I wonder what they will do in Amanda.
It is necessary that a solution is found.
Upright!!!
Luffy!! Rise.
Does the enemy approach, you include/understand?
Made fire!
Go… Luffy.
Awake!
What?
Luffy!!
Captain!
It is which this type?
Captain, of the nerve!
Not, it is dying.
What does it occur?
Captain!
Which disaster…
How you ace which been able to do that, dumb?
Te does not appear that one will forgive you so easily!
We will say it to the owner!
One can go there now?
He, Luffy was taken along.
Ahhh not!
What makes Zoro and Sanji?
The moment is critical!
It is true.
But we are not
able to occupy us of them.
We must trust Luffy.
They are not continued?
Not…
Impossible…
One cannot do that.
If one leaves Amanda to the hands of Baian,
what will it arrive to him?
You know these pirates?
You explain!
And in details, please.
If that is not appropriate to me,
you could regret it.
Go.
To be useless in such a situation…
If you are not there when it is necessary,
for what are used you?
Luffy also was useless for him!
But its sleep was really not normal.
Cock-San,
it is not because of what you put in our meal?
It is him which is responsible for what one eats,
how could it?
I wanted just that it is a little calmer,
then I put sleeping pill.
Why you ace does that?
But I put of it only one small amount.
Yes, but that can be too much much for
somebody who does not have the practice.
Good, what do you hide?
Forgiveness.
Bonny and me let us belong to this group of pirates.
We captured Amanda because it holds
the secrecy of a fabulous treasure.
I am sorry…
The calm one.
You want to say…
something of other that food?
A true treasure?
Yes.
Does Amanda know the secrecy?
Why not have said it to us as of the beginning?
The poor…
I think that they will return.
Milia-Chan.
The treasure is hidden on this island,
thus if our sister speaks,
they surely will return.
Is the treasure on this island?
Yes.
It has been for that one camps here for a month,
it is to find the treasure.
But it is not easy.
We did not can anything have made without Amanda.
That hurt!
After you.
It is a little seedy character.
That resembles it in what more
lived the prehistoric men.
It is because one built it with goes-quickly.
Come quickly.
It is well, hein?
You do not believe?
You really dug very deep.
And all that in one month?
It is because one was justified,
one dug for the treasure.
But alas, one found nothing.
It is thus for that one uses it as dwelling.
Drives out it with the treasure?
But how it is made that these kids
know the existence of a treasure?
It is because the father of Amanda is one
hunter of professional treasure.
The true father of Amanda?
Yes.
Their father found the treasure,
and when it returned at his place,
it had wounds mortals.
It had much evil to reveal in Amanda
where the treasure was hidden.
Amanda said that it was on this island.
I am sure.
It is really on this island?
She would not have told you tall stories?
Not… it is the truth.
Hein Milia?
Yes.
Dad said that it had started from Mamana towards Samua, and that the island with the treasure was on the road.
One followed the way of Samua shown by
Eternal Poses, and we arrived here.
Thus I am sure that it is well here.
But there must be much other islands between the two.
You do not have the air very not convinced.
You think that an innocent child could lie us?
Did I say that?
Is Amanda well of her family?
Yes.
Then, which could be the treasure that Amanda hiding place?
Hein?
It is the secrecy of the treasure.
Yes.
But it is all that I know.
He Nami!
It is really nice of your share.
Even if you find this treasure,
it belongs to them.
You heard them…
Not Zoro…
I know what I do,
I like to render service to people.
Liar! Your face says that you are interested only in the money.
It is true.
I think that it is not a problem,
because my big sister makes fun well of the treasure.
Really?
Look at.
That shines!
Incredible, it resplendit!
It is possible that a person resplendisse like that?
My eyes!
But… we must divide with Marcus.
No problem,
that must really be a fabulous treasure.
You are sure that goes?
Your father left it to you.
My big sister does not like the adventures and drives out with the treasures.
Dad adored that.
But because of that, my sister very only felt.
Milia, and you?
I…
I love my sister,
and I love my father.
Me too!
It is me which loves more the dad!
Look at, dad gave me that!
Oh! This collar is splendid.
I am hungry.
Holly, is looked at…
Very well, one will eat now.
Holly, come to help me.
I am where?
What occurs?
Why I am attached?
Lastly, you awake.
Be to you which you?
I am called Amanda.
One was captured by pirates.
My hat! Where is my hat?
You me listenings?
You saw my hat? My hat?
Not.
You did not have while arriving it here.
It is not true!
Is necessary that I find my hat!
Your friends had to keep it with them.
My friends?
I include/understand!
Heu… Where are they?
Keep silent yourself…
They remained on the island where we were.
An island…
You know where it is?
Yes.
Très bien, allons-y tout de suite.
If it were so easy, I will have already done it.
We are prisoners.
You believe that one can from go away like that?
Y' does not have reason!
I will not remain here!
I go there.
It would be said that we arrived.
You had to wait a long time?
When did you arrive on the island of Mamana?
That made one month, where had you passed?
I am sorry.
The reason is strange.
The island did not have a magnetic field.
They hid over there,
then that took time to me.
Without magnetic field?
The island of Mamana is not it on the way
island of Samua?
Yes, it is exact.
It is that!
The treasure is hidden over there!
Bring the young girl!
Pirates of Baian, ahead!
Ahead all!
The treasure awaits us.
What know you?
I brought it here.
Why are you with the current?
It is supposed being a secrecy between Milia and me.
Te here.
I wanted to see you.
You are the girl of this type?
You know my father?
Of course.
Your father was one of my friends.
It is for that I am with the current for this island.
Es you of agreement to show me the chart?
You over there…
Be to you which?
When are you escaped?
Captain.
This type damaged my boat.
Idiot.
You cannot only charge you?
It is because…
I believe that he ate a Fruit of the Demon…
What? A Fruit of…
It is you the Captain?
You can bring back for us with your boat?
I want to find my friends.
Your friends?
Yes.
Its crew is on the island where we go.
Someone else with
special competences?
I will undertake some now.
He!
Do not worry you, the boat moves towards the island.
Really?
This type wants more in connection with the treasure.
It is necessary that they lower their guard before our attack is launched.
Eh Ben then, these types are not malicious.
Fortunately.
I thought that Luffy was there,
then I prepared full to eat.
You thus will have to eat more.
I undertake some!!
No the problem!
You did something over there?
Nothing presses.
It is a new weapon which us
manufactured Chopper and me.
You will be able to throw an eye there before our next combat.
You will see…
It is really succulent.
Listen to me!!!
It is me which prepared shrimps.
They is super.
You said?
Drop…
They is very good.
Eh? Where is the small one?
Eh?
It was there, it helped me.
Aren't Milia-chan, you hungry?
Sanji-San.
You worry for your sister?
Yes.
Sanji-San… A treasure
really fortune brings?
I do not have any idea of it.
Dad sought it because of us.
But…
Setting with share fortune,
we did not cease being the target of the pirates.
Thus our sister forever intended to live thanks to the treasure.
But, we have only troubles because of him. I do not like that.
It is not that, a fortunate life.
It is an delicate subject…
But… Milia-chan.
Sometimes the human beings must
to fight to protect something.
It is what your father tried to bequeath you.
You cannot forget it.
You do not resemble a pirate, Sanji-San.
It is strange.
I am well a pirate, but I am
especially a chief-cook.
Well… Is necessary to eat now
before that is not cold.
Of agreement.
Milia… come!
This dish is delicious.
Taste my shrimps, soeurette.
Hurry, it nothing any more will remain.
But it is which this type?
A monster.
Heu… Captain.
We do not have any more a vivres.
What does one make?
What?
Stop cooking, or then we will die of hunger!
Send the music, we set out again!
Everyone in position!
Yes!
Who has there…
Qu… that does occur?
I cannot move any more.
What you made?
What do you think of the symphony that we play?
You are not nice?
In your dreams.
How did you dare to damage my boat?
I will not forgive it to you.
A boat?
About what you do speak?
Detach me!!
Idiot.
I do not save anybody who is
with the current for the treasure.
A treasure?
Even if you ate a Fruit of the Demon,
our music will control you.
As envisaged.
As for your father, Amanda…
You said that you were his friend!
You lied.
Not… we are friendly.
Did idiot, you really believe it?
Your father was an idiot,
he refused to speak to me about the treasure.
He said that it was not easy to find great fortune.
He said to me:
“I will not give it to anybody”.
He impressed me.
I did not have the choice,
but I am always constrained.
Please, make like your father,
say to me all that you know.
Say to me where it is.
I do not know what you have in the head,
but…
I go you botter the buttocks.
Be held quiet.
Shit!
Nothing presses.
You will play the most important part of the history.
You will devote yourself to it later.
On your back?
Very well. Here is the chart with the treasure?
It was just there.
It is well there, on the cross?
It is very simple this chart.
But, that imports,
one will check.
Thank you very much.
Now, it belongs to me.
There! They arrive!
At 5 a.m.!
They brought back another boat!
Amanda?
Is it well?
Wait…
What is it that this ship?
Baian,
the Baian captain is there.
Exact.
One died,
y' has anything to make.
But… it is our fault if it is in danger.
As a pirate,
I must bring back Amanda at it.
Even if that costs us our lives.
It is true, you are right.
It is what this music?
They is not good.
The symphony!
Luffy!
I see Luffy!
Really?
What does it manufacture?
A priori, not something of good.
Everyone, flee!!
It is useless.
Leave!
What you factories, Luffy?
You want to kill us?
Are captain, you well?
I am sorry, but I do not have the choice.
It will end up breaking the boat.
It is because of Baian.
Baian can control people with this music.
You should have said it to us!
Nami, you have my hat, thank you.
The farm!
Your friends cannot anything for you.
I already said you, I am a man-rubber band,
it is useless on me.
I give up.
Already?
They fight between them.
I will regulate their account with all to them.
Bonny… it is the moment!
Yes.
Not!
Stop!!
I am afflicted, Zoro…
I want really to beat them.
Then do not take any to you with us!
I do my better!
Dumb!
I already said you that it was not me!
The guy, if you touch with the mandarin trees, I kill to you!
Dumb!
That made a long time.
Where do you go?
Zap!
You want to fight against me?
NR… not.
I want that you slacken Amanda!
It is only one child.
Be sick for you or what?
This young girl is a goose that lays the golden eggs.
You do not believe nevertheless that I will slacken it?
But, you do not need to destroy all its family.
Bonny!
Do not mistake.
You are not in a position to negotiate.
You really believe that it is worth the blow of it?
If you really hold to with it, I go exaucer your wish.
When I find the treasure,
I will send all to you by the bottom.
Luffy!
Dumb!
How oses you to strike Nami-San?
I am sorry… Nami.
Control yourself, Luffy!
Even…
If the music does not stop…
Usopp, uses the “trick”!
Can that touch these singers?
What do you want to say?
Yes!
Take-that!
It is a trick which one invented, Chopper and me.
Ouais that should go.
Go!
What?
I can again move as I want.
You saw?
It is Chopper and me which invented them.
The balls sleeping pills!
Read the precautions for use well before taking them.
The song is stopped,
we stopped them.
You could have fled,
instead of trying to resist to me.
Let put an end to me to your lives.
Marcus!
He, young lady.
One takes you along with us?
You two…
One will leave oneself never again only.
If we are able to flee,
we will be able to live together.
Milia and Holly need parents.
It is a good market.
After having seen your face,
I will like to think of it a little front.
What does it occur?
Zap!
You are the next one!
Prepare!
How did you dare to destroy our ship?
Big sister!
Big sister, here you is!
Milia, Holly!
I am sorry for all.
I am content.
If you had not returned,
we would not have known what to make.
Idiot.
How will I be able to give up you?
Good, of course you should be supported.
Thank you with all for your assistance.
Thank you to have avenged our father.
Of nothing, there is boot to him the buttocks!
I thank you nevertheless.
During the month which was passed,
I had evil to include/understand the intentions
of my father in connection with the treasure,
since it always left to the adventure without thinking of our lives.
Even if I have the chart, that does not change anything,
everyone runs nevertheless after the treasure.
But… it is really stupid you
to have involved in this history.
Forgiveness.
You are wrong, big sister.
It is to give us that our father risked his life.
We were to inherit his will and to improve our life.
You are right.
Well, let us re-examine all in detail.
Here is the chart of this island that one
recovered on the back of Amanda.
X shows the site of the treasure.
If the chart is right,
it must be some share in top of the mountain.
And we could need that.
It is a collar which his/her father gave to Holly.
And the strange mark on the chart…
If one poses the collar of Holly above,
in the direction indicated by the mark,
a piece is then covered.
I think that there must be something.
And when we are there, there should be the entry of a cave which leads to the treasure.
I do not manage to believe what Robin said.
But I intended some to speak, therefore that must be true.
When I think of it, the magnetic field is weak on this island.
And it is the best proof from the point of view of the magnetic field.
It is true?
I do not manage to believe in it.
Robin was right,
I never yet saw this kind of thing!
Really?
Sanji says that they are dangerous,
and wants that we turn over on the beach!
Frankly, y' does not have a means to remove
this image of the back of Amanda?
A girl should not have this kind of mark on the back.
Of made you not.
There exists a grass which we could use to erase it.
Pas la pains.
Eh? Does that go?
I am well. It is my first step,
it is the beginning of my adventure.
Very well. They is good, Sanji.
One moved away, and all is ready.
Heard.
Zoro, they is good.
Included/understood.
It is necessary just that I cut that.
Move back Luffy, or you will be wounded.
Of agreement.
That arrives!
Zoro… Here too.
Do not give me an order.
Stop marmonner, and do it!
Go!
It is not a couteau de cuisine.
That opens!
If they is too large, that could touch benches of corals and one would remain wedged here.
And there will be much grass
because of the accumulation of mud.
One hardly manages to see whether it is an island or not.
One calls that a “hole of boat”.
And here.
It is an oyster.
It is enormous!
Why is it so large?
Super… Sanji.
That with the delicious air.
You want to eat it?
Y' has some enough for 10000 people at least.
But that foutrait me the tokens if it really managed to eat it.
Now…
Here is the treasure of the father of Amanda?
It is that.
Amanda, I want to leave to the adventure.
I want to find the treasure which will accompany my affection for you.
And then, one will be happy as if your mother were still there.
I want to find the super gross fortune.
Super!
It is a pearl!
It is enormous!
Well, this should bring happiness to you.
It is all that I can do for you.
Forgive me.
There is one treasure.
Yes… only one.
Only one.
Dad.
Thank you, dad.
I included/understood your intentions, dad.
I thank you.
Amanda!
Your father is fantastic!
He found a large treasure!
It is quite true!!
They is best fathers!!
Eyes fixing reality
can nothing see, with share the dreams.
Extraordinary poursuiveurs of dreams
do not see the power.
The affection is not necessary…
Go from before with the smile.
The significance of the family it is “they are your onions”.
Whether you are hungry or that you cry,
I will always give you a knack.
The best friend is always the best.
Not only knowledge, not only friends.
We are a family.
Not only our close relations or our brothers.