Today the great performance!
Basket Basket Assembly!
The hopes of the desperate people are being destroyed by a sand cloud.
Some seek hope, and others try to keep a glimmer of hope.
Their ideas were mislaid, and in confusion, the curtain of the history was closed on a tragedy.
Those which try to stop the battle.
Those which try to prolong the battle.
These two camps are gathered in Alubarna!
Now, Usopp and Chopper fight againstÉ
Mr. 4 and Miss Merry Christmas in a keen fight.
Will Arabasta fall in ruin?
Or will it reach a durable peace?
God of the destiny counts the seconds before the end.
DO NOT TELL ANYTHING, OLD CRONE!
ITÉ
É CANNOT HAVE DIED!
IT CANNOT HAVE BEEN MADE BEAT BY CROCODILE!
Did Ah ouais? And why couldn't it?
Because it must become the Lord of the Pirates!
It cannot die in this desert like that!
S- Lord of the Pirates!?
Lord of the Pirates!
The lord of Worst the Rats!
It is too good, that one!
How if a vulgar kid could claim to become the Lord of the Pirates!
Mr. 0 made well kill it, this small presumptuous!
A Ba of less!
What a Ba!
LISTEN WELL, CHOPPER!
A manÉ
It is time to finish some, Long Conk!
must sometimesÉ
same ifÉ I it is about to dieÉ
to face the wild enemiesÉ
Right in hell goes!
Usopp!
Same ifÉ
it knowsÉ that it does not have any chanceÉ
Mr. 4!
There stop remaining to laugh like an idiot!
You put in position!
4 Your Beats!
One arrives!
USOPP!!
It does not matter what the weak ones do, with final they remain weak!
Look at it!
REFUSE!
YouÉ!
Hein? You want a piece of it?
Be useful yourself.
We will flee with far us planquer like this coward from Long Conk!
CLOSE it!
UsoppÉ
Usopp is not a coward!
There are timesÉ
É where a man cannotÉ
É to move back in front of the combat.
Quoââ?!
You are stillÉ!
This moment is when his/her companionÉ
when one makes fun of the dreamÉ
É of my friend!
ImpossibleÉ
Mr. 4 broke cranium with his beater to him!
He cannot be in life after that!
He should be dead!
How it could be raised?!
It is still one of its small rounds?
Luffy did not die.
I know that he will become the Lord of the PiratesÉ
And it will become it!!
AndÉ
AND I WILL NOT LET ANYBODY SE MAKE FUN OF HIM!
I believe that it did not have its accountÉ
One gives that, Mr. 4!
Not so quickly! I will not let to you make!
Now, you will seeÉ
my special point of transformation!
USOPP!!
It does not matter the force of your willÉ
this time, one does not go you louper!
CH CHOPPER!
PlaceÉ you behind me!
Hold good!
You are ready with batter, Mr. 4!?
Eat that.
TheyÉ are with you, Chopper!
Well!
This dirtiness left its shoes to flee!
QU WHAT!?
Not, Mr. 4!
It is me!
He!
He the ugly one, looks at what I have for you!
One succeededÉ
Usopp!
Go, rises!
Do not die!!
That somebody calls a doctor!
Hein?
A DOCTEUUURRRRRR!!
It is you!
Hein?
Does Ca go?
O- YesÉ
Kohza!
You are well?
Yes.
Is this the ball of Nanohana which does you always badlyÉ?
It is a battle field, here.
Do not occupy you of that!
Most importantÉ
I need a horse.
If I can overlap from here in the middle of the city,
I will be able to go to the palate in the Northern district!
The palate?
What do you want to make there?
I will summon Cobra to capitulate.
Do not do that!
There are Chaka and Pell which order the troops over there in the districts North!
They is too dangerous!
Our manpower are not complete!
The reinforcements coming from the other camps are not yet there!
Let us wait, they are too dangerous for them to only act!
It is already too late.
Cover me!
He, Kohza!
Halt!
A rebel?
This street leads to the palate, the access is prohibited there!
You heard me?
All the citizens were evacuated!
You must leave the city!
He, you us listenings, young girl?
It is not a cour de recreation, here!
I know well!
Princess ViviÉ
Vivi-Sama?
Is this Vivi-Sama?
Where is my father in this moment?
E-Eh wellÉ
In this caseÉ
Bring me at Chaka!
I need him to do something!
The dumbÉ!
What a kickÉ!
How can it hold head with my Kenpo Ballet?
Bouuuuge out of my cheeemin!
You will have initiallyÉ to pass to me on the body!
Eh well, if you really want it, my cabbageÉ
Each day, each day!
Lesson! Lesson!
You are not size vis-a-vis my Dancer Kenpo!
To try to avoid my fists will change nothing there!
This combat does not bring anything to meÉ
I will finish some with a kick!
This dumbÉ
He stopped my Shot SheepÉ
The blow of this cookÉ
cannot equalize my Swan ArabesqueÉ
Thus cease having fun!
Enough, now I will have it!
I am serious!
Henceforth, I am serious!
Show me that.
You!
You still will test my capacities!
And nothing is more impressive than my storage capacity!
To employ that, for example.
I can create an assembly like this!
Once you will have seen this, you will have completely died of laughing!
Initially, the strangest head of the world!
Then, eyes more mild nutters!
Strangest of the noses!
The strangest possible mouth!
Now, for your visual pleasureÉ
Great Execution Today!
90% of this face are the tienÉ
Release from there.
It is not a play, dumb!
What? You do not have blood or tears!?
DEMON!
I do not have time for your small performances.
Performances?
Nothing!
My performances are nothing!!
Once, a long ago, I met a man.
And the friendship remained my way of harming to him!
I see.
ÒThis man in front of meÉÓ
I believe that I have an ideaÉ
ÒÉ is a person!Ó
ÒI think that I am in love!Ó
ÒI realizedÉÓ
ÒYou need me!Ó
É of what I must do.
Now, I would like to see you striking oneÉ
Q- What is there!?
It is the face of your friend, not?
You would do that with your friend!?
It is sure that are stupid for you.
It does not matter with which you resemble,
it is always you of below.
I am not this kind of the type which falls into the panel because of surface images like that.
PeopleÉ
É have a heart!
PeopleÉ have a heartÉ
It is ifÉ
PURE!
I have if shame to take this formÉ
I include/understand.
Even if IÉ
É changed me into it.
Mellorine! Mellorine!
It does not matter which of your friends I chooseÉ
É that will not have any effect.
Mellorine! Mellorine!
Too much easy.
Mellorine! MelloÉ
I cannot believe that it either so easy.
Really so easy?
Moron.
It is Vivi-Sama!
What?
It is true!
Is the Princess of return?
Why is it here in a similar moment!?
Ah, reallyÉ
You have all your spirit, Vivi-Sama?
If we do thatÉ
If we do that, what?
This country will die?
I do not think.
It is not Arabasta.
The kingdom of ArabastaÉ
...com carries all those which suffer in this moment!
If they are alive, Arabasta will be always a country!
The battle must cease, it is all that imports!
Please!
If I can draw their attentionÉ
even for a few momentsÉ
I will be able to do something.
I know that I can do something!
This palateÉ
Destroy it!
Q- WhatÉ
What do you say?
Princess, the palate represents 4.000 years of history!
Do not be insane, Vivi-Sama!
Chaka-Sama!
I rely on you, butÉ
the King is absent!
He would never allow such an egoistic act!
But, your HighnessÉ
With this pace, the existence even of the kingdom will be in danger!
And then?
Want you to destroy all the peopleÉ
É without knowing the cause of all that?
It is what will destroy the country.
We will take the offensive.
Crocodile is in Rainbase.
With all my respect.
If one attacks Crocodile now,
it will be like putting oil on the fire of the rebellion!
While we attack Rainbase,
the rebellious army will seize the occasion to strike and occupy the palate!
And one does what if the palate falls to the hands from the rebellious army?
Even if the royal army were to be destroyed, in five years or more,
the country will recover.
We are not those which must be protected!
They are the people of this country!
Never forget it.
A countryÉ
É is its inhabitants.
Vivi-SamaÉ
With your orders!