Vice-admiral! He is not there!
IT IS NOT POSSIBLE!
Where is party?
Its bicycle is not there any more, it probably left at sea.
You dispatch, call the Council of the 5 Seniors!
Yes, Chief!
Oops, sorry.
Still this man?
Probably in tourist visit, as usual.
Does it realize well of its responsibilities?
It poses problem to us when it walks like that.
The most powerful man of the Navy
The Admiral Ao Kiji.
What?
This crew is only one band of nazes.
The man of pride! Foxy the Silver fox!
He, Captain!
Stop playing and come to help us!
The waves are gigantic!
Giiigantesque!
And that amuses it.
Lastly, he will laugh less when the boat capsizes.
It would be necessary initially that the mast holds out.
Really?! What will it arrive to us then?
Do not worry you.
The boat will not run even if the mast is broken.
And we have a qualified and nice navigatrice on board.
Iya! The mast will release!
Really? What it will arrive to us?!
Do not worry you!
The boat will not run even if the mast is broken.
He! The guy!
Ca made a bucket!
Oyabin! It is Straw hat!
Oi, Straw hat!
Do not occupy you of us!
I am not in so bad posture to need your assistance!
Bye!
Oi! If you want to help me… No problems!
Oyabin, behind you!
It is nothing!
NORO NORO BEAM!
Oh not!
He, that feels bad for them!
A small boat as this one will not hold out.
You move all!
Catch that!
Morons, not that! The cord!
I hold you Luffy!
I am so ashamed.
I lost my 500 team members.
And now I lose my ship.
It would seem that he finished himself for me, Foxy the Silver fox.
It would have perhaps been preferable that I sink with my boat?
Oyabin!
What do you say?
It is not my role to say that, but it is a lie.
Please, take pity of me and lets me remain on your boat!
Ok. You do not have the choice as long as you do not have a boat.
Here a little soup.
Ca will heat you.
Ah, that with the good air.
I will eat with Choppie.
Sanji, lets me have some a little!
It does not remain about it any more. Wait until tomorrow.
What is there? Would not be timid.
It is what that?
There is nothing to eat in it!
Would not be so impertinent! I you will make it puff out!
He, is calmed…
The calm one, Sanji!
, Excuses you too!
Hein?
Iya, they is marvellous!
As much gold.
They are so rich?
Oh not, soup will cool.
Choppy! You are there, is not this step?!
Choppy!
Hein?
Oh, it was right a candle.
Heu? Where is Oyabin?
Choppy!
As if I were to fish.
I am the guest!
There is enough food here.
He is really stupid.
It is…
Oyabin! It is S.S. Sexy Foxy!
What?
Do Oh, then you leave us?
They from go away?
Banzai! Banzai!
Password…
Sodium.
Where are they?
They are already assembled on board their boat.
My companions… You did not can forget Oyabin in spite of our separation?
Really?
All is arranged so that you can join Foxy Pirates.
What is what does not go the guy?
Let us have fun the festival.
It is impossible, Foxy-san.
What?
Who are you?
[Fang-frog = Frog-Poisonous]
And they are under my orders!
Fang-Frog?
Who are they?
One would say the pirates who were made beat in Davy Back Fight before us.
Were they made capture by them, this time?
Stupid Head of puzzle.
They are feeling reluctant them pirate which gained, after all.
If you hope to settle on this ship, I will not remain.
Allons-y. We do not have anything to make here.
Wait!
I did not finish any with you!
My new crew still did not withdraw his mask.
It is a horror. They seem to rely always on their former captain.
It is because they do not love the new captain.
Oyabin is really cool.
But it is always a head of puzzle.
The weak ones follow most extremely, that they respect it or not.
If they see you being made beat, they will change opinion.
Face me, Foxy the Silver fox!
Poor clown…
Do you think of being able to beat me?
It would seem that he wants to fight.
He, Tête of puzzle is in anger!
You dispatch, go up to see!
Head of puzzle?
In anger?
Oyabin…
What are there, Porche and Hamburger?
Be more enthusiastic!
We will recover our boat and our crew.
We, Foxy Pirates, ask Davy Back Fight against you, Fang-Frog Pirates!
I will show you who am the captain here!
You praised capacity to beat me?
If you want a combat with against one, start with a match captain against captain!
No the objection?!
Oyabin takes all its time.
It is because it has a capacity.
Will it make use of it?
What do you want that it uses of other?
It left!
NORO NORO BEAM!
The guy, catch it!
It is easy to avoid the rays by reflecting them!
I know your weak point!
Oyabin!
What do you make?
Stop immediately!
Throw your weapon!
Shit!
You saw the stupidity of your former captain?!
You should not count on somebody like him! Included/understood?!
He, you!
This was not a combat with against one?!
It is rotted!
You it intruding, the farm!
I never said that I accepted Davy Back Fight.
Which bastard…
Stop.
It is their combat.
Do not interfere yourself that.
It is true.
Keep silent yourself and looks at, Straw hat.
I will show you how proud Silver plated Renard, Foxy, bldg.
Ah! It is what that!?
This dirty Fox left.
Where it passed?!
Ah, by there! It is true, I saw it leaving by there!
Yosh, by there, OK?!
Berner will not be left!
Are they making a banquet or what up there?
I should go perhaps there too.
What? You would prefer that she pursues you rather than to remain here with me?
Look at, it is your turn.
And a roasted fox, one!!
Oyabin!
Return there!
I am your boss!
Aren't He, the weapons prohibited?
Why do you strike your own soldiers?
If you use violence to make you respect, you are nothing more than one gangster.
You are not a sizeable captain.
Give up…
This ship…
And this crew!
I will not give myself anything of all that!
Your mouth!
Oyabin!
He, Head of puzzle!
Cling!
It is you, Straw hat?
I authorize you to see me in such a state.
He.
Do I can make you a last request?
Take this.
It was the greatest battle of my life.
He, it is…
You were brilliant until now…
I am your adversary!
I await you!
Fang-Frog Pirates!
It is a cut afro!
He, you have nothing to do with that.
Of course that if!
I do not want to fight against a guy who is worth 100 million.
What is what I gain there by striking you?
What is what you say?
If you low the crew of Straw hat, you will empocheras for 160 million rewards it!
But it is not all…
They have a large gold heap on their boat!
Ca does much money!
Surprised?! Fight, salts robber!
Frankly, when they have…
Since when is it so trustful?
I wonder whether the heap narrowed… I will throw a glance after…
A gold heap…
Really?!
Execution! Aim Straw hat!
Fire!
Allons-y, us too.
And you?
He!
Give us nice gold…
They will not be calmed as much as they will not have taken a beating.
Ok, I go there.
We are 500!
Catch it!
let us not understand we anything!
- Héé!
No the chance, they do not listen to you…
He, looks at over there!
He, wait!
How is what you believe?! That I do not have the force of my brother?!
There is nobody here except me which can beat it!
Go ahead gently on your force.
Remember that your adversaries are the human normal ones.
SHINKEN SHIRAHATORI
But what is what you insane, whore of cook?
Did rot… you make fall Nami-san at the moment, not true?
I protected it! You find something to repeat!?
And if Nami-san had been wounded! Cretin!
You donot can make there with the women…
SHINKEN SHIHATOWAH
HOW IS WHAT YOU INSANE!
The farm! I did not finish!
Hein?! You want to fight!?
Release!
Hmm… A human fireworks…
They seem to have fun.
The chronic disease…
He, you go Bi…
You fell into the trap, young man!
They is not good. Let me see. I am doctor.
Stop lying!
It is Ketchup Star!
Ouch… my back…
He, clings to m…
CA FACT BADLY!
GOMU GOMU NO…
MUCHI
[Muchi = whip]
GOMU GOMU NO…
GUN!
Played well, Hat-of-straw!
You were splendid, as usual.
I was dazzled by your charisma.
Just let to me say a thing…
Stop… Not need to thank me…
NORO NORO BEAM!
Congratulations, Oyabin!
Remember of that Straw hat
I am a man who always obtains what he wants!
Foxy, the silver fox!
The destiny led me to edge of this boat! It is insane!
You did not pay enough for humiliation that you made us undergo.
I will empocherai the 160 million and all your gold!
This time, I inform you with certainty…
That Foxy Pirates are the most powerful crew.