The raid of Erik!
The great escape from the Gunkan island!
Yo! Apis, with which do you speak?
Not… Remain behind!
Lost Island?
The island which ran 1000 years ago?
According to what Ryuji says to me,
it should remake surface soon.
But he does not remember the localization of the island.
There are no indices in the old legend…
Ryuji lost all its force and
was separated from his/her companions.
I want to bring back it on his lieu de naissance at all costs.
Ryuji, you always say that.
If you turn over to the nest of the dragons,
you will find surely your force.
No matter what it arrives,
I will find it for you!
Good! In this case, I bring you to it!
In Lost Island!
Did Luffy, you listen?
She said that Lost Island had run in the ocean.
But legendary Sennenryu said it.
Lost Island must be some share!
An island which isn't on any chart?
Yes! Therefore let us go there we!
Ah it makes hot!
What is this… Still pirates?
He, the guy!
You should see that!
What did it occur?
And then… the 1201ème generation…
He always speaks…
He! You should listen to that…
Ok! I am upright!
What? It is already the morning?
The history of the old man was so long that
one fell asleep on the spot.
There are problems!
Bokuden-San!
Where is Apis?
What is there?
You are pirates? There is a fleet of the Navy which drops anchor in bay!
Not possible!
They would be still after Apis?
It is what the problem with this gamine?
He, everyone, come with me!
Yes, Nami-San!
Why?
Be satisfied to come!
And for the old croûton?
Hmm… Let us let it rest for the moment.
He, if Bokuden-San awakes say to him this:
“We will protect Apis.”
D… Of agreement.
Their boat wets with starboard!
Well! I want that a group accompanies me
to unload on the Gunkan island!
The others, seize their boat!
Hello, everyone!
As we said the Bokuden grandfather, here legendary Sennenryu.
Ouais! They is really too cool!
Stop making as if it were the tien!
Thus when you approach Large Line,
you see similar things?
Eh well we saw monsters before,
but it is not one…
Es… Es you sure that he is tamed?
Yes! Times, it are a little senile!
If he thinks that you are food,
it will try to eat you!
Too much late…
Isn't that does not make badly?
You resemble a trout!
You will remain planted there?
Make leave to me!
Let us let it be made puff out.
Zoroooo…
You would not have, it will poison you!
The farm, cook charmer!
The Navy wants this Sennenryu.
The truth, it is that after having reflected there,
we decided to bring back Sennenryu on Lost Island.
You laugh?
The Navy is near!
It was already hard to be left there all alone,
but with such a large trick…
Ryuji wants to really return at his place!
Then…
And I bet that Luffy said:“Sure, I you
will bring back! “, or something of the kind…
Yes, I promised that it would be brought back.
But… we do not have any idea of the place where the island is!!
How will one make to go there??
They is good! That will go!
Not, that will not go!
I think that if Ryuji returns at his place, it will be better.
The animals have the instinct.
Sennenryu will be perhaps able to reveal us something.
Yes, let us find Lost Island!
But how…
Eh well, it will go in a way or another.
Zooorooo!
But what should we make with him?
The fact of reducing to him the mountain will draw the attention.
Initially, we need a carriage
to put Ryuji at it.
Super!
There is enough of it?
Ok!
Good… I suppose that I must help now.
You be a bootlicker!
That should go!
That should be perfect so that Ryuji settles above!
It is sure!
But… the Navy always wets in bay.
And for our boat?
It will arrive something!
Not, nothing will arrive.
One can fight them.
That does not seem to me badly!
Not, one cannot!
That would endanger Ryuji…
Let think to me of a means of transporting it over there.
But of course, the Vogue-Merry always wets in bay…
It is the invaluable gift of Kaya!
I will recover it!
They is too cool!
However… Zoro comes too!
Me?
Ok, one leaves you that!
And if we wait fallen the night?
Not!
Bring the boat close to this course which resembles the nose of Usopp.
He, you are right!
It is the nose of Usopp!
But what will you make?
If the boat is brought…
Do not worry you!
I do not think that they can find us here.
At all events, you dispatch!
Ohh, then now one must make quickly…
Sanji-Kun and Luffy, bring Ryuji in the carriage!
Ok!
Yes, Nami-San!
Old croûton! Say to me where this girl hiding place itself!
I am serious! Awake maintaining!
The war lasted until the 1201ème generation…
What do you tell?
Major!
Something seems to have left a trace in the back-yard!
Erik, which did you find?
I think that they are at the end of this trace.
They hide some share in the mountain.
Well! Let us start to seek!
For this reason one should have waited the night…
What do you make?
I go up.
Ahh ymoonnbuuuu!
(Ahh! They saw me!)
It is them!
You will not escape! Fire!
Zoro! Zoro!
There was another of their crew!
Stop! Stop immediately!
Halt or we draw!
What? They will strike us!
Zo… ro!!
They will strike us!!
All sails outside!
We will not manage to move in time!
Prepare you to continue them!
Yes!
Weigh the anchor!
All sails outside!
Follow the pirate boat!
Here they are!
Oh not, the Navy climbing the mountain!
Ah… they are a little advances some on what I hoped for…
But what will we make?
The calm one, of agreement?
We always have these deux-là.
When the Vogue-Merry passes opposite
course of the nose of Usopp, we will move.
Still this boy.
Is brothel, what it?
A monster!
And moreover, we found the elixir of eternal youth, Ryukotsu.
Do not move back!
Our main aim is Sennenryu!
We will surprise them and capture it in a flash.
Yes!
After all that, I always have this trick in the mouth!
Not, it is not finished yet!
Do not let them escape! Capture them!
Zoro Zoro Zoro Zoro Zoro Zoro!!
Pay attention to the veils!
I know it, cretin!
Make shit, they go quickly for a so large boat.
Not! Leave quiet Ryuji!
Apis!
Ryuji!
As I thought it, this small idiot knew Sennenryu.
However, I did not suspectais it to have met one of alive of them!
The girl is not important any more.
Now, our goal is the elixir of eternal youth!
Fire!
Stop!
Not well!!
How it has…
It has… the balls just…
Therefore, you have the capacity of a Fruit of the Demon.
It is that! I am a man-rubber band.
A man-rubber band?
A Fruit of the Demon?
About what does speak he?
Use your swords!
The balls do not have any effect on rubber.
Sanji-Kun?
Yes Nami-San!
And does that say Navy?
If you want that something is well done…
What is it?
A knife?
My name is Erik the Tornado,
a mercenary employed by the Admiral Nelson.
You do not interest me,
I am worried just about Sennenryu behind you.
If you resist to me, you will taste with the capacity
fruit Kama Kama d' Erik Kamaitachi.
Kamaitachi = the false razor
What does he want to say by Kama Kama?
You see, me also I have the capacity of a Fruit of the Demon.
Okama?
Maintaining what?
Nami! They is good?
Almost!
To be able to see the ocean of also far,
Nami-San is so brilliant!
Eh well, which they hurry.
He! You them leeks! You listen to me?
You is Erik the gay, it is that?
Okama = Gay
Not!!
Pas le Kama in Okama!
Kama Kama in Kamaitachi!
I joke.
You will regret having irritated me.
What?
I included/understood what he wanted to say by Kamaitachi!
The wind that I create is as sharpened as Meitou.
Meitou = Name of a katana
To tear somebody right through is a play of child.
Is it good now?
Not, not yet.
Now, you draw aside!
Leave Sennenryu.
Never!
My Kama kama No tsumojikaze…
You still want some?
One can go there, Nami-San?
Yes, they are in place!
One releases!
Sanji-Kun! Luffy!
Yes, Nami-San!
What?
We are there!
Nami-San, my catapult of love!
You will not escape!
You will not escape.
There is a rock on the way!
Luffy!
What is it that?
It is like that it goes!
Ball!
Thank you to have saved me!
She said to move vis-a-vis the point of the course it is that?
Yes.
To shit, that could become bad!
One would say…
It would be said that we do not have other choices only to beat us.
One goes there!
It was that their plan?
Eh well, impeccable result!
It rightly!
Continue this boat!
The mast is broken! One cannot move!
What do you say?
That should do it.
It was funny!
Really funny!
Does Apis, that go?
They is good, Luffy!
One leaves when you want.
On the way for Lost Island!!
And it is by where?
By there? Perhaps over there?
Will one leave oneself there?
One will see well.
It is not on any chart.
Nice Nami-San is so splendid!
Why me?
We arrive… Lost Island!!