What?
You already heard
to speak about Kairouseki…
Eneru?
Now, join death!
Stop.
I know. You have Reject.
Considering your state, you will die too.
What do you still wish?
You Vearth, isn't this wanted?
Close it.
Death is all that I wish…
if I can carry you with me!
With… Stop!
Reject
“Keep the truth in your
hearts, the closed mouth. “
“We are those who
will weave the history… “
These words were engraved on
Ponéglyphe, 800 years ago.
Ponéglyphe?
When those which sought
the stele appeared,
Warriors of the Gold City,
Shandora, fought with bravery.
They gained?
Yes, they gained.
But…
The battle was devastating.
The losses were disastrous.
Following the war, those
who tried to survive…
gave the responsability themselves to protect discreetly
ruins of the city and Ponéglyphe.
And they are our ancestors?
But 400 years ago, our island
was propelled on Skypiea…
and people of this country stole it to us.
This ground that our ancestors
protected during centuries…
we was catch!
Upper Yard…
Our terre natale disappeared
in darkness of time…
with its enthralling history.
But even if it
find in the sky,
The courageous Flame of Shandora
must never die out.
fuearii vaasu He No yabou
The Covetousness of Faiy Vearth
The Maxim Arch!!
hakobune makushimu
Robin…
Odd knight!
He…
It…
fact of beating its own heart?
It is not God only
people fear.
It is the terror which it incarnates.
Who is… this guy?
Wiper warrior, I had you
isn't defendant?
I had said to you to stop.
You saw what occurred?
You are really pitiful…
Wiper warrior.
Do not pronounce my name…
without reason!
It was 800 years ago…
when the destiny of this country
was sealed in the battle…
by the proud Shandia warriors!
And we are their descendants.
One day, our terre natale
we was suddenly concealed,
and during these 400 last years, we have
carried the regrets of the Large Karugara Warrior!
Since generations, our ancestors had one goal:to find this place!
And let us be there we finally!
And you are…
across our way.
I heard what you have
known as presently, Wiper.
Your Kairouseki has certainly
caused damage.
To use Reject only once is
sufficient to destroy human banal.
You hold still upright afterwards
to have used twice.
I congratulate you.
However, you have badly
chosen your adversary.
The drum is transformed into bird…
30.000.000 VOLT
[Note:Hino = God of
thunder of Iroquois]
Is Kairouseki in it?
You also, epeist of the Blue Sea?
It is a thing which I must make!
[Note:Kiten = God
Japanese of the thunder]
ZORO!
It is not possible.
Even Zoro…
They… were done all to beat.
Why…?
This man…
He was seriously
touched, and despite everything…
And despite everything, it
wants to still fight?
What do you make there, upright?
You will die soon.
Why not leave in peace?
You said that 400 years ago…
you them Shandia, launched this war
in order to recover your terre natale.
Then finally, you are only
warrior who arrived up to now.
This country will turn over
soon in the Blue Sea.
It is God.
While continuing to fight, you
make that to worsen your situation.
Nobody can beat it!
Why remainders you upright?
For my ancestors!
I hoped for a more relevant answer.
I do not even know if
you are still conscious.
EL THOR
There remains nothing any more but you.
I…
I want to come with you!
I am to you!
Towards the World of the Dreams!
I cannot?
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
Wiper.
Wiper, come there.
Yes?
I will tell you a thing to
matter of the Large Karugara Warrior.
There was another reason why
he wanted to recover our fatherland so much.
Another… reason?
Yes.
For Karugara, it became
its greater regret.
Listen now.
The Large Karugara Warrior had…
That there
does it have?
You changed opinion?
Yes!
Heu not. I arrive!
What?
You want to take along that?
Not…
If I cannot, I leave it here.
I do not think that you will be able
to use where we go.
Lastly, make as you want.
Thank you very much!
I there am very attached.
Does that disturb you?
Oh, not…
Would not be so modest.
All that is due to their incapacity
to include/understand the capacities of God.
But you are different.
Frankly, it must be heavy
burden to keep in oneself the fear.
You do not believe?
Yes, certainly.
One should not only it
notice what I do.
I must do what he says.
I will find a means of
to flee. I am sure.
But until there…
What can it there
to have in it?
Excuse me…
You will follow me in silence.
It is what?
Then?
Splendid, isn't this?
This boat is single in the world. And I
am the only one with being able to control it.
In other words, it
function thanks to the lightning.
Incredible…
I include/understand your surprise.
All this was made possible thanks to a material able to transmit my superfluous energy.
A material able of
to transmit energy?
Yes.
It is the gold which
found in this city.
The people of this island will be magic.
While mourrant,
they will see their own eyes
the only flying boat of the world.
A flying boat?
It is impossible!
If this trick really flies,
I could not escape to me!
The Arch, Maxim!
In this boat, we will embark for
to travel towards the infinite ground, Fairy Vearth!
One is outside.
One finally arrived there.
The ground is paved.
Which is this place?
You see something?
He, I speak to you!
Luffy!
I LEFT!
I ARRIVED THERE!
He, looks at that.
Where sums us?
There are ruins everywhere.
This enormous gold bell
must be in the corner!
This would be…
our terre natale?
It is?
The guy, you are cool.
Is He, it what?
There is a giant hole with…
Luffy!
Wait!
What still occurs?!
You go where?!
Zoro!
He, go!
You insane what?!
If you were there, then…
how that could arrive?!
Nami…
Where is Nami?!
It is not there!
WIPER!
Even Wiper…
The guy with the bazooka…
It was so strong.
Who could all well overcome them?
It is Eneru!
It is only…
who could do that.
Is Eneru God, it is that?
Yes.
My Mantra did not go
when one was in the snake.
I could not know
what occurred outside.
Robin!
Madam Navigatrice…
left with him.
He, wait!
Quiet remainder.
Did Nami leave with God?
By where?
I do not know.
Listen well.
If nothing is done, this country…
Skypiea will be destroyed.
The celestial island?
Our village too?
All.
Each man, woman and
child in the sky…
will turn over to surface.
And Eneru?
It will try to reach
the Gold Bell?
Yes, it is certain.
But if we make
less error while seeking,
We will not arrive there in time.
Do not make any you.
I hear them.
There are two votes which
move on the island.
It must be Nami and Eneru.
Aisa.
Take me along
over there!