Fortress G8 the steel.
The pirates are not welcome there…
If you came, 188 guns would accommodate you.
We are proud us,
sailors who protect the G8 fortress.
But,
recently, our fortress was victim of
bad comments near the Navy.
He tell that it is the time of peace,
and these funny always disparages the others.
Do not prevent, is necessary to acknowledge that this place does not have
summer attacked by pirates since years.
What?
I did not say anything.
It is right a rumor, a rumor!
Pfff, would be necessary that they will be made look after…!
Peace reigns.
And it is what there is of more important.
In fortress G8 the steel…
All is calm, here.
This boat is really badly in point.
If you it to repair, that you
will take at least two weeks.
Me just was however said three days.
Ralala…
I think that this boat had to climb the mountains.
It is Mechanic-san?
It is true.
Even by climbing mountains, its state
could not be worse than now.
Ouais, ouais but p' small fireclay cup which it fell from the sky!
Perhaps…
that it was crushed when it crossed the channel.
Yes, the channel is narrow.
And it is difficult to cross it.
Good, truce of chattering!
We concentrate on our job.
Ouais, ouais…
Which waste.
Nowadays, the sailors do not treat
more their boats correctly.
What is there, Mechanic-san?
That fears!!
GENERAL ALARM!
INFILTRATION OF PIRATES!
D-of the intruder infiltrated by the sky!
By the sky?
NOT SKY?!!
Of the intruders infiltrated!
Quickly!
Dépêcnez you to close the channel!
You charge with the coast!
Units of help, you move!
I am still sleepy…
Close the channel!!
By here!
It is by there!!
Direct all the projectors by there!!
One… A boat of pirates.
This flag…
A tête de mort… with a straw hat…
It is the crew of Cnapeau de Paille!
Q-what?!
Prepare you to draw.
Aim at the boat of Cnapeau de Paille.
Is this the boat of Straw hat?
Allons-y!
Major Drake.
The intruding boat proves to be that
of the pirate to the Straw hat.
Straw hat, you known as?
Where is the commander Jonasan?
It… remains untraceable.
Brothel, this type…!
Incredible…
They suddenly appeared in the sky…
Any resistance is useless!
No exit is possible!
“ART CULINAIRE MARINIERE”
Made your job!
It is noisy denors and it is only one beginning.
Yes.
They should negotiate more calmly.
It is hot.
Stop speaking!
Listen!
What we must do, it is to prepare
a good meal for the sailors.
In two hours,
the service of night will arrive.
There are not time to lose in chatters!
But…
Noise right at the moment…
He the guy, not need to worry.
If ever this fortress were brought
to disappear, the world would be already finished.
Compared with the anger of Jessica-sama…
“ART CULINAIRE MARINIERE”
Jessica-sama.
What is there?
Commander.
Where were you?
You did not show yourselves day.
Still today?
However, all went well yesterday.
The subject is not there…
but if the commander is always absent.
It is not well?
Does that pose a problem?
Commander! There is some cnose
that I must announce you!
The sentinel saw it closely.
One of the sailors informed me…
And he said…
What?
Speak immediately.
Yes, it is that…
They affirm to have seen a phantom.
Thus…
it was a kind of phantom coming from the sky.
It is a flying monster…
who jumped right in front of me, and disappeared.
And of the hands… of the hands…
It is what the problem with the hands?
Hands pushed by all
parts of my body.
Then I fell and very suddenly darkened.
Yes, they was hands of woman.
That must be…
A GHOST SHIP!!
Stop your stupidities!
Yes…
This boat belongs, without any doubt,
with the pirates of Cnapeau de Paille.
To say that it is a ghost ship is absurd.
What? And you mentioned that it
had surely fallen from the sky…
Hmm…
They probably came from the sky…
I had said you well that there was one
means of penetrating the fortress.
Isn't this? Major…
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
It is that…
A ghost ship…
So embaumé.
Commander!
Look at what I found.
An old pure gold diadem.
Which old object.
It perhaps was to fly of the ancient relics.
Autentifiez it immediately!
Yes!
Let us see seeing inside.
This noise…
Where?
Just South-bird.
Be not frightened.
South-Bird?
It is because their heads are
always directed towards the south.
They was very invaluable formerly.
It is an amusing bird.
Does that go?
It is so wild.
All these ustensils are ready with employment.
Books of physics and history.
It would seem that the phantoms of
this boat are intellectuals.
Which kind of phantoms are they?
It is absurd…
Good work, let us seek the phantoms of this boat.
Phantoms of this boat?!
Phantoms?!
Fan….?!
Phantoms of the boat?!
I count on you…
O-Oui!
It seems that this boat is
moored in Jaya before.
It is acted in fact of the coffee of Jaya.
Yes…
According to the color and the odor of the coffee
who were left on board,
It is indeed the coffee of Jaya.
That I drank myself without the least
hesitation? What a courage!
Heuu in fact…
And there is also South-Bird which is one
bird characteristic of the forests of Jaya.
Comprenenez you?
More especially as it is told that
much gold is hidden over there.
Commander, all that to say that this boat…
To know where it went is not used us for nothing.
But it is clear that it comes from Jaya.
It is hardly a ghost ship.
Yes, I already saw it twice before.
It is well that of the Straw hat.
But you have just affirmed that
it was a ghost ship.
There are many soldiers and civilians here.
Before we know
the intention of the Straw hat,
it would be their to better hide the truth…
the fortress will be in a chaos…
It is for that I made them believe
that it was about a ghost ship.
Excuse my manners, Commander,
but do not should not organize to us
a special team
for thus capturing them quickly?
We of it are responsible.
Gently.
But…
You must reinforce the Monitoring.
You, deal with the guard of the channel and the lake.
Yes!
You, deal with arms manufacture,
and essence out of equipment.
And you of the main roads occupy.
And of the harmony in the units too.
Included/understood, chief!
You do not approve, Major?
Not.
He makes already night, they do not certainly go
not to act now.
Toutfois, our situation remains the same one.
As of tomorrow morning, your troops would have
chercner a place where
gather many people.
The place where everyone gathers…
Yes.
The green ver de terre is harder
to find in green grass.
If pirates of the Straw hat
covered our uniform,
one as of theirs could be disguised
in one of my men,
and I could not have completely
confidence in my sailors.
These alleged pirates quickly will be famished.
We should find them with jeun with the rising dujour.
Yes!
The guy…
Where are you?
It is what this place…?
Thin!
Fortunately that I had this waver.
Alarm was given…
We must flee quickly from here.
Impossible… There is…
Ah it!
We fell to the bad place.
I wonder whether Nami-san and Robin-chan
succeeded in fleeing.
What is there?
I believed to see a light in the tree.
A hallucination?
One cannot smoke even any more quietly.
Ox, pig, chicken.
Ox, fish, pig.
Meat! Meat! That meat!
I did not eat anything since we are here.
Nothing to make.
So only opper was there,
it could feel this aroma.
In this case, we cannot
us rapprocner of Merry.
Finally we did not find any sailor.
But with the fact, these guy of the team of the material
claim to have seen a monster.
Ouais.
Even the commander affirmed that it
acted of a ghost ship.
It is norrible, being induced with the monitoring
of this terribly empty boat.
It is thus that.
The Navy thinks that Merry is a ghost ship.
Ghost ship?
J I will teach me to them!
However, as long as they believe that, we do not have
no the concern to make us for Merry.
You are of agreement with me, is not this step…?
Ouais, Ouais…
I like that better.
I see…
thus this boat would have been cursed by
the gold stolen among the ancient relics.
In this case,
I toucné gold…
A hand, this hand!!
Luffy with the straw hat… and
the hunter of Zoro pirates.
Perhaps that this flying monster and the woman
with the thousand hands are their partners.
L has seven people there.
Among these seven people,
there is a cook chief,
a doctor, perhaps even also a historian.
Y has something which bell, quickly by here!
How this is possible?!
How I could land in a similar place?!
- Other side!
- It is included/understood!
Saved!
And then?
By where must I go?
That then… Whatever the place where one
look at, it does not have no visible exit there.
Raaah…!
We fell into an enormous lake without exit.
First of all we must find
information to be able to escape to us.
Then Mr. Length-Conk?
I am not enough insane to venture me over there.
A hallucination?
Which moron, I fear the worst with him.
I do not have the least idea of their goal.
Why are they here?
At all events, our fortress is well protected.
Wait, it was necessary that one falls
on a basis of the marine?
I am hungry…
If one very does not include/understand the EC what it
happens, that is used for nothing to act!
Then shows them, which
it is that a chief cook!
It is with me that you say that?
I am hungry!!!
Welcome with the fortress of Navarone.
It is with me that you say that?
Soon in One Part
Sanji the cook!
The marine art culinaire!
I will become the lord of the pirates!
SANJI THE COOK!
ART CULINAIRE MARINIERE