Fact of shitting! Fact of shitting! Fact of shitting!
Why is it necessary that one is made attack by the Navy now?
If you want to remain in life, keep silent yourself and row!
ONE GOES MOURIIIR!
He, Luffy!
You would not come to give us a knack!?
I cannot. I am tired too much…
I did not eat anything since the breakfast.
You ace hunger now!?
Major!
Major Pasqua!
Please please go on the bridge immediately!
Stop jacasser, cretin.
I had already heard the first time.
My excuses, Major.
But the man whom one continues is infamous Monkey D. Luffy!
What?
You were quite long.
You failed to miss this historical event.
Ouais, gives me the binoculars.
That is not any doubt.
It is undoubtedly the flag with the straw hat of Luffy.
Of course.
This idiot…
We sent shootings of warning,
But they do not have the air not decided to yield.
Major, if you could, please.
Me, hein?
You are only incompetents.
It left.
Wah, it will do it!
The infallible attack of the Major!
Known legendary technique to have run innumerable pirate ships, Finger Bomb!
Euh.
What do you make, Major!?
It was what that?
They ran their own ship?
Take that, stupid Navy!
I had planned all that since the beginning!
When had planned you that?
Yosh.
Now one can use the side which this ship covered to escape!
Help the men of the vessel in perdition!
Are He, you well the guy!?
Going Merry is already out of sight.
Yosh!
It is not a good thing!!
It seems that the wheel of the destiny changed camp
We were so close to capturing Going Merry!
Yes, all occurs as he was written.
And now he escapes, Major Pasqua!
All the crew! This ship will carry on its road towards Ruluka
The legend of Rainbow Myst!
Old the Henzo of the island of Ruluka.
You see the Navy?
It seems that they were sown.
The combat by here are really dangerous.
With two sought criminals on board this ship,
It is not astonishing that the eyes of the Navy turn to the red when they see us.
Nico Robin 79 million Berrys.
Monkey D. Luffy 30 million Berrys (100 million actually)
Roronoa Zoro (60 million Berrys actually)
Luffy…
That is to say careful.
It with the air to have there many rocks immersed in the corner.
A port!
Really!? A port!?
Look at! One can see the headlight!
A port…
Ca wants to say that one finally will be able to eat!
Hein?
I do not have the impression that it is a headlight.
It is really a large tower.
One of insane! Let us seek to eat!
To eat!
I have already all that I need.
Essuie dribble on your figure!
You there, halt!
If you intend to drop anchor in the port of the island of Ruluka, or even on the rock funds,
You must pay the harbor tax!
The harbor tax?
Well, he says that one will have to give money to leave the ship here.
He!
Why does one have to pay for only leaving our ship here?
Because it is the rule!
Will you pay, yes or not?
He.
Do not point that on an young girl.
What!?
To eat!!
To eat, eat, eat, eat, eat, eat!
This moron…
Does that go?
Yes, I am perfectly well!
Well, then allons-y.
I want to buy paper for my charts.
I will accompany you, Nami-san!
J I come too!
H-He wait! I come too!
He, you there!
I will like to ask you something!
A new kind of actor, perhaps?
Ca could be a false merchant.
You are wrong both!
One among you T it has seen a Rainbow of the Fogs during your voyage?
What?
A Rainbow of the Fogs?
Ca is useful has anything. It is an idiot.
You judges right from that?
Is He, what there!?
It is you who put the question! It is what this attitude!?
Could you please explain us that of which you want to speak?
Ossan, another!
Of course.
Special for Mister.
One second for me too!
Here for you, speciality of the day.
He, you would make have money better.
Ouais, it is occupied some.
He, why ME!?
I will tell you the secrecy of the Rainbow of the Fogs.
It is right that you pay.
It is not even me which required!!
My name is Henzo.
I am a brilliant scientific genius, which studies the Rainbow of the Fogs.
Who will dare to qualify genius?
It is generally those which are called themselves of the geniuses which appear finally as finished idiots…
Mr. Henzo.
Call me Professor.
He.
Did you hear of this book?
This book…!
I obtained it in Arabasta.
It is true.
I said myself well that I had heard of the Rainbow of the Fogs…
It is the title of the book which Robin read.
This book was written there is more than 40 years, and the author is unknown.
If one believes the book of it, the Rainbow of the Fogs leads to the Country of the Gods… and the Gold City, El Dorado.
It is only one legend.
Many adventurers came here, with the research of the Rainbow of the Fogs, because of this legend.
But not only one did not return from there.
Yes, even some of my friends.
It is thus for that you study the Fog…
He, Mister.
You should not take as much with serious what this type tells.
What do you want to say?
It is only the dog of the Whetton Mayor.
Dog?
Ouais!
It obtains financings by the Mayor, and it saw that.
It is only one impostor!
The team of collection!
The team of collection is there!
What is what…?
He, dispatch to finish your glass!
Well, well, citizens.
Do you appreciate your meals?
You there. It is good beer which you are drinking.
When you drink, you must pay the tax on drinks.
He, wait one minute, please!
The money in this wallet is useful to me has to nourish my wife and my children!
You must pay the taxes as a citizen.
Whoever does not satisfy this obligation…
No right to life in this city has.
What does it have this type?
It is the son of the Mayor Whetton, Philippe.
It is a species of dumb who puts taxation of all that one makes.
Well, well, wouldn't this be Professeur Henzo?
My father sought you.
He worried about the advance of your research on the Fog.
As usual.
Considering one does not know when nor where the Fog will appear.
Which pity.
Your research is financed by the taxes of these brave men citizens.
The tower of the Rainbow is also in construction according to your research.
Did you forget that the more you will spend time, the more you will annoy these poor citizens?
Well, excuse me.
Well, well.
You there. You a large dish of spaghetti, isn't this eats?
Ouais.
I was famished.
People who eat large dishes must pay great taxation of food.
Ben, it is him which pays today.
Why me!?
Why was it necessary that I pay?
Fact of shitting…
Thank you!
You are well foutu of me!
Now you saw your own eyes.
Unless you do not want to be rejected by the population…
You do not approach Henzo.
Thank you for the warning.
But it is not me which will decide.
It is our Captain.
You are…
You are still buying tricks?
Of course!
Ca would be terrible if I did not have any more paper whereas we are on the open sea!
But it would be said that you buy a ton of useless things…
I will be able to make shopping until the depths of the hell if it is with Nami-san…!
You are!
It is them, just there, Mister!
Then it is you the poor cretins which refused to pay the harbor tax.
I am the small son of the Mayor Whetton, Reik.
I will have to force you to pay the tax.
If you cannot pay, you will have to leave!
I do not know what occurs, but…
If you intend to stop our amusing session of shopping,
I would make you regret it.
Sanji!
Shit! What does it make?
I do not know…
At the time or I touched his body, I felt an electric shock.
It is useless.
It is what arrives at all those which try to raise the hand on me.
Electricity?
I see, it with the one of the capacities of a Fruit of the Demon!
It uses a generator!?
Equip with Dynamo, send the juice!
You know what? Ca does not feel good.
Now you will test the true power of my electric combination!
Rolling Thunder!
[Waves of flash]
Hein? Flashes?
It was right…
You have chance to have avoided it.
But the next time you will not be also lucky!
Chopper, take care of Nami-san.
Included/understood!
Sanji-kun, is careful.
Yes, rams Me! You do not have with you to make some for me!
In fact I worried for that.
Oh, that?
It… it is démoniaque…
Y does not have to be done some.
Not a trace of dust will not soil these bags.
This Mayor seems really to be a horrible type.
To impose taxes for all and anything…
Why is necessary that there is this rotten tax for the large dishes!?
I excuse myself…
Hein?
Near you.
Why you excuse yourself, Ossan?
You ace not heard what the type of presently did say to us?
Nan, not a mot.
Listen!
It makes party of these official robbers!
Because of its odd project, the taxes of everyone are wasted.
Es you able to include/understand that?
Nan, nothing the whole.
Be really long for you with the Luffy relaxation!
Does He, what it occur here?
A galleon appeared suddenly in the port.
A galleon?
It is not possible!
Ca with the cool air! Allons-y!
He, wait one minute, Luffy!
OAU, it is immense!
It is rather old ship.
Tyrielshin!
Tyriel-
Q-qu - What… H-He, Ossan!
OAU! Impressing!
They is too cool!
It is so brilliant! If cool! I want it! I really want it!!
I knew that you would say that…
Rolling…
Useless!
Sanji!
My bags of races!
It is insane…
I was sure to have avoided it…
It is you the insane one.
Sanji, it is metal!
Metal conducts electricity! Balance all that you have on you the metal one!
Not!!
Ca was expensive!
You know what I will do to you if you balance them!
But if somebody of normal had received as much electricity…
He would be already
It is not normal! He is well!
WHAT!?
They is not good.
None of my attacks goes…
He, it flees!
Wait!
Reik-sama!
It is our chance!
You had interest to keep my bags of races!
Yes, rams Me!
If they are so important, why YOU do not carry them?
Isn't Ca gone?
If…
Lapanui!
Isoka!
Longo!
Pukau!
Akibi!
The guy!
THE GUY!
He, Ossan!
GOMU GOMU NO!
ROCKET!!
Are arm!
Ossan, it is necessary that you give me this boat!
You… ate a fruit of the demon…
Me? I ate the fruit Gomu Gomu.
I am a man rubber!
This machine…
H-1 is something which I cannot give you.
Oh go, are not like that! Give it to me!
It is as if there were somebody it is not a long time.
But there is not a being on board.
This ship… left to the drift 50 years ago.
50 years!?
One would really not say.
Now, I am sure.
It is exactly in the same state as this day there.
He… About what you do speak, Ossan?
Q-what?
This signal…
The radar detected something!
I never saw such strong statements!
It is that the Rainbow of the Fogs?
Shit…
H-1 cannot leave so far…
What I must make…
Oh, of course!
I borrow that!
WHAT!?
Do not take our ship!
Why you do not take this galleon to go over there?
The bar of Tyrielshin is broken.
Whetton made it fly in glares.
D-of what you do speak, Ossan?
How do you know that?
50 years ago, I were on board Tyrielshin.
It disappeared!
Going Merry left!
He… It is what this brothel!?
These types, they had to confiscate it to cover the tax!
We do not have other choices only to excavate the port.
Shit! This dumb of Marimo is really useless!
He… One really will enter there inside!?
None the adventurers who entered there from it are come out!
One will enter.
I have continued my research during all my life while waiting for this day.
Are you afraid?
J-J I am not afraid!
I am more the great man on Large Line!
The Usopp Captain!
One enters the Rainbow of the Fogs!
Is professor, which this place?
It is Ape' S Concert.
Ape' S Concert!? Would this be…!?
What is it?
A place from where one will be able to never arise now that we entered there.
A cemetery of boats.
Q-QUOI!?
Ouaouououaouououa!
www.rival-spirits.com
http://www.zento.fr
www.saiyajin-team.com
www.kyubi-wolf.net
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/rival-spirits
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/zento
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/saiyajin
IRC:/irc.fansub-irc.org/Kyubi-Wolf
CYB3RFR34K-ISO