Venture with the country of sand!
The demons which live in the extreme desert
With the kingdom of the Oases.
Three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
In a howl of sadness, this desiccated ground sinks from now on in an enormous wave of agitation.
The old green city, Erumalu, fell in ruin.
To try to stop the rebellious army, Luffy and its crew…
got under way to cross the desert towards the oasis of Yuba.
I burn…
I do not perspire even any more…
Stop your moanings, Luffy.
Be to you exhausting you all alone.
You listenings even not what I say to you.
I can about it more.
The cold is appropriate to me perfectly but I do not support heat…
It is because you crowned one peeling.
Why don't you withdraw this costume?
WHAT YOU SAY, MANURE?!
Do not make fun of the reindeers!
AAH! A MONSTER!
Chopper! Grown not like that!
I cannot any more draw you!
Who is a monster, moron with the long nose!?
Qu-Qu-Que want…
Why I am…
Take again already your usual size!
Heat does not seem to affect to you much, Vivi-Chan.
I was born and I grew in this country, I am accustomed there.
Are shit, why these blasted dunes also high?
I thought that the deserts were supposed being flatter than that…
It is an old desert.
The largest sand dunes can culminate with more than 300 meters.
3… 300 meters?!
One could just as easily climb mountains!
Aaah… I can about it more…
The weather is so hot…
Luffy! Just a mouthful!
Just of what to fill you the mouth!
It IS TOO MUCH!
Leashes for me too!
You have just taken 18 mouthfuls of them!
WAIT!
You have just had some!
It is my turn, now!
You do not beat!
You will waste your forces!
He, you did all to me to spit!
Are Oh, for that, you the only one to blame, not?
It is true! It is you who started ace!
I am famished!
Stop being if glouton!
It is still believed! Does not eat it!
Nami-San!
It is soon ready, thank you to have patience still a little bit!
Ca feels good!
PAS TOUCHE!
And why? It is ready, there!
Let eat them to us!
PAS TOUCHE!
The weather was so hot during the day.
What did it arrive?
In the desert, where there is nothing to absorb heat,
the days are choking and the night, the temperature falls in lower part from zero.
The desert abounds in unforeseen dangers.
Look at all these stars…
You could see stars from your island, not?
On this kind of islands, the sky is always hidden by thick clouds of snow.
It is the first time that I see so many stars.
I have well too cold to look at stars!
I am well in the cold.
It is too well to have something of heat beside oneself!
He! Do not rub against me!
I make it because you are very hairy!
Do not make fun of the reindeers!
AAH! A MONSTER!
Chopper, does not change like that!
Be to you really shitting.
So hot.
Come nearer!
I bet that are you hot, hein?
Ouais.
Doesn't Ca astonish you?
In connection with Luffy-San.
I have me also astonished at the beginning.
Luffy-San does not have the behavior of a captain.
It is normal that a captain is respected by his crew.
And only this afternoon still, they fought so much just because he had drunk a little water.
However…
You know what?
After being remained with them during some time, I start to include/understand them a little.
It is well the manner of making of Luffy.
It did not change an inch since its childhood.
And although it is like that, people always gather around him.
It is a silly little brother but it has a strange charm.
Did Ah, you know it already?
Ca makes a long time that I know it.
But, thank you.
Ca worried you to know if I were anxious of his fate.
Yes…
But it seems that I worried for nothing.
I found a shrimp!
It is thus that a shrimp!
Too much extremely!
There are no shrimps in the desert.
Look at!
Oh, you are right! It must be a shrimp of the desert!
It with the air appetizing!
You think that is eaten?
Why not? I already ate lobsters.
It is the first time that I see a true shrimp!
Luffy-San, they is dangerous!
Throw it far!
Not! I will not waste it!
It is a scorpion!
It is small but its poison is mortal!
If it pricks you, you will die!
What? I cannot eat it?
Good, Ben, I leave it to you, then.
Does not give it to me!
Good, I throw it then.
I am terribly sorry. I should you have said it.
It is obvious!
What doesn't go, Chopper?
Something… arrives!
And this “something” would be… what?
Ah, the wind rose.
Everyone!
You put at the shelter under the rocks!
He? What?
A storm!
A tempête de sable arrives!
Impressing!
What a force!
The desert has too many tempêtes de sable well.
I forgot to say it front but the tempêtes de sable are one of the many dangers of the desert.
TELL US THIS TYPE OF THINGS EARLIER!
Good blood, it was what that?
We all were deadened…
He, Sanji! Give us our bentos!
A bento of pirate!
Not now!
Not before Vivi-Chan does not say it.
Vivi! One can take our bentos, hein?
I am with end of forces!
But we made only one tenth of the way for Yuba, Luffy-San…
You pleasant, there?
You do not know the proverb which says:
“If you are hungry, eats.” ?
Not! Liar!
You have just invented it!
I include/understand.
Then, that do you say to make a pause with the next rocks which we will meet?
Yosh! With the next rocks!
He the guy! Dispatch we to reach these rocks!
Janken:Pierre-paper-scissors
That which gains in Janken will have to carry all the luggage!
Do not decide all alone!
It is not the losing one which carries the luggage normally…?
Well, it left!
JAN! KEN! PON!
He! Wait a little!
You played after having seen our hands!
I gained!
IDIOT.
Heavy…
It is heavy…
And the weather is hot…
I gained in Janken… Then why?
It is precisely because you gained in Janken.
Keep silent yourself and draws.
And drops nothing, hein!
Right in front of, rocks in sight!
Really?!
The hour of the pause! Yahoo!
OH! IT IS FAST!
Ah, of the shade!
It is if booooon!
He!
Cling!
I will seek a doctor!
URGENCY!
What? Why it returns?
There is a band of birds over there which are wounded too much to move!
Chopper!
Yes!
Yosh! Allons-y, Chopper!
We will save these birds!
Birds?!
Wait a little, Luffy-San!
These birds must be…!
All our businesses disappeared!
One was played!
I swear it!
There were birds with the anguish here it a minute ago!
I am really sorry.
I should have said it to you.
Waru:Malfaisant; Sagi:At the same time héron and swindler
Warusagi are birds which bernent the travellers and steal their business.
They are called the “swindlers of the desert”.
Quoooii?
Birds which claim to be wounded?
It was will hérons?!
Yes, of will hérons.
Me was rolled?!
Luffy! To say that you were swindled will not change anything!
There was for three days of provisions!
Stolen by a band of emplumés odd…
Now we are wedged in the desert in the middle of nowhere…
whereas we do not have any more luggage?!
How are us supposed to cross the desert without puffs out nor drink?!
It is not worthwhile to be irritated against me. I was trapped.
Thus be stupider to you than a pigeon?
What you ace known as?!
You will stop, the guy?
I am much more intelligent than a sparrow!
Not, absolutely not!
You want to fight with me?!
Do not annoy you to try to stop them.
On the contrary,
rather let regulate them that with their idea.
That which is really stupid…
… it is you!
You are right.
You cannot be a little more reasonable?!
We rest a little.
I was anxious for them, moron!
We are simply irritated because of heat.
But of what did you think, good blood?
Even without food, in one way or another, one will leave oneself there.
Was necessary simply to leave them!
Do not say that to me!
It is not as if we were going to die of hunger.
Moron!
It is you here the moron, imbecile!
Let us forget all that for the moment.
Keep silent yourself, stunned!
To only think of it my throat drains.
All is of your fault!
Ouais.
RETURN TO US OUR BUSINESS!
Luffy-San! Do not continue them!
Which idiot.
He! How you will make to find again your way?!
Return!
Luffy!
Stop!
Cease fleeing!
Arrêteeeez!
It is what that?!
It is what this trick?
A mysterious plant of the desert?
It is too strong!
What do you make?
Be to you funny sacrament, you!
You want that I help you?
It is an not to be eaten good thing, hein?
While I was occupied fighting against this trick, these person who is damned birds were made the trunk!
There are really many odd tricks which live in the desert, hein?
He, the camel.
What do you make here all alone?
Ah? Does Y have a problem?
You see something?
It is what that?
Luffy takes its time well…
I wonder whether it is not lost, after all…
Frankly. It left without having the least idea from where it went.
And there are still as well dangers in the desert as Luffy-San does not know…
It must be rather famished considering it did not eat anything since an end of time…
It would seem that we do not have too the choice…
I think that have you reason.
Afflicted…
My carefree man little brother…
… need has well that one deals with him.
One counts on you.
Ouais.
What?!
What? Why the ground tremble does?
Still a tempête de sable?
Not! It is not that!
It is…
Luffy!
…?
It would be?
What occurs? It assembles a camel?!
Then? It is what the trick which continues it?
I do not manage to see!
But it would be said that there is something under sand!
It IS ENORMOUS!
It is what this trick?!
A giant lizard of Sandora!
C-C-how that?!
They is largest of the reptiles of the desert!
It awaits its prey hidden under sand.
It has claws and teeth as sharpened as of the razors…
… but it has only seldom opportunity of using them.
Indeed, they are so large that generally they avalent their prey in entirety!
It as regards causing troubles, isn't this is a genius?
Good, let us forget the camel for the moment…
Under which star I was born to have so much problems?
He, stupid camel! Stop!
Luffy! Be ready for you to regulate its account to him?
One comes in support!
Ouais, I brought back a little meat to us!
I arrive, lizard!
Muchi:Whip; Tatsumaki:Tornado
They did not need to make some so much…
I am almost sorry for the monster, considering they were put there at three.
There is still one of them?
I forgot to say it, but the giant lizards of Sandora…
… always drive out to two!
Tell us this type of things earlier!
Ace!
Made attention!
It makes shit, him.
You want to play with me?
Yosh, yosh. Not the choice then.
Supervise it.
The rocks of the corner are like natural frying pans.
Good. It is what this camel?
'Do not know.
When I continued the birds, I found it being made puff out by a mysterious plant.
It does not have the air of a wild camel.
Yes, it has a saddle on the back…
It is you!
I see. I am quite content.
What? You know it?
Ouais!
It is the camel which carried me a little, enabling me to escape from the oasis of Katorea!
Well! Then one can assemble it?
If we can assemble it, it will be easier!
Yes, that well will help us.
I think that one can assemble it to two.
The camels are adapted perfectly for the desert.
Good, then, I am preum' S…
He! It is what your problem?
“I am a camel in love with freedom, hard to cook and chivalrous.”
Thank you “to have left me this delicate situation.”
“Ca is equal for me that one assembles me, but I do not accept the guy.”
Dumb…!
Liar! You ace carried well Chopper!
“By chivalrous spirit.”
Stop of you it Peter!
Moron of camel! Moron of camel!
Moron of camel!
I am sorry. My comrades are so malicious with you.
, Is not this is to you a nice camel?
How will I call you?
Moron.
Stopped.
Ball.
Good, then, it will be “Matsuge”.
He… It was the worst choice to be made.
Good now, goes up, Vivi.
Ca goes, I can still go.
Go.
Perverse camel.
Perverse camel
Good, one should go a little more quickly thus.
We must reach Yuba as fast as possible and persuade the rebels to stop.
Ahead, Matsuge!
Wait a little!
, Dispatch you go!
If you trail, you will never leave the desert!
Stop your doubtful jokes!
I like this aspect of Nami-San!
Let us follow them! Quickly!
Chopper, one goes there!
Ouais!
Wait!!