Duel in the heat haze!
Ace VS Scorpion
With the kingdom of the Oases.
Three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
In a howl of sadness, this desiccated ground sinks from now on in an enormous wave of agitation.
Vivi knows that the leader of the rebels, Kohza, has hot blood…
… and that it will fight until death to save his friends.
Further towards Yuba where the rebellious army settled, Luffy and its companions continue their voyage in the desert.
What is there, Popo?
Smoke!
This would be…?!
This tattooing in its back…
No the doubt, it is him!
Ace with the Burning Fists…
It ended up coming…!
Portgas D. Ace!
I waited this day so much!
It is all that there is to eat?
Rab! I want rab!
Rab!
Stop your conneries, you are too greedy.
There was sufficient what to nourish you.
He! Luffy, species of dumb!
I into reveux! I into reveux! I into reveux!
Do not prick puffs out it others!
Occupy you.
Why does that to each meal turn to the catastrophe?
Do not pay attention to them.
Look at. Ace-san finished to eat and it is washing its fork and its plate.
Yes, you are right.
It is really different…
Return my puffs out to me!
Does not want!
… of its andouille of brother.
But, with his good mannerss, there is evil to believe…
… that there is such a large reward on its head.
Is its head put at price?
I think that somebody had of it enough that everyone puts the bargain hunters on an equal footing.
Ace with the Burning Fists, member of the pirates of White Beard.
When the pirates hear this name, they start to tremble.
So that Ace-San is as much with its cases, Barbe Black must really be somebody of méprisable.
Black beard… A traitor who does not hesitate to kill his own companions.
It would be said that it will continue it until the end of the world.
Ace…
Ace with the Burning Fists.
With this blow, I all will shave!
But I will not kill you, oh that not.
I just will attack the rock on which you sat.
I will burst it!
I will withdraw a very great pride from it to capture you alive!
Well, we can raise the camp
Today is…
I say to you to return to me my puffs out!
Not, the-I leaves!
Do you go…
TO STOP!?
Allons-y!
Yes.
Now help with all to clean us!
We are ready to leave for Yuba!
I- Incredible!
It is enormous!
Oh not! He saw us!
Magne, frérot!
The meat speaks!
How?
Do Luffy, what you tell?
Meat! The meat is made the trunk!
Await me, the meat!
Luffy!
Wait, wait, wait, the meat!
Where did it pass? By there!
One succeeded, frérot!
Is they good, Chip?
It has been our first meal for 10 days.
Go ahead gently.
One can finally eat a little meat…
Hold, big brother.
We never had meat in the Hostile Grounds.
Ah? You come both from the Hostile Grounds?
In this deserted area.
Who are you?
Food will not be returned to you!
Made a gesture and you are a dead man!
It is not your toy which will frighten me.
Did big brother, you already draw with before?
Sure Es you that it well will function?
C- How do you want that I know it?
A- , I wait go just…
Stop!
What occurred?
Let us stop playing dangerous plays.
You should rather return to the house to make your nap.
It turned over the ball against the rock!
I never saw such an incredible person!
Who are you?
There would be a service to ask you!
We need your assistance to find a man and to capture it!
Catch it and one will pour you a reward of 1.000.000 of Berry!
1.000.000 of Berry?
I… do not have the means of paying you for the moment…
But when I am taller, I promise to pay you!
Find this man!
The ultimate weapon of Scorpion.
When I make fly, this rock will be reduced in crumbs.
When Ace is wedged under the debris, I will not have any more but to capture it!
Be held ready, Popo!
Did shit, how a piece of meat can escape to me?
For the sorrow, I will thread it.
What?
Why you have…
Moron of sparrow…
What you made ace?!
I will kill you!
Nooon!
Not! He you, the kid in bottom!
Insane the camp from here!
When that will explode, half of Arabasta will leave in smoke!
All Large Line will be found on the Moon!
He, kid?
What?
O-where is the bomb?! The bomb!
You want to speak about that?
Nooon!
Ossan, you make me marrer!
He, kid! Instead of you foutre of me, gives me a knack rather!
But… But…
Where… Where it passed?
I cannot allow myself to waste my time here!
Popo!
One must find where it went!
My brother and me, we followed its traces up to now since the Hostile Grounds.
But then? Who is this guy?
Scorpion.
An bargain hunter.
An bargain hunter?
Why would devil of the kids be with the continuation of an bargain hunter?
Eh well…
I have also an account to regulate with him.
The man who beat Black Barbe with Yuba…
It is called Scorpion.
If I go in Yuba, it is to meet it.
Hein? It beat Black Barbe?
This man?
Ahead!
Then which are you, Ossan?
One can say that you one lucky devil, kid.
You will be able to see with the work largest of the bargain hunters of the world, Scorpion-Sama!
Are Ossan, you an bargain hunter?
Would not be astonished with listening by the account by my quite as extraordinary exploits the ones as the others.
Dany the Double-trigger, Ruth the diabolic one and all the villains in this kind begged me to save their lives at the end of our combat!
Super!!!
Is it true?
It is what I provide!
Is Ah, it what you provide?
At all events, I will eliminate Ace with the Burning Fists.
Nobody of other will be likely to succeed!
Will Ossan, you try cramer Ace?
Ca will be funny to see!
Do not make fun of me, kid!
I am a man who can transcend himself when the stake is important.
Yes, I am animated by a great ambition.
I must theirs show…
Their to show?
With which?
The Scorpion, with the attack!
But Ace…
You really think that this Scorpion beat Black Barbe?
I know anything of it. I cannot you say it before to have met him.
Ace? It is really you?
Ace with the Burning Fists?
What is there, Ace?
Two men… and a bird.
What?
They arrive.
I found you, Ace with the Burning Fists!
I am called Scorpion!
The invincible hero!
I have came by far to defy you!
Ca will be a true combat!
Then it is him, Scorpion…
He! Is everyone there?
L- Luffy?!
But what you insane on the back of this sparrow?
It is there in flesh and bone…
This guy, it is Ace with the Burning Fists!
What doesn't go, Ossan?
Hein? Euh, nothing…
Miss chance for you!
I am a specialist in the combat!
Today I will put a term at your legendary bravery!
It is unconscious… which imbecile…
I am very excited!
Ace! A true combat!
Do not deflate!
How if I were going to deflate me!
Eh well, I have to me also something to ask him.
Break from there, Luffy!
What arrives to me?
I should not weaken!
I am invulnerable.
I cannot die…
… since they await me!
I arrive, Ace with the Burning Fists!
Take that!
AH! Q-Q-Q-Q-what?!
It turned over the steel net against him!
If Ace with the Burning Fists had been beaten also easily, the combat would not have been interesting.
It would be said that you decided to continue.
The Combat of the Hell can now start!
Popo! My Prescorraci rifle!
Rifle pressurized with the corrosive acid!
Q- WHAT?
Corrosive acid?
With that, I will sprinkle you of pressurized acid!
Afflicted, but that really does not resemble a combat.
One had to expect it, but…
… the history as what you did eliminate Black Barbe was only one lie, is not this?
You knew that while spreading this rumor in connection with Black Barbe, I was going to come to your meeting.
It is well that?
Just.
It, which do you think was not a bad plan?
We were of equal force until now.
It is time for me to pass to the serious things!
Ca is enough!
Dad, that is enough!
“Dad”?
“Pa Dad”?
Stop!
D-Dip! Chip!
Dad!
You are not enough strong to beat it.
It is Ace with the Burning Fists!
What you made there?
When are you parties of the Hostile Grounds?
Dad, looks at!
A large potato was really found!
He, you are right.
There still was only one potato to eat this evening.
I would like at least once, to eat until being able moreover it.
Imbecile! Do not say things like that in front of dad!
Dad gave up his row of bargain hunter to deal with us whereas it was very important for him.
Yes…
Beyond the sea, there are exceptional men who live extraordinary adventures…
There is not only one can make to go up the moral one to him?
Of course that not!
Even without anything interesting to make, we will remain in life!
Dad gave up his dream for us.
For us, the most important thing, it is to remain in life.
It is what these sad faces?!
Stop to you apitoyer on your fate of the kind!
Dad!
Listen to me well!
I will become again an bargain hunter!
I will defy celebrates it Ace with the Burning Fists!
And after having disputed largest of the engagements in the world… I will return here as a winner!
It is too hard, this larger combat in the world!
One came for you, Papa!
What do you tell?
Your father is currently the largest bargain hunter in the world.
Dany the Double-trigger, Ruth the diabolic one and all the other villains in this kind begged me to save their lives…
It is what you envisage to do.
Then you knew…
Eh yes, your old father is only one boasting who is not worth large thing.
But, there was a share of truth.
It does not matter that you can be weak or even unimportant,
if you have will, then you will be able to even defy the most powerful men of the world!
I wanted to show you…
I wanted to show you a great dream!
A man must have a dream which animates it.
One should not be let cut down!
It is necessary to fight!
It is necessary to continue to laugh and live!
Since you defy the impossible one, you will live in a paradise.
It is what I must show you,
even if I must risk my life.
Yes, if you do not lower the arms, then all will be possible!
Pa Dad!
You thus could see the invincible spirit of your father!
How? I will not lose!
As a long time as I will be animated by this great dream!
Popo! My Bazooka!
Ace with the Burning Fists!
It is the end!
Dad! Stop!
Please!
Dip! Chip!
I included/understood what you wanted to say to us!
But we also envisaged to beat us!
Of living each day as it arrives!
Since you will be there, we will have courage!
I am sorry to be to me apitoyé!
I make fun about it, of food!
I am happy since you are with us!
I love you, Dad!
I love you too!
Dip! Chip!
Dad!
I undertake some!
You are well?
Ace!
Dad protected us!
He, Ossan… Died to you?
E- Species of simpleton.
As if I could die…
… and to give up my expensive let us fistons.
Scorpion-Sama is invincible!
I thank you for being come to seek your old father.
Let us turn over on our premises, in the Hostile Grounds.
Well, it is here that one separates.
You us free really, Ace?
Yes.
Barbe Noire is not in Arabasta.
I do not have any reason to remain in this country.
I see.
Where do you hope to go then?
Scorpion told me that a guy had seen it in the West.
I will try to seek in this direction.
Luffy.
Always keep it with you.
What, it is right a bit of paper.
This bit of paper will enable us to meet again.
You do not want any?
If, if.
After all, it is normal that I worry for my little brother.
It may be also that it burns you unceasingly the hands.
Take well care for me.
Luffy, the next time that one will see oneself, that will be at the Top of the Pirates.
Of agreement!
Exceed yourself.
He!!!
Hein? Where did Ace pass?
It left.
Ace with the Burning Fists…
It will be re-examined.
Yes, I am sure.