On board the Maxim Arch,
God Eneru and Luffy
clash finally!
What are you thus?
Dumb!
I am Luffy.
Pirate and Man-Rubber band.
Rubber band?
Power of the lightning
do not affect a Man-Rubber band.
Even Very Powerful Eneru
start to fear Luffy!
GLOAM
PADDLING
Gomu Gomu No Ono
Whereas the combat in is
soon with its paroxysm,
the Gold Arch, Maxim,
rise in the airs!
Circuits for the ultimate function of the Arch
were engaged, and they turn to full mode.
Its name is Deathpiea.
It is the name of the despair which
will be the saver of this world!
Then to be God…
allows you to take what you want?!
Gomu Gomu No Bazooka
Gomu Gomu No Files
Luffy Falls!
The Divine Judgment and the Desire of Nami!!
The Arch was released from Vearth!
It goes up more and more high
! What will one make?
The Arch takes off in the sky!
You did it…
You did it!
You beat Eneru!
Mr.-MR.-but
the Arch…
The Arch continues to fly!
Impossible.
It is raised?
Poor insane.
C this…
Once removed from you,
I will be supreme.
Once again, all will fear me…
will adore me…
and will incline themselves in front of me!
It will be my world!
Those of your species cannot
not to hope to beat me!
For somebody like me,
nothing is impossible!
I AM VERY POWERFUL GOD!
Will run for your lives! Quickly!
Help me!
Look at!
There is something which floats in
airs above Upper yard!
U-Un boat?
It is impossible!
Ever intended to speak
of a flying boat!
Then this boat is the cause
darkening of the sky?
God must be on board!
He!
Hurry to escape to you!
ALL WITH THE BOATS!
There are many boats
who flee Angel Island.
What occurs?
What can it occur
under this black cloud?
Somebody approaches.
Populate Shandia!
Prepare your boats quickly!
This country is on
not to be destroyed!
What?
You must escape!
Towards the Blue Sea!
L it Blue Sea?!
An Arch…
Eneru God…
Now looks at, Man-Rubber band.
Look at the anguish of a condemned island.
The celestial island will perish…
and lives of the angels
will be reduced to nothing.
And nobody can stop me.
Even you!
Stop that!
GLOAM
The gold wall?!
Dumb!
PADDLING
C-CHAUD!
It mixed it with electricity?!
HEAT! It IS HOT, BROTHEL!
Luffy!
I cannot withdraw it!
Shit!
Man-rubber band of the Blue Sea.
I do not need to test
to beat me with you.
Remove to me that, dumb!
I would be negligent if I you
still let disturb my plans.
I believe…
how it is time to say good-bye!
This gold babiole will be
reward for your valiancy with the combat.
It is for you!
Luffy!
Without you,
I am again supreme!
No other mortal in the world
will not be able to beat me!
In the world?!
Be to you idiot or what?
There are heaps of guy
who can beat you!
It there more guys surpuissants on
the ocean in bottom which you cannot imagine it!
Somebody like you…
A kid who does not know
when to hold its language.
Now fall!
With the celestial island!
Somebody like you…
Oh not!
Luffy!
Luffy…
WHORE!
It is Luffy,
Bird-horse-chan!
Luffy falls!
It is…
Aisa and Pierre!
Then they are there.
In fact the voices
whistled around us.
FIGHT WITH ME!
Luffy, one comes to save you!
It is afflicting!
All that you will try will be futile!
Aisa! Pierre!
Made attention! Start from there!
ENERU!
The Divine Judgment!
EL THOR
LUFFY!
Aisa!
Pierre!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
Luffy… Aisa…
A combatant until the end.
This elastic consistency…
Ca really posed problem to me.
But good, that returns to same.
It is so large!
This is the Arch that the Guards
were forced to build?
Just there.
The northern part of the island.
Once recovered gold,
we will find ourselves on the coast here.
Then, when everyone
will be there, we will be able to leave!
Of course, as long as the treasure
arrive over there, that suits me!
N-Nami-san…
They move towards the north-eastern coast,
to join their boat.
I will go over there and
I will await their arrival.
I must guide them with the Blue Sea!
I am the only one with being able them
to show the exit of the celestial island!
I must quickly reach the Merry Vogue!
I made a long dream.
Yes, I dreamed of you.
Ah, Nami-san…
I ate the fruit
interdict with you…
and we walked in the paradise.
Do not let to me awake.
I want to remain in this marvellous dream.
Just us two,
to never awake…
Ah, Nami-san…
What?
I wanted to remain in
my dream with Nami-san!
Nami-san?
Where is Nami-san?
Nami-san!
What…?
But it is what that?
“Mellorine… Mellorine… Mellorine…”
“Mellorine… Mellorine…”
“Mellorine! Mellorine! Mel…”
Nami-san!
What occurs?!
He! Upright, Usopp!
It is not the moment of
to sleep, draft!
It is for what?
Where am I?
Do not seek. Prepare it is all.
To prepare me?
We will save Nami-san!
To save?
To save…
Oh! I remember now! God!
God was there!
Oh shit!
It already left!
It had to capture Nami-san!
N-N-Nami
?
Make shit!
It is because of our uselessness
how it was captured!
Nami-san is so nice!
If she were kidnapped…
Where is it?
Up there!
What is this… that it is?!
An Arch… in the forest?!
Ca lasted only one moment,
but I know that I saw it!
Nami-san is on this Arch.
I insane of what it is!
And besides, Nami-san
its Tee-shirt did not carry!
Ca does not have ANYTHING to see!
I do not include/understand what occurs.
Where are Conis, the Knight
Odd, and others?
I do not know.
For the time being, we must make quickly!
O-where this is
that one goes, Sanji?!
On the Arch, obviously!
Q-what?!
If it still moves away, us
will not be able to go up any more above!
It is our only chance!
By chance, you imply that
I must also go up on board?
Absolutely!
You still have this invention, not?
The cord which leaves your size!
Ah yes, you want to say
“Usopp Ahhahhahh”?
Ouais! I go you it
to give and await you here…
Not question! Hurry!
Not! Have-await one second!
Cretin! There are not time!
I arrive!
Nami-swan!
With the Maxim Arch,
now airborne…
all tears and cries of the people…
will not save this country.
The celestial island will fall of the sky…
and me, Very Powerful God,
I will go up towards the ground
infinite, Fairy Vearth!
The Gold Maxim Arch, will carry out me over there!
Ah, yes. I should not forget.
There is a treasure which I owe
to acquire before my rise.
Pride of Shandia, one
gigantic gold bell.
And the formidable one
belfry which supports it.
I was interested by this belfry.
The Gold Bell.
Ca is appropriate to me perfectly, it
directing Paradise itself!
A colossal bell!
That there
does it have?
You managed for
to survive all this time.
Forget these lower imbeciles.
There is a future which you wish, not?
A future which I do wish?
Yes, I have one of them.
But, if I were to leave with you,
I would be alone.
Go up on board! Go up on board!
It is the midnight supper of the Gold Festival!
With us the treasure!!
GOLD!
Which is the interest
to have what I wish…
when I cannot it
to divide with anybody?
The truth, it is that there is a multitude
of thing which I want to make or to have.
But if I must give up these people
and outward journey with you to have them…
Then I do not want anything!
You do not want anything?
I suppose that includes your life.
What did it occur?
He, Suu!
Usopp-san and
Sanji-san…
should not move in
isn't their state?
What did it occur?
Why aren't they there?
Where are they?
How I can say that…
Ah, it is that!
Initially, the type with pretty
eyebrows awoke.
Sanji-san awoke…
and it awoke Usopp-san.
Then they all are
both put to run.
They left.
to go up on board flying arch.
They will jump…
up there?
What?! You want to say…
on the Arch?
These deux-là…
in their state…
It is delirious!
One really will try it?!
It is not question which we make
that through these strong winds!
I believe that I have a beginning of my disease
chronicle I--can-not-outward journey-in-height…
He, I will spin you this trick, and
you will be able to go there all alone…
Stop feeling sorry for you!
Now!
Do it!
Do not reproach me anything!
Go!
I would qualify with difficulty
that of intelligent decision.
You now lost
your only chance of survival.
If you do not wish
to remain on board this vessel,
then you have only one
only possible destination.
It is…
a forthcoming life.
Not! Not! I
do not want! Save me!
THE FARM!
Yes, Mister!
He, Usopp!
Do not lower your guard!
STUPID EGGPLANT SPECIES!
Usopp Ahhhh…!
Ahhhh…!
Go!
I of insane who you would be a god.
If you installations would not be this
that a finger on Nami-san,
I will become the Demon of the Blue Sea!
NAMI-SWAAAN!
I will put my heart and my body at it.
Even if I must use each piece
of my intelligence and my body…
I will survive it!
Once again…
Yes, to sail on the sea with
everyone, once again!
Luffy…
I will borrow you your courage!