And Ben, this place was brilliant!
You find?
This cemetery of boats was rather alarming!
Bah, it was terrible and all, but…
I would go back a day well there!
It was so that?
It rains?
Ca… it is not rain.
Hail?
I do not think…
One would say rather…
One has steals the Log!
The King of the Fishing out, Masira!
HOLD GOOD!
KEEP THE CONTROL OF THE BOAT!
Hein?!
It is what that?!
He, but what it is?!
THAT EAST
WHAT?!
I dream!
Ouais, ouais, that must be a dream!
A dream?!
God merc…
Attention that continues to fall!
Made blunder!
Take the bar!
The bar!
It is not the sorrow with these waves!
Luffy! Protect the boat!
It is sufficiently damaged like that!
OK!
Usopp?
To dissipate its fears, to calm, close the eyes…
Then to open the eyelids slowly…
You see? Calm and peaceful…
A SKELETON!
CRETIN! DOES NOT LAUNCH IT ON ME!
ATTENTION, IN HERE Of OTHERS!!
A SKELETON!
CRETIN! DOES NOT LAUNCH IT ON ME!
How that is made that one
does boat fall from the sky like that?
Funny of phenomenon…
There is nothing up there.
Brothel, Grand Line is so alarming!
There was a cemetery of boats in the Fog of the Rainbow,
And maintaining a boat fall from the sky…
What doesn't go, Nami-san?
Ca fears!
The Log Installation is broken!
It is pointed towards the sky and it does not move any more!
Error!
An island having magnetic fields more powerful…
constrained the needle to indicate a new direction.
If it points to the top…
that wants to say that it is attracted by a celestial island.
A CELESTIAL ISLAND?!
It is what this is delirious?!
An island which flies in the sky?!
The boat filled with skeletons would have fallen from up there?!
But… there is nothing in
sky which resembles an island.
I would not say that.
To be more precise, an ocean is above us.
An ocean?!
It is increasingly strange.
Then there is an ocean with an island in the sky!
One goes there immediately!
Ok, the guy! At your stations!
DIRECTION SKY!
In any case, one cannot point the bar, Capitaine upwards.
To tell the truth, I never saw this celestial island.
and I do not know any about it!
Of course that not!
It is impossible!
Islands and oceans which float in the sky…
The Log Installation is broken, it is all.
Not, Madam the navigatrice.
The question is not to know if the Log Installation is broken or not.
But to find a means of going in the sky.
As odd as can appear the circumstances,
as delirious as can be the situation,
you should never doubt the Log Poses.
It is the gold rule.
On this ocean, if it is necessary to doubt something, it is of your own generally accepted ideas.
Where point this needle, you will find an island.
It opened the coffin…
But what does it make?
Then? What does that give?
I do not know.
You have morbid pastimes!
See a so pretty body beside one
corpse, it is rather nice in oneself.
Where is Luffy?
Jump, Luffy!
Okay!
What do they foutent these deux-là?
A small exploration.
Reconstitution carried out.
These holes, here, are artificial.
Then this guy died
transpierced by something?
Not, it is the trace of a medical operation.
A trepanation, don't you think, Mister the Doctor?
Euh yes, formerly, to extract one
tumor, one bored a hole in cranium.
But it is an antiquated practice!
Exact, this man died
since at least two hundred years.
He had just had about thirty.
During its voyage, he succumbed to a disease.
Its teeth were preserved better than the remainder of its skeleton.
They had to be tarred.
This habit is practiced
in an area of South Blue.
Taking into account the historical data, this ship carried out surely a mission of exploration.
Here.
This boat, Feels it Bliss, was originating in the kingdom of Bliss in South Blue.
It took the sea here are two hundred years.
It is this same boat which fell to us above.
Ouais, I saw the same symbol on his remains.
This wreck thus wandered in the sky during more than two hundred years.
You find all that only while examining some bones?
Deaths do not speak but they
many information contains.
If it were indeed a ship of exploration, there must remain indices among the remains.
Yes, but the wreck is almost absorbed.
AAH! BUT WHAT
YOU MANUFACTURE BROTHEL?!
LUFFY! HOLD GOOD!
Au seglouuub! (With the help!)
He, the guy!
I succeeded!
I made a super discovery!
Subdue that!
A chart of the celestial island?!
Skypiea?
Then?! Then?!
Then there is really an island in the sky?
One succeeded!
The celestial island exists!
An island of dream!
On the way for the paradise of the adventure!
The paradise!
Hurrah! Hurrah! The celestial island!
You do not pack too quickly.
Ca remains an assumption.
The world is truffle of trick cards.
On the way for the sky!
Oups, sorry.
It exists, it exists.
It exists, only…
Listen, Luffy!
I do not know how to go there!
Ah… Nami… gently with the boat.
It is you the navigatrice! Find!
It is not so simple that!
Nami-san is so beautiful when it is in anger…
Me into insane! I want to go in the sky!
We are wedged!
In all the cases, impossible to continue like that.
Robin rightly, it is necessary more information for us.
If this enormous vessel really went in the sky,
there exists surely a means of also going there.
It is necessary to recover more indices among the remains of the boat.
Ouais, but the wreck completely ran now.
If it ran, fish out it!
It left!
PAS AVEC CA!!
Fishing out?
It is a technique for
to reassemble the cast ships.
But one cannot fish out this one.
It is too large.
He, He, He, He.
You make us do anything!
NAMI-SWAN!
Count on me to bring back tons of indices on the celestial island!
I count on you!
Do not worry you.
My diving-suits are perfect!
And well, good luck.
One will request for you.
Oh, oh, oh.
Here Chopper.
Answer, the guy.
Here Luffy!
Y' has a package of monsters here!
It is a nest of giant alarming specters!
Here Sanji! Ouah, y' has of them one which looks at me!
Ok.
OK?!
All will be well! They will be able to manage!
Chopper, hold the brake well!
Yes.
Pfiou… I made well of step go there.
[Note:Sarubeji (ang. Salvage) = fishing out]
Sarubeji! Saru-Be-ji!
Sarubeji!
It is what that?
Saru-be-ji!
Sarubeji! Saru-Be-ji!
Sarubeji!
Saru-be-ji!
With my command, halt!
AYE, AYE, SIR!
It is here that the wreck sank?!
BOSS!
BOSS…!
It is of ME that they speak!
Everyone at its station!
This run ship belongs from now on to the Boss of the pirates of Masira…
The King of the Fishing out, Masira!
And just when one did not need that, of the balls point themselves.
Oh, you them guy! What you made there?
It is my territory!
Your territory?
Ouaip!
All the ships which run here are with me!
I advise you of step to touch there!
Apparently, it for fishing out the wreck.
Ouais, one would say.
And then?
It is a chance, not?
Stop your chatterings!
Answer when I speak to you!
Excuse me! Do I can ask you a question?
You will answer the mienne?!
Good!
Go ahead installation!
Hope to be reduced the wreck to surface?
Hein? Saru?
[Note:Saru (beji); saru = monkey]
You really find that I have the air of a monkey?
A monkey?
Ca wants to say that I am beautiful
kid! You really think it?
Of course…
Not, you are too pleasant!
You pleasant there.
Then, you will fish out it?
Obviously! The question does not even arise!
If a boat runs, it is with me to fish out it!
And if it still floats, I run it and then I go up it!
There does not exist any ship but
my crew doesnot can save!
Then…
One can look at?
Did Oh, then you never attend a fishing out?
Ca rolls! Approach and admire the spectacle!
Perfect!
Let us observe their technique, the guy!
Att… Attention…
Chief! There is a problem!
Which?!
When the cradle touched the ocean floor, the crew…
They were made have by a monstre marin?
Not, one would say rather than somebody tabassés them!
What?!
There is somebody in bottom?!
It is them…
Shit… Oh shit.
Then…
He, you them guy!
Ah! Us…
There is of the intruders in bottom!
Made blunder!
O-Okay!
God thank you, it is a cretin.
THE GUYS, TURN OVER TO FIX THE CRADLE!
LET US GO UP THIS WRECK!
AYE! AYE! SIR!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
It makes us sign…
Usopp, one should not especially
that he notices the air pumps.
I… know… well.
Go, the guy.
Made not attention!
They are right spectators.
You do not let impress!
AYE, AYE, SIR!
Low the cradle!
And take guard with the intruders well!
AYE, AYE, SIR!
They have the air very proud of their work.
I believe that they really make a point of impressing us.
Do not waste time!
AYE, AYE, SIR!
He.
Above.
Fixing of the cradle confirmed!
It is what this tru…?!
It is what this trick? This monkey there?!
There is a monkey why there?
Oh, that?
You have the eye, p' tit guy.
Yes, it is not an ordinary figure de proue.
AVOID TO PLUNGE!
BARCO HUNTER!
AYE, AYE, SIR!
Monkey, monkey, monkey!
Ouah, it is terrible!
Incredible!
You find?
Forty meters before the target!
Thirty meters.
Twenty…
Ten…
Barco Hunter stowing…
Succeeded!
Perfect!
It is the moment to blow!
AYE, AYE, SIR!
Not possible!
It really will bring back the wreck into blowing in this tube?
It is nutcase!
Air?!
The wreck goes up!
Now! Fish out to me that!
AYE, AYE, SIR!
Continue to send air!
AYE, AYE, AYE, SIR!
BOSS!
INTRUDERS!
That there is?!
What occurred, the guys?!
There is somebody aboard ship!
DUMBS, HOW YOU DARE
YOU TO TAKE SOME HAS MY MEN!!
YOU SUMMERS WHICH IN THE JUSTE?!
Afflicted, we do not have a camera.
Good Ah?!
It posed for a photograph?
Boss! With the aid…
Hold good! I arrive!
You others, continue the fishing out!
AYE, AYE, SIR!
MONKEY PUNCH!
Here we are!
Ouf! One can withdraw our diving-suits.
Which incredible quantity of air.
But I wonder who am going up the wreck…
Me, I hope especially that
Nami-san and Robin-chan are well!
I tried to contact them,
but they did not answer!
WHO SUMMERS YOU BROTHEL?!
Who dares to come to encroach on my territory?!
Ah, a monkey.
I have really the air of a monkey?!
Ouaip, you make more monkey than a true monkey.
You stop this weak conversation?
Ben what?
From where you leave, you?
Oh, what a impolite I ouais make!
You have the eye, you know!
He, one required of you who you stays!
He… under the boat…
Something approaches…
Then as that you come from East Blue?
Ouaip!
And more I look at you, more I find that you resemble a monkey!
Stop flattering me! You want to make me redden?
It IS WHAT CA?!
It IS WHAT?!