GOOD-BYE, FORTRESS!
The FINAL ESCAPE
That fears… That fears… That fears… That fears… That fears…
My unit of attack!
You caused us some problems,
Sheppard inspector.
Their boat is taken with the trap!
I let to you deal with the remainder!
If they are able to escape, I will hold you
for person in charge, Commander!
To hold me responsible?
No the concern…
To mention in your report/ratio the name of
those having put our operation in danger…
The crew of Mugiwara…
They proved to us that they were
such as the Admiral Akainu predicted it to me.
Thanks to them, in a certain direction,
We could justify the importance
Navarone fortress.
They penetrated an impregnable fortress.
To thwart all the traps undertaken against them…
and they are now always in mare.
But it does not matter how much
these pirates can be gifted…
Indeed…
It is you Sergent? Ah well.
Remain in alarm until new order.
Yes, Me sior!
Remain in Alarm!
Commander! You will leave them
to escape without anything to make?
Please, remain quiet to observe the scene.
The échec et mat approaches.
But!
As I have just said it,
it is as if they were already caught.
The nine hour old trap crushes has
already be install,
See.
See? But to see what?
You venz to say for nine hours crushes…
If I say it to you…
it will not be any more one surprised.
Yosh! Full right throttle in front!
It would be said that our navigatrice is not interested
not too so that it occurs.
Nami-san! What doesn't go?
There is something behind us?
The fleet of Navarone follows us closely!
God thank you!
It would be said that they do not have any after us!
They dropped anchor?
They undoubtedly declare fixed price.
I wonder it…
They were crushed by our know-how!
They throw sponge!
Why don't they draw us above, at least?
Waits a little, you believe that they
manigancent something?
It is what worries me too!
When it worries, Nami-san…
It is so beautiful!
Commander… The hour came!
Yes, now follow the orders to the letter.
It was Drake? Why you do not have him
ordered to continue the continuations?!
Why the fleet did drop anchor?
It dropped anchor…
Because it is…
nine hours crushes.
Still this history of hour…
If they do not drop anchor…
They will be devoured by the hooks
sea of Navarone
Hooks of the sea of Navarone?
It is what this noise?
A river would be said.
A river on an island?
I did not see any of all the afternoon of it.
You see there better, there?
Is Nami-san, what it?
The rudder does not answer any more!
Y' has a trick not normal in this fortress,
it changes the conditions weather!
NOT!
Devoured by the hooks of the sea?
Even with the brilliant navigatrice
of Mugiwara on board,
Their boat will be unable
to escape this trap.
I never let my prey flee.
Then, here is reason.
Why do you have the air so satisfied?
The first time that one tried to escape,
I wondered why they used
a so rock port as a base.
It is not a little late for that?
What really astonished me…
It is the quantity of water little
deep in the port.
Normally, they open and close the lock
to control the water level inside.
They use the periods of low tide,
to make sure that nobody
fear of entering or of leaving.
It is an immense natural fortress!
What explains the intervals
regular times,
during which no boat
do not enter or does not leave the base.
Nami-san has a deductive power
so impressive!
Then, one does what now?
Yosh! Right in front of the lock!
ONE CANNOT, MORON!
Full right throttle in front!
You ACE LOST the HEAD OR WHAT?!
Luffy!
Q - What there this master key?!
One will fail oneself on the rocks!
THE BOAT WILL NOT HOLD!!
I knew it! There is a hole in the hull!
Oh, not!
It is a whore of hole!
There is board?
What?
Water was evacuated.
I drown!
I…
Oh, the boat is completely out of water.
Oi, that wants to say that…
That one can neither escape nor to even move.
Ca means that the enemy had very planned.
I drown…
I drown! I will drown!
The more that goes, the less that is arranged…
One does what?
One gives up the boat and one bars oneself?
Hmmm…
You want to still remake the same thing?
It is not the same thing!
When the tide will come, the boat will run!
With our gold?
I will not let that arrive!
Help me, please! I have the flagstone!
I have the stomach in the heels!
Wait a little…
The Dial Impact!
One can use it?
Water is rather low…
Not to have to worry for
boat until the next high tide.
But we cannot see
what the enemy is making.
Let us go eat small something!
How you can think of puffs out!
Look by over there!
Mugiwara Luffy!
As all its band!
“HYDRATES DE CARBONE
FORCES GIVE "
Mugiwara was made take by
the nine hour old trap crushes!
Even these guy cannot escape
with the hooks of the sea of Navarone!
What will arrive to them?
Eh well you see…
The captured pirates… are always carried out.
You should not leave in this state!
Dad, you are still sick!
Keep silent yourself! My tiredness started from itself!
This cretin would do better not
to destroy this splendid boat!
If it does it, I will botterai the bottom to him!
Tanuli-san!
Even in the navy, there is
a powerful fortress,
under the command of G-8 Division
I as well congratulate you to have fought.
You have admirable convictions,
but there, there is échec et mat.
Mugiwara kaizoku-da
You do not have any more any gleam
of espoire to flee.
I already anticipated all it of what you think.
Here, it is a good boy.
Under the authority of the command of Navarone.
All the band of Mugiwara will be
escorted, and to receive its sentence.
Give up the rebellion.
Luffy!
Mugiwara, You and Roronoa Zoro
be sought criminals,
Then we must lead you
at the General headquarter!
You have my word that the remainder of your band
will leave itself there healthy and except!
However, if you tents to flee,
I will be irritated!
Too much nice, that!
It is me which orders here.
You are only one inspector, I would be to you
admitting to observe without stumbling.
If I do not do anything, I will be nothing more
that a insect with the eyes of this old badger.
Moreover, I came here to prove
the uselessness of this fortress!
Excuse to me one moment.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Here is the answer!
The Dial Impact.
I have to absorb several impacts
since we are escaped!
One should be able to leave the boat
rocks with that!
I see! One could use it for
we to leave from there and regain water!
But that is likely to take more than only one shooting…
And with this large hole in the hull,
one will run as soon as one is on water.
That would be well if one could again
to use the takoballoon to fly away.
Ouais, it is an good idea!
If one uses the Flame and Breath Dials,
isn't the octopus will reinflate itself?
Ouais! It is an excellent idea!
There is not the pieuve…
The pieuve…
Pieuve…
Ouais…
Whore of octopus!
I have it…
He says that he has it…
He has it…
Shit, it has it…
It has it…
You have it?
Ouais, just there!
LOOK AT!
HOW THAT SE MAKES THAT
HAVE you THIS TRICK, YOU?!
Eh well, you know, it has us
helped to go down from the sky.
Ouais, but good…
you did ace not found that a little dégeulasse?
Why that?
Let us leave to Octopus-san us
to help once more.
Of agreement, Mr. Length-Conk?
, That waits a little made one moment
that I did not see the DIal Flame…
It was funny then I have
played with in the kitchen!
It is Chaud!
Now, it remains more than to decide
who will engage the Dial Impact…
Why you look at me all like that?!
With which it is, this Dial Impact?
It is that of Usopp.
Isn't this, Mr. Length-Conk?
Good, like he says it so well,
it is necessary that it does it.
You are marvellous, Usopp!
I have respect for you so much!
How? We will help you!
All is regulated!
NOOON!!!
Sergeant! Prepare you to attack!
With your Orders!
Prepare you to draw
Avoided to draw! Loan!
Darling, you succeeded!
Work, it is the important one, but you
must also eat at the hours of the meals.
But I said to you that I do not like
broccolis, carrots and poivr…
Not! I want to say…
I have still work to finish.
To have taken with the Mugiwara trap and all
are crew also perfectly,
Isn't it enough for you?
All that you have to do
now, it is to capture them.
Indeed, but they surely go
to thwart our plans again.
You encircled the sea and the ground,
how could they escape?
Te you remember how they are
entered initially?
Hein?
It remains to them…
Sky!
All is profiled well!
Included/understood!
All is ready here! Now,
all depends on you, the guy!
I do not want! I cannot do it!
When I will make fire, that will burn with death!
Three!
Two!
One!
Dirtiness of Mugiwara! You want
me to humiliate, hein once more?!
I will crush you personally!
IMPACT!!!
How I thought it, they can fly!
Look at that!
WHAT?!
Hummm… How to say…
One falls! One falls, one fall!
Robin, It has you!
CIEN FLOWERS!
One continues to fall!
Luffy! The Dial Flame!
YOSH!
INFLATE!!!
Usopp-sama once again!
I am not a vulgar piece of tofu!
If one leaves oneself there, I will treat you like
tofu of the first quality!
Of agreement?
Of agreement?! Better is worth to burst!
FLY!
Fly! Fly, Please!
I said to you to fly away, then flies!
Hold good, Octopus-san!
Look at! It is necessary to act!
The tide starts to come!
Ah, makes shit!
Usopp-sama will start again!
I sacrifice a shoulder and an arm again…
Quite known as!
It is perfect!
This pain… It is that of Going Merry!
Three!
Two!
One!
FLY!
IMPACT!!!!
A giant octopus!
You insane of me!
Ouah! That went!
A mongolfière, I see that we do not have
the intention to take account of my council.
Good, as soon as they reach
the zone of shooting, cut down them
Hein?
However, do not run up against the boat!
They must be taken alive!
It is difficult, like order.
To send to them a shooting of warning!
If they do not stop,
made fire in the balloon!
Included/understood!
Do not escape to you, Mugiwara.
Not yet…
The first shooting is only one warning.
You gave that…
Commander Sheppard.
This type…
It was barred.
Tanuki-san and its band… Flew away!
What I had said to you!
These guy came from the sky!
Too much cool!
That really resembles a hedgehog!
What a brilliant fortress!
OSSAN, WITH MORE!
GOOD-BYE, JESSICA-SWAN!
At this altitude,
can they draw us above?
This Fortress was built for
to defend against the marine attacks.
They do not have any artillery
able to draw also high.
Darling…
Then they ended up fleeing.
Ah, Sergeant! Is everyone well?
Yes, Commander,
The gun was destroyed,
but nobody was wounded.
Hum, it is well.
Commander!
Let continue them to us!
Give us the order to take them in hunting!
They already volitilized. Tombr is left.
But…
Lieutenant Drake,
you worked well!
Thank you with you.
Commander…
What is there?
Commander Sheppard!
Commander! You claim that all
what arrives is of my fault?!
It is entirely of your fault!
I will contact the District
General and to make you transfer!
TO TRANSFER! TO TRANSFER! TO TRANSFER!
I insane that you are it
protected from the Admiral Akainu!
My report/ratio will put an end to the command
of this fortress which you have!
And be sure that all your subordinates
will be also thrown out of the Navy!
I swear it to you…
Species of IDIOT!!
Darling, are you sure of not
to want to continue them?
Mugiwara you escaped ace.
It is not as if I had invited them here.
Moreover… I already reached my
the most important objective.
Hein?
You noticed how all the personnel
does base work together?
I believe it of what you want to speak.
It does not matter, these pirates brought to
fortress that which it needed.
The General headquarter can think that
this fortress survived its uselessness.
They can say that it is oversize
or even pacifist if they like that.
The “pacifist” word is appropriate to me completely.
Most important, it is that us, soldiers,
and you, the civil personnel, let us can
to help and work together…
to protect this peace, you do not believe?
There are many Pirates like
Mugiwara outside.
The General headquarter will on the occasion to re-examine
at which point this fortress is important.
I will not leave any of
you on the roadside.
You still like me?
idiot.
But, this type, Crois you that it will write
a report/ratio at the General headquarter?
It my so put out
of me that I have it frapp…
I of insane!
I failed to strike it myself!
Eh well, Mugiwara,
where will you go, you and your troop?
There are people at the General headquarter which
narrowly were interested in you.
The road which is drawn up in front of you
will not be easier.
It is brilliant to fly!
Until where one will fly?
Who knows? Ask the octopus.
It is pleasant to depouvoir to profit
of a voyage by the airs.
But I do not want any more
to never see basic Navy.
It does not matter where go Nami-san and Robin-chan,
it is always a paradise for me!
Imbecile!
Hein?
I said that you were an imbecile!
Imbecile!
Ok, I will repair the hole in the hull.
Ah, but me, I have the flagstone!
Sanji, to eat!
I am hungry!
Ahh, the fortress was interesting!
But sub of Gomu-Gomu-No-fansub
Was too ROTS
A chance that CYB 3R has to correct full with trick!
TOO MUCH COOL YOU THINKS ALL!
SHIT THIS GUY IT ENSURES!!
OUAIS CYB 3R KILL LA PLACE!
GOOD…
FAK ONE CONTINUES TRUE THE HISTORY!
OUAIS CETAIS DEGEUX CEST FILLER OF SHIT!!!
Soon in ONE PART
Longring Longland! The Great adventure!
I would become CYB3RFR34K!!!