A battle of very hot kitchen?
Sanji against a tempting chief-cook
I sought you Sanji…
since ten years!
It is called Carmen!
The best chief cook of any East Blue!
The Impassioned Woman, thus one me
call to me blazing Carmen.
I am its first disciple, Leon!
And me the second, Jose!
Oh! What a creature!
For a chief as splendid as you, to seek me had to be…
Ah, I am with the paradise!
I am honoured to make your knowledge, Carmen-san!
How oses you?
What a overflowing passion!
But, Carmen-San…
One already met some share?
Jose! Leon!
Explain to him.
Yes.
Look at.
It is what?
They all are of the chief cooks.
Yes!
They are of course the most famous chiefs of East Blue.
But each one its turn, they faced
Carmen-sama and lost all in beauty!
Yes, I am the “number one” of all
chiefs of East Blue.
Among all the chiefs who dared to defy me,
none arrived to me at ankle.
I started to believe that I did not have the equal one in East Blue…
But while you still worked
in Baratie, an article was published.
I could read above that their younger chief
was the best cook of any East Blue!
To lose such a title vis-a-vis an unknown?
It was ridiculous!
Since, I put myself to seek you.
I excavated all the corners of East Blue
during the 10 last years!
In fact, that done only 10 days.
Carmen-sama likes sometimes exagérerla situation.
Your mouths, both!
Face me, Sanji!
Come to the contest from kitchen
this afternoon with 13:00!
Over there, I will overcome you no matter what it arrives!
Prepare!
You over there will be awaited!
Ah, Carmen-San.
What a exceptional woman!
Will year-chan, you really take part in it?
Year-chan:man of the west of Japan
Euh? Not, this type of things does not interest me.
This jerk…
I sought it in all the recesses of
this city and always no sign of him…
But Captain?
Why one must get dressed like that?
Don't my word you know only one makes the pirates here?
In this city, bump a dangerous Colonel
name of Smoker.
If it finds us my revenge on Straw hat
and us all will not form any more part of this world!
A thing is sure:
one must find Straw hat as quickly as possible!
Included/understood?
He, I can about it more!
I had never puffed out as much before this meal with Logue Town…
I started to have the flagstone.
In fact me too.
I was hungry but I did not have money on me.
Fortunately that you saw me presently!
I do not have money me either.
What?
You of ace not either?
Why I would have some…
You marks a point!
I have some enough of all this research!
This jerk of Straw hat,
I will kill it out of my own hands if I find it!
And how one will pay our meals?
I will never forgive him…
Perhaps what will they let to us leave?
NEVER!
Oh! Lucky!
You us offers the meal? Sympathetic!
Thank you!
Thank you for the meal!
You give… pleasure.
So long!
Thank you!
This voice!
Ah, it was the kid with the Straw hat.
It is true, Moji?
Species of imbecile! Will follow it!
Yes!!!!
It left where? It left where?
A market…
Logue Town is really with the height of his reputation!
The quality of the products is exceptional!
It is excellent, that!
Year-chan, you have good eyes.
They were fished this morning close to the coast…
Close to the coast?
Indeed, the fish is fresh,
but I never saw the similar one.
You really fished it in East Blue?
Year-chan, you do not know yourself there badly, one would say…
It is fish species
that one can fish only in West Blue.
The majority of people of East Blue do not even notice it.
West Blue?
Why say that you fished it on the coast then?
Were year-chan, you never in our city before, not?
Because Logue Town is the city nearest to Large Line.
In other words, only fish are not fished
of East Blue but those of the other seas too.
Those of the other seas?
Yes.
They surely arrived here by the force of the currents.
That very often arrives.
It would be said that they caught something.
One will see, Year-chan?
It occurs what?
Ah! It is one…
Brilliant!
It is an tuna-elephant with the blue scales?
Exact!
It must surely come from the South Seas and
one took it with a fishing cane!
A fishing cane?
An tuna-elephant?
Come to see! This fish with the odd air!
About what you do speak, Sanji?
A book on edible fish?
You study it?
It is not an tuna-elephant that?
Hein? You know?
It is also called the “Jewel of the Ocean”,
it is an ingredient miracle!
But I never saw some.
Of course that not!
This fish lives only in South Blue.
You will never find any in East Blue.
But if Al Blue existed,
y' would have some over there.
Ouais, but that does not exist.
You ace reason.
It is what Al Blue?
“Legendary Sea”.
All the fish of the world would swim over there.
Do not say that, it is only one kid!
He really will believe in it.
Where it is?
You see? It did not even understand that it was a joke!
I lied you, Sanji.
There is no chance that it exists.
Forget all that. Continue to work rather.
All Blue…
Well, one will raise it.
Wait a little!
It costs how much?
Sell the-me!
What?
I have money.
Please, sell the-me!
Please!
Out of the question. It is not to sell.
I have just decided to make some
a reward. Afflicted.
A reward?
Ouais.
The contest of kitchen of the East
is about to start.
Big bosses of any East Blue
came here to take part in it.
The winner will gain that in reward.
Ouais, it is an tuna-elephant with the blue scales after all.
It will be a first perfect price for the champion.
If you want it at all costs,
why not take part in the contest?
You are a big boss, not?
The inscription is done over there.
If you want, are registered it and made this contest.
If you dispatches not,
the inscriptions will be closed Year-chan.
With more!
A contest of kitchen? Well…
Euh, wait…
Face me, Sanji!
That does not do anything.
The hour finally had just begun the contest of kitchen!
All the big bosses of East Blue gathered!
What a crowd! What does it occur?
The price of this year:
an tuna-elephant with the blue scales!
This treasure of the ocean, this ingredient miracle…
The only one which will leave with this tuna-elephant
will be gaining it of the contest…
Who will gain this title this year?
Surely me!
I am so happy that you would not have fled, Sanji.
In any case, the title of better chief
of East Blue will be soon mine!
I will implement my exquisite direction of the taste.
Ah, Carmen-San!
I am so happy to re-examine you!
A kiss for our meeting again…
How oses you?
Always this overflowing passion!
He, wait a little!
Look at over there!
Hein? One would say Sanji…
Oh! Oh! 1:00, 2:00, Sanji!
Sanji-Kun!
In Japanese, Sanji means “three hours”
Nami-San!
You came to encourage me?
At all.
One just passed like that.
But why you were registered with this contest?
Oh, Usopp.
Came to you too?
It is me which called you in first!
Lastly, it is time to start!
Here members of the jury!
For an equitable judgment, one requested from Sam-San a person like the others, to belong to the jury!
Are Sam-San, you ready?
Sam-San?
It left!!
The payment is simple.
Each combat will be held with against one!
The best of each duel will be able to advance in the competition. That which will remain at the end of this contest will be declared the best chief of East Blue!
The first match will begin on your left.
Fine bottom of the east, it acts there of
prestigious Shuutai chief Hokage!
And to represent Logue Town, Ekkuri!
Loans?
Start!
It is what that?
Do Sanji, you want the title of better chief of East Blue?
Imbecile, it is at all that.
I want to pose the hand on the fish which is over there.
The fish?
Oh, it is this special fish…
Ouais, to find the secrecies of this fish
will not be at all a play of child.
And here the so much awaited final!
They have all the air excited!
It is clear!
An amazing talent and tastes,
arrived up to now without the least fear… Sanji!
A dance envoûtante, having beaten up to now
all its adversaries… Carmen!
Who of both will gain the price this year?
And now, that the final starts!
Washing!
It left!
With the first glance,
its movements appear complicated to us.
However, it makes only a little personalized basic gestures!
How will react Sanji?
It paid not attention there.
Contrary, it handles to perfection its knives!
As so of nothing was not,
it continues to cook peacefully.
Sanji-Senshu!
Senshu means “Champion”
It exists!
It exists, it is certain!
What is this you tell,
species of imbecile?
It is you the imbecile,
was not necessary to tell that with the kid!
I am not a kid, species of jerk!
Calm yourself, Sanji!
There are not time to listen your are delirious!
Stop, will wash these plates in the place!
I know
that something of such should not exist.
North Blue. South Blue.
East Blue. West Blue.
Red Line which crosses North towards the South
and Large Line which traverses Is in the West.
There does not exist any other ocean besides these quatre-là.
Would a sea where all the fish of the world live together?
To tell the truth, that seems impossible.
Despite everything, it exists.
I am sure!
It is true. If not how to explain them
fish of West Blue… and this tuna-elephant?
When the old man had spoken about “possibilities”,
he wanted to surely say that!
I knew it. If it exists
I must seek it in Grand Line!
I insane of time that will take to me!
I will discover it one day!
Legendary Sea…
All Blue!
Sanji seems to be arrived at the final phase!
Carmen also seems to be returned at the same point.
What a atmosphere!
Only one will receive the tuna-elephant!
But which?
It remains little of time…
and it is finished!!!
Sanji-Senshu finished its preparation,
follow-up by Carmen-senshu, of which all dishes
are ready for the final judgment!
They finished both.
And now,
who will receive the first price?
Now I will announce the results.
For the contest of kitchen of this year,
the winner is…
San…
Wait!
I…
I… I will never forgive myself it.
I wanted a duel against you since so a long time.
This is why I worked without slackening to improve me.
I wanted to divide the same title as you.
For this day, 10 years ago,
your dream did not change at all!
I thought of being able to beat you. I cannot forgive myself to have been also arrogant!
I lost, your kitchen was delicious.
The best chief of East Blue, it is you Sanji.
Really?
After having intended Carmen-San to say these words,
I am really with the paradise!
Still!
What you does ace made with my face, salt dwarf?
I acknowledge myself overcome today.
But the next time it will have more to be prepared!
I will not lose any more.
If it is a challenge coming from Carmen-San,
I will accept it with pleasure.
Winner:Sanji-Senshu!!
Ah, it was interesting!
There are many duels today…
Say, why I must carry the heaviest part?
Ah, in fact, this tuna-elephant,
I ask for myself which taste it A.
Do I have to make a soup of it?
And its ears then?
Ah, I must quickly return to cook it!
What is there, Nami?
The air changed.
Air?
It will rain!
Hein? With a similar time?
I am sure.
We dispatch!
Euh? Oh…
My hat!
Wait!!
Wait, Chapeau!!
Luffy?
Finally here you is, Hat!
I found it!
Lucky!
I found it. By here!
What? It is true?
It is over there?
Yes, as you predicted,
a man corresponding to his description
has just been seen on the place.
Well.
One hurries.
He finally left his hole.
Await me, kid…
Here thus what the Lord of the Pirates saw!
And after having seen that, he died!