Kingdom of Arabasta. Nanohana
City
Katorea
Arrival with the kingdom of the desert!
The creative powder of rain and the army rebel
We almost arrived.
Would not be too impatient.
But I imagine that it is stronger than you.
Will you have enough men to stop the rebellion?
One will make with what one A.
But nothing says that will bring peace.
I have if hunger.
I am so hot.
Please, made not madnesses…
It is thus with that a town of Arabasta resembles.
To eat!
Listen to all, I will not repeat it.
I await to you an exemplary behavior in all circumstances.
Yes, Nami-San!
That which should listen to that has already foutu the camp
TO EAT!!
HEY! RETURN!
It is not normal.
What will we make?
No concern.
It is enough to go where there is grabuge,
it is there that it will be.
It rightly, you knows.
Good blood.
I hope that he remembers that its head is put at price.
Especially in such a large country.
Let us let do it, it will not have a problem.
Rather let us eat.
One will think of that later.
Not to repurchase the other!
Karu and me let us not can follow you.
Why? You have the disturbed stomach?
Too many people can recognize me here.
It rightly.
No the problem.
I will pay to you to eat, Vivi-Chan!
What is there?
The boat of Mr. 3!
One had not regulated his account to him, with this dumb?
It is well it his.
If I remember well, this boat functions thanks to the capacities of Doru Doru Fruit.
It is thus well there.
Ca feels the troubles.
We are likely to be recognized.
Ca will go. I have a plan.
Thus, they will be unable to say where we are.
And we can move without us to show.
I think that we are even more visible.
Yosh! They is good, the way is free.
One already realized some.
It would be said that nobody noticed us.
Ca, it would be a miracle.
Vivi-Chan, you will be here with the shelter of the inquisitive eyes, for the moment.
Vivi-Chan?
Yes?
Yes, yes, what is it?
What doesn't go?
I am sorry.
I thought just that…
At least, when I look at the city, all still seems to be well.
And yet, I cannot have the mind at ease…
But I think that it still can…
… to be saved.
It is true, it has all the air of a peaceful city.
He, Vivi.
You said well that you were able to stop the rebellion, not?
Which is the following stage?
What do we have to make?
If we can still stop them,
we would make well act.
Yes, it is true…
But simply promised you to me to be led to Arabasta and…
Enough! I do not manage to believe that you still think like that.
Nami-San!
One sailed together up to now,
and you believe that one will release to you now?
It is true, Vivi.
One will not give up to you now.
And I am interested enough by this Shichibukai.
, That is enough for you with that!
In any case, cease to have similar thoughts.
And of course, everyone is sought, except me.
Sanji-San.
It is like that.
Moreover, if this country is destroyed, I will never be paid to have brought you here. Included/understood?
O-oui!
Well, you seized.
You merits of going in hell.
Thank you Zoro.
I did not forget your debt either.
You…
I will recover my money even if I am a phantom.
Argh, dirtiness!
You owe me 400.000 exactly Berry!
You increased ace!
If you do not refund me soon, that will increase even more!
Euh… Usopp, you can…
Thank you.
Not.
Nami-San is in its right!
WHAT!?
In the North-West, there is an oasis called Yuba.
It is the base of the rebels.
To stop the rebellion, it is initially necessary to go over there.
But to go to Yuba, the desert should be crossed.
We must thus gather here water and the vivres necessary, but…
If Mr. 3 is downtown…
Oh, if there is only that, that will go.
It me forever considering.
It is true. Sanji-Kun forever met this moron.
And there is another of them.
Yes, there is also Chopper.
Perfect.
There will be full with things to carry.
I count on you.
, Heard well!
Are Eh, sure for you?
Ca will go! I want to better do my!
If I am in this form, that should go, not?
Yosh! Be to you a guy well… finally a reindeer well!
Then, if you want well…
You can count on us.
It is necessary for us in priority provisions,
and I would like well that you take clothing too.
Clothing?
Yes, like those of the inhabitants, not to be made locate.
Oh and some perfumes!
Yes, Nami-San!
Food and water.
Tabasco.
Forget that, buffoon.
Food and water…
Tabasco.
Forget that, buffoon.
Good, and now…
This idiot. Where is it and that devil can it make?
Hum, that does not resemble a place frankly where there could be a restaurant…
Ouais me and with all that…
I AM OR?
Pas le choice, is necessary that I turn over on my steps.
Smoke.
And which says smoked, known as…
TO EAT!
He says that it is meat of stag.
Completely what one can find in a country with the rich person inheritance.
They have a multitude of interesting dishes.
Does Y' have a problem, Chopper?
There is an odd odor mingled with that with the dishes.
An odd odor?
Ah, they is the scents of the perfumes.
Perfumes?
Look at, that comes from this shop.
I do not like much this odor.
HE!
Miss, I must acknowledge that you are delightful.
With this mysterious fragrance and your dazzling beauty, all the remainder becomes fuzzy.
Good. What would you say to take a cup of tea with me?
Good blood, Chopper!?
I was in right track there!
What do you make?
The provisioning is more important.
I know it!
Ah, I can of it more this odor!
Ca returns to me sick.
Go, go, does not force too much.
I will deal with the races,
you ace that to await me some share.
With more!
Miss!
Will it arrive there?
They is not good.
I start to have the symptoms of an insolation.
It is necessary that I am a place with the expenses.
Ah, it is pleasant.
I will rest here until the return of Sanji.
I wonder whether that will go.
Ca… that will surely go…
You closed ace?
Ouais, allons-y.
It would be awkward if one were made locate.
Where did it can well go?
Nanohana is famous for its perfumes but…
they in fact are manufactured in the oasis of Katorea.
It is in the West of the city.
It is what that? Ca does not even resemble a little bit a restaurant.
Excuse me!
Does Ben, y' have anybody?
Oh, of water!
Aaah it… I would have been happy even with some unhappy drops…
It is what that?
What is it that this green powder?
Is Ca eaten?
Ca does not have the very appetizing air…
Beurk! They is not good!
It is what this wretched trick?
It is frankly dégueu!
Oh, perfect!
This trick must be a poison!
You ace that to burn!
I lost only too much time here.
It is necessary that I hurry to find to eat…
What…!?
Rain.
Oh it is brilliant! Water!
Q - what occurs?
All the bags disappeared!
What you ace which been able well foutre?
Who are you?
Keep silent yourself!
I ask you what arrived at the powder bags which were at side!
Powder?
I did everything to burn!
To burn!?
My Dance Powder…
The treasure of my life…
Let us go, pépé, why are depressed to you?
Keep silent yourself!
How did you can dare to burn my invaluable powder!?
Do you know only how much it cost me!?
Nan!
Moreover, what try to you to make here?!
Do you realize of what you did, dumb?!
Return to me my dream!
It was your dream?
Yes! It was the first step towards the realization of my project!
I am sincerely sorry.
To excuse you nothing will change, return to me my money!
I cannot, I do not have money.
Do not take to me for an idiot!
I built this hut in this deserted place…
I had finally arrived from there there…
Go, is not necessary to take it as that.
You ace that to repurchase some, not?
Ca is not bought so easily!
Its production and its sale are prohibited in the whole world!
What, what?
Are Pépé, to you a criminal?
You bored me up to date.
Thus burst!
What? What is this…?
I am where?
Eh? Eh?!
It is which them?
Where?
Rifles!
Does Y' have a problem?
I believed to hear something with the back.
But y' has anything.
I do not know who it is but they do not have the air very nice.
It is necessary that I left myself quickly from there.
Ullage…
Beautiful work.
You are late a little.
Ouais, this dumb of trafficker of weapons wanted to make us pay expensive.
And it looked at from where we came…
Nothing there can.
If they got information about us, one will not draw any easily.
Where is Kohza?
Inside.
One also took a little food.
It is with the back.
Included/understood.
It is what that?
They bought a whole stag?
Kohza, we have arm.
Not much however.
It is already that, it was a dangerous job.
It is nothing.
What do you have? Why you remainders there?
This country… became insane.
This rate/rhythm, we will be the first to disappear.
Or…
In any case, peace will not last.
Since we, the 300.000 royal guards… naps come to help you, you have enough men.
But we do not have enough weapons.
Nor enough of vivres besides.
Our manpower reached its limits.
To pour still a little more blood will not change anything.
Our next attack will put a term at all that.
We, the rebellious army, will transform this country.
Was Hey, there no meat with the back?
Somebody of it is undoubtedly already charged.
It will be necessary that I check that.
What?
Water?
You ace that with drinking what there is in the bucket over there.
He, still a voyage and they will be good!
Give me a knack!
Ca goes!
Is L it way free?
You saved me!
Thank you!
But why did you save me?
“For the fun; does that give me the cool air, not?”
Be odd for you you, hein?
Thank you very much!
A little odd but a nice bloke.
I have the feeling which one will be re-examined.
But which was these men?
Good it, of which Nanohana east coast is not all?
Beuh, it is on this side.
Be really strong for you.
Nobody can beat me.
I want to believe well, with such a power.
I excuse myself sincerely.
Not, not, not, not, on the contrary.
It is me which am sorry to have burned something of also important.
Oh not, not. We are wrong both.
But, more important, does not speak with anybody about this powder, please.
He.
It is what this powder with the Juste?
T you do not know?
Not, that has a dreadful taste.
Then, you see, it acts of Dance Powder.
Dance Powder?
One also invites it “Powder-Which-Fact-To rain”.
The downpour of presently was caused by Dance Powder.
Do you want explanations detailed?
Even if you gave some to me, I would not include/understand.
It is well the impression which you give.
Do not take to me for an idiot!
Good then, this powder makes it possible to create rain artificially.
I.e.…
Dance Powder synthesizes…
… of the crystals of rain present in all the atmosphere…
… that the core is called…
… in which accumulate the water droplets…
… and when there is enough…
… of the clouds are formed…
… and it rains!
You ace very seized?
Good, it is a magic powder, what.
Splendid, it included/understood!
Do really not be sympathetic for you.
And why use this powder to make rain?
My word, but you do not know really anything of this country.
Ouais, my boat has just dropped anchor.
The country of Arabasta fought against the dryness since old times.
The dryness?
It is when it does not rain and that the ground is desiccated.
I know it, that!
This country thus always was in chronic lack of water.
And especially these last years, where there were only weak precipitations.
It is rather odd.
The majority of the oases start to be desiccated.
Why not use this magic powder then?
Completely!
But Dance Powder is prohibited by the World Government.
If he discovers that you use some, you are carried out.
They also say that the rebellion of this country is due to the dryness.
Really?
You know really anything, hein?
Then pépé, your dream is to save this country with this magic powder?
You said well that they was invaluable for you, not?
Eh well, not… I had not thought of something of as well.
Then what?
Ben, in such circumstances, if you can create water, you can make large benefit.
Hey, you ace reason! You are malignant sacrament, you!
Good, at all events, that has nothing to do with me.
Will be necessary that I recover in search from food.
Hum, please, does not speak with anybody about all that.
Ouais, ouais, releases me with that.
Please!
I will give you all that I can!
Really?
Really, really.
He, thank you for the package.
Afflicted to take your lunch to you, pépé.
Oh, if it is all that you want…
Yes, yes, they is good.
With more, pépé!
Do not forget, please!
Worry you, worries you!
I would speak about it in vain, nobody would not believe in it.
Because I am a pirate!
Bye!
Thank you for the meal!
Oh, it is unjust!
Ah, it is splendid!
I adore this kind of clothing.
In connection with the races which you were charged to make, Sanji-San…
Wouldn't this be… behaviors of dancers?
Adorable, not? It suits you so well!
But I asked you for clothing as those which people carry here.
Eh well, there are also dancers!
But to go in the desert…
Do not worry you! If you are tired, I will carry you!
As much to speak with a deaf person.
But you know… compared to the girls,
you always resemble a pair of robbers!
You looked at yourself?
Do Chopper, what you make?
I try to stop me the nose.
Did Ah yes, to the fact, suit you where?
Here and there.
It is sick?
Oh, it is right which it does not support the perfumes.
Perfumes?
Of course, the nose of Tony-Kun is very sensitive.
Ah, you find.
Certain scents are very strong.
Like this one?
Ah, stops that.
Ah, I fall in your feet, my “Mellorine Love”.
Mellorine is a frozen dessert
It is that, and remainders there.
In any case, it seems that all the desired material is had…
… to achieve our goal, isn't this?
Yes.
You said well that our destination is Yuba, hein?
Yes, it is that.
But to reach it, the desert should be crossed.
It will be a voyage much more frightening than all than you can imagine.
You never know what can arrive.
A false step and nothing guarantee to you that you will remain in life…
… in this frightening desert.
I have always scruples to involve you in such an adventure, but…
… I want to bring back peace in this country.
Then…
Then, I would like to still ask you something.
You all! Lend to me all your forces, please!
Please…!
You finally said it.
Only that was awaited.
Not to know what will arrive, it is like sailing, not Vivi-Chan?
Ouais, nothing again what.
I am in a hurry to see the desert.
Well, the guy!
Tops the hearts, one leaves for Yuba!
Ouais!
Friends…
One forgets nobody, there?
LUFFY!
It was not very nutritive.
This moron of first.