The race with the miracles!
Arabasta, country of the animals
With the kingdom of the Oases.
Three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
Luffy and its crew succeeded in escaping from the trap of Rain Dinners.
The 2 million men who account the Army Rebels directs towards Alubarna.
Attracted in an ambush tended by Crocodile, a great battle occurred.
But, confronted with its incommensurable power,
Luffy is completely made crush.
Does this terrible fact mark the end of this apogee?
Look at!
I it has there so much!
Look at…!
It is water…
Water remakes surface!
I had not said it, Luffy?
This ground is strong.
Yuba is always in life!
Yuba will die.
With this ultimate tempête de sable.
And the heinous flame of the rebellious army will burn again.
This feeling of compassion will destroy this country.
The same applies to you, straw hat, Luffy.
If you had been unaware of these stupid feelings as of the beginning, you would have lived longer.
Water…
And I suppose that you are not also any more grateful for this water.
Impossible.
You are always in life?
You seem to suffer enormously.
But you will find soon peace.
Good-bye.
Which waste of time…
What?
We will fight this sand.
And it will still rain.
As that always was.
STILL AND STILL, SHOW ME WHAT YOU ARE WORTH, TEMPETE DE SABLE!
YUBA WILL NEVER BE DESTROYED BY SAND!!
And afterwards, at this time precis,
I was turned over and I said to him:
“YOU HAVE THE TWISTED LEGS!!”
And thanks to that, all the crabs of the world noticed their twisted legs.
Thus therefore they go on side…
Ouais.
Moreover, there was another animal which jumped everywhere behind him.
It was a shrimp!
But then, the shrimps are also crabs?
Ouais, they are crabs.
Wouldn't Zoro, you be wasting your forces?
Close it.
Thus leave it, Nami-San.
If it is not involved, it accumulates too much tension.
And it raises it moreover easily.
And especially…
It has just realized of the power of Shichibukai.
He, dumb.
What try to you to say?
Spit!
Well, I you will say it.
You are afraid.
That Luffy can lose.
ME!?
FEAR!?
YOU…
SALT QUEER!
Tain'!!!! You irritate me!
Green foam head!
WHAT!?
You want to fight, moron!?
You stop!
It is not the moment.
Well, well.
This dispute put everyone on the nerves.
It is the moment for me, the vice-captain of…
He is well!
Listen to all…
Huh?
Luffy-San will not lose!
We made a promise, not?
We said that we will await it Alubarna!
It IS YOU WHO WORRY You MORE!
Deal only with the rebellion.
If one did not follow oneself, one would be completely lost.
Afflicted, Vivi-Chan.
Yosh!
Now let us travel towards Alubarna!
Ahead, Pincemie!
What is it?
It is the name of crab.
Pincemy!?
Does Ca pose a problem to you!?
At all.
You order to me to go in Alubarna?
Do I have to continue the pirate straw hat?
Or do I have to lend assistance to the royal army?
I trust you.
When you are there, you will decide.
But…
What do you want to say?
Am right clean tone direction of justice.
It does not matter what occurs…
I will take the whole responsability for it.
Colonel Smoker, where do you go?
Urgent businesses.
I must take again the sea.
Be held lends to receive orders at any time, Tashigi.
Yes!
Look at very attentively what occurs in this country.
Whether it is destroyed, or that it survives.
It is the kind of thing which occurs with the turning of a new era.
Sergeant!
Your orders?
Yes!
Look at very attentively what occurs in this country.
Whether it is destroyed, or that it survives.
It is the kind of thing which occurs with the turning of a new era.
We will continue the Luffy pirate with the straw hat, and its crew.
All the units, gather your business for the departure!
You and on the way for Alubarna equip!
With your orders!
Luffy with the straw hat.
WHAT!?
THIS CRAB CANNOT CROSS THE RIVER!?
The “Crab-Mobiles” live in the desert.
They do not support water.
But it is a crab!
A CRAB!
It is not a shrimp, of agreement!?
MADE SOMETHING!
He, they is not good!
Ca poses problems!
Look at that!
This river is practically an ocean, if we are not able to cross it, we will never arrive in time!
And even if one manages to cross this river, there remains still ten kilometers to be traversed in the desert!
If this crab does not manage to reach the other shore,
we are good to run the remainder of the way!?
I think that one does not have the choice.
ONE WILL NEVER ARRIVE THERE!
Y' does not have an other way!
Shit!
He, here is the river!
I see Sandora!
What?
Please, do something, Pincemie-Kun!
Yes!
Pincemy adores the dancers!
Like us?
Perhaps.
OHHHHH!!!!
It looks in this direction!
It accelerated!
NAMI-SWAAANNN!
You managed to persuade two animals thanks to your talents!
Brilliant, ERO POWER!!
And… in what will that solve our problem?
CHOPPER!?
GO!
BRILLIANT!
Ho, Ho, Ho!
It is really astonishing.
I cannot believe it.
It is formidable!
It is a miracle!
Maintenances at water surface in this direction!
Course! Course! Course in this direction!
Go!
You can do it!
You will arrive there!
You do it!
You are a crab, you can do it!
Now, starts to swim!
Does He, it occur what?
It runs?
One runs!?
We run!!
DO NOT RUN, STUPID CRAB!
There are not time to hear you groan.
Advances.
Oh. Have-await one second.
There is no boat!?
Which distance separates us from other bank?
Approximately 50 km.
ONE CANNOT SWIM ALSO FAR!
Thank you!
Thank you, Pincemie!
It is not really the moment to thank it, not!?
What is it…?
A rare catfish of Sandora!
They are called as that because it is extremely rare to see one of them!
Save to us your tourist details!
And the human ones are its favorite food!
WOULD HAVE TO SAY CA IN FIRST to you!!!
He, is pushed!
I see more anything!
Chopper! Push yourself!
Kung Fu Dugong!
They said:“One could not give up the disciples of our Master”
Euh… one is not really the disciples of Luffy…
But at least, one is healthy and safe!
Oué, it remains to us still way to be made!
With the next one!
Thank you!
Bye Bye!
One is in times.
You think that one can do it?
It is difficult to say.
Even with Matsuge-Kun, that is likely to be hard.
And it cannot transport…
that… two people!
And if Works Baroque attacks us, they will do it more close to the city!
There is not another way so that one travels all together?
Does shit, nobody have an idea?
Look at!
Over there!
What is it? An enemy!?
III they come towards us!?
Not, it is…
Karu!
The squadron of the super-mallards!
You came to help us!
Karu!
MEAT!
You and me…
… sums of the pirates of different classes.
Yuba will die.
And the heinous flame of the rebellious army will burn again.
Mercy…
Why do you fight?
You who bear the name of “D”?
D?
Who are you with the Juste?
It is a rather useless question.
I found you!
Where is Vivi-Sama!?
Ah?
Already upright?
I know your capacities now.
Ca will not be as easy as the last time!
Do not do too much of it.
You are seriously wounded.
Which perfect synchronization.
You can save this man who to lie there.
It is this valiant knight knight who brought your invaluable Princesse up to now.
And your Princess is in perfect health.
She is on the way for Alubarna at the time when we speak.
I do not know what will occur.
The things are what they are, after all.
If I can nothing make for it, which can protect Vivi-Sama?
MEAT!
You do not lose anything to wait, Cobra!
We will protect Arabasta!
Your reign touches at its end!
Capital of the Kingdom - Alubarna
Quickly!
Do not weaken!
Keep rate!
Prepare the guns with the Southern Door!
Do not lose a minute!
Quickly!
Bring more boulets de canon!
Chaka-Sama!
The number of rebels exceeds the 2 million easily.
Say to me, that you of the attack of the King think on Nanohana?
I was useful under the orders of his majesty during ten years, it does not have there reason to believe…
Yes, there is no proof that it is him.
It is unthinkable that a thing arrived to the King to make it change as much.
Thus, it is paramount not to lose this battle.
Let us not be afraid of the number of enemies.
For our King!
And for the return of Vivi-Sama!
WE WILL PROTECT THIS COUNTRY UNTIL THE END!
How all the not requisitioned civilians evacuate the city!
We cannot protect the lives from those which remain!
Run! You are likely to be taken in the battle!
Look at as agitation starts to reign here.
You dispatch and that the battle begins.
One waits there and one is bored.
I make fun to know if it is the good King or anyone of other.
It is out of the question which I remain here to observe this type!
Out of the question!
Not! Not! and Not!
Of course, to infiltrate in the palate by thwarting the vigilance of the guards and to remove this type…
… was a mission made for us.
But maintaining that is enough, one should not be wedged here to be bored to die like that!
Not true, Mr. 4?
Euh…
You me listenings or what!?
What are slow for you.
Slow to answer. Frankly.
Ah, that gives me badly with the hip! My sciatica!
Chaka…
Kohza…
You should not beat you.
You are what makes this country.
You should not destroy you mutually!
Those which deplore the combat.
Those which will fight.
Allons-y!
Those which encourage with violence.
And those which know the truth and which will try to prevent it.
Each one carries its convictions.
They will run up in the capital, Alubarna!
The port city - Nanohana
The final rebellion started.
Their boat was there.
I hope that Vivi-Sama and the others arrived healthy and safe, but…
I must make quickly!
I hope only that I will arrive in time!