What?
Whew, this is heavy.
What is that?
I found these in the storage room.
Aren't those cannonballs?
I figured we could practice using
our hard earned cannon.
Then I'll take care of it.
I think I was 3...
Traveling half-way around the world,
riding on a cannonball...
How do you use this.
Listen to me!
Hey Zoro! Do you know how to use this?
He's been sleeping for a while.
No fun.
If we go a little south, there's
a perfect place for practicing.
Really? Let's go, let's go!
Hey, can you shoot cannons as well as I can?
People called me the cannon master...
Listen!
THE PAST OF THE THREE SWORDS!
THE PROMISE BETWEEN ZORO AND KUINA!
Anyone here?
Anyone here!?
I am a doujouyaburi.
(Doujouyaburi - someone that challenge a dojo and defeats all it's members.)
Any strong person come forth!
Come and fight me!
It's pretty rare to see a doujouyaburi these days.
Hmm! Don't underestimate
me just because I'm a kid.
I'm undefeated in all of nearby towns.
That's fine.
We accept your challenge.
If I win, I'll take your signboard.
If you lose?
Lose...
If that happens, lets see...
I will join this place.
That is acceptable.
Then!
Kuina!
Yes, father.
What's the hell?
You're not the one fighting?
Even though Kuina is a girl, she is stronger
than the adults in the dojo.
I'm not a father that brags about his daughter.
I got it!
Then, please come inside.
I can use any of these right?
As you please.
Then, let's begin!
Yes, come and try me.
Bow to the Gods.
Is he stupid?
Bow to the opponent.
Begin!
Da-damn!
You...
have been taught two-sword techniques?
I wouldn't know!
Today is the first time I ever held a shinai.
(Shinai - bamboo sword.)
The first time ever?
Damn!
I'm strong, and I'll become stronger!
How... how can I Iose to this girl?!!
Why isn't he dodging?
Single blow!
Stop!
This kid is like a boar.
Hey, Kuina.
A poser like you...
Is ten years too early to wIeld two swordsl
What?!!!
What?
Do you want to go for another round?
Shit... a loss Is a loss.
Good, very straight forward.
Then...
Okay, l'll join this place.
Any problems with that?
I don't.
I'll...
Continue, continue, continue to train.
And I will beat you!
And I will beat youI
Remember that!
That'll never happen.
(DOJO)
Single blow!
Stop!
Winner, Kuina!
2000 wins, 0 losses!
Da... Damn.
You're weak as usual, Zoro.
How can you be so weak...
as a man.
Zoro isn't weak, right?
He the strongest among the male students, right?
He even wins against adults.
However, he's weaker than me.
Even with two katanas,
a weak guy is a weak guy.
A dog that loses should stay quiet, barking
about it only makes it look more pitiful.
You've lost again.
Zoro, you have gotten a lot stronger.
Sensei, you're not giving her special training
just because she's your daughter are you?
That's not fair!
No, I wouldn't do something like that.
It's true that Zoro has gotten stronger.
However, Kuina also has gotten stronger.
Zoro...
Zoro?
I'm going to wash my face.
Damn!
Why can't I beat Kuina?
Why?! Why?!
I'm going to become the strongest man in the world!
Why?!
Tonight...
I will duel her once more.
It's only been a year since he joined...
Zoro's progress is unbelievable.
He practices a lot more than anyone else.
The outcome of his training is quite expected...
However, he still can't defaat Kuina.
There's a huge wall blocking a
female swordsman's future.
Under the current circumstances,
I can't let her inherit the dojo.
Father!
Kuina san!
You shouldn't eavesdrop, Kuina.
I will become the world's greatest
swordsman to show you!
Kurina..
a woman...
will not be able to become the world's best.
Zoro...
What are you doing here?
That's what I wanted to ask you.
What are you doing here during
this time of the night?
I came here to request our 2001st battle.
For this will be our last duel.
Let's end this.
Fight me with a real sword!
You do have a real sword, right?
With me?
Fine!
Wado Ichimonji
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Two real swords must be heavy.
It seems like you still lack a bit of stamina.
Shut up!
This is my 2001st win.
Damn!
Shit.
I can't accept this...
I'm the one who wants to cry
because I can't accept it.
Girls...
when we grow up, we become weaker than men.
I'll probably be overtaken by you soon.
You always said you'd become the
best swordsman in the world.
My father told me that...
it's not possible for a woman.
I know...
I already know about this.
But... but, I can't accept it!
Zoro, it must be nice to be a man.
I also want to become the world's
greatest swordsman.
My chest is starting to grow out.
If... If I was born a boy..
After beating me, how can
you say such weak words!
That's despicable!
You've been my goal all this time!
Zoro...
Weather you're a man or a woman...
Is that what you're going to say
when I beat you one day?!
As if it wasn't because of my skills.
It makes me, who's been training
hard, a complete fool!
Don't say things like that!
Promise me!
One day either you or me will be the
greatest swordsman in the world!
We will compete to see who does it!
Stupid, saying that even though you are weak...
Promise!
Amazing...
Doesn't she seem to be even stronger than before?
I must increase my stamina.
Until I can wield as many swords as I want...
If two isn't enough then I'll use three!
What's the matter with you?
Kuina is...
Kuina is dead.
She missed her footing on the
stairs in the storage room.
Storage room?
It seems that she went in there
to find her katana's whetstone.
Why look for such a thing...
Who knows...
She was still a kid.
You can't understand humans.
Who knows what will happen tomorrow?
Humans are really fragile beings, Zoro.
Kuina was...
That girl hated to lose.
Ever since she was little, she trained in this dojo.
Obtaining skills that would even beat adults.
Because of that, she became arrogant...
At that time, Zoro...
you appeared before us.
I sincerely thank you.
To be able to beat you, who has
become stronger day by day...
she concentrated on her training even more.
She didn't want to lose to a boy like you.
Thus she started breaking the obstacles
of being a swordswoman...
I'm just an ordinary father after all.
Even now when I look at you...
I feel a pain in my heart.
Sensei...
That katana... please give it to me.
Kuina's katana?
I will... take her share of training
and become even stronger!
I'll become so strong that my
name will reach the heavens!
I'll become the strongest swordsman in the world!
We promised...
I...
That's fine!
Kuina's soul and dreams...
I leave them to you.
It's been eight years since then...
You'll finally go on your journey.
Yes, sensei.
To fulfill... my promise.
Zoro!
Take care.
I missed.
What are you guys doing?
We re practicing shooting the cannon.
But it's harder than I thought it wouId be.
I told you, let me show you how it has to be done.
Eh, with our current distance... this is about right?
Fire!!
Amazing!
You hit it with one shot!
It reaIIy hit the target.
Of course, when it comes to aiming, I know
everything. So you beIieve now?
You're the shooter from now on.
What? I'm not the captain?
I'm the captain!
That's okay, I'll let you have that position for now.
However, if you do a poor job,
I'm gonna replace you.
That's fine.
Before that, I've been thinking.
Before going to the Grand Line, we
need to filI one more position.
need to fiII one more position.
Right, and we have such a nice kitchen!
If you pay me, I'll do it.
It's an important personnel for any long trip.
That's right, it's someone that we
must have on a pirate ship!
A musician!
Are you an idiot?
What the hell do you think sailing is?!
I thought you were actually saying
something constructive for once.
But pirates have to sing.
Come out you pirates!
What what?!
Who are you?
Shut up!
It doesn't matter who I am!
How many of them are there?
Is there... one?
Then leave it to him
I've killed a countless number of pirates.
But a no name pirate like you
dares to try kill my partner?!
That voice...
What do you mean, partner?
I don't know what's going on.
But don't damage our ship!
No..
No chance at all.
What was that?
Hey you! Aren't you Johnny?
Who is it? Calling out my name with no respect.
Zoro-aniki!
So it is Johnny.
Why are you here, aniki?
Where's Yosaku? You're not together?
What, what?
You two know each other?