Luffy against Vivi!
The desire for crying of the companions
With the kingdom of the Oases.
Three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
In a howl of sadness, this desiccated ground sinks from now on in an enormous wave of agitation.
In the hope to stop the rebellion, Princess Vivi goes to the oasis of Yuba.
But they discover that the rebellious army for a long time left the city.
During this time, the Agents Officers of Baroque Works remainders started to move.
It would seem that the final confrontation between the royal army and the army rebels became inevitable!
Well, friends!
We had a hard day!
Let us take a little rest to take again forces for tomorrow.
Good night.
You slept all the time!
Moron…
Do not compare to me with you, you are monsters!
It is like that.
Moreover, today the price of laziness should return to you, Nose-Blue!
But I cannot support heat!
Sanji-San, it is my…
Yes, I thought that you would feel less only this night.
Do Eh, what you believe being making?
It would be said that somebody wants to die.
Which of you has just launched me that?
Do you include/understand the significance of the word “To sleep”?
You died!
Take that!
Why you attack me me!?
Eh, Ossan…
There is no water which leaves.
My throat is very dry.
It is rather hard to live outside like that.
Water will come.
The oasis of Yuba is always in life.
Yuba will never be overcome by a little sand.
I will continue to dig, it does not matter the number of times that I must start again.
It is the invaluable ground which the King entrusted to me.
Hein?
Well of agreement! I will dig too!
Eh, of the calm one!
Do not send sand in the hole where I dig!
Try you to stop the hole or what!?
Not, I dig the hole.
It is not what I want to say! You send all sand in my hole.
Whereas I was the first to start to dig a hole, you see?
Ah.
Oh, then it is a magic hole!
But at all!
But I think of it… That makes a small moment that I did not receive from sand.
How did it can dig such a large hole also quickly?
It must be tired by its long voyage.
You rest this night well.
Meat…
Good night.
STOP JOKING!
How long it still will make us wait!?
Give me Poulpa.
I will dance.
I will do it, you know!
I am a swan!
A swan!
I will turn!
Mr. 2, please, remain calm.
Ouais, really. Imbecile!
Your cries hurt me with the hips!
You also, Miss Merry Christmas.
It would seem that you do not like to wait.
Well, it does not matter in fact.
Miss All Sunday.
Thank you to have made all this way to come.
I am content that you could all come.
In the city where people dream to become rich while gaining with the plays.
The city of the dreams, Rainbase.
And it is in the largest casino of the city, Rain Dinners, that I wish you the welcome.
Let us pass the formalities and go directly to essence, Miss All Sunday.
As you want.
I will continue the briefing.
Ouais, go ahead.
Start immediately!
Start now!
Continue now!
HOY! HOY! HOY! HOY! HOY!
But front, I must present to you…
… the Boss of our organization, that of which you never saw the face.
Until now, I acted like his representative…
… and I transmitted his orders to you.
But it will not be soon necessary any more.
You, isn't this includes/understands?
In other words, the moment came…
… for the Utopia Operation.
Crocodile…
The final objective of Works Baroque.
As envisaged, you seem to know it.
Its face all at least.
Of course that we know it!
But what does Shichibukai make here?
This guy is rather a large size!
Does that mean that we worked for a pirate all this time!?
Thus it is you the Boss?
Objections?
I do not have an objection, but…
Shichibukai is a pirate who has the permission of the government and which can plunder what he wants.
Why did you need to create this organization?
What I want, it is not money…
… or a social status.
It is a military capacity.
A military capacity?
Let us discuss each thing one by one.
In first my objectives, then details of the Final Operation of Works Baroque…
Does such a thing really exist in this country?
Or do you hope to seize all the country?
I am so excited!
Approximately, our last orders…
… are to carry out the various facets of the final plan?
It is exact.
Each action that you carried out since the creation of the organization was part of this plan.
And these are the last orders that I will give you.
Time came for the kingdom from Arabasta to disappear.
Once you will have supplemented your last tasks,
the kingdom of Arabasta will crumble itself.
The rebellious army and people, plugged by the rage…
… will fall tragically into the hands from Works Baroque.
In only one night, this country will become our Utopia.
It is most important and the final plan of Works Baroque:Utopia operation.
The failure is unacceptable.
We will start tomorrow at 7 a.m.
OK!                     OK!
Let us request to be lucky.
I ask that the Utopia Operation be deferred.
Mr. 3, how did you find this base secret?
Mr. 3! Under which stone you had thus taken refuge!?
I conform to the orders, I thus will kill you!
Wait, Mr. 2.
“To be dissimulated”? As you are désobligeant.
I simply took the shuttle on the way since Spiders Café.
With the back of the body of Banchi, obviously.
Enchanted, Boss.
I came to ask for a second chance.
As I did not achieve the orders,
you, Mr. 2, of course received the order to eliminate me.
For this reason, I modified a little bit my way and I went to the point of appointment of the Agents:Spiders Coffee.
You did not achieve the orders?
About what do speak you?
I speak owing to the fact that I left Straw hat and Princess Vivi to escape…
You let them leave!?
Summers you saying to me that they are always alive?
Den Den Mushi = Snail Phon
What do you have says me to Den Den Mushi?
Hadn't you said me that you had dealt with each one of them, Princesse included/understood?
Den Den Mushi?
About what do speak you?
I am sure not to be to me served as my Den Den Mushi when I was in Little Garden…
How!?
Hey, thank you for your call.
It is the Restaurant of Shit.
Which is your order?
That could pose problem.
Now I know why Unluckies did not return yet from the island.
Well? You at least one or two out of them, isn't this killed?
Eh well, you see…
There was an error in information!
There were in fact 4 pirates with it!
A nose… There was one with a long nose of them…
Dumb…
Zéro-Chan! Can you explain us what it speaks!?
I do not include/understand anything the whole!
I…
I met these guy!
On my way, I met them!
How?
This guy!
And that one!
And it!
And him!
And he also, isn't this?
Moreover, it was Miss Wednesday and Princess Vivi!?
And you me known as that these guy are my enemies!?
Yes, they know my identity.
If I do not pay attention, they will interfere with my plan.
And as Mr. 3 has just said it, there was another person with them. As well as an animal.
If the animal is forgotten, they form a group of 5.
We can suppose that they already arrived at Arabasta.
Mr. 2, take some photographs by taking again their faces.
M- But, Boss!
I will exterminate Vivi as well as the group of the pirates if you give me…
Silence, you are really only one good with nothing!
Mr. 3…
Mr. 3!
Do you know why I gave you this title!?
In capacities of combat, you are lower than Mr. 4.
Mr. 3!
I believed that you had tenacity necessary to carry out the orders by employing the most underhand methods!
And I am very disappointed.
What is it!?
He is desiccating itself!
Water…
Water!
Wood all the water which you wish.
It is the hour of the meal.
Which is this place?
Am I under water?
Ca resembles an aquarium…
Bananawani!
Bananawani = Bananacroco
This moron had what it deserves.
Even its death is not enough for me!
Listen to me, the pawns.
Engrave these 5 faces in your brains.
Their goal is to stop the rebellious army.
If they are not continued, it will show themselves.
But, Zéro-Chan…
Even if it is the princess, it can still stop the rebellious army?
They would be annoying.
The leader of the rebellious army, Kohza and the Princess Nefertari Vivi…
… are amis d'enfance, according to our sources.
It is a movement of 700.000 people.
Even if it cannot stop them,
she can certainly make them hesitate.
I already set up several Billions in the rows of the rebellious army.
I do not have for the moment received any news of their share,
what means that they did not have to act up to now.
We cannot let Vivi come into contact with the rebellious army.
Miss All Sunday.
Yes.
Considering the circumstances, you are authorized to use Den Den Mushi if need be.
Order with the Billions in place to eliminate these five people if they meet them.
Let neither the Vivi nor pirates enter Katorea!
Vivi and Kohza should not meet!
Yes, I go there.
You all can leave.
You will be late for the festival.
Our Utopia is held in front of our eyes.
I trust you so that there are not other problems.
Let make us, Boss.
Yes, let make us!
Have fun.
I am afflicted, Vivi-Chan. You do not should have seen that.
Not, at all!
We will leave now, Ojisan.
Ah, Luffy-Kun. Hold, takes that with you.
Wow! Water!
Water!
It left the ground?
Just after you would have fallen asleep by digging last night.
We reached the level of water.
I drew a little water and I distilled it.
Ca seems a little complicated, but thank you!
The genuine water of Yuba.
Afflicted, but it is all that I can give you.
I will drink it by paying to!
Do Eh Luffy, what you make!?
Luffy?
What doesn't go, Luffy-San?
I give up.
To give up?
Do Luffy-San, what you want to say?
Go, Luffy. We do not have time to yield to your whims.
Rise!
One sets out again.
One must advance!
One must remake all the way towards Katorea and stop the rebellious army.
If a million people fight, it will be the end, you include/understand!?
It is for Vivi-Chan.
Go, come, one sets out again.
I don't care.
But what are you making!?
Vivi.
What?
I want to beat this refuse of Crocodile!
If we stop the rebellious army, that will stop Crocodile?
Even if we reach Katorea, there is not only we can make.
We are pirates.
You would make better go there without us.
Sometimes, this idiot without brain uses his head.
Lu… ffy can surprise us sometimes.
It… It is not…
All that you want, it is that nobody dies in this combat.
No inhabitant of this country.
None among us.
You speak about Shichibukai and a million people who are ready to fight.
And what you want, it is that nobody is wounded.
Is it a joke?
Await Luffy, cannot you try to include/understand the feelings of Vivi?
Nami-San, wait…
But…
What bell for you?
Which evil is there to want that nobody dies?
People die.
Stop speaking like that!
I will not let myself say that one second time!
It is exactly what we try to avoid!
The army of the rebels, the royal army…
Inhabitants of this country…
It is not their fault!
Then why should somebody die?
All that it is the fault of Crocodile!
Then why would you you risk your life?
He Luffy, you go too far!
Dumb, Luffy!
When you look at this country, what you see the urgent one to regulate…
Take that!
It is however clear… for me!
Yuba will never be overcome by a little sand.
You believe that to risk your own life, that will be enough!?
And then, what am I supposed to risk?
I will never forgive with this man!
What am I…?
I do not have anything else to bring into play…
Nothing…
Try to risk our lives at the same time as holds it!
We are your companions!
What? One would say…
… that you cry.
I will stop the rebellion.
You are that which suffers more, and you want to fight it more than whoever.
Now say to me.
Where is Crocodile?!