Yes!
Seek freedom,
And your world will stand stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides your spirits,
Conquer it!
Bear conviction behind your flag!
I began my search,With a blast of water,
Toward a boundless,everlasting world
With this overflowing passion in my chest, I'll go anywhere
Seeking the light l've never seen
When the summer-colored sun shakes the sall of my heart,
It's a sign the door to a new world has opened
Swaying between the waves, I can escape despair,
For the horize on the other side is what I aim for!
I began my search, With a blast of water,
Toward a boundless, everlasting world
With this overflowing passion in my chest, I'll go anywhere
Seeking the light I've never seen
Your desire does not lie within this country!
Am I wrong?
You're fighting for someone else's desire!
Why would you die for that!?
Like I said...
You don't understand anything.
Vivi...
She tells others not to die...
But she's the first one who throws her life away to save someone else.
That's why I'm saying you should just abandon such an annoying-
I DON'T WANT HER TO DIE!
WE'RE NAKAMA!
Vivi-sama...
Devoting my life to the service of the Nefertari Family...
...fills my heart with such everlasting pride.
I am a Guardian Spirit of Arabasta!
The Falcon!
One who destroys the enemies of the Royal Family!
It exceeds!
It rains to Alabasta!
Pell...
That crazy bastard...
He protected the country.
Oi
You gotta be kidding me...
Wait...
Please stop, all of you...!
Sergeant Major, watch out!
What?
Tashigi...
Watch what happens to this country very carefully.
This is the kind of thing that happens at the turning point of an era.
Madness...
Why... don't they stop?
PLEASE STOP FIGHTING!
PLEASE...
STOP FIGHTING!
Vivi...
PLEASE...
STOP FIGHTING!
You idiot...
You three!
What the hell are you standing around for!?
Punch them, kick them! Anything!
Whatever you have to do to stop the rebellion!
Hurry up and GO!
Save as mary lives as possible!
PLEASE...
STOP FIGHTING!
At long last...
The new era has begun.
The day my ambition becomes reality!
This country is MINE!
I DON'T WANT HER TO DIE!
WE'RE NAKAMA!
That's why as long as she doesn't give up on her country...
We won't stop fighting!
You... can't...
...defeat me!
Are those the only words you can squeeze out?
A bluff from a dog about to meet his death...
How fitting.
Groundless!
I am...
...the man who will become the Pirate King!
Listen, boy.
The more you get to know this sea, the more you learn not to make impudent statements like that.
I already told you...
There are so mary rookies just like you on this sea!
The more you learn about the level of this sea...
THE MORE YOU LOSE SIGHT OF THOSE DREAMS!
I am...
...the man who will surpass you!
The scorpion poison should have taken effect.
Where's this kid...
...drawing all this power from?
The Mr. 5 Pair was defeated, you say?
Who the hell could beat them?
Monkey D. Luffy?
Never heard of him.
Hah. You must be mistaken.
What?
Are you telling me they're still alive!?
Sir Crocodile.
Those pirates have entered the city.
You're just some kid who showed up out of nowhere!
JUST WHO THE HELL DO YOU THINK I AM!?
I don't give a shit who you are!
I WILL SURPASS YOU!
I'll destory you along with this temple!
SANDS
HEAVY
GOMU GOMU NO...
DESERT
STORM!
LA SPADA
Incredible!
There is only pure bedrock between this room and the surface!
Stop!
Oi, look! Up there!
CROCODILE!
At this rate, blood will soon be shed throughout the country!
It will become war!
Just getting there alive is no longer enough!
I have to get there as soon as possible!
If I don't make it in time,
1,000,000 of my people will engage in meaningless slaughter!
Really?
Then all I have to do to Crocodile...
...is kick his ass, right?
Luffy-san...
Not sure how he got blasted up all the way over there...
HOW ELSE!?
I never had a doubt in my mind...
But now...
HE WON!!
Even when there's no one left to fight...
Please... stop the bloodshed...!
PLEASE STOP FIGHTING!
Kohza!
Are you okay, Kohza?
See?
Do not doubt him, Kohza.
The rain shall fall.
The battle...
...is over!
Rain...
The madness has ceased.
The confusion has stayed their weapons...
The smoke is being suppressed by the rain.
PLEASE DON'T...
...FIGHT ANYMORE!!
Vivi's voice is...
...reaching them.
Vivi-sama...
Vivi...
I thought the Princess had gone missing...
Hey, you!
Crocodile-san!
Why did he fall down here?
Crocodile-SAN you say...!?
I'm gonna tell you a thing or two about what he's done to this country!
Oi, wait, wait.
Calm down.
This rain, just as it is falling...
Just as it always has...
...will fall again.
The nightmare... has finally ended!
My thanks.
No problem.
What course can I set that will lead me to a better tomorrow?
Taking the helm, I spread out the map of miracles I had shut in my heart
Aiming for the sky, searching for a dream, there were times when I lost my way
But this isn't a dream, I found a wonderful part of myself when I met you
With a small bit of courage, I gained something large
So now is the time to change my dreams into vows.
Shining Ray! Find your brand new way.
Let's paint a story of the future
And put all of our thoughts into this new wind
Shining Ray! Find your brand new way.
A never ending journey to be together.
I'll chase it anywhere, this Shining Ray!