What a speed!
To this pace it soon will catch up with Porch-chan!
The wall.
It of it is magnificiently drawn!
It is nothing any more but one question of seconds
before it catches up with Porch-chan!
It is already there?
Take that!
Here, am my councils and that will go.
They is good!!
Remain Luffy upright!!
APOGEE Of an EXPLOSIVE RACE!
TO GAIN THE FINAL ROUND!
Go! Still an effort! Fight!
That emotions…
They is good! Be to you there almost!
Yosh! I am upright!
Hold the blow, Usopp!
What a speed! Too much extremely!!
One will not lose!
Extraordinary! The moment of front, Luffy with
straw hat did not even hold upright!
Now it patinates as quickly as
Chiqicheetah, however at the head!
Shit!
Shit, I forgot to say to him how to turn!
Luffy with the straw hat still left the track!
Here it is excluded from this sleeve!
(It is really not the moment…)
Ca is badly…
The Chiqicheetah pirate carries out the race with 4 turns!
Length-nose, clings to me and sinks!
The blow of the lasso of the archeologist Nico Robin!
Will it succeed in taking the top?
Iyan… This woman!
Porch-chan, lets to me deal with that!
Chiqicheetah has just passed the third speed!
He! It left the track!
It did not leave it!
It remained in the air!
The complaint of the burning Sanji coach will not succeed!
They will not arrive there without my assistance.
Oh not!
Do not try to struggle.
That would do nothing but tighten my pressure.
Useless!
I am a mollusc, that does not do anything to me.
Played Juubei well!
Finished playing.
Shit, Robin it is made trap!
Idiotic He of coach,
if one does not stop this Chiqicheetah, one will lose.
I know it well!
Chiqi… cheetah… chiq…
perhaps that…
Ossan!
The old man with the horse, be to you there?!
It is of me that one speaks?
Where you ace found the funny one of kiwi, which you spun ace with Luffy?
But what can that to you foutre?
Your mouth!
Ossan, answer, that is urgent!
Ah that? On this tree with the interlaced branches!
Quickly head of cactus, brings back for me a branch of kiwi!
It is like that you requests a service?
It is perhaps our only means of stopping this type!
A means of stopping it?
Yes, hurries!
Qu… What you made?
Take Shelly!
Here!
I am unaware of if it will go but…
one will have at least tested.
Already 4 minutes…
Chiqicheetha is at the head with an advance of 13 turns!
4 minutes and 30 seconds, now…
It with maintaining 15 turns in advance!
The situation is desperate for Mugiwara Dangers!
It puts to time this dumb of it!
It is that?
4 minutes and 50 seconds!
In 10 seconds, Foxy Devils will have gained the part!
I will not arrive there…
5 seconds…
What does it occur?
Oh, it is…
What it arrived at Chiqicheetah?!
Chiqicheetah left the track at 5 seconds of the end!
What a finish!
Mugiwara Dangers gain an unhoped-for victory!
Chiqicheetah… Iyan…
WHAT!?
Round of applause-Banzaï!
Why?
But, why that!?
Certain kiwis push on the silver plated vine…
I intended to say that the cats
fall in extase in front of the strong one…
odor released by the silver plated vine.
The cheetah being same family as the cats…
I thus had this idea.
Then it is for that it reniflait Luffy.
Undoubtedly.
Very impressive, Main Cock.
If you it known as…
It was less one…
Mugiwara Dangers gained a point…
but Foxy Devils are not acknowledged not overcome!
Pas le time to enjoy your victory,
the fourth handle soon will start!
The Point-Getters are,
The historian Nico Robin…
against Juubei the man-fish.
Two master cards!
Luffy, when you arrive at the curve…
I have measuring rod the trick, that will go.
Will that go!? You ace considering how you patinas…?
Zoro, do not make any you.
You said to me to observe how the others patinate, not?
Hein?
It will still use its perfume, it is sure.
Ah! Fact of shitting, this dirty perfume.
This head of breeze block…
Oyabin!
Usopp, listening that!
You be an unpleasant girl…
Good idea, not true?
It would be said that Nami the navigatrice scheme something.
It has the glance even more cheating than Oyabin!
It is which that you treat of cheating!?
You…
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
MUGIWARA-TEAM
C is the hour of the fourth handle!
You heard ace?
Loans…
LEAVE!
Be not made illusions.
Perhaps Chiqicheetah beats me, but I remain fast.
The 20 seconds passed, defense can leave!
Will that go for Luffy?
Super!
Be the best for you, Luffy!!
No matter what you make,
you will finish victim of my Mucha Caramente!
Certainly not!
Ooohh! It finally overcame somebody…
Luffy with the straw hat beat Juubei!
Sink, Robin! I deal with that one!
Included/understood.
Where my stick passed?!
Afflicted
Iyan! You are caught for whom?!
Sitted remainder. It is for your good.
Yes!
Fantastic!
Mugiwara Dangers control the race completely!
I will show them…
Hamburger.
Prepare in “Dull Dash”!
Yes.
Usopp, it from goes away.
Lends to launch the plan of the “reversal to 180 degrees”?
Ok.
Nasty face of puzzle!
You still make the clown?!
Head of puzzle… Clown…
He lies! You are fantastic, Oyabin-chan!
You really believe it? Species of imbecile!
Not I am serious! I admire you! I love you!
It is obvious that she lies! Deformed head of puzzle!
Do not criticize my head…
Be brilliant for you!
Head of puzzle!
I love you!
Old idiot!
Head of puzzle!
Nami, you must continue to praise it!
I can about it more…
my belly is tied with each word which I pronounce…
Usopp, replaces me…
How they dare… Bastards!!
I do not manage to say good of him…
Tant pis, allons-y à fond !
Ouais!
Be brilliant for you! Head of puzzle! Be brilliant for you!
Head of puzzle! Be brilliant for you! Head of puzzle…
It cannot use Noro Noro Beam any more!
Our Oyabin will collapse it under
power of their words!?
Time remaining is reduced!
… Be brilliant for You! Head of puzzle! Be brilliant for you!
Head of puzzle! Be brilliant for you! Head of puzzle!
Head of puzzle!
Be brilliant for you!
And the sleeve is finished!
Mugiwara Dangers have completely
dominated this fourth handle!
The two teams are entitled to 5 minutes
rest before the ultimate handle!
How I could fall into their poor trap!?
Who would have believed that they would hold
until the final sleeve…
Listen,
one should not lose any more!
One will use “the Plan”, one will undoubtedly gain!
We will use it?
Ouais! One will gain!
And now, here is finally the final round!
Place on the starting line!
Oh! With share the Point-Getter
no Foxy Devil N is on the track.
Perhaps it prepares its special blow?!
Special blow?
It is still its ray pourrave, it is that?
Iyan, you said it.
Its Noro Noro Beam will undoubtedly touch its target!
All the plan turns around that…
When you include/understand, it will be too late.
But about what do you speak, saw you well the last round?
There is our plan of the reversal to 180 degrees.
Luffy, do not make any you and rolls thoroughly!
Ok! Count on me!
Go, with your marks…
Loans?
LEAVE!
What!? Already?
Head of puzzle! Be brilliant for you! Head of puzzle!
Be brilliant for you! Head of puzzle! Be brilliant for you!
Here it is! Noro Noro Beam with fast shooting!
Why…
doesn't the plan of the reversal to 180 degrees go?
You known as something?
It has earplugs!!
Mugiwara Dangers are in the soup!
It is not our Oyabin for nothing!
Shit!
Hein? It diverted Noro thingummy-trick?
Iyan, you noticed ace?
Noro Noro Beam does not go on Girarin.
Ah yes? And why thus?
It is one…
secrecy!
It is a secrecy, it is for that?
Then it is for that you ace left the track.
Yes, Thus only your fellow-members
will be touched by the ray!
You will not even be able you
to serve as us like shield.
It was that the plan? One is badly!
The 20 seconds passed. Go!
Nami-san!
In the thousand!
Nami the navigatrice and Usopp the marksman…
were taken in Noro Noro Beam!
Luffy, pay attention behind you!
Luffy with the straw hat was also touched!
Will they be able to overcome?
Then it is you the last?
I should not run the risk.
If I am touched by this ray,
there will be no more average to gain.
What does it occur?
Nico Robin of Mugiwara Dangers,
who supported the effort a long time,
the sponge would thus have thrown?
It leaves already the part,
whereas there remains still a minute?
The effect of Noro Noro Beam lasts 30 seconds.
It must avoid the other rays.
I am sure that Luffy will arrive there.
I should not fail.
I should benefit from this chance.
Robin-chan, that is there?
While putting to me there I am with the shelter of the ray, not?
Robin-chan…
More than 40 seconds.
Foxy Devils carry out of 3 turns.
I transform you into two of tension
with my Noro Mani, just if.
Luffy with the straw hat, one had fun up to now,
but it is time to finish some.
More than 30 seconds.
If Luffy with the straw hat is still touched
by the ray their defeat will be certain!
It is the moment!
Shit!
Roll, Luffy! Time presses!
Yosh!
More that 20 seconds!
Come by here…
You prefer them been useful believed…
or fried?
More that 10 seconds!
The speed of Luffy to the straw hat is surrealist!
It would be said that it will gain the victory!
It is… It is not possible!!
Oyabin tasted with its own capacities!
More that 5 seconds!
A sword which does not slice…
that does not frighten me!!
What a unexpected victory of Mugiwara Dangers!
YATTA!!