What is that look in your face...
You want your village back that badly?
I make you a deal,
If you want it back...
What is it!?
I see...
Get 100 million beli for me.
I'll set you and your village free.
Really?
If there's money involved, I would
rather die than break a promise.
I don't care how many years it takes.
I'll keep my end of the deal.
Get her!
I'll gather 100 million beli, no matter what!
Bellemere-san, I'll do it!
No matter how long it takes!
LUFFY STANDS UP!
END OF A BROKEN PROMISE!
Gen-san...
And the Marines?
Are you Nami, the thief?
We heard by safe source that your
hiding big amount of stolen money...
As of now, we, the government will confiscate it
all the goods you have stolen.
What's the matter? Didn't you hear me?
It's decided that all the stolen pirate goods
will be taken into our custody.
Well, well.
How diligent you guys are in your duties.
You don't have the courage to stand up to pirates,
so you pick on smaller game to raise your standings.
How noble.
Let me tell you something.
I'm one of Arlong's crew.
Touch me, and Arlong won't stay quiet about it.
Is that your idea of threatening me, little girl?
Find the treasure!
Wait!
ST0P!!
Is this what the Marines do now?!
Arlong's gang is killing people and destroying villages!
You know it!
Even now they're taking over this
island, and wrecking lives!
To ignore that and take care of one measly thief,
Is that what you should be doing now?!
Don't talk as if you're superior.
Continue the search.
The people of this island have been waiting
for the Marines, help for so long.
How can you pass them by
and come straight to me?!
Captain, this orange orchard
seems a little suspicious.
Dig it up.
Don't touch Bellemere-san's orchard
with your filthy hands!
I won't give you my money!
That money is for...
It's for...
THE GIRL'S MONEY IS GOING TO
SAVE COCOYASHI VILLAGE!!
Does that make you think you have
the right to take it away, Marine?!
What?
Is one of the little villagers talking
to me, a Marine Captain?
Gen-san...
How did you...?
I've always known, Nami.
I'm... gonna...
I'm gonna join Arlong's gang.
Nami!
Back then. I just couldn't believe what you'd done.
So I questioned Nojiko.
From then on, everyone in the village knew.
That in order to save this village,
you joined Arlong's gang.
But, we pretended not to know,
so that if you ever wanted to run away from Arlong,
our hopes wouldn't pull you back into his gang.
Can't be...
What are you guys talking about?
Are you saying that the whole village is in
on the theft and wants to be arrested?
Is that it?
We're saying that we are fighting for our own lives!
Because you Marines can't be relied upon!
If you've no intentions of saving this village,
then get the hell out of here!
If you stick around, you'll be Arlong's target as well!
Arlong's target?
I wonder...
You still haven't found it?
It's not like we're searching for a grain of rice!
It's 100 million beli!
Hey, you bastard!
How do you know the amount!?
Ah. 100 million.
Well, I just had a feeling it would
be around that much.
Don't tell me...
Don't tell me Arlong sent you here?!
Who knows...
As government officials,
We're just doing what's necessary
to persecute thieves.
You corrupt bastards!
How could the Marines stoop so
low as to be pirates, lapdogs!?
Arlong!
It's here!
This is amazing!
That little girl sure did gather a lot!
But it's all stained with blood and in bad shape.
Who cares? Money is money.
And one third of this is all mine.
Don't touch it...
Nami!
DON'T TOUCH IT!!
Nami....
Nojiko!
NOJIKO!!
A pinwheel, huh?
That was so cool.
Oh! I just thought of a good move!
Doctor! Doctor!
What happened, Gen-san!?
Nojiko's been shot.
By who?
The Marines.
Marines?
Nojiko?
I... I'm fine.
Arlong was collaborating with the Marines.
What?
He turned his back on Nami eight years ago,
and never intended to keep his promise.
What!?
What? That means...
That bastard! Our Na-chan...!
Na-chan...
Nami...
Yo, Nami!
What's up?
Can I help with something?
You're STILL here?!
This is none of your business!
Get off this island!!
Arlong...
Arlong!
Arlong!!
If there's money involved,
I would rather die than break a promise.
I don't care how many years go by,
l will keep my end of the deal.
ARLONG!!
What's her problem?
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Arlong!!
Yo, what's up?
My prized map surveyor...
What's that look on your face?
Those Marines you sent took all of my money.
Didn't you say you would die before you
broke a promise involving money?
Right!?
WHY!?
Exactly when did I break our promise?
Don't play dumb! You used the Marines to...
When did I break our promise?
Tell me.
Dammit...
Dammit!
Is that so? All of your money was taken away?
That's unfortunate.
However, a promise is a promise.
Unless you bring 100 million beli before my eyes,
I can't release that village.
You scum!
It's only 100 million beli.
You can just gather it again.
Or are you gonna escape?
However, you know if you run away,
I kill everyone in this village...
We pretended not to know.
So that when you wanted to run away from Arlong,
Our hopes wouldn't pull you back into his gang.
Running away finally?
It's okay if we don't chase her?
Chase her? Why?
There's no way she'd escape.
She can't forfeit the lives of the villagers.
But what a devious trick that was.
I can't let a refined mapmaker like Nami get away.
But still, I'm not a demon.
Once she draws up maps of the whole world...
Then, I'll set her free.
And how many decades will that take?
She can die hundred times before finish it!
Okay!
Let's meet up with Luffy as soon as we can!
Hey, Sanji. What are you doing?
I'm cherishing this happiness.
What are you talking about?
Nami-san has suffered a lot.
Much more than anybody.
And I'm going to take away all that suffering.
Is there anything better than that?
Your motives are obvious.
Love Cook.
That is what a real gentleman do for
a beautiful and suffering ladie...
What's wrong with fighting for somebody beautiful?
We're doing this for everyone else in the village too.
Shut up.
Quit bickering.
Let's go.
This is as far as it goes!
Get your weapons! We're gonna fight!
YEAH!!
Gen-san...
Everyone...
Please! Don't be rash!
You can't die! Everything will be over!
You have to survive! Or everything will be over!!
Eight years ago,
we said we'd never throw our lives away!
That no matter how bad their
abuse against us became,
As long as Nami was fine,
We were going to continue our fight of endurance!
But this is how they answer back!
Now that there's no way for this village to
be free, we have no goal to survive for!
Furthermore!
We will not forgive them for
preying on Nami's kindness!!
Are there any objections!?
No way! Let's go!
We're already prepared to fight!
We're not gonna take it anymore!
YEAH!!
Wait' everybody!
Nami!
Just wait... Just wait a little longer!
I'm going to try again!
I'll get the money again!
It'll be easier this time! I have lots of experience!
It's okay. You don't have to worry!
Compared to that time...
I don't want anyone to die anymore!
Everybody, I'm fine!
I'm fine so...
That's enough.
We know what futility is like.
You fought well, for our sake.
It must have been more painful
for you to join that crew,
more painful than it is to cut yourself.
You fought well.
Gen-san...
Now, leave this village.
Gen-san!
Do it, Nami!
I can't!
Na-chan.
Nami
You've got brains,
and you've got a dream.
Nojiko! Everybody!
I won't let you!
Stop it, everyone!
I don't want to see anyone get hurt anymore!
You're gonna die.
We know.
It's useless.
We've already decided in our hearts.
Out of the way, Nami!
Let's go, everybody!
Even if we can't win, we'll show them our pride!
YEAH!!
Arlong.
ARLONG!!
Ar...!
Luffy...
What do you want?
You don't know anything.
You don't know what's been happening
for the past eight years on this island.
Yeah. I don't.
This is none of your business!
I told you to get off this island, didn't I?!
Yeah. You told me.
Go away!
You!
Go away!!
Go away!
Go away...
Luffy...
Help me.
DAMN RIGHT!!
Don't touch my treasure!
Luffy...
We're going.
Right!
Hey!
Are you guys okay?
Were you beaten up by Arlong?
Out of the way.
We've come to see the mermen.
After finding out the truth about Nami-aneki,
There was only one thing left to do, beat Arlong.
With that in mind, we came here.
But, we lost easily.
No offense, but we ain't moving for you guys.
You, who have no chance of winning.
What?
We're waiting for ''those guys'' to come.
''Those guys''?
Bet your life on it.
''Those guys'' will definitely come!
There!!
Them...
Those guys? What about them...?
If those guys can't stand up to them,
Then there's no hope, not only for this island,
But for the whole of East Blue.
Remember the faces of those four,
that have come to change the future.
Move.
Hey, do you think those two idiots
were part of Zoro's gang?
Zoro's gang? They were far too weak.
They weren't even worth killing.
So true.
What the...?
Which one's Arlong?