Too much coooool!
Delicious!
They is good?
A room V.I.P? I do not include/understand.
Not, not, it is not that…
I decided not to pay only one Berry.
Thank you for these good repairs!
Customers, should cease to you making fun you of the carpenters.
Ah… Excuse me.
In the carpenters, the pirates cannot impose their rules.
This tower is one of the elevators.
All is so large!
They are strong…
They are qualified…
They are the pride of Seven Toilets!
Effrayaaaant!
It is what?
It is a shop of masks.
CP9
Robin?
I thought that I attacked somebody of deadened…
Franky Family
and Iceberg-san.
Who are you, dumbs?
Answer!
“Answer”, you say? Eh?
Zoro the hunter of pirates!
We are bargain hunters!
Known under the name of Franky Family!
We will accept readily your premium of 60 million.
We wanted to take to you in ambush on the bridge…
And to capture the remainder of the group in the tread!
An enormous profit! Lucky!
I am the first!
“Lucky”?
Isn't this rather “Unlucky”?
No the hesitation!
Style with two sabers…
NITOU RYU
SAI KURU
Completely null…
Me-shit!
It is here!
Then, that do I can for you?
We want to exchange that.
How much that made?
Mr. Director! It is a serious business!
Such-so much of gold!
What?! Send immediately them in room VIP.
They is marrowy!
And that rebounds! Are these seats filled with water also, nan?
Isn't Oi, according to you, they are not counterfeits?
In any way!
I have been an expert inspector for 25 years!
With a rather fast evaluation, that is worth…
C… HUNDRED MILLION BERRYS??!!
Baka! You speak too extremely!
No matter who can hear!
really Have-have-have-go we to have as much money?!
Luffy, you speak still too extremely!
There that is worth certainly this price!
They are very old, and originally preserved… gold is splendid.
It is largely sufficient to repair Going Merry!
We will have money to do it.
Then we will be able to buy a bronze statue with the remainder of the money.
Do not buy that, does not buy that…
If we start to make the agreement…
Please sign then leave a print of inch.
I will prepare your money immediately.
Yosh!
I will leave my prints several times!
If it is not sufficient, I will do it too!
What? What doesn't go Nami?
I have three things to say…
Mr. expert inspector.
Firstly:
I forgot to say it to you, but this guy has a premium of 100 million on his head.
Secondo:
I am not agreement with this conclusion.
Thirdly:
If you lie us once again…
I remake you the face.
It is all…
Pa-forgiveness!!
Tr-trois hundred million Berrys?!
This is a dream?!
Our adventure in Sorajimas paid finally well!
I am somebody of very rich!
“We” are!
Thank you to be come…
We have 300 million.
And I carry 100 million!
Nami is really alarming when it makes threats!
I included/understood its swindles because I had already made an estimate.
Then when he said 100 million…
You were excited, then it tried to swindle you.
Oi, Luffy! Do not balance the bag like that…
Good, in any case, they is cool. Very happened well.
IT GOES IN THE RIVER!!
The 100 million Berrys will fall into water!
It was right, it was right.
I will kill you!!
I will remake you the portrait!!
Déf…, I flee défolé…
You heard that?
Ouais, 300 million Berrys.
It is the crew of Straw hat.
It is a large sum which the total of their premiums.
Change of strategy.
Oi, let us call the others on the boat.
Eh, Nami. Don't you think that it would be to better bring back the money to the boat?
It would be too long, the boat is with the other end of the city, on this hill.
Oi, I am shocked a little that you do not entrust any more the money to me!
Now, if we could just meet a carpenter.
We will have to turn over to Merry to make an estimate of the price of repairs.
I see, I included/understood.
I never kept as much money, I do not know what I must do.
It is a normal reaction.
We do not have the same reactions as a guy who makes whirl money in the vacuum.
[Manjuu = Brioche cooked with the vapor with yeast so that it goes up]
I will buy a hundred of it.
The farm!
Then thousands.
Then ten millet…
The farm!
We returned at the entry of the shipyard.
Well… One would say the place where crowd was.
In all the cases let us find…
… The um… how is it called T?
Iceberg-san.
Ouais, Ice-ossan.
With what does resemble T it?
The grandmother of the station said that it was advised to ask him for our repairs.
Who could know it?
For the moment, can we enter here?
Afflicted disturbance…
Still a connery…
Oups there…
Please… you wait are a foreigner, not?
Above all, let us speak outside.
Nobody enters the workshop separately the authorized personnel.
Do you have an order to make in this dock?
Ah, it is Usopp.
Oi! I am here on your line, Luffy!
It is true, him its nose is square!
That means that it is square Usopp!
My nose is not triangular, nor square!
We want to ask you for hum… I will like to meet Iceberg-san.
Iceberg-san?
A customer?
Ah, I see.
It is a letter of recommendation of the Kokoro old woman of the Shift station, it is that?
Huh?  Be to you an old man?
I am 23 years old!
“I am 23 years old”… You speak like an old man.
One often says that to me!
Then, do you know this man, Iceberg?
I know it, as everyone here… it is the mayor of Seven Toilets.
It is so important?
There is not only that…
It is the director of Galley it Company and…
It is also the contractor of Umi Ressha.
This most important of this city is?!
Ben, it has there nobody in Water Seven which does not know it.
Where can we meet it?
Where could it be in this moment?
It is difficult to say, considering it is a very occupied man.
It is possible to contact it?
It is not impossible but… are you in a hurry?
We are not in a hurry but…
In fact does, this conversation relate to the repair of a boat, not?
Where is your boat moored?
Ah… on the rock hill.
Yosh… then I will see and evaluate the conditions of the boat.
In your conversation with Iceberg-san when you meet it.
You will be able to discuss the price with him.
See? With Yagara Bull?
If I did that, you would have the impression to wait eternally.
Well, have patience just 10 minutes
10 minutes?
Yes… 10 minutes…
Too much fast!
It flies!
But wait… beyond here it is…
A CLIFF!
It fell!
Impressing!
It is well?
He travels freely in all the city…
People call it the wind of the mountain…
Of Galley it Company, dock n°1…
Foreman carpenter…
Kaku!
Well, well, I see…
It is a water city. Very impressive.
Rivers and fountains…
Beautiful streets filled with world…
And a package of beautiful women.
I will like to have a date with Nami-san and Robin-chan in this splendid city!
A beautiful flower in each hand, that would give good impression…
It is Nami-san and it is Robin-chan…
Hey, nii-chan.
Do not make such a strange head.
Which mizu-mizu Chinese cabbage do you want?
[Oba-chan = Lady of Middle Age]
I want the products freshest of the city. What do you have?
Mizu-mizu apples and mizu-mizu pears.
Do you need fresh fish?
My husband left to the fishmonger.
Where is it?
Go on the dry land a few times then turns to 6th on the right and 12th on the left.
Hum… and now…
These tricks are surely shaken when I walk…
Still a cul-de-sac? Fact of shitting…
Am I lost?
They is not good…
That makes me resemble a certain swashbuckler of shit…
Robin-chaaaaann!
Ooooi, it is me!
Yahoo!
Robin-chan…
Disappeared?
However, there is neither carries nor passage…
Did it fly away or other?
Usopp?
Which is the problem in this city?
Or it is me which am badly?
It is the boat.
Excuse me.
Oh, it is Usopp.
I see, it is very damaged.
The mast needs to be replaced, it is sure.
Usopp?
WAIT ONE MINUTE!
You ES WHICH YOU!
Did my excuses, I awake you?
It has surprised me.
It flew from here!
Nmaa… To have banals engineers would be damage…
Who is this?
To manufacture a boat of quality quickly…
Normal physical capacities are not enough.
Moreover, Kalifa…
Yes, I made research on them.
Luffy with the straw hat, Zoro the hunter of pirates, Nico Robin…
The total sum of their premiums is of…
239 million Berrys.
They are originating in East Blue.
Currently, they are a group of seven known under the name of “the crew of the Straw hat”
They know all…
I see, welcome.
I am the chief of the city, Iceberg.
And this mouse which I have just found…
Its name is… see seeing…
Tyranosaure.
It is necessary to prepare food and a cage.
It is already done, Iceberg-san.
Nmaa, you are very far-sighted, Kalifa.
I am touched.
In addition…
In 10 minutes you have a dinner with the chiefs of the manufacturers of glass to the Chiza Hotel.
Then, a reading in the Riburia place.
When it is finished, a conversation with Sir Bimine, the mayor of Pucchi.
Later, you will have an interview of the company of newspapers…
Then we will return to the main office of the company…
To note your prospects officially.
I do not want!
Ok, I cancel all.
Can Oi, you do that?
I am a person of being able who can make this type of things.
You are completely bad as a mayor!
Which egoistic person.
But it is not the person about which the grandmother spoke?
Ouais, it is him.
Insolents!
What does it make?
They was alarming!
How dare you to say such things of the world leader of naval construction.
What does it occur?
Kalifa is irritated easily these times!
I would like to be struck, too.
Excuse me…
I inopportunely lost my calm.
But Iceberg-san is an idol for the citizens, try not to be also impolite more.
Do not put Kalifa in anger…
When this woman is in anger…
She is rather awkward.
You put to him full with kicks!
It is you the impolite one!
But in any event, you, isn't this is Iceberg-san?
Look at that. It is a lettre de recommandation.
Of the Kokoro old woman…
“Repair their boat”, it says to me…
You will not do it?
Please repair our boat! We have sufficient money!
Going Merry is outside because navigation is impossible by here. Please, ossan.
Okay.
So slightly… it is really Okay?
Ouais.
Then why did you tear the letter?
Of lipstick I did not like the mark.
The Kokoro old woman is a friend with whom I drink a blow from time to time.
Hmm… if not, Kaku already left to examine your boat.
Let us wait until that occurs quietly.
In any event, it is one day tedious.
Do you want to make a visit of the building sites?
Ooooh, really?!
Please it is by here.
Is this a behavior of man who cancels his work?
Yosh, let us visit the shipyard!
They is good, the money…
Money…
What is what does not go, Usopp?
The money… the money disappeared!
Look at better!
It is not there.
It is there!
Oi, you are who, band of bastards!
Why you steal the money of the others?!
Wait, enfoiréééés!
Thank you, my guy!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO