Jango!
I will take care of this kid.
I'll leave Kaya-ojousama to you.
She will write the will as planned...
Then kill her!
Usopp Pirate crew!!!
Protect Kaya!
Luffy!
I'll take Usopp and go after the hypnotist.
Any problems?
Nope! Get goin'!
What?
That's Captain Kuro!
Captain Kuro! Banzai!
Captain Kuro!
Kuro of many tricks!
That name... Don't call me by that!
For this is... my plan to completely
be rid of the name, ''Captain Kuro''!
I had enough...
The days when I had to plan everything for you
guys, whom only knew how to make a ruckus!
Enough of those government dogs who
kept chasing me for the reward!
Wha... what?!
You can't take it anymore, you say?!
If you're so afraid of the fame on the sea,
then you're not qualified to be a pirate!
If you wanna compare ambitions...
Mine is much greater!!!
PROTECT KAYA!
USOPP PIRATE GANG TAKES ACTION!
Is that hypnotist still behind us?
Nope, don't see Him.
We'll definitely lose him!
It's just not possible to catch us in this forest.
Don't worry, Kaya-san.
We'll protect you!
Right, we swear it in the name
of the Usopp Pirate crew!
Thank you.
Not here...
Where are you, little weasels?!
Don't be so sure that you can get away from me!
In that case, maybe I should just
clear out the entire forest.
He seems to be very angry.
He's not just a hypnotist.
Where did they run off to?
This way!
Where did you go?
You little brats!
Hey! East, go east!
I said east, didn't you hear me?!
How should I know!
Just say left or right!
Then, go the other way, to the left!
The other way?!
Kaya-san!
Sorry, you guys should go ahead
and escape without me.
What're you talking about?
Our mission is to protect you, Kaya-san!
Oh no! She's burning up!
Hang in there Kaya-san.
We need a doctor, a doctor!
Idiot! This is no time for a doctor.
We're about to get kilIed!
But, we can no longer run.
Still...
Where are you, little brats?!
Thank you.
I'm happy that you guys are watching over me.
I'll keep that spirit in my heart...
Now, you three should escape.
Where are you running to?
No use in escaping now!
Come out!!!
If we leave Kaya-san and run, we'll surely make it.
Definitely.
Captain always said, ''If you find yourselves
losing, then turn tail as fast as you can!''
Damn kids, where are you!?
But, Captain's just a liar!
He's fighting hard himself.
Disregarding his own life, trying to protect us!
We can't let Kaya-san die!
In that case, we're gonna go all out!
Usopp Pirate crew!
Yosh!
Let's fight to the death!
No, don't!
You guys are still kids.
You guys can't die just because of me!
''We're not going out to die, we're fighting to live!''
That's what Captain always said.
Brats.
That bastard...
Captain Kuro's cat claws...
Only five left, eh?
Those weird swords of yours.
It's alright, he can still fight!
Right, he's still got his other hand.
Slaughter that guy, Captain Kuro!
Hey, ain't that name taboo?
I'm sure that he's known as Kuraha-something
around here...
Then, we'll let's just call him ''Kura-san''.
Kura-san, kill him!!!
Kura san kill him! Kura-san!
You fools...
SHUT THE HELL UP!
I will exterminate all of you later...
Of course, Jango as well!
Why do you wanna kill us?
Don't kid us around like that, Captain Kuro.
If we were to attack the village now,
it still shouldn't be too late.
Besides, as long as Captain Jango gets that girl
to write the will, the plan will be complete!
You don't need to worry about the plan anymore.
As long as your bodies are here,
I can prove my innocence.
I never planned to have you guys
leave this village in the first place.
It would've been troublesome.
I don't want anyone to find me still alive and kickin'.
No way!
So, you've already had plans to kill us all?
That's right.
I planned it way back when I was still
Captain Kuro, three years ago.
Everything...
Everything was planned!
Are you all morons?
What a dumb pirate crew...
''Dumb'', you say?
A pirate crew is merely a bunch of dogs which
aren't fit to live in a civilized society.
Without a plan laid out for them, what can they do?
It's always been my plans that they follow.
Shipmates are just pawns at a captain's disposal.
Whether they live or die, it's all up to me!
No matter how big the obstacle
is, my plan must proceed.
They are supposed to die to fulfill my plans.
This is the fate of pirates!
Don't you dare lecture me, boy!!
Even if a captain like you...
had tens of thousands of men...
You can never win against Usopp!
What'd you say?
I can't compare to that make-believe captain?
That's right.
That's really funny.
Don't think too highly of yourself just because
you took care of one of my hands.
Where can he surpass me?
Tell me!
Composure.
What?
You don't know the real meaning of being a pirate!!!
That bastard...
He can actually keep up with the
speed of the Stealth foot?!
You dare insult me.
If you really wanna know what a real pirate
is like, then let me show you right now.
How terrifying..
How terrifying a pirate is when he's been
to helI and back countless times!
Hey, that pose... could it be...?
He's going to use that?
He's got only one enemy.
But... no doubt about it!
It's Shakushi! He's going to do the Shakushi!
We shouldn't just be standing around here.
We're within range too!
Is he going to kill us too?!
Didn't he say that earlier?!
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
Don't do it!
We'll do anything you want!
Please, Captain Kuro!!
What's going on?
Isn't he just swaying back and forth?
Captain Kuro!
Captain!!
Please stop!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Please stop! Captain Kuro!!
SHAKUSHI!
Cheap.
I thought they'd have more treasures than this.
Now then, it should be over right about now.
What?
Nobody's moving.
Is it over already?
He's here!
Ho... how did he get killed?
Another!
This time it's the rock.
Please stop this, Captain Kuro!!
No use!
This is a blind attack using his Stealth foot.
This is a blind attack using his SteaIth foot.
He's moving so fast that he can't
even telI who he's killing.
In the past, he killed countless numbers
of our own men with that move..!
Hey!
Wh... what's going on?
Why's everyone getting killed, so suddenly?
Reveal yourself... caretaker!
What do you take your men for?!!
Luffy...
Found ya.
You bastard...
You should've just stood still and let me finish them.
Look!
Because of you, all my beloved men are half dead.
It would've been more humane to kill them off.
What now?
You look like you've got something to say...
I will never become...
A man like you.
It's not that you won't...
You can't.
Not with that talent.
Furthermore...
You're gonna die right here.
You're going to feel the agony of being
cut into pieces and then die.
I'll treat you with special care...
I won't hold anything back when I work on you.
Don't think so!
SHAKUSHI!
Come out, you little brats!
I know you're hiding around here!
Just give it up!
We give up!
You can have Kaya-san.
Come here and we'll take you to Kaya-san.
I won't fall for that.
There's no way I'd believe words from little brats.
He fell for it!!
Now!
Take that, Pepper Attack!
I knew it... it was... was a trap.
Here you go!!
Die, you hypnotist!
Don't get cocky.
Damn, we failed?
You didn't take me seriously.
I am a pirate after all.
Tamanegi!!
You guys went overboard posing as pirates.
Where are you hiding, Ojousan?
I'll kill these three first.
You can all contemplate on how stupid it
was to mess with a real pirate, in hell.
There you are...
Don't!
Run! Kaya-san!
Run!!!
Hey!
It's their voice!
That way!
Please stop this.
Don't hurt them.
I'Il write the will.
No, you mustn't!
Once you write it, he'll kill you!
I'm sorry...
Stupid, don't negotiate with me.
Captain Kuro wants me to kill everybody.
That can't...
If you don't meet my demands,
I won't wait for you to kill me!
Then there'll be no will!
N-No... no..! W-wait... wait..!
Don't do that!
I'll be dead meat if you don't write that will!
Ka... Kaya-san!
Fine, I'll let these kids go.
However, I doubt that they'll
be able to escape anyways.
Here.
Don't forget to sign!
I know...
Damn!
''I leave all my wealth to my caretaker, Kurahadol.''
Good, this'll do.
This saves me the trouble of hypnotizing you.
You promised not to kiIl them, right?
Don't worry, I'm a man of my
word, despite my appearance.
Kaya-san!
Found 'em!
Found 'em, found 'em, found 'em..!
I'm wounded there!
Over there!!!
Yosh! I'm off!
This is the end, you hypnotizing-freak!
Shit! He found us!
It seems like I have to end this quickly.