A city which loves the pirates?
Arrival with Whiskey Peak
But from where this foutue snow can come well?
The weather was nice and hot one minute ago.
Ouais, and here!
The man who goes down from the sky:
Mr. Bonhomme de neige!
I never saw somebody of also no one to carve snow.
Admire! Here is the art come from my heart:
Snow Queen!
Ouah! Too much extremely!
Fist of Mr. Bonhomme de neige!
I go you botter the bottom!!
Ah! Mr. Bonhomme de neige!
You will see!
Hold!
Take that!
Dumb!
You will see…
Where these deux-là find do as much energy by a similar cold?
Nami-San, how long will I continue my clearing of snow of love?
Until it stops snowing, Sanji-Kun.
Of agreement, Nami-San!
He, you! Does Y' have anything to eat on this boat?
That curdles here.
Close it!
You are not our guests, you two!!
Leave from here and will remove snow!!
A flash?
Does Y' have a problem with time here or what?
The weather was very nice presently,
and without reason, it started to snow.
And maintaining the thunder and the flashes…
The seasons are completely put out of order.
It is as Crocus-San had said…
It is Grand Line.
It would be said that you do not know where we are.
And you do not even use the rudder.
You really believe that it is an good idea?
I checked our direction just a second ago.
Qu… What?
It is what?
What is there, Nami-San?
Impossible!
Make turn the ship of 180°! Quickly!
180°? Why half-turn is made?
You ace forgotten something?
The ship reversed its direction and we go in the bad direction.
I left the Log Poses eyes only one second.
And the sea was so calm.
You are really navigatrice?
On this ocean…
Wind, sky, waves, clouds…
You cannot trust them.
The only thing that you can believe,
it is the direction which the Log Installation indicates.
Included/understood?
Stop making me the lesson and leave to help them!
Turn the mainsail!
Made take the wind by starboard to him!
Turn the ship of 180°!
Usopp, occupies jib!
Sanji-Kun, take the bar!
I occupy myself some, Nami-San!
You two, do not trail!
What a malpolie, the bitchy girl!
He, wait, the wind changes direction!
Impossible!
The first sign of spring!
What?
Species of moron! Do not sleep whereas you are covered with snow!!
He, y' has dolphins over there.
Let us see them!
Close it, you!
The waves do not stop growing bigger!
Iceberg at 10 a.m.!
Nami-San, of the fog!
But what is it that this ocean??
One will run up against it!!!!!!
He, the ship takes water in the compartment!
We must stop the escape of speed!
I undertake some!
The clouds move very quickly.
Wind…
Enormous!
Here it is.
Lower the veils!
The wind is increasingly strong!
If the veils continue to take the wind like that, one will be turned over!
You all, here is a in-case!
That will give again you forces.
Morfale! Take too much of it to you!
Zut! The sail tears!
You ace nothing to make, then goes up and manages to repair it!
There is another water way in the hold!
Good blood!
Which good nap.
You are not a little lazy whereas the weather is splendid?
You know where one goes, not?
You…
What do you card-index on board both?
The farm!
We move towards their city.
A place called Whiskey Peak.
You want to say that they on their premises are brought back?
It is not as if them something were owed…
Ouais, it is true.
Good, for what I say…
You have underhand heads plotters.
It is what your names already?
I am Mr. 9.
Wednesday miss.
Really?
I do not stop thinking of these names since I heard them.
P' to be to you although I heard them front, or p' to be to you not…
Finally… Not engraves.
You.
I hope that you appreciated your small nap.
You ace not stopped whirring despite everything our efforts to awake you.
Remain all on your guards.
Who knows what still will arrive to us.
I finally manage to apprehend the dangers of this ocean.
I include/understand from which this name comes from Large Line.
Even me, with my qualities of navigatrice except par, I have evil!
But that will go!
One… really will leave oneself there?
That will go.
Something of good will arrive to us.
And if you want a proof… Look at!
The first stage of our voyage is finished!
Ground!
Then here is Whiskey Peak.
This island is odd.
Look at these enormous cacti!
It is here that we go down.
Thank you for the ballade, my nice.
We will be re-examined, if it is written.
Bye bye baby!
They left.
But it was which these guy?
One of fout! One arrived!
It there with the mouth of a right river in front.
One will be able to unload here.
You do not believe that one is likely to meet monsters or another thing here, not?
One never knows, that could arrive.
It is Grand Line.
If monsters are crossed, one will have to only draw, not?
Wait a little.
Do not forget that we must remain a certain time on this island.
Why?
The Log Installation must memorize the magnetic field of the island
and then, we will be able to move towards the following island.
Time that it is necessary for this memorizing depends on each island.
For certain islands that will take a few hours,
and for others of the days.
Qu… Qu… What?
Therefore, even if one wanted to draw from this island to the monsters,
one could be obliged to remain days because of the Log?
Exactly.
If that arrives, one will see at the proper time.
One goes there!
Luffy rightly.
On the way. That will lead us to nothing to think of it without stop.
And no matter what it arrives, I will protect Nami-San!
He… the guy, listen to me.
I caught a disease which prevents me from leaving.
Go, one goes there!
Loans?
But, prepare you do not forget to flee or beat you at any time.
Euh… It is… Euh…
And my terrible disease then?
Does nobody listen to me?
I wonder what one will find in their shops.
Please…
It is a pirate boat.
Pirates arrive.
I see movements.
People? There are people on the beach!
Remain all on your guards.
Me… Shit.
I believe that I must prepare in the worst case.
Monsters or no matter what you are…
You show!!!
Welcome on Large Line!
Welcome in our city!
The city of the celebration… Whiskey Peak!
Does the island with the monsters… accommodate us?
Quest this that wants to say?
Pirates! Be welcome!
Long life with the heroes of the seas! Banzaiii!!
Y' has full girls guns here!
They love us.
The pirates are the heroes of everyone!
Bienve…
My my maaa.
Welcome!
I am called Igarappoi.
I am the mayor of Whiskey Peak.
I am called Luffy.
Enchanted!
Ossan, your hair is buckled bloody too much.
The alcohol distilling and the music, it is that, Whiskey Peak.
We are proud of our hospitality.
We have a whole spirit ocean for your good pleasure.
Would you agree to join to you to us to have fun the festival and to share the stories of your adventures?
Us serio…
My my maaa.
We would be charm to hear them.
With pleasure!!!
Three idiots…
He, say to me…
How long is it necessary for the Log Poses to memorize the magnetic field of this island?
Log?
Now let us not speak about tedious things.
Thus take a rest deserved well after your voyage, I request from you.
, You all go, prepare the feast.
A song for our adventurous guests!
Ouais!!!
And after I said, very calmly…
“Filth of monstre marin, you will not touch a hair of my friends!”
Yaaaa, Usopp Captain!
Bah, when one is escaped of Calm Belt,
I admit that even me I shivered.
Shivers of excitation, of course.
Super!
A cheer for Usopp-San!
Here! Drink as far as you want.
Not, thank you. I do not drink alcohol.
You in fai…
My my maaa.
Of made you not.
It is our finest wine, manufactured with vines of more top quality, our “Special Drink”.
Although it is called the Wine of the Sea,
it is far from alcoholic.
It is true. It is really delicious.
The harvest of vine was exceptional this year.
And to celebrate harvest, our traditional contest of Kampai!
I explain you. It is a contest where everyone drinks without stopping,
and the last upright is the winner.
Everyone can take part.
Not, that will go.
I will not be able to undoubtedly drink as much.
The reward is of… 100000
Fill to me that!
Zoro, you participles too!
Be mown to you, not?
Kampai!
Ouah! It is already with its 10th tankard!
I in…
can more…
But it is already with its 12th tankard!
Oh Yeah!
Still!
The captain ate like 20 people!
The cook disappeared!
… Rest is necessary for me.
And this type picks up 20 girls at the same time!
But what is it that this crew?
Which délici…
My my maaa.
Which delicious evening.
Which joy of seeing that everyone has fun.
Yes, really.
Which joy.
“And thus, because of their intervention, our mission of provisioning failed.”
“Nevertheless, we announce you that we attracted them”
“successfully on the island of the cacti.”
B.A.B.Y.
Very well. Let us send that to the Boss and we will be out of cause.
You are right. I will deposit it in the box of Unluckies.
They will carry it for us…
With the Boss…
And here. I can about it more.
A small nap.
And after 13 tankards, Oniichan is with the carpet!
Does Bah Zoro, it arrive to you what?
Which chochotte.
There remain only these deux-là.
It is with its 15th tankard.
Its rival is Sister!
You should go perhaps there mollo for your health.
Of no matter what you cause?
I laiss' spoke not to fall before having the reward!
They was too good!
And now, three cooks are with ground!
That pleased to me.
It is too…
I gained!!!!!
Oh, I do not feel well.
And finally, it is with ground.
I adore this city.
I am with the paradise…
Lastly, they are exhausted and they fell asleep.
Made beautiful dreams,
my small adventurers.
This night, the splendid Rock-Cacti resplendissent with the moonlight.
I did not know you poet, Igarappoi!
Or rather, Mr. 8.
It is you.
And them?
They fell.
Right in hell.
Frankly,
which band of heading.
One had to add more and more alcohol in their drinks.
In the contrary case, they would be still debouts to have fun the festival.
And then, was this really necessary to make all this comedy?
For five unhappy kids?
One should have regulated their account with the port to them.
Already before their arrival, the city underwent a shortage of food.
I suspected that these deux-là would not bring back meat for us of whale.
I do not allow you!
We made our better, I announce you!
You calm!
Look at that. I got information about them.
Tren… Thirty million Berrys?
For these types?
Insane which is that judges a pirate on his only appearance,
Miss Mo…
My my maaa.
Monday miss.
I have shame.
But now that their fate is regulated,
we can send a report/ratio favorable to the Boss.
Let us take all immediately their valuable articles in their boat.
And them?
What does one make some?
If we kill them, we lose 30% of the premium.
The government prefers the public executions.
Go! Capture them alive!
He! Afflicted to stop you.
You could not let them sleep still a little? The voyage tired them.
Mr. 8!
Monday miss!
The type with the katana slipped by!
It is up there.
Dumb!
You should be drunk dead!
No swashbuckler worthy of this name
does not let itself take with the trap of drink.
I include/understand what occurs here.
It is a den of hunters of premium.
You mislead the pirates very glad to arrive on Grand Line,
and then steal you to them all that they have.
There is about a hundred hunters of premium here.
I will deal with you,
Works baroque.
From where do you know the name of our organization??
A few times ago, I were me also trade.
And your organization proposed a place to me,
but I refused, obviously.
The members of the organisaton are unaware of all of the other members,
and they are called by code names.
And of course, the identity and the den of the Boss remain a mystery for everyone.
An criminal organization who obeys the orders well wisely.
Works baroque.
Was Oh, it supposed being a secrecy?
Here are which is very surprising.
Since you know our small secrecy, we thus will have to eliminate you.
This night still…
We will add a new tomb stone on the Rock-Cacti.
Kill it!!!
It… disappeared!