Alubarna cries!
The terrible combat of the Karu Captain!
The hopes of the desperate people are being destroyed by a sand cloud.
Some seek hope, and others try to keep a glimmer of hope.
Their ideas were mislaid, and in confusion, the curtain of the history was closed on a tragedy.
Overlapping the squadron of the Super Mallards,
Zoro and the remainder of the crew attracted with far Number Agents from Works Baroque.
IncrŽdule, Vivi was drawn up in front of Kohza to stop its attack.
But words of ViviÉ
É lost themselves in a sand cloud.
The rebellious army encircled AlubarnaÉ
É and the royal army which protects Alubarna from now on made speak the weaponsÉ
É and the rebellion started!
Vivi-Chan is in danger!
Usopp, will give a knack To be pinched.
Chopper?
Goes at the entry to South-east!
Eh? Of agreementÉ
Vivi-ChanÉ
Hold good!
Time that I arrive!
A rebel!
It is over there behind!
A rebel!?
It is of me that he speaks?
A soldier of the royal army!
Descend it!
He, He. I am neither a rebel nor a soldier.
I am the allied one of a Lady!
The South-eastern entry of Alubarna
These deux-lˆÉ
They disappearedÉ
Mr. 4 and Miss Merry Christmas.
Where did they pass?
Q- What do they make?
Good blood, that are they?
Not, what you are you?
I find that you speak much.
Well, lets to me present to youÉ
É our N®4 beater.
N®4É
É a beater.
What I can makeÉ
I must do all that is in my capacity!
I amÉ
I am a pirate!
Burst!
Princess Vivi!
The desert will be yourÉ
É TOMB!
Karu!
AfflictingÉ
ButÉ
You will not escape to me!
I said that you will not escape to meÉ!
Ca is enough, stop youÉ!
I will absorb youÉ!
Both!
KaruÉ
You protected meÉ
But nowÉ
You are with end of forceÉ
Not! If one goes straight, one will be made trap in the staircases!
Do not complicate the things!
Stop running!
Let go down to me, Karu!
I will fight it, thenÉ
Wait one minute, it is the cliffÉ!
Hein? He will not dare!
What does it occur!?
This dirty duck goes up to the plate of Alubarna!
Imbeciles!
Now go down until me and undergo my Kenpo Ballet!
This is the proof that we are companions!
Why do you cry, Karu?
You can count on us!
Vivi is our companion!
WhatÉ!?
Karu, you are incredible!
You flew!
Now that one is all in top, I am persuaded that Mr. 2 will not be ableÉ
What a impertinenceÉ!
Salt duck!
Nothing is impossible for me!
I poured blood, sweat and tears to improve myÉ
Statement!
Karu, will you have the force to cross this battle field?
I will never find Kohza in the middle of this battle.
We will seek Chaka to the palate,
before the rebellious army does not reach the heart of the cityÉ
I rattrapŽŽŽŽŽs you!
A STRAY BULLETÉ!
KARU!
Vivi is our companion!
It is useless!
KaruÉ!
KARU!!
I had said to you that it was useless!
I include/understandÉ
Be to you a true poison!
I also will finish some with you!
DECREE!
Poison-poison-poisons!
Poison-poisonsÉ
It is youÉ
You managed well, Capitaine Karu.
You behave as a man.
Sanji-San!
The guy, you can also ravel you.
You want to always stop the rebellion, not true Vivi-Chan?
I will deal with him!
It is you?
That which makes all these whores of merdic imitations.
Remain with the variation.
Who? Who are you thus?
Leave.
I entrust Karu to you.
Ahh! It is escaping to me!
Stop to you foutre of me!
You will die!
You took the invaluable glasses of tireur d'Žlite of a friendÉ
É and I you will take them again!
What?
I am not as weak as him.
Would you be one of the companions of Straw hat?
Would you be by chance infamous Mr. Prince?
Whole.
I am called Sanji.
The best cook of the seas.
A cook!?
I am good also!
Now, why a cook would be caught some with an criminal organization!?
I form also part of an criminal organization.
I am at the same time a cook and a pirate.
ÒEye for eyeÓ?
Exactly.
Remove your dirty legs of this country.
Western district
Go ahead! Go ahead Zoro!
Good blood but what do you wait!?
Go ahead and cleans the ground with their heads!
Close to it good blood, and will put yourself at the shelter!
I hope that you will divert me a little the guy.
Catches them, Zoro!
You do not have an other choice, not true?
Magne of the assÉ
É to antirÉ
É these dreadful gorillasÉ
What are you in the train of mijoter?
Hein!?
First rule to assassinate:
To always occupy itself in first of the weakest target.
Observe how the pros operate.
M- Me?
A- Wait one second.
There is really no reason to kill me.
My face and my style are the best in the world butÉ
É I donot can fight.
Eh well it is as had said we.
To start with people as is to you the fastest manner to finish some.
I see what you want to say!
Of course, of course that you are right!
I would make the same thing!
I had said to you to close it and to put yourself at the shelter.
Ca must be the entry of the South-east about which Sanji spoke.
It would be said that the battle is finishedÉ
Where is Chopper?
Chopper!
Eh, Chopper!
Hold good!
He! He!
UsoppÉ
I am happy that you are well.
Would not be stupid!
You are wounded?
Nothing serious.
Then?
Mr.4 and its binomial are flee?
And just when I came to lend strong hand to you!
It is really not chance, hein!?
I was going to show you how the Master of the seas,
largest of all the heroes, the Usopp-Sama Captain fights!
They are always there, some share.
Take guard.
WHAT!?
Why you did not say it earlier!?
WhatÉ?
I do not see anybodyÉ
They are under ground.
Mogu = Mole
Miss Merry Christmas has the capacities of a mole since she ate the Fruit of the Demon Mogu Mogu.
A human mole?
The other, Mr. 4 is a N®4 beater.
Moreover, it has its dog with him.
Hein? I did not include/understand anything of the whole.
About what you do speak?
Here it is!
BEND DOWN!
You are well, Usopp?
You saved me!
Thank you.
Was good blood what it?
N®4 beater = most extremely of the beaters on the bench is the fourth beater
I said to you that Mr. 4 was a N®4 beater.
Moreover, it has its dog with him.
And I said to you that I did not have any idea of what you told.
Ah! Here it is!
A dog.
Good blood, it is what this trick!?
The favorite weapon of Mr. 4:Lasso the dog rifle
(It is caught cold)
Caution!
Q- What!?
WHAT!?
Ca arrives!
STILL!?
You must move away some!
USOPP!
Usopp!
You are well!?
I go you redemander.
Good blood, it is what this trick?
It is bombes ˆ retardement.
Even if they are not touched, they explode nevertheless.
They calculate exact time that it is necessary to send the ball to us.
No matter what it arrives, they will explode nevertheless.
I thought of being able to stop one and to start again it of them like a counter-attack.
But these balls are as heavy as boulets de canon.
It is possible no to stop them.
To be able to strike them with its beater with as much speed,
the arms of Mr. 4 must have a superhuman force.
L---has---S---S---O--- !
But which kind of beater it uses?
L---has---
Eh, Mr. 4! Mr. 4!
Molasse species.
Not! Not!
What you made with glander there!?
Magnez you to botch them!
Destroy them! Destroy them!
He! You! Then! Ho!
You are really only one molasse! A molasse!
Ba (Baka) = Stunned
Ba! Be to you a Ba!
There! The human mole!
A MOLE!
I AM NOT TRANSFORMED YET!
BA! You ES a BA!
Chopper, you occupy yourself some.
Will you throw ash my body wounded with the sea?
YOU SAID THAT YOU CAME TO LEND STRONG HAND TO ME, MORON.
Listen well!
What is it that this dog initially!?
How do you want that I fight against these monsters!?
I am only one human! You measuring rods!?
I am also human!
Not, imbecile, you are a monster!
Eh well looks at a little the length of your nose!
Close it, blue nose!
You initially, long nose!
You really believe that it is the moment of you chamailler, hein!?
AfflictedÉ
The name of this thing is Lasso.
Inu = Dog
It is a weapon which ate the Fruit of the Demon Inu Inu.
A weapon!?
A weapon which ate a Fruit of the Demon?
It is a novel method coming from Large Line.
Even objects can eat a Fruit of the Demon!
Balivernes!
How can it move if it is a weapon!?
The Fruit of the Demon cannot in no case to give him this faculty!
And how the weapon did can eat this fruit initially!?
Oh closes it!
What good is knowledge since you will die!?
It moves and it is all!
Ba!
Ba species!
It is not true, Mr. 4?
O--U--has--I--S--
You have measuring rod?
You will not set out again from here alive.
You put the feet on our territory!
Have fun!
Our territory appoints the taupinière of the 4th Avenue!
It is transformed into human mole!
A penguin?
I AM A MOLE, SPECIES OF BA!
It left under ground!
Yosh!
IT IS TIME SE TO BREAK!
WAIT!
I let to you occupy myself some!
Caution!
It arrives by there!
It is a curved ball!
NOT!
Above you, Usopp!
A FLOATING BALL!
Ah! Well, well!
I suppose that Mr. 4 does not have a good average of striking!
I can dodge it without problem!
A Spin!
Spin = an effect
Attention behind you!
It is not normal, the N®4 beater should always be called Mr. 4.