Throw that gas mask away!
You re not one of mine anymore.
Just die.
Like I'll let you shoot that poisonous gas!
Don't be in a hurry, Hammerboy.
Damn it!
Gin!
I've never heard such cowardly words.
!'m gonna destroy him right now.
You! Don't mock Don Krieg!
He's the strongest man alive.
He can't be defeated.
You idiot! Open your eyes!
Of course.
That guy's trying to kill you!
For me to talk about my feelings,
Is to betray the role I have.
That's why...
That's why this is an obvious consequence!
Gin!
Why? Why?!
You realize at the end eh?
But it's too late.
Die together with that cook.
POISONOUS GAS...
MH5!
I WON'T DIE!
LUFFY VS KRIEG! CONCLUSION!
Here it comes!
Dive into the sea!
Owner! Into the restaurant, quickly!
I'm borrowi' this.
Sanji, Gin! Use it!
Waiter boy!
Now for mine...
ARA?! Everybody has submerged!
What'm I gonna do? What'm I gonna do!?
This is... Strength.
Im saved!
Thank god this suddenly appeared...
W...W... What kinda guy...
To fight using poisonous gas...
That guy is the Devil!
Yeah, that's not how humans fight.
Are Sanji and the Waiter boy okay?
Who knows.
Look! The gas is lifting!
Gin.
Move,
Move your hand!
GIN!
You... your mask?
Mask...
Did you give it?
Gin!
What an idiot.
This happened because you made
such a big deal out of food.
I guess an idiot won't learn till he dies.
Why that son of a gun...
As commanded, he threw away his gas mask.
To go that far, as if subordinates like him exist.
Don... Krieg...
Gin.
Gin... You,
You chose the wrong man to follow.
Are you sympathizing with my little scumbag?
Scumbag!?
Exactly.
An idiot who refuses my order without thought
of the consequences, is no good for anything.
Isn't killing him before he makes the same
mistake again, a sign of my love?
It can't be.
To think Don would kill his battle commander...
No way,
No matter how much... no way!
Gin-san is Don's right hand!
Yeah! Till now no one has worked
for Don as hard as Gin-san.
Even at that time,
When we had just escaped the Grand Line
and Fullbody's marines were after us.
At the time when the commander
became the decoy for the Don!
He abandoned everything and fought for Don Krieg!
To think he'd really kill him!
That's cruel...
Patty! There's antidote in there right?
Yes but... they're our enemy...
Who cares? Just get it!
Idiot! First put the mask on his face quickly,
There should some kind of antidote in there already.
Take him upstairs,
That should let him breathe easier.
It's the best be can do if we want to save him.
Hurry up! Patty! Carne!
I got it! Shutup already!
Me too?
It's useless.
At the most he's got an hour.
Don't die, Gin.
Don't die for that guy.
You have to survive, okay?
I'll destroy that guy.
No, stop...
You can't win against him,
Calm down!
If you go straight at him, you'll fall into his trap!
You'll die!
I won't die.
If you wanna shoot me, then take your best shot!
Hey!
Fool. Still trying even though you
know you're going to die.
The sea is your hell, Hammerboy.
In front of you lies...
It's here!
Bombs...
YOUR GRAVE!
My grave?
Crap! Run away, Waiter boy!
He's hit!
Killed eh?
Waiter boy...
He...
GOMU GOMU NO...
Fool! Come on then!
It's out!
Come on!
That's low!
PISTOL!
WHAAAT?
Don Krieg got hit!
What is that guy?
He punched right into the frickin' spikes!
This can't be...
I've never seen this before.
Don Krieg getting beaten like this.
He actually hit Don, through his 'Kenzan cape'?
Can you believe it?
So this my grave?
Your grave?
My grave?
Like hell.
Don't decide my grave...
I'm not meant to die here.
He's too reckless.
Sometimes you see idiots like him.
People that fight till the death once
they've chosen their target.
...that fight till the death?
To have that sort of person as your enemy is bad.
This fight will end.
Whether he wins or loses.
I like those kind of guys.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Hey crewman!
Get a hold of yourself!
Breath some fresh air, Breathe lots of it!
'you alright?
Want to drink some water? Hey!
This is bad!
Want some of my special pudding?
Idiot! What are yout thinking, feeding
poison to a poisoned person!
My food is poison? You've no right to say that!
What was that? My food is called the best in the world! It's to DIE for!
Hey! You can't die! what will we do?!
Hey! Hold on! Don't die, crewman!
Is he dead? Is he really dead? Is he really dead?
Is he dead? Really! Is he really dead?
SHUT UP!!
He's alive!
Don...
Krieg...
Don Krieg?
What... What's going to happen with this fight?
Idiot! It was just luck!
There's no way Don will lose to such a guy!
Don't worry!
Waiter boy...
You say you're not meant to die here?
If this isn't your grave,
Then whose can it be?
Yours, right?
NO, IT'S YOURS!!
He got beaten again!
What the hell is happening here?
Normally the enemy dies without
touching Don Krieg,
The Don's supposed to be invincible!
That guy...
WHAT IS THAT GUY?
He's pretty good.
Yeah....truly
That guys awesome!
Just defeat Krieg already!
It's possible! If it's that guy!
That kid, he's a match for Don.
This isn't a dream is it? To that guy... Don will...
Don is supposed to be invincible!
At this rate... The legend of Don Krieg will...
Don't be ridiculous!
What the?
It's finally out!
Don Krieg's ultimate weapon,
The Great Battle Spear!
What's that?
It explodes...
Now then...
How long are you going to run for?
Let's see. Hammerboy.
This spear is totally different
from those tiny ones earlier.
After 2 or 3 hits with this, you won't survive.
If it hits you, you're finished!
What kind of weapon is that?
What is that thing?
It explodes every time it hits!
Huh? What the? My legs...
The fight's lasted too long.
He's lost too much blood.
He's not gonna make it.
Nothing you do will work.
It's about time for your strength to reach its limit.
Shit. Since the floor is in so many
pieces I can't fight the way I want.
What a pain.
No matter how many times I see it,
that Great Battle Spear is amazing.
Yeah, the harder you hit with that,
the greater the explosion.
It's something that can be used
only by someone like Don!
That's some strength.
Two shields and one spear should weigh about 1
ton, but he's using that heavy weapon so easily!
That's the reason Don is called the greatest!
Die!
Waiter boy!
That was close!
You... Weak Insect!
Waiter boy!
Waiter boy?
Are you alright?
Not yet.
You've pissed me off.
I won't let you die so easily.
Shit. That Krieg... He Just brings
weapons out one after the other.
This way theres no chance to...
Even if he was equipped with a thousand weapons.
He may not be able to defeat
the one 'spear' that kid has.
Nothing special.
You should realize who is the strongest here.
Life or death.
In a pirate's fight, the one who hesitates even for a
split second thinking about death can get crushed.
What are you talking about?
At least
At least...
that kid...
has no hesitation.
Is it that he has what it takes to survive?
Or does his conviction mean
he simply refuses to die.
His conviction?
You...
You damned...
Amazing!
Keep at it!
Like I said! This is your grave!
I'm the strongest man alive!
If Krieg's massive fleet is strength.
And his thousands of spears
and poison are strength.
Then that kids 'spear' is equal to it.
That same spear...
I know someone like that.
Someone who would get attached to that
'spear' for his own stupid reasons.
The Great Battle Spear!
What did you do!?
I just punched it five times in a row.
Your 'method' won't work anymore!
Prepare yourself.