Go to hell!
Oni-giri!
I can't believe I lost to thieves.
We aren't thieves. We are pirates!
The map of the Grand Line!
I will never forgive him!
(Episode 8) "Who Will Win? Showdown
Between the True Powers of the Devil!"
(Episode 8) "Shousha wa Dotchi?
Akuma no Mi no Nouryoku Taiketsu!"
(Based on Manga ch.19: "Devil Fruit", ch.20:
"The Way Of The Thief" and ch.21: "Townies")
In my whole life, nobody has
ever made me hate someone so much.
Shanks took my most
important treasure away.
I don't know what's your
relationship with him....
...but I'll say what I want about him!
There you two go, fighting again!
It's                                          No, it's
North Pole!                                 South Pole!
You never stop.
I am right. Why should I stop?
You really have guts!
Let's fight until one of us lose!
Show me what you got!
I'll teach you a lesson
you'll never forget!
Enough!!
Why is it so important to
know which pole is colder?
If you really wanna know,
find out for yourselves!
You need to cool off!
Ship approaching!
Enemy from the northeast!
Head straight for them!
It's time to fight!
Aye!
Ok, rob as much as we can.
You look happy, Buggy.
Of course.
An enemy boat is like
a big treasure box.
It's our destiny to rob as pirates.
You are so right.
You're too soft.
You are like the other
pirates. You're all too easy!
You don't know what a
pirate is really like.
What's this?
T-T-Treasure
map!
It's great to see it.
It's undersea.
Great.
Now I will be the
richest man in the world!
It's a total victory today!
Hey, Buggy!
Why don't you join us?
There are some trophys.
I didn't take anything!
I don't know anything!
What are you talking about?
Nothing...
You said you will
leave the boat someday.
What are you gonna do?
I want to have my own boat.
Find some reliable crewmen
and see the whole world.
No matter how long it will take.
I will still be a pirate.
You are so naive.
What?
But you're a good fighter,
I'll tell you what.
If you are not that naive, I would
love to take you as my crewman.
Your crewman? Are you kidding?
We have different ambitions.
We're better off on our separate ways.
That's what pirating's all about.
You call yourself pirate?
If we meet on the sea, we will fight.
Yes, that's also what
pirating's all about.
Sometimes, you baffle me.
Didn't you just say "trophy"?
Yeah. There was the
devil fruit. Devil fruit?
They say it was enchanted by sea devils.
You will get amazing powers after eating
it, but you will be cursed by the sea.
You have to stay on land.
What kind of idiot would eat that?
If you can't swim, how can you
get the treasure buried under sea?
Some would pay 100
million belly's for it.
What?
I, apprentice pirate Buggy,
will now eat the devil fruit!
It's good to be young. You don't
have to think about the consequences.
Now what, Buggy? Feel any different?
No, nothing. It's a fake.
Devil fruit is only a legend.
It worked.
It's too smooth.
The fake is my masterpiece.
I can't believe it's so easy!
I will get out of the
boat when nobody notices.
With the money of selling the devil
fruit and the treasure from the map,
I can buy a pirate crew!
Hey, Buggy.
Why're you laughing?
It's you. Don't scare me.
What's with that look?
Stop stealing food...
...or the cook will skin you alive.
That was close...
Oh, one more thing, the captain said...
Shanks, you bastard!
You... you... you...
What's that paper?
My map!
Hey, Buggy!
What's happening? I can't move right!
The fruit is working. Help me!
What's wrong?
You supposed to be
good at swimming, right?
Buggy!
Help me!
I am coming, Buggy!
So Shanks saved your life.
That's against the point!
It was him who delayed my
grandiose plan for years!
I was still determined.
If I can't get the treasure IN the
sea, I'll take the treasure ON the sea!
I have the Chop-Chop power.
If anyone tries to touch my treasure...
They're dead meat!
Hands off...
...my treasure!
I've been found out!
Don't think you can
get away from me, Nami!
I will chop you up!
Curse you, Gomu Gomu boy!
I'm still your opponent!
Something's wrong.
It's been a long time.
What happened to the mayor?
Maybe something happened in town.
The sound of the cannon fire
was much more louder than usual.
OK! I'm going into town.
You guys wait here.
I am going too.
Stupid, they are pirates.
It's Buggy's pirate crew!
That's why I am going with you.
If we can't protect the mayor,
what kind of citizens are we?
You can't stop us.
It's our choice.
Very well. Let's go!
Yeah!
Hey.
Drop the loot and get out!
He'll keep coming after you.
No!
You want me to leave the treasure?
I will never do that!
Why should I give up the treasure?
What do you mean "never"?
That's right!
I am a master thief!
And I stole your treasure!
That's why I said! They are mine!
Uh...okay.
Bull! That's mine!
It's not yours until
you get away with it!
It's a basic fact about pirating!
Criminal lecturing
criminal. What a joke.
What?
I'd never stoop so low as
to take lessons from you!
Then suffer the consequences, Nami.
CHOP! CHOP!
FESTIVAL!
Try to save your friend
now, GOMU GOMU NO Boy!
Damn, he's all over the place! Oh?
What?
Nami!
Give it back! No way!
How do you like this?
Cut it out!
The one who'll cut it out...
...is you!
I will take the treasure.
Let go! Let go!
Let go of it! It's mine!
You let go!
Go to hell!
You're supposed to be fighting me!
That was for the mayor.
Thank you for saving me.
No problem.
Hey! The map! My treasure!
Not so fast, Gomu Gomu Boy!
He's still alive!
Shut up!
Look what you have done to me.
I will never forgive you!
CHOP! CHOP! Come Together!
What?
Are you looking for this?
My body!
Good job, master thief!
Goodbye, Buggy!
GOMU GOMU NO
Wait!
BAZOOKA!
I win!
Hey, Buggy was kicked
up high to the sky.
What do we do?
Keep playing dead. OK.
It means alot to you, doesn't it?
It's OK! I can still wear it.
Felt good to kick Buggy's butt!
Hold on. Let me help you.
With what, Nami?
You can help me carry this.
I split them into two
bags. You carry one for me.
It's so heavy.
You are so...
Buggy was picky on
treasure. Nice quality.
It's worth at least ten million belly's!
Take it.
The map of the Grand Line.
Isn't it what you want?
You want to give me that?
Who told you to save me?
Thank you, Nami.
I finally got the map of the Grand Line.
Yippee!
Would you like to join our crew?
I said I didn't want to
be part of a pirate crew!
But I admit...
It's good money though.
But I wanna say it's only cooperation.
Remember that.
Ok.
Hey, Zoro. Get up.
Let's go, Zoro.
All done? Yes.
Both the map and the crew are found.
God, I lost too much blood.
I can't walk now.
Of course not!
If you can walk, I wouldn't believe
that any of you you're human.
Don't lump me with him!
You're even less human than he is!
What about the mayor? Oh yeah.
We should wake him up too.
Hey you!
Are you strangers?
What about you?
We are citizens of this town.
Did the pirates mutiny or something?
Come on, talk.
Townspeople? What a relief. I
thought they were pirates, too.
It's the mayor!
Mayor! Are you hurt?
Mayor!
He's blacked out. It
must be the pirates.
Damn it!
Sorry I hit that old man!
They didn't have to know that!
You saw it, too. Didn't you? I did.
But there is a reason...
Why did you do that to him?
Explain yourself!
Who are you? Are you with the pirates?
I can smell a fight coming.
If he said he is a thief or a pirate...
We are pirates!
Get them!
Idiot! It's true!
Pirates!
How dare you to ruin our town like that?
Even if you were a child,
we won't forgive you.
Now what?
They wouldn't listen to whatver I say.
Run fast.
Get them!
Don't let them get away!
How dare you attack our mayor like that?
Why do you always make things worse?
Everyone loves the mayor.
No matter how we explain,
they will be angry anyway.
Turn here.
Hold on. You should
have said it earlier!
They're in the alley!
Chou Chou. That dog.
Get away, Chou Chou!
Hey.
They are bad people! You are
barking at the wrong person.
Why stop us?
Chou Chou! Let us through.
Chou Chou.
Bye, dog.
It's so scary.
Chou Chou let us escape.
Why are we always in bad luck?
It doesn't matter.
Things are all done.
You are right.
Hey, is this your boat?
It's nice.
I think it's OK.
It's stolen from a pirate.
You are really something!
You are finally here, girlie.
I didn't expect to see you here.
Your friends? We had a bad history.
Not just that. We hate each other.
You have pals.
Then I will kick their butts too!
It's not right to steal other's things.
Hey, I am talking to you.
Mayor! You're awake!
Thank goodness.
What happened?
What the heck?
When we got here, it
was already like this.
The rest of the pirates have run away.
Don't you know what happened?
Where are the kids?
Kids? Are you talking
about the three kids?
Are they still alive?
That kid! How he treated
an old man like me...
We chased those imbeciles out of town!
But I am still mad.
They thought we were worthless!
Look what they have done to this town!
They will never know
how much we really have!
You are so right.
Let's go find them, and drag them back!
Shut up!
I'm the only one who has
the right to call them names!
Nobody else but me!
What? Why do you protect the pirates?
They ran away without hearing from me?
Where did they go?
They ran to the port.
The nerve of that kid!
How dare you do this to my town!
I have a lot of things to say to you!
OK, let's go!
That sail has Buggy's mark!
It was his boat. I will
get rid of it later.
Hey, hold on!
Kids!
Mayor.
Buggy would have killed me!
I was desperate and thinking
it was OK, even if I die.
Thank you! I will
remember your kindness!
You're welcome! Take it easy!
Kids...kids...kids...
I don't know what to say.
What?
You left a bag of treasure there?  Yes.
It was worth half a million belly's!
They needed the money
to rebuild the town.
That was MY treasure!
It took me a lot of
effort to steal them!
How dare you!
Stop it! I can't swim!
I know you can't!
Go get it if you want.
It's too late! You go get it!
No way.
I will die.
Come on. Just die once for me.
If you do it again, I will
throw you into the sea!
I don't know if it's our luck or not.
Anyway, we have one more
pirate with us on the search.