To save Nami on the way
and the remainder of the crew,
Luffy, Sanji and Usopp entered
the Forest Lost, on the island of God.
But they had to face the appalling one
Ordalie of the Bubbles of the Satori Priest.
Always in life, really?
Admirable! Admirable!
What you of a gift would say that
I especially reserved to you?
Meanwhile, Chopper remained only on
the Sacrificial Furnace bridge in order to keep the boat,
It is attacked by
Shura, one of the Priests.
Not!
Now, your life offers to God!
NOT… NOT QUESTION!
Die!
All my excuses for waiting.
Knight of the Sky!
You could with what await you while coming
here… It is you the criminal now!
Now, I will show you the power
of my anger vis-a-vis the bloody nuisances!
Ordalie of Wire!
A deep mystery! Ordalie
wire and Ordalie of the Love?!
Oh not!
Show yourself, my
Dragon-bubbles!
It is what that? It is right a heap of
your Clouds Surprised hung between them.
It is judicious to impress me?
Of course. But I go you
to entrust a small secrecy.
It is entirely made Surprised Bubbles
charged with explosives and filled with projectiles.
What?! You want to say that…?!
If you effleures would be this only one of
Explosive bubbles of his body, you are foutu!
A detonator would start one
series of explosions in chain…
thus causing gigantic
instantaneous explosion!
Chain Surprised Bubbles!
Ahead, Dragon-Bubbles!
GOMU GOMU NO GUN!
What?! He! Wait, Luffy!!
Do not touch with this trick!
If you it effleures with
, one pains is all died!
One would fly in glares!
How I make if I
donot can touch it?
I say to you that had you
not need to beat you.
All that one can do, it is to flee!
And to go where?!
What I know some?!
Oh, I know!
Jump!
What that fout there?!
You can never stop you.
No matter what one does, that
always returns to same!
Before you are not
completely exhausted,
I will make you taste with my
final bouquet of the Dragon of Bubbles.
You will not laugh!
Aisa!
Where were you?
Kamakiri!
Still in Upper Yard?
And your bag is filled with Vearth.
You should stop.
You risks to leave your skin there.
I do what I want!
Look at, are not even to you
able to beat Eneru!
Horrible little brat!
A chance?
Yes.
Gan Fall went on Upper
Yard for an unknown reason.
This old man persists in believing that it
can take again the control of the island.
Coarse error.
To overcome or perish, nobody can envisage
which will be the exit of a combat before the end.
Shandia (Warlike of Shandora) Wiper
Karugara, the Large one
Warrior, said one day…
“Let us revive the flame of Shandia!”
It is exactly it
that we will make.
That our enemy is Gan Fall, the old one
God, or God Eneru, that is equal for me.
It is the similar one with same, as long as one
so-called “God” will want to reign…
our cause will remain intact.
They deserve all to be eliminated!
Wiper.
People rebelled
against Eneru on Angel Island.
An young girl is in the beginning.
It is the first time since
beginning of its reign, six years ago.
And then?
Gan Fall saved it Judgment.
What means that Eneru found one
reason to judge former God himself.
As a Knight of the Sky
and even as a former God…
Gan Fall does not have us
ever carried reached.
And he never confronted himself with Eneru.
But this same man comes to
present to press the ground of Upper Yard.
Ca me gene not only it
will defy one of the Priests.
Unless you try to say to me…
that we would not have any more
to regard Gan Fall as an enemy?
To have a joint enemy
fact not of him our ally.
If that disturb you, then I do not want
of you on the battle field, Laki.
You would be only one ball!
Aisa.
What?! I was not
not on Upper Yard…!
It is not the moment
to enter the tipi.
Wiper, or rather the descendant of Large
Karugara warrior, is of bad mood.
Yes, it terrorizes me.
Still more than God.
… To help?
Us?
Yes, it is that.
We will do our better
to help them to escape.
I do not arrive at
to follow their movements.
It is incredible…
I lost enough time like
that with your childishness!
Peuh, always also ramollo!
It is what this combat?
The Celestial Judgment…
This girl was a idiot.
One never should
to irritate Eneru God…
Return us, please… God.
Be taken to you with the trap!
A problem, Gan Fall?!
Demon, which you made?!
Why? Why I
donot can move any more?
Deaths… do not have
not need for answers.
Ordalie of Wire, a deep mystery.
Upper Yard… You can enter there if you wish it, but the impregnable fortress of the Four Priests…
is well too large for
dead losses in your kind.
Eneru God…
is powerful and untouchable.
Yes.
The Crowned Earth will sing again.
One day, undoubtedly.
Knight…
Knight of the Sky!!!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
I must save it! I must save it!
If not… Celestial Sharks
will devour the Knight of the Sky!
Peuh! Park with the ire of Eneru-sama!
But, to save it…
I cannot swim…
And Celestial Sharks
will eat me too me.
“Only one does not touch
hair of my companions. “
“Do not destroy the boat.”
“I do not want to die.”
Here is a difficult customer.
A small so capricious shit.
Ca returns to me furious.
Why you are so weak,
if you hold so much with the life?!
Shit!
It is what this Knight of the Sky?
He sat down on
divine throne of God?
It did not even arrive at
ankle of a Priest like me.
Knight of the Sky!!!
Are Peuh, you Zoan, not true?
You cannot swim, imbecile!
It is true that you are Zoan, you too.
They is rather unhappy.
You want to join your Master?
Brothel, which waste of time.
These weaklings really aggravated me.
So still this river did not have
basic, they would have a chance.
But damage, because it has one of them.
And now…
I wonder whether the fate of
three fugitive was regulated.
Is it if
extraordinary what that?
Yes! It is inconceivable which it
that is to say hidden under a so large tree.
The process of evolution of nature
and of civilization is reversed.
Mouais, in any case, if one does not find
a means of crossing this river…
one will be able to never explore
this forest entirely.
One is not likely to meet
God at this rate/rhythm.
This civilization did not know to predict
growth of the vegetation.
It is the first time that
I meet such a phenomenon.
He, Nami!
You see something of up there?!
The Field of God, Upper Yard…
He, I cause you! Say something!
You can see God?!
Perhaps it has
fact a discovery.
Would this island be…?
It is finished by it you, the guy.
But be not disappointed too much.
I am a Priest. You
will be able to never overcome me.
It is useless! I
died of jitter.
My heart will stop beating.
Your last chance
passed soon.
Your boat is already almost
arrived at the exit of the forest.
What means the end for you.
Unless flying away in the airs like birds, you will be able to never leave these places!
You will wander in this forest until
how the will to live leaves you!
You believe…
that one will let you do that?!
Of course!
Chain Surprised Bubbles!
Ball Dragon!
Oh, it is amusing!
Where is the Bubble-Detonator?
A simple contact and you will die
in a gigantic explosion!
Good. It is now or never.
I can still do it!
I leave it to you, Luffy!
Oh, you think of going up to
trees to escape to you?
How you make for
to see in my thoughts?!
Release me!
Co-how?!
Ah, I have measuring rod!
It used a string
to control it.
Then…
Here!
I cannot control any more
the Ball Dragon…
Do not play the impertinent ones with me!
Come by here!
Coward the other piece of string!
It is here!
I suspected it.
No doubt. It is the exit.
But good, why there
didn't I think earlier?
We fell the top
of a cliff while arriving…
it is logical that the exit
also find it in altitude.
If we can reach the exit,
can imports the road which we take.
I must make quickly!
This explosion had the air malicious.
I hope that they are well!
It passed near.
I do not return from there.
He sought with me
to explode with him.
Which shame… I miss
still of drive.
It had almost succeeded in turning over
situation in one moment and I was lost.
My Mantra was
destabilized by this shock.
It is quite true!
It passed near!
You are always in life?!
Not!
Release! Scrapings!
Te does not stick to me
how that, salts perverse!
Go! Brushes!
C-cretin! Moron!
Hold it, Luffy well!
Do not let this Bouboule escape!
You?!
Ah, Sanji! Be alive for you?
I AM HAS HALF DIED, THANK YOU HAS YOU!
PAY TO WHAT YOU DO!
Lastly, in short, Bouboule…
Do not stop you bathing us with
your Ordalie by-Ci, Ordalie by-there.
But to tell the truth, I have some
not retained a traitor mot.
But now, you will discover
Mega Ordalie Merdique Flying.
There are two fragile young ladies who
wait until I come to save them.
In other words, you can call that…
Ordalie of the Love!
It is as loony as the other!!!
Release me!
H-H-He
!
Shit!
Let leave to me!
Bandage cowards!
It is not right to attack to two!
You kidnapped our
friends without preventing…
fact of crying an adorable angel
and tried to assassinate it…
and you oses to treat us cowards?
Ouais, it is true.
It is quite beautiful to be able
to anticipate our movements and all…
But even if you can envisage them…
that is used for nothing the whole
if you cannot avoid them.
Have-stop, idiotic!
I am a Priest with the service of God!
Let leave to me! He!
You me listenings?!
To pass in addition to the Judgment of
Priests is a crime of Class 1!
You really think that you
leave yourself there after that?!
It will be a declaration of war
against God Very Powerful Eneru!
Firm your mouth! Your
bad breath escapes.
Look at how I rather succeeded one
good mignonnette seasoned with pepper…
It is necessary to tenderize
meat, with force…
Brutally.
To cut out of small pieces
without the least hesitation.
Because thus, all savor that it
contain releases itself from only one blow!
Moron! Stop!!!
Ah, stops! Stop!
That will hurt! Stop!
TO CRUSH!