LONGRING LONGLAND!
THE GREAT ADVENTURE
One moves in the right direction? Nami-san.
Obviously!
You are marvellous Nami-swan!
The last small effort and one will have very repaired.
I suspected it well…
Fortunately I bought
nails, in the old man of the dock.
I had a good intuition.
Ensure you Ussop!
With force I took the practice to anticipate
this kind of nuisance.
Ah! Fire disappeared!
Y' has more fuel.
Hey, Ussop!
One will land!
Hurry Chopper! And brings back
all the matos which I left.
Euh… included/understood well!
Still an effort… the octopus montgolfier!
Be stupid for you?! Prepare one
will have to land in urgency!
More quickly, more quickly…
One has…
One survived!
Do not fear anything with that you will not feel any pain.
Thanks to you one arrived there, one owes you
a proud candle my old man!
Thank you.
Pay attention to you!
You will not be forgotten my friend!
Hurry to grow!
The octopuses of Large Line are
much more imposing than you!
Goodbye! Ingredient of first choice.
Thank you!
Take care of you well!
Now…
My crew!
Put the right course in front of worms the next island!
Await a little Luffy!
Leave us time to put back us.
Naive, naive!
If it were also easy on this ocean…
nobody would have difficulty in sail.
Even you you put yourself at it.
Recently, the waves have the odd air.
Go, with the job the guy! Rudder with port side all!
With your orders! Nami-swaan!
You saw that?
Do something, Sanji!
They is dangerous!
It would be said that it y' has something inside the waves!
I will die!!
That it arrives to you?! It is due to what all this din?!
You bar!
Do not push me! I can nothing make!
Then why our friends fight do?
Bellamy?!
Sarquiss?!
Please stop them!
Please…
Stop that!
Why that is done?
What occurs?!
Sarquiss with the air really badly.
Why?
You want to know why?
Sarquiss.
Bellamy.
Because you soiled my emblem!
Here is reason.
Perhaps that the celestial islands exist or perhaps not.
Or that the gold city is only one vulgar myth.
Ca does not have any importance.
You always have the same opinions of the others.
Isn't this?
Bellamy?
Donquihote Doflamingo!
They is members of Shichibukai!
[Shichibukai:7 Captains Corsairs]
In time, it was worth more than 300 million berrys!
What does such a personality make here?
Within my subordinates, I do not have
not need for small strike.
Washout!
Make shit!
I do not manage any more to control my body!
Please stops!
Forgive us!
Nannnnnnn!
Bellamy!
Last once…
Last once leaves us a chance.
I, not… we will follow your orders!
Bellamy!
Ca is enough Bellamy!
Even if I lost,
I never contradicted your ideas!
I respect your emblem!
It is right my way of doing the things!
To destroy all these poor wretches réveurs.
and a day I would be in your place.
My expensive and obeying subordinate.
You will make me cry.
Bellamy…
It is that which I like in you.
The new era is very close.
You are free to do what you want.
However.
I do not need more you at my sides.
Doflamingo!!
This gangster of 55 million berrys,
corrected like a kid. Bellamy!
I do not manage to believe in it.
The horror will begin!
Dispatch you to prepare you!
For a world where only pirates
strongest will survive!
The weak ones will have to flee!
Those which will not manage to follow this
vagueness will perish with their doubts!
A new era will be born!
It would be said that was calmed.
One cannot slacken his attention by here.
Emergency report/ratio!
Ship in sight at 12 noon!
What? It is an enemy?
Not now?!
Eh well.
They do not have a flag nor of veils.
Funny of boat, There are no initials.
What do you say? They do not have any decoration?!
What they make at sea?!
I know anything of it!
But most equivocal…
its crew is very reduced…
And… Hein!
They do all of the odd super mines!
One with the impression which they have any more no heart in them!
Flee!!
They are monkeys of sea!
Still them!
This time, they are much more numerous!
Miss pot does not have there wind!
Hoist the sail!
Veil hoisted!
It is what?
It fout what this ship?
This ship is likely to be carried if it
continue to capsize of the kind!
Hey!!
The guy!!
The waves and the monkeys will involve you with them!
Ridges half-turn!
A ship.
Hey!
It is a pirate ship!
You awake all!
There is an enemy ship! Let us steal their spoils!
Think already of the giant wave who precipitates towards us!
Ouais but the other ship will benefit from it to escape!
Prepare the gun!
Since when a dumb as you gives me orders?!
Ridges half-turn!
It is funny of crew…
They said to want to plunder our spoils.
Let us be unaware of them.
Where is the sail?
How do you want that I know it?
That somebody brings back it!
The navigator?
He is not there any more!
Captain!
HE IS NOT ANY MORE!
Who is the jerk who made use of the gun?
One will not leave oneself there unscathed!!
This crew is made up only of large cretins!
One is made like rats!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
MUGIWARA-TEAM
It is the second time… that really made shit.
Ca with the air to be itself calmed.
I think that this tidal wave was
a joke of the monkeys of seas.
There is nothing any more to fear, time is again stable.
Eh well, it would be time to pose foot on a new island.
Hey, Robin?
You see something?
Ca makes one moment that I see an island.
IS NECESSARY TO SAY IT THEN TO US!!
Without heart!
Listen! The next time that you see an island, say it to us!
Prevent the others!
The guy!
Ground right in front!
Maintaining in your turn!
The fog is rather thick.
YOU STILL HAVE FUN has TO BE UNAWARE OF Me?!
Fog…
Ca is likely to be dangerous.
Chopper!
I let you guide the boat, you of it are responsible.
Included/understood!
You do not realize at which point
one would have liked to see this island!
I am sorry.
I will pay more attention.
If you pay more attention, that suits me.
And then…
This boat does not worry you, the guy?
No the captain, not of navigator…
no the flag, nor of veils, no spirit
of team and no motivation.
I do not manage to believe that it was a crew of pirates!
Perhaps that they fought and that they lost.
And that the captain was killed, and that one stole all to them.
Precisely.
I looked at their boat well.
There was no sign of battle.
On each ship, it y' has objects which
represent the ideology of the pirates.
And on this ship there was nothing of all that.
Then they were not pirates.
Be not made a concern.
However I cannot prevent myself
to think that they are really pirates.
I have a bad presentiment.
You always have some.
I hope that it y' will have a city!
I also hope that it y' will have a shipyard!
Luffy!
One cannot unload immediately.
I wonder whether one will find a good engineer naval!
I see the coast!
Prepare the anchor!
The guy… listen to me all!
Chopper!
Ussop still caught the syndrome of the '' I
donot can unload on an island unknown ''.
I cannot look after that!
Go, go, go!
It is what…
IT Y' DOES NOT HAVE ANYTHING HERE!!
It is what this place?!
Coooool!
There is that plains as far as the eye can see!
It is not really very sensual like place.
I wonder well if somebody saw here.
YOU ALL!!
Ah! These types!
One knows nothing of this island and they launch out lost body there.
Ca appears quite empty.
I imagine that it nothing this will pass here.
What it y' has, Chop…
With all these hairs and this size
enormous, it is not human!
Undoubtedly it is a bear!
Gigantic!
This bear is bloody tall!
Too much large!
They is apples, they are all maiiiiigres!
DO NOT EAT CA!
They is delicious!
There are really nothing in the neighborhoods.
Hey! Look at!
It is not a house?
Ouais one would say.
I hope that somebody saw inside.
Let us see.
A relative with you! A relative with you!
I am a reindeer! HE It IS a DASH!!!
The leg!
Subdue to me that Chopper.
IMPRESSING!
USSOP TOO COOL EAST!
Sat!
Now make the beautiful one.
Wah, it is super length!
I manage more to see his head.
Where they still went…
They were it here y' has one moment.
One could do to a turn us too?
It could be that there is some
thing of good to be eaten by here.
Hey! Robin-chwan!
One will make a small round.
Yes!
Ca also it is looooooooooooooong.
All that is here is super length.
To only look at them…
I have the impression that my face stretches.
Which kind of island that can it be well?
HELLO!
Y' HAS SOMEBODY!
You cannot enter like that!
Wait, await Luffy!
I am ready to bet that this house
belongs to the boss of this island.
It is sûrement.un monster snake super long eater
of man or a démoniaque spirit!
There is nobody here…
Hey Luffy!
Ussop!
I found a giraffe!
WHAT?
It is not a giraffe.
It has a large neck but it is a horse.
A horse with a large neck.
Es you a horse?
What a beautiful horse!
It is called Shelly, it is a girl.
She has a saddle, it must have there somebody who saw here.
What doesn't go Luffy?
Ussop.
It is well a bamboo which pushes over there?
Ouais.
One cannot see the top!
It is so high.
Look at this bamboo more closely.
He flees!
Ca must still be funny of animal!
The bamboo attacked Luffy!
Hey! Nothing of broken?!
I will not lose against a bamboo!
Pay Luffy attention!
It gained!!
Ouais!!
I pété it into two!
Where is your Master?
You do not know.
You have the air quite only.
It is perhaps an enemy, hides by there!
What occurred?
Look at…
When I broke the bamboo…
a spirit appeared.
They wedged the way…
of our boat.
What do they want?
This ship…
it is that of presently.
Who be you?!
Come in bottom if you want to fight.
WE ARE THE PIRATE FOXY!
Do not be in a hurry! We want just…
A DUEL!!
A spirit?
Eh well…
It appeared when I broke the bamboo.
Hey! Said something!
Of course that I remember you.
Did Ca make one moment, what you become?
Do Hein, you know it the guy?
Not me.
Me either.
Ah, for this reason you were to me if not very familiar.
You do ACES SAY CA TO the CONK? AND THEN WHICH ES YOU OSSAN?
My name is Tonjit.
I must say to you thank you.
It is you who struck in my stilts, not truth?
Stilts?
Ah, yes it is us!
But this bamboo was so large
that I could not see the top.
Yes.
It is exactly where I was.
You are not a spirit appeared afterwards
that I broke the bamboo.
You fell because I broke one of your stilts.
Why used you of so large stilts?
Since always I like to walk on the stilts.
Then I took the largest bamboos of this island.
To try to manufacture the largest stilts
world, I thought that I was going to amuse me!
But when I am assembled above, I had
if fear that I could not go down any more.
You are not a little idiot, ossan?!
Then I remained 10 years there.
YOU ES REALLY TOO IDIOT!
You remained on these stilts during 10 years?!
Indeed.
And during this time there, bamboos
continued to push.
With time Ca became even harder to go down.
Ah! It was terrifying.
It is all that you find to say after 10 years?!
Eh well here all is super large, even
perched on my stilts…
I have to find to eat, by taking them
fruits all in top of the trees.
It is really an incredible history.
That lived you during all this time.
While speaking about large super tricks, ossan.
Why all that is here is also gigantic, that they are the trees or the animals?
It is a normal reaction on behalf of the foreigners.
It y' has an obvious reason.
This island is only one vast extended from plains.
In a word…
Everyone likes to be stretched and be released.
Of agreement.
Which explanation.
For example, look by there?
Kaaaamonoh Ashi!
You just lengthened the sound!
That there it is…
Daaaaachund!
It is not the dog of presently?
It is still there since presently?!
There are also dangerous animals.
Look by there.
He it is the léoooooooooopard snows.
You made not bite.
Why that one with the head lengthened on the side?!
It would not be…
the captain of this crew?