I troubles…
It is soon finished this rain, brothel!!
Heh, Ussop…
You ace something of interesting to make?
Yes.
I have a small fireworks which I designed.
You want to test?
Of course!!!!
Does not even think of it.
One is likely to be located by an enemy ship.
I cross which have you reason.
Hey…
What is what you are spirit of reading?
Luffy interested by a book?!!
Koi?
I said something of bad?
Not.
At all.
Fog of the Rainbow.
It is the ihstoire of a fog coloured like a rainbow
The author in this book racontre his adventures in funny of ocean.
Adventures!!
Ca parrait interesting.
I cross not my ears!!
It does not matter how much il' is annoyed, I will never have believed.
The sea is a mysterious endroi.
Hey, I saw an island.
Really?!!
Something does not go?!
No, nothing.
I will make it flower!!
The Huit-Shaku ball of the Ussop man.
Koi?!
It is ok.
Dad! Mom!
Take care of the ship!
Yes…
Worry you!
Hey!! Y' has a city!!
heh.
Wait! Luffy!
A city.!!
It is small like city, but it is well animated!
I bet that one could supply oneself here.
You will buy some Ussop things?
Can be!
Hey! the guy!
Come quickly!!
It is what.
Posters of premiums?
. It is koi!
Oh! A Festival of fires of artifices!
And that even occurs this evening!
It is fantastic!!
Ca makes well a long time that I did not see fires of artifices!
In this case.
Allow me vous' to accompany there.
Nami-san^^.
Pas la pains.
Miss of your business.
Fireworks!!
I am excited!
Say to me.
I ever saw you by here.
Summers you come for the fireworks?
Not, not exactly.
Why?
Are your fireworks also popular?
Yes.
Our island is famous for its festival.
It has become an annual event for 400 years.
400 years?!
That made so a long time!
Look at.
You see the tower on this mountain over there?
Since 400 years.
. .cette house created fireworks,
from generation to generation.
In this moment, it is only one hurdy-gurdy
man and a little girl who live there.
Therefore, the hurdy-gurdy man only manufactures all the fireworks with him?
Not, not.
This little girl also assistance to do them.
They work all the year without slackening only for this night.
It is really admirable.
Why that take a whole year to manufacture fires of artifices?
Be to you that an idiot! It is because of.
Many things.
Even if I explain to you you nothing goes measuring rod.
ah good!
I found!
I have almost more gunpowders!
Can be if I go over there, they will be able to give some to me a little.
wait.
I will return later!
But….
I hope that will not pass like last year.
Yes. Me too.
What is what occurred last year.?
Oh, during the last festival.
Hey! They traversed all this way to have fun.
Pas la pains of their wasting the pleasure of it.
You are right.
Afflicted, it is nothing low register.
Forget all that I said.
In this case.
We must turn over to warn Zorro and Robin!
Yo!
I will say it to Robin-chan!
Wait.
I cross which one must dabord eat.
Why that!!
With my talent I can do one crowned fireworks.
When I show them this, they will burst.
“Which talent!!”
“Take all that you want, it is FREE!!”
I do not know if that will occur like that!
No chance!!
It is what this strange face!!
Summers you the craftsman-in-chief of the fireworks?
He even.
I am the craftsman-in-chief of the fireworks
Odama!
P.Peu imports, I need your assistance!
You have a little time, Non?
You must have tons of powder, not true?
In this castle, there is no powder but
I can give you.
Please return or you come.
On this, good day.
Hehh, wait one minute!
Castle, turn. it does not matter, at least throw
a glance with this before judging me.
It is a true part of Article.
Note:Giant ball N° 14
A balloon. !!
Immense.!!
White!!!
Note:The ball has a height of 8 shaku (Approximately 2.42 m)
For which you begin to encrust you like that
in the houses of the others after being returned!!
Hey, thus say!
It is truth this trick?
It paper-is chewed, not?
That is what a craftsman of artifices foutrait with
paper-chewed in this house?!
It is a truth.
Did Hey, you claim to have a beautiful piece of art?
Ah, Q. .quoi?!
ahh, it is nothing.
A Dango ball. mm?!
The aspect is not badly, and it is well packed.
Why do you hide it?
What a waste! You must complete it!
Heh, Qui' are you?
Me, it is Kodama.
The little girl of Odama-jii-san.
Thus small the gamine which designs fires
of artifice with the old man it is.
Yes, It is me.
The fact that I would be a gamine is not a reason to take to me with the light one
I am at least as good as this old catch.
Ca made maaal!
Or is what you put the head!
I cross to have said to you to give this message to the group of the shooting?
I did it.
They said that they will pass to take them the rather possible one.
thus I thought of preparing the balloons!.
Y' has too many things to make before they arrive,
how to charge the tubes with release in the coach!
Yes! Yes! I know!
I went there already!!
That is what are to you spirit to look at.
Ceases to make this head of idiot and will help it!!
Why!?
Do not ask why! move!!
What is what bell with this guy?
At the beginning he asks me to leave, just after he says to me to help it.
Make shit! I break!!
Hey!
You draw already.?
Make me a knack!
You are not an apprentice?
Of course that not.
I just came here to seek gunpowder.
By looking at this firework which you carried.
I believed that you were there like apprentice.
It was right something which I did in my temps libre.
Y' had any means which I would be a pro.
I was unaware of that.
But it was well done, I ensure you!
You must complete it the rather possible one!
I precisely thought of it, you already spoke me.
What did you want to say?
It is already finishes, in what relates to me.
The goal to make fireworks is to decorate
night sky by pretty flowers.
It is there or work is completed.
Therefore, of the fireworks in their tubes.
are loins to be completed.
It is like these tubes of shooting.
They will not be complete as long as they will not have a ball inside.
Tu' be admirable!
As I already said.
Do not take to me slightly.
It is the same case for this large fireworks over there
It is not yet finishes either, truth?
I would like to undoubtedly see this trick bursting!
Last year.
We tested with something similar.
Did Y' have some already like that?
Yes.
But that failed.
Our equipment did not can support it.
But that wants to say.
My Dad, and my Mom.
This same day last year.
They died.
At the time or the 205 Ball had burst.
Crowned bad weather, not true?
Do you think of suspending the festival if that continues like that?
Not.
I cross not to be able to do it.
Dad, Mom.
Continue with the préparatives ones.
Ok.
What is what you cross not to be able to make.?
Listen.!
If the sky is cleared up with fallen the night.
I will launch the Ball-205.
Stop that…!
The fireworks it is not puffs out.!!
Idiot.
Do not howl like that.
D.désolé.
But. You cannot only burst this great trick with you.
Worry you!
I asked in secrecy for the assistance of the team of shooting.
But that is likely to fail again.
They is dangerous.!
It is well, I want to do it.
It is not well!!
You want to also burst the team of the shooting?
Of course that not.
When all is prét, I will ask them to be held with the shelter.
I will even do it me!
“Jvé to even do it me!”
Not question, not question!
I will say it to your grandfather to stop you.
It is what these idées de génie!!
It is what I was going to ask you!
Does not destroy the dream of my parents!
The dream of your parents?
Yes.
My family designed fireworks during all the latter 400 years.
I am well.
Cease moving!
In the past.
They had talent to design and launch the Ball-205.
But at a certain point.
they stopped this tradition.
Ressusciter these talents.
It stays the dream of my Dad and my Mom.
Today.
I will carry out their dream!
Good, you ace of cranium.
A.attends one minute.
Why you tell me all that with me?
You want to really know?
You will not say it to your grandfather?
No, the team of shooting soon will come to recover the ball.
Therefore, I need you to retain
grandfather until they finish.
Please!
Idiot.!
It is as if I helped you to do something of dangerous!!
Dad, Mom. your dream is with half carried out.
I will carry it out for you.
Wait one minute!!
A prayer before the fireworks.?
Ca appears to me well.
But one will not draw that one.
One will use only the small balloons.
The team of shooting.
Why? How did you know?
Would not be ridiculous!
Everyone thinks of you.
Why?
Why? I said to you how much that counts for me!!
Afflicted, Kodama-chan.
But they is dangerous.
Ca is likely to fail.
How can you know!
And even if it is risked, I am not afraid!
Ca is enough!!
It is not as if I did not include/understand the feeling to be abondonné.
But it is not the way of inheriting their will.
Kodama-chan.!
Ca will be perfect.
Good, One will continue with the préparatives ones.
Yes, Thank you.
You to continue to prepare you
even if that continues to rain?
The rain goes soon arréter.
The wind blows of the east.
What I cannot include/understand it is Kodama.
Grandfather.
Does this tower, it hold here since 4 ciécles?
Yes.
Why this question?
I thought just of a trick.
You want the knowledge?
Hey, of the tombs?
It is sad, heh.
Yo!
Dad, Mom.
As I said.
If this rain arréte.
Will Ca want to say that you give me your agreement, Vrai?
To launch the Ball-205 for you.
But I cross.
I will not succeed, heh?
Of course that one does not want to say that you will not succeed!
Kodama, If you launches your fireworks,
One will mettera fine with this rain with joy.
But.
Your dream will not be.
You cross which one has only one dream?
Tu' be our dream
Our dream with us, it is that you become
large a craftsman of the fireworks.
Kodama.
You can take your time and creates your own 205-Ball.
You all the time have world in front of you.
If you will be able one day to make a success of the Ball-205.
Ca will carry out also our dream.
Let Gran-father occupy himself some.
And continues to make pretty fireworks
so that we look at them paradise.
Ok!
I will do it!
And a day. I will create my own Ball-205!
Thank you to be understanding.
And as promised!
How you have. It is astonishing!
Who are you?
Me?
I am a messenger of the paradise.
Ussop Angel!
Ussop. Angel.
It is strong!
Ussop Angel!
Thank you!
I will do my better!
They is marvellous.
They make a true spectacle.
But, still a little.
It used the wheels of the cart of the garden.
to build a crank to slip the ball into the tower.
Therefore, this tower at 400 years.
was useful for launching of the Ball-205.
But, which is really this type?
Great Final!!
Large spectacle, heh?
Yes. It is an excellent performance.
Does Ca occur how?
All is prét.
The last!
Ok!
Koi.
It was what this small fireworks.
Let us see!
It is all that my first fireworks can do?
Ok! Large Odama father!
Dad.
Mom, it is their fireworks…
They made a so pretty fireworks.
Mom…
Dad, you are really génials.!
I am unaware of.
If one day I will be able to create a similar fireworks…
Mom, Papaa!!
Thank you!!!
Large father.
You cross which I will have the right to a little gunpowder?
Dirtiness of kid.!
You appear of nowhere to ask me something similar?!
Take all that you want!!
To follow!!