One precisely spoke about you.
You want something?
Ouais!
Return the gold which you stole
in Papi Head of Diamond!
Gold?
You want to say that of the old Cricket?
I will return to him who flagstone!
I stole it to him, as a pirate.
You are a pirate you also, then
you do not have lessons to give me.
However if.
These guy are my friends.
Then I theirs will return.
ichi oku No otoko
The man has 100 million!
The greatest council of the world
and the pirate Beard Black!
sekai saikou kenryoku
to kaizoku kuro hige
I would like to know…
You can fight?
Do you can at least strike?!
What have I to fear of one
weakling like you?
W-were right…
It is well him!
Eh! What you
swings still with this trick?
You can make confettis of them!
But, and if this opinion of
was research a truth?
If it is worth really 100
Million Berrys…
Bellamy will be never
enough extremely for…
Ridiculous!
Look at to me this kid!
One in vain looks it from every angle,
it does not have anything a dangerous murderer.
I really start to doubt
this poster to 30 Million me too!
If you remainders planted to tremble
of fear like presently…
you risks not of me
to take again anything.
Lopette!
This afternoon, it was different.
It is that!
In what is this different?
This time I will make sure that you
will miss me never again of respect!
Ca collapses!
One will finish some quickly!
SPRING SNIPE!
He! Straw hat jumped!
Small maggot!
What it came
to make here, this snotty-nosed kid?
Bah, let us admire the show of Bellamy!
It had a large mouth, but there one
would say rather than he flees like a yellowbelly!
I see any difference.
Nothing changed since presently!
I believed that you had
to take again gold to me!
You ace that mouth!
You do not make the weight vis-a-vis me!
Be right good for you with radoter
with your stupid dreams!
For which you want to be made pass?!
It falls us above!
We draw!
You can fight as much as you want.
Nobody can escape
with my capacities Hamper Hamper.
[Note:Hamper = Spring]
Be already re-silvered to you?! What a shame!
This snotty-nosed kid is really not
of size to face Bellamy.
Do not say to me that he already died!
It was raised!
I do not have the intention
to finish some so quickly!
I am on the point of
to begin the true show!
SPRING HOPPER!
Bellamy disappeared!
It is the technique with which
it spread out Roshio the Executor!
These guys are your FRIENDS?!
Ah yes, it is true that this old man and
its monkeys are same species as you!
A band of morons who gobent the lies
of a dead type four hundred years ago!
Which Gold City?
Which celestial island?
The COMPLETED ERA OF the DREAMERS EAST!
YOU ES THE SHAME OF THE PIRATES!
Do I can strike?
Stop it, Bellamy!
The good-for-nothings as do not deserve to him
no food in the real-world!
GOOD-BYE, STRAW HAT!
He, Bellamy, stop blaguer!
Go!
You cheeks the comedy, not true?
Say something!
He, Bellamy!
Stop talking cock!
Be raised and made us
your usual show!
Bellamy!!
You have a premium of 55 Million
Berrys, you remember?!
Exact! Guys of this afternoon…
They have both a premium
higher than holds, Bellamy!
T you see, I had said it!
The gold of Papi.
Return it to me!
To repair the boat!
To hoist the prow!
They have fishing, these guys!
It is done!
They took one removed rust from
and they are already on feet!
And even while Chopper
look after their wounds…
They recover drôlement quickly!
Why you did not accompany it?
Hein? But it is what your problem?
A blow it is “does not fight! ”…
The other, it east “fight! ”…
Then, “does not go there! ”…
And “Go ahead!”.
It is not what I wanted to say.
But you also, you are
taken a beating, not?
A beating?
It is not as if they were
across our way.
I do not like to fight
adversaries which make me pity.
What do you tell?
Be to you idiot or what?
The farm! Insane me the camp!
You me genes!
What you ace?!
Always make of it you that at your head!
Why I would listen to you?!
He Ho! Made blunder,
species of morons!
Ben, surely because
I am right always!
This boat is our
well most invaluable…
Break from there!
He! Stop-that, cretins!
What you ace?!
Never repeat that!
Ca is enough, band the weak ones!
I have it! I have it!
This species of dwarf…
It was a blow of bowl…
HE, JERK!
WAIT!
I AM ALWAYS, YOU DO NOT SEE?!
GO, BRINGS ITSELF!
Y' does not have average that one loses in front
a stupid dreamer in your kind!
WHAT THERE IS?!
OR YOU GO, STRAW HAT?!
Where?
In the sky!
Then these types made fall Sir
Crocodile, one of the Captains Corsairs…
Monkey D. Luffy and Roronoa Zoro.
Santoryu Ougi!
[secret technique with three sabers]
Sanzen Sekai!
[Three thousand worlds]
To strike a man in the back
is humiliating for a sword-man.
Admirable.
EXCEED me!
RORONOA ZORO!
Then as that these kids attracted
attention of the World Government, hein?
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
Holy Land, MarieJoa
How?
The Russet-red one?
Yes, its intrigues
become worrying.
Lastly, it is not like if it
had moved in person.
Exact!
It is about an action
indirect using a messenger.
But all the same!
A meeting between White Beard
and the Russet-red one is really dangerous!
[Note:Sekai Seifu Saikou Kenryouku = greatest political authority in the world; Gorousei = the Council of the Five Seniors]
Hum. It is exact, indeed.
However, if we let the Russet-red one become insane
furious, it could escape our control…
Nevertheless, it does not have the ambition
to change the world with him all alone.
Satisfy we to observe it
without making hasty decisions!
In the immediate future, which imports, it is
the problem of the Seven Powerful Corsairs.
We must quickly find
a substitute with Crocodile.
It is advisable to fill
this vacancy.
If the Three Great Capacities came to
to crumble, the world itself would fall of pieces.
Measures should be taken.
Well!
This is why we have already
convened the Seven Powerful Corsairs.
But I am unaware of how much enter
they will answer the call.
They are pirates after all,
they make any only at their head.
Rotten Crocodile…
With your schemes, you have us
put in a delicate situation.
And as regards this
man who overcame it…
We cannot any more leave it
to run the seas with impunity.
Monkey D. Luffy.
Arrival with MarieJoa, District
General of the Navy…
Seven Powerful Corsairs…
Donquihote Doflamingo-sama…
Follow-up of Bartholomew Kuma-sama.
[One of the Seven Powerful Donquihote Corsairs
Doflamingo Ancienne precedes:340 Million Berrys]
[One of the Seven Powerful Bartholomew Corsairs
Kuma Ancienne precedes:296 Million Berrys]
H-He!
Stop…
What takes to you?!
It is not me!
My hands do not obey me any more!
Stop your conneries!
It is not the moment to joke!
It is not a joke!
I do not control myself any more!
How if I went gober that!
Ca is enough! What
you have both?
You want to kill me?!
BUT NOT!
Stop!
Where you believe you?!
[Amirale Defect of the General headquarter of
the Marine Tsuru, Chef d'Etat Major]
He! Ca is enough!
I know that it is you, Doflamingo!
Stop that immediately!
If I do it, say us
what one has to say…
and let us stop with
this stupid meeting!
H-He! Stop, idiotic!
Stop!
Slacken them, Doflamingo!
Dumb!
Enough!
Cease these squabbles!
It is a war which you want?
[Admiral as a Chief of the General headquarter of the Navy
High Ordering Sengoku Marine the Buddha]
Ah yes, all my excuses for my delay.
I am happy that you came.
Rabbles of the seas.
And well, terrible opinion
that you have us.
, Want you start?
I guess that nobody any more will come.
In to have joined together two on
six exceeds already my hopes.
You astonish me!
I did not want to come either.
But the businesses go so well
on the island which I am désoeuvré.
Therefore, here me is.
I see. It is rather
painful to hear.
There is nothing more opposing to learn
that the businesses of the pirates go so well.
You are of provocative mood.
It is not worthy of Buddha, that…
Admiral as a Sengoku Chief.
I believed to hear a futile discussion.
Would I be misled to me in place?
Eye of Falcon!
The General headquarter of the Navy
and Seven Powerful Corsairs…
A roundtable with two groups
of power equalizes in conflict…
great interest with my direction does not have.
Ben, known as thus!
You stays well the last that
I expected to see arriving.
I would never have believed… but you…
What?
I am here only in so much
that simple observer.
I am interested in certain pirates
it will be question this time.
It is all.
In this case, will not see you objections
so that I assist with this meeting me too?
Lastly, not completely in
as long as simple observer.
Good god, but which are you?
How you entered here?!
And well, I did not expect to see
so many prestigious characters brought together here.
By chance…
… this meeting…
… I came to assist to with it…
… and to take share there.
I learned that Crocodile
its place had lost…
and I wondered to times you whether
would not seek a successor to him.
You…
You would be Laffite?!
Laffite?
Oh, I see that you know me.
I am very honoured.
It was a famous guard
peace of West Blue…
But its inclinations for the ultra one
violence cost him the exile.
It is old story.
But what you think
of me imports little.
I came to propose a certain person
within the Seven Powerful Corsairs.
Shanks…
Ca makes a long time that I
did not hear this name.
Then like that, this
is letter of Shanks?
Yes.
It appears that it is very important…
It thus sent me to be ensured
that it would arrive at good port.
Congratulation. Ca did not have
to be easy to arrive up to now.
Not, it was my duty as
new recruit of the Pirates Of the Russet-red one.
[Pirates Of Russet-red (New recruit)
Rockstar, Premium:94 Million Berrys]
But, that made a few times
that I officiate in piracy.
I must say that I am rather famous.
He, you over there!
You already intended to speak
of Rockstar, not true?!
Not, that says anything to me.
And then, he said that the King of the Seas was
the best thing than it had ever tasted…
Wait!
Q - What!
To send a letter to me to me…!
Since when this kid
he believes so important?!
He, But wait!
Okashira specified well that this
letter was very important!
[Note:Okashira = Chief]
O it is in the train of
to speak about Russet-red there!
Es you conscious of what you do?!
I am White Barbe!
Captain, you drank alcohol too much.
Idiot!
I drink when I want to drink
then that cannot make me of evil.
Okashira said that this
letter was urgent!
I guess what it acts.
It is about Ace and Barbe Black.
You will say to this snotty-nosed kid
of Carrot Hair…
that if it has something to say to me, it would make
to better bring to drinking and to point itself!
You can lay out now.
I have to better do than to discuss
with a small scrapings like you.
Mug of cake!
[The man most extremely of the world. The large one
pirate Beard White Edward Newgate]
Always also dry, the old man!
Y' does not have what to laugh, Okashira!
I suspected that
would happen like that.
Give me more time!
Me had ever been humiliated kind!
He, Ho! But what do you say?
Drop!
You made ace of the good job.
Now, returns!
But my honor is ridiculed!
The life is more
important that honor.
There is no more only you can make.
You gave him what to reflect.
Then?
What goes one
to make, Okashira?
One moves!
Prepare the boat!
One will see White Barbe?
Just.
You believe that the Government
will remain without anything to say?
I am not done any for that.
What?
The Government
that will surely not tolerate…
But if they are put transversely
from our road, that will heat!
Ahead the guy!
Will have action there!
Ouaip! Take our
better rum barrels!
Teach?
Yes.
It is the name of the Captain
of our pirate crew.
Ever intended to speak.
If nobody know it…
it could never be used for
to impress the other pirates.
Exact, we of it are conscious.
Moreover we prepare one
small operation to cure it…
if ever you give us
a little more time.
It is amusing!
He! Give them a chance, Sengoku!
The crew to which I belong
name the Pirates of Black Beard.
Try to remember you!
Did He, you hear?
It appears that Bellamy
was made demolish!
By which?!
100 Million…
I found that 30 Million it was not
sufficient for a kid with so much of ambition…
But, as long as that…
Whereas will be done, Capitaine?
He, jerk!
Remain not planted in the middle of
passage like a large dung!
It is not the moment
to irritate me this evening!
Crush!
I am not interested in small fish!
It is at least a head with 100
Million that we needed!
I aim at the gold mine!
And it is already moving!
One finally will go
to claim our reward!
Captain!
We were not to find
Laffite in this city?
[The Quartermaster of the Pirates of Barb
Black. Champion Jesus Burgess]
It would seem that its future
was some share elsewhere.
It is the destiny which wanted it!
Isn't this, Auge?
[Note:Trough = Eye (German)]
[Captain of the Pirates of Barb
Black. Black beard Marshall D.Teach]
[Tireur d'élite of the Pirates of
Black beard. Supersonic Van Trough]
Exactly!
The human existence is in
permanence controlled by the destiny.
[Ship's doctor of the Pirates of
Black beard. The Reaper Doc. Q.]
Papi Head of Diamond!
I bring back gold for you!
Await me!
Soon…
I will be soon of return!!!