Fatal counter-attack!
The sharp spirit of Usopp and Kaenboshi!
We are there!
I see!
It is the second island of Large Line,
Little Garden!
What is this it is that this island?
Reads… Little Garden?
This island…
What “does Little” want to say?
Ca must be one of these prehistoric islands.
They remained at the age of the dinosaurs.
Our duel has lasted for 100 years.
Reason?
I forgot.
But it is not the problem.
Then, why do you fight?
For the honor!
Ouahou! They are enormous!
God of the war…
Elbaf, God of the war
its judgment returned!
I lost his favors.
Who did that?
You show!!
you are those which ruined the duel of the Giants-Ossans.
I go you botter the bottom!!
It is useless!
Your companions will become my next masterpiece!
Luffy!!
Ah… This tea is very good.
Luffy!
What you…
This tea is so good.
Luffy!
What you insane?
Species of cretin!!
It is the end of the history for you, the balls.
You will test my best weapon!
What a cretin! he missed his target and struck his own comrade!
I did not see any ball!
Did I forget to say to you that my breath is explosive?
Shit.
It is too…
Not balls…
Karu!
Does Ca go?
Do He, you leave itself there over there?
Yes, I am there! Thank you!
Its last attack burned its Tee-shirt and destroyed the trap!
You will not control me any more with your odd painting now!
I will not let any of them die!
I am really irritated now!
Hold, it is really odd…
Ca makes hours that I wait and nobody still returned.
Something had to arrive at Nami-San or Vivi-Chan.
If it is the case, it is really not the moment to cook the lizard!
Namiii-San!
Vivi-Chann!
He! Said something!
I love you!
What is it that?
While you made the idiot,
your companions were already reduced to that.
And then?
They are always alive!
Eh well, that I do not know it.
After Miss Week Golden delicious painted them,
they will be perfect wax statues.
It is too late to save them, Straw hat!
Indeed, it is right!
It is well too late.
Now, taste infinite despair
of my attack.
What does it make?
It is what is worth the 42.000.000 Berrys on its head.
The ultimate masterpiece of Mr. 3…
Now, Miss Week Golden delicious!
Recover to me your adorable colors
in an artistic way.
After will I be able to make a pause?
If you want, but do not remain in the way.
In this state, I am completely invincible!
My splendid wax Doru Doru is as hard as of steel.
My whole body is protected by an unbreakable armor!
Therefore, I do not have…
no weakness!!
Too much cool!
Does not admire it!
Engagements it!
Well!
Coat of color finished!
Now…
Useless!
Ca did not go!
Its attacks cannot penetrate its solid armor!
Shit, vapor of wax…
Of wax?
I see!
Why didn't I think of it earlier?
If the wax vaporizes,
it can be molten!
Luffy!
You must ignite his wax!
Whatever its solidity, it is only of wax!
Even if Zoro, the others and main Brogy already hardened, it is still time!
One can save them!
What?
It is true?
Yes, it rightly.
How can you say that to them?
Of course, the knowledge does not make any difference!
You have neither the chance, nor time!
In 30 small seconds, their hearts will stop beating!
Even now, they test pain and anguish during their last breath of conscience!
They taste the horror of death!
We do not need 30 seconds, I will save them now!
Usopp!
You do not listen to it?
You are not likely any to gain.
Shit! We do not have any more time!
Give up!
Listen, this cord…
Oh! Ca with the funny air!
With what did think you?
You let me go up above?
Karu!
Course!
Course!!
No matter what it arrives, continues to run around the base!
Whatever your plan, it is useless!
Excuse me…
I wonder how much kilos you will be able to support!
Always upright? Dirtiness of bird!
Give up!
They will be my adorable chief-of works!
You think that I will let do that?
They will not die because of a guy like you!
If one needs fire to melt it, I will use that one!
Not! Stop!
Luffy!
This small flame will not make them melt rather quickly!
Light the cord of Karu!
The cord of the bird?
It soaked in oil.
It is a special cord!
Ok! Everyone awakes!
The situation will be heated a hair.
Try to adapt to you.
Stop!
Hot! Hot!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
Enormous this fire!
They will be left there?
Not! Cursed Straw hat!
How did you can ruin my Candle Service Set?
I will not forgive myself it!
You will not flee, band of cowards!
Shit!
Bandage the small bastard ones!
Now, you did it!
It is the end!
And now,
I will burst you the head!
Oh not!
It was hot in it!
It is all that you could do?
Which kind of luxury did expect you?
You should thank me for being in life!
You are right! Thank you!
I cannot believe it!
We are in life!
You dissolved wax, what a wound!
But I will not let to you any more interfere in the mission!
Mr. 5!
Cretin!
How much time should I prove it to you?
The powder does not go on man-bends!
Which taste that has?
Afflicted, but I am a liar!
It is not powder in your mouth. It is my special Tabasco Boshi!
Ca burns!
Would be sure to know before speaking!
Pirate poor wretch!
How oses you to try this trick rotted on me?
I go you éradiquer with my Full Body Explosion!
You will be less than powder of bone when I finish some!
Not! Stop! Not!
Usopp!
Wait! Not!
I am sorry! Afflicted…
My katanas is well when they are ignited.
Zoro!
Yo! It would be said that one leaves oneself there.
Ouais!
Master…
There remain about it still two.
Bird!
One will not forgive them!
That which destroys a duel is not a man!
Therefore, you came!
Welcome in my castle Doru Doru!
It is what that?
And now, I wonder whether you can say where I am?
You were not malignant to follow us.
We are the most intelligent combo of Works Baroque.
A surpuissant idiot who walks only to the instinct like you
cannot hope to overcome us.
I am Mr. 3.
And I always finish my missions.
Please, thus advance!
But if you turn me the back,
your heart…
will be transpierced at this precise moment.
How…
you knew
which I was?
Instinct.
For the tea of the afternoon,
Earl Grey is really the best.
He, wait a little!
I should not be here sitted with drinking tea by making manners!
Nami-san and the others must await my assistance!
Ah, what a embarrassment!
But I wonder really what such a place of comfort in this jungle does?
Hein?
It is Den Den Mushi.
Den Den Mushi = Snail Phon
Yes? Thank you to have called!
It is the restaurant of shit!
You order something?
Stop talking cock,
asshole!
Your report/ratio is late.
Ah? My report/ratio?
And I with whom do I have can know the honor?
It is me.
Mr. 0!