Nami was trapped on the Maxim Arch until the arrival of its two savers…
Sanji and Usopp.
One already had to be made locate
by the enemy since one moment.
They know that one is there?
How one makes now?
Useless to worry some!
When one is inside, one
separate and one goes on the bridge.
Nami-san
find over there!
During this time, after Eneru took with the trap its arm in a gold ball…
and made it fall from Maxim
in the Ruins of Shandora,
Luffy is raised again
to regulate its accounts!
Good!
Shit!
I do not manage to remove
this gold testicle!
Do not speak about testicle!
Usopp arrives in time for
to save Nami of this mud pit,
but it is not size with
to face the power of Eneru…
and it is on the point
to remain there, when…
EL
Sanji-kun!
You bar!
THOR
I sought fire
to light my cig.
Capriccio of the Destruction
The imminent destiny of the celestial island!!
Chialer?
Really?
What?!
The Arch!
Bastard!
You would have…
Ouais.
Prepare with chialer.
Dumb!
What you have…
fact in the boat?!
Species…
of bloody nuisance.
One of the gears was moved.
I must position it back.
Good, it left.
Do not make any you.
Nami fell without
damage on the ilonimbus.
C-C' is high!
JSe do not have to fall into the jungle.
I should not fall on the ruins.
It is necessary just that I concentrate
to reach the ilonimbus.
usopp
[Note:Hopping = Scintillation]
I have S-S-sautée
too much far!
I jumped too far!
NOOOOOON!!!!
Oh not! I fall!
I will be crushed! I will be crushed!
I will be crushed and creveeeeer!
I forgot to detach it!
Usopp! Sanji-kun!
Is Oh, it you, Nami?
It would be said that you left yourself there!
What a relief!
He, Sanji!
Are Sanji-kun, you well?
You ace be heroic presently!
I am sorry that you would be
still wounded because of us.
He, you ace not interest of clamser!
He!
J-J' chokes!
I choke!
N-Nami! Quickly! Hurry
to leave me from there!
Oh, sorry.
In any case…
it is necessary that one leaves from here!
Why I am not able to release you?!
I die.
Cursed living Blue Sea.
You believed that my Arch
would be so easy to destroy?
I know perfectly its
mechanisms of propulsion.
Even without electrical energy,
there is a back-up system
coming from my terre natale, Bilka…
who uses the power
from two hundreds Jet Dials…
and it can maintain the Arch
in the airs one hour whole.
You can resist
as much as you want!
The end of this country is imminent!
Look at this giant bean.
If it is the same one as
I saw since the ruins,
then this ilonimbus
is just above.
Ruins…
L it Quoted of Gold?!
You found it?!
Yes.
But, Eneru took all gold.
In any way, ruins
are in lower part of us.
Ruins of Shandora
Zoro and others
are surely over there.
Current location
I am not sure of what
you say in connection with the ground…
but I have the feeling which it goes us
to arrive of the trifles if one remains there.
Completely. Go up!
The others should be found
and to draw from this island.
D-D' agreement!
There is no more no place
with the shelter on Skypiea.
Luffy, pay to!
It is too fast!
L-Luffy, wait!
It is not by there!
Goes on the left! On the left!
Mr.-MR.-but I cannot
to turn also quickly!
[Note:Hook = Hook]
DO NOT DESTROY THE ISCED OF MY ANCESTORS!
One can see Giant Jack up there!
I know, but…
DECREE ALL TO BREAK!
HE!!
Yes.
The clouds of flashes are
quite again charged.
The rat gave up.
Really shameless.
But it does not matter.
No matter what it arrives,
my official reception will be magic.
Hein?
Robin is not there any more.
Zoro and Chopper either.
Neither Wiper and nor God.
Where did they pass?
They had to climb.
Oh, Robin had to take them along.
Good, allons-y.
He, Aisa?
I do not know.
Listen well.
If nothing is done, this country…
Skypiea will be destroyed.
The celestial island?
Our village too?
All.
Each man, woman and
child in the sky…
will turn over to surface.
Luffy…
Ouais?
The celestial island…
really will be destroyed?
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
As soon as one is
left, I will see Wiper.
I suspected it, the arch
direct towards the Large Belfry.
What it arrived at Madam
Navigatrice and others?
I really hope that they
are not on this arch.
One succeeded!
Up there!
Luffy! Stop! Stop!
Robin!
What you make?!
Deal with
these deux-là!
Stop! Stop!
Luffy!
It has arms which push!
From which does this gold leave which hangs with your arm?
Robin, the Bell of Gold is with
is top of bean, it that?
Does Eneru want the bell, not true?
If the Belfry exists,
GYAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
G Y HAS HAS HAS HAS HAS HAS
But, even if…
OK!
Luffy!
It left.
Then, young girl.
Did you see Madam Navigatrice?
A girl with orange hair.
You speak about Nami?
She is on the arch.
Hein? I hear only one
only voice in the sky.
Here they are!
He, Robin!
Madam Navigatrice!
Long Nose-kun!
Cook-san!
Aisa!
Good!
I am content that you are well!
Nami!
Zoro!
Chopper!
Odd Papi!
E-and the warrior!
Brothel, everyone is K.O. !
So only I had been there!
Oh, Aisa. Where is Luffy?
It was not with you?
Luffy left to save you, Nami!
It climbed bean
to face Eneru!
What?
Has Zut, one just missed it?
Just at the moment.
I tried to stop it.
This guy never reflects!
There are not any more time!
If one does not draw quickly from here…
Ok, I will follow it with Waver.
You, find a means
to reach Merry!
What?
Shit!
This boat is fast!
ENERU!!
Go up on board boats!
The sky becomes completely black!
That there
does it have?
It is quickly necessary to leave.
Chief…
Aisa is always over there!
It did not return yet?
Aisa is an intelligent girl.
Let us hope that it is
with one of the warriors.
Yes.
Go! Made quickly!
Captain!
If we do not use
boats on the quay,
there will not be enough
of place for all!
It would be too long to reach them…
You!
Use emergency Dials
to create a river!
Yes, Chief!
You all, please! You must join Cloud End on bank of the cloud…
and to flee towards
Blue sea immediately!
Eneru God with the intention
to destroy this country!
While remaining here, NONE
will not survive us!
Since six years,
over all, we know that Eneru…
the capacity of us has
to bring despair!
And this time, it is for soon!
What good is it to await a miracle?!
Before requesting,
before closing the eyes on reality,
we must initially make
what is in our capacity!
We cannot hide us
behind its victims to survive!
If we do not do anything,
it does not matter with which it fault,
we will have lost our lives!
Now,
you must be solved
to leave this country!
How much inhabitants left?!
Almost half.
Do not let them take luggage!
Evacuate the island all
whole towards the sea!
Yes, Chief!
Wait!
Each one must pay the tax of unloading of 2.000.000 000 of Extols before leaving!
Amazon-san!
You must flee you too!
Join Cloud End
as quickly as possible!
This country…
will be destroyed!!
Oh, the wind stopped.
Will run! Will run!
The hour came.
And now, the official reception.
It is time to start.
[Note:God of the thunder of
aboriginals of central Australia]
You move away from the island!
You do not turn over!
The flashes are increasingly large!
They attack also the quay!
Go on the west coast of the beach!
As quickly as possible!
There remain still boats!
Flee towards the West!
As quickly as possible!
Drop your luggage!
Chief!
We must make you go up on board!
Yes.
Large Karugara Warrior!
Please, protects to us all!
These flashes are enormous!
If one remains there, it will not remain of
us that ash in the sky!
The guy, turn over to the boat!
I will seek Luffy
and I catch up with you!
O-Ok! Included/understood!
Quickly, Robin!
It is necessary to find a means of
to carry to the boat!
Wiper!
Mister Epéiste!
Odd Papi!
Brilliant, you are awaked!
He, one does not have any more it
time! You can walk?
Did Eneru start?
We dispatch.
There are not only us
let us can make here.
Wiper…
Even Luffy cannot anything against
an enemy who can fly!
I must reach it before
total disappearance of this country!
It is necessary to flee from here!
Splendid!
Do not believe to draw you like that,
Eneru!