USOPP HAMMER!
USOPP WAGOMU!
(Rubberband!)
HISSATSU KAEN BOSHI!
(Ultimate Fiery Flaming Star!)
USOPP HAMMER!
I win...
To kill humans like you...
I don't need to do it myself... just
a little water is all it takes.
That's the difference between
you humans and us mermen.
Nami-aneki!
Yo, Nami.
I was just giving some loser pirates
a demonstration of our power.
What brings you here?
I'm here... to kill you.
LUFFY'S BEST!
NAMI'S COURAGE AND THE STRAW HAT
Here to...
kill me?
You still haven't given up.
How many times have you tried to
kill me, these past eight years?
Murder, poison, assault.
Has it ever worked?
You should know better than anyone else, that
we can't be killed by you humans so easily.
Listen, you can never kill me.
And you can never run away from me.
Nami.
You'll remain as my cartographer.
Besides, you know I've been good to you.
I really hope that you'll continue
the map-making, if possible.
So, how does this sound?
Because of what's happened, normally
I'd kill all of these people, except you.
But, if you make a decision now
to return to the Arlong Pirates,
and continue to draw maps for me...
I'll spare the people of Cocoyashi.
But these guys won't be spared.
They were too foolish.
So, it's your choice.
If you choose me, the people
of your village will be safe.
Or you could choose to fight
against me with these fools.
But, these guys you hope to count on
are in such bad shape right now...
I don't think there's any way to
avoid this ending in tragedy.
Nami.
Are you my nakama,
Or are you theirs?
No way...
If I say I'm Luffy's nakama, everyone will be killed.
If I go back to Arlong, then everyone
from the vllage will be safe...
It's all up to me... Everyone's fate...
You bastard!
No matter what your say, you just want to keep her!
But!
Help me...
DAMN RIGHT!!
I can't doubt what he said!
Everyone, I'm sorry!
Will you die with me?
YOSHA!!
Let's go!
So, you wish to be slaughtered.
Plea- please, please...!
Live! Live! Live! Live! Live!
What's that?
There he is...
All that's left is for me to take
care of the block on his feet.
What?
I get it now.
Can it be?
Luffy-aniki!!
Hey kid, hang on!
Thirty seconds.
I can't hold on any longer than that.
Zoro...
That's more than enough!
I don't remember a fountain there.
Could it be that rubber bastard?
That's not what you should be
worried about right now...
You half-fish bastard!
Didn't I tell you never to say that word again?
Looks like you're about finished, Zoro!
If I can just break that block, then he'll be free.
Luffy...
You're the only one who can take him out now!
Those with the power of the Devil's Fruit
lose all strength when they're in the sea.
He should be dead by now.
If he's still alive...
Then someone must've been messing
around with my little game.
Hey! Are you okay! Thank God!
Hah... huh?!
What? What is it?
Ossan, where's your pinwheel?
It was so freakin' cool.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU? THIS ISN'T THE TIME!
Messing up your game?
I thought it was messed up to begin with, bastard.
Whatever, I'll find out who's doing it.
Move.
TAMAGO BOSHI!
(Egg Star!)
I've got you covered, Zoro!
Usopp-aniki! Are you alright?
How brave! He's facing him without fear!
Oh yeah! I fight with no fear!
Why are you over THERE?!
Usopp!
Hey Nami, check it out!
One of their guys, one of 'em was finished
off by ME! Me, of all people!
A guy with a face like this...
These mermen are NOTHING!
Chew! You bastard...
You betcha!
My appearance signals the climax of this battle!
Get ready for the big finale!
Hey... Can't you break it by yourself?
Nope. No way.
I'm totally powerless right now.
Come on... come on, come on!
Oh! It's our Cook-aniki!
I'm not sure what's going on underwater,
but right now, whatever Cook-aniki's
doing is crucial...
Zoro-aniki! Stand fast to stop Arlong!
Yosh! Just stop Arlong from getting
into the water, right?
I can handle that.
Not a chance, you bastards!
Hey ARLONG! Over here, dork!
Usopp-aniki!
He's so brave!
USOPP WAGOMU!
You dare to stand in my way?
You want to be the first to die, Roronoa Zoro?
Now! Go, Zoro!
Hey! What're you trying to do?
I will not die.
Allow me to break that ugly nose you love so dearly!
Fool...
I love it because it's unbreakable.
If you weren't hurt so badly, you might've
given it a bruise or a scratch.
Aniki...
Look, over there!
Ah! That octopus jerk woke up!
Huh? What's he doing?
Crap! I thought a rubber band was coming!
WHAT THE HELL?!
WHAAAT?!
Of course, I was aiming for him!
Didn't you shout, ''ARLONG?''
Octopus...
Roronoa Zoro! I won't let you get away with this!
Watch how I kill your nakama in the water!
Don't get frustrated, you'll all be dead soon enough.
ANIKIIII!!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Nami-san's Onee-sama, leave the rest to me!
A merman!
Watch out, please, Onee-sama.
I'll take care of that with a single kick!
The Octopus!
TAKOYAKI PUNCH!
ONEE-SAMA!!
ZORO!!!
Done already? How boring.
By the way, what's with this huge bandage?
Did you fall somewhere or something?
Holy shit, what's with this wound...?
How can he still be living with this body?
How can he still stand?
What's with the look on his face?
Is this the look of a dying man?
No doubt.
He HAS to die. I have to do it right now.
If you take it easy, the wounds won't open...
That's all you have to say?
You think you're funny, don't you?
I didn't mean me. I meant the octopus guy.
What?
I told you before.
We've already won this game.
SHIT.
That had me scared!
This is all your fault! You had
to go complicate things!
Get outta here, you piece of shit!
Go beat the hell out of that freakin' shark's ass!!
Is it coming, kid?
Yeaaah!!!
I'm BAAACK!!
Rubber boy!
Luffy-aniki!!
Luffy!
That rubber bastard...
You're late, idiot.
Zoro!
Hey, stop it!
You're not gonna...
SWITCH!!!
YOU MORON!!
GOMU GOMU NO KANE!
(Bell!)
MUCHI!
(Whip!)
GOMU GOMU NO!
PISTOLET!
GATLING GUN!
TAKE THAT!!!
Done!
No way...
Did you think that'd do anything?
Not a single scratch?!
Nope. Just warmin' up.
I'll... kill him!
What's wrong with you, you pathetic scum?
I think you would have been happier
sleeping at the bottom of the ocean.
No, actually, I'm pretty thankful
to have been rescued.
Because then you wouldn't have
to see how angry I am.
To see my brethren killed by your lame pals...
Soon enough, you're going to be
wishing you had died earlier.
Luffy-aniki is going to be all right, isn't he?
All of his attacks, did no damage!
More importantly, where did Zoro-aniki land?
Go, Luffy! I've got your back covered!
I don't think that'll help!
If he loses, you're all gonna die, aren't you?
So it seems.
And then, East Blue will be done for, too.
Do you know what the difference
is between me and you?
Noses.
Chins?
Is Aniki... trying to joke around with him?
No, I'm afraid he's quite serious.
Oh, the webs!
It's our very race!
That idiot, he'll bite off his own tongue!
His teeth must be...
He bit the column to pieces!
Scary!
Holy shit, what is this guy?
Those teeth... they wouldn't just scar
him if he were toget bitten...
It'd go through and break his bones, too!
Behold.
This is the true power of mermen.
The Heavens have made a distinction between us.
The Heavens only gave you humans
enough strength to exist below us.
You are inferior animals!
From the very moment we were
born, everything was different.
I'll show you just how different we really are.
Sure, show me.
But there's no way in hell I'll lose to you fish-people.
Because I'm...
The man who'll become the Pirate King!