Courrage Coby!
The newspaper of Coby and Helmeppo
The wind again stopped…
One is in a hurry to join Little Garden,
but one will have to make another pause.
While one is wedged here,
time passes…
Do not worry you.
I know that you must go to Arabasta as quickly as possible.
Owl! Let us fish!
Does He, somebody know what arrived at the soft foods?
Soft foods?
Oh, these things in the bucket, I ate them.
You puffed out them?
They was maggots!
Good Ah?
They were bloody good.
Be not supposed to you to puff out them!
What will one make now that you ate all the soft foods?
One will be able to fish more!
One has only to take that.
ONE CANNOT SIN WITH CA!
Oh. They is not good?
And with that?
Ouais, that can go.
Wait!
Wait, return!
CRETINS! SIT YOU AND CLOSE IT!!
You can the guy
YOU TO CALM ONE SECOND?
What doesn't go?
Ah! Nami-San is so beautiful when she is irritated!
Good blood.
It is odd.
It is worth 30 million Berrys of reward.
I expected that it is a little more anxious.
Eh well, I suppose that you did not imagine that.
But if you make the account of all the villains whom it overcame:
the tyrant with comes up of iron of East Blue, Arlong the man-fish,
the admiral of a whole armada of pirates, Gift Krieg,
and although nobody is with the current, the infamous swindler,
The Captain Pirates Kuro.
And it is not all!
There was this bastard Navy which held up one crowned axe in the place of its hand.
Ah! Morgan “the logger”.
Morgan “the logger”?
I heard of him.
It was a Captain of Marine dreaded in any East Blue for its cruelty.
You beat somebody of as extremely as him?
Oh, the old man with the axe?
Ah yes, I wonder what becomes the guy who was with him.
I wonder whether it is always in this camp of Navy…
A guy?
Ouais.
It is Coby, its name.
It is my pal.
Lieutenant.
We are ready to leave.
Very well.
How all the boats weigh the anchor!
With your orders!
Luffy-San, did you succeed?
It is me!
It is Coby!
Since this day when our ways separated,
I worked hard.
The way was strewn with obstacles, but
I finally achieved my dream to become Naval officer!
Morgan captain?
COBY…
You ES READY TO DIE, COBY?
Luffy-San!
Yo!
Coby.
They is so marvellous!
I… dreamed!
What?
Do not make the mariole with me, cretin!
Ca is enough!
Silence!
The farm and sleep, stunned!
Blegarde sle kle tlu fléé ace!
Allette tles clonnelies!
However, Luffy-San…
I work in the Navy now.
Zatsuyou = Drudgeries - the low level of the hierarchy of the Navy
The son of the Captain Morgan, Helmeppo-San, is also assigned Zatsuyou like me.
He, stops rêvasser.
Ouais…
He Zatsuyou, is ensured to clean the panes well.
Yes!
And do not forget to leave the dustbins.
Hein? And the dinner then?
I suppose that you will not have finished before the dinner.
After having finished here.
I will burst hunger…
Helmeppo-San!
Helmeppo! Coby!
One allowed you to enlist in the Navy without no qualification,
in the special condition which you would work like Zatsuyou.
As if it were them which had enlisted us…
Yes, of course Sirs!
I will do all that I can!
Find to me anything to make!
Very well, as long as you included/understood.
You with the task hang!
Yes, Sirs!
You can count on me!
We will make even the laundry of everyone!
LARGE CRETIN!!
Hein?
Good blood, why you go voluntary for more work?
But it is what us, Zatsuyou, are supposed to do.
And now, with the job.
Us?
If it is what you think, make the drudgeries all alone!
1,2,3,4!
He… Ca fears.
This blasted Coby.
Why I must be Zatsuyou, good blood?
So only I could return at that time…
Helmeppo-Sama, your cocoa.
He! Try you to burn me?
Afflicted, excuse me!
With which believe you to speak?
I am the Large Captain of Navy,
the single son of Morgan,
Helmeppo-Sama, included/understood?
Yes, Helmeppo-Sama!
Ahh, the things were better front.
Shit.
But now I am wedged here.
And it is the fault of Straw hat!
It took from Papa his rank of Captain of the Navy.
1,2,3,4!
It is entirely its fault.
All that arrived to me, it is by the fault of this foutu Straw hat!
Helmeppo-San?
What? I said to you of step to touch me!
I am afflicted, as you are my friend,
I wanted to ask you something.
Friend?
Who is friendly with you?
Are Eh well, we both Zatsuyou, not true?
I am not the type of man to remain wedged here like Zatsuyou.
This asshole of Straw hat.
You cannot put all that arrived to you on the back of Luffy-San.
To blame someone else for his faults will not change anything.
You do not believe that they are there the signs of somebody of weak?
What?
Helmeppo-San, for a very long time, you made use of the capacity of your father to live.
But, now you must go from before all alone!
Let us follow our dreams of all our forces!
You…
I have a dream.
One day I will become a Naval officer,
and I will fight the good-for-nothings!
How can you believe in a similar trick?
A p' tit snotty-nosed kid like you,
to become a Naval officer?
Ca will be able to never arrive!
Of course how that will be able!
After having seen how Luffy-San carried out its life, I made my choice!
I will become the Lord of the Pirates.
It is what I chose, therefore that done anything if I must die about it.
This is why, I want to be like Luffy-San and to risk my life for my ambition!!
Then?
Why not do it together?
Do not joke with me!
Me, to cooperate with you?
Since when became to you if hefty man?
There is nothing to include/understand on the rotted lifestyle of Straw hat!
I will not let myself insult Luffy-San!
All that I said was true!
Ca gives me still more desire for vomitting!
Helmeppo-San, opens the eyes!
You ace not of natures to be given me!
Good blood!
Open!
What?
Your eyes!
What do they make up there?
Stop that!
What is there? What does it occur?
Helmeppo-San!
Mister! The two Zatsuyou boys fight on the roof!
What do you wait?
Dispatch you to stop them.
YOU TWO!!!
One is sorry!!
Hein? It is you who caused this explosion?
Did the Navy return you?
Thank you.
Not, one succeeded in saving our skin.
One will simply not be paid for the 50 years to come.
One would have better done to be returned.
Good courage to both.
Good! Look at that!
Luffy with the Straw hat causes a riot with Loguetown!
He manages to slip between the fingers of the Smoker Captain!
Luffy-San!
Ca means that Luffy-San…
grand Line reached!
It took the first step in
the achievement of its dream!
Everyone with the guard with you!
I now will summarize you the details of our mission.
Look at!
To look at what?
Dad!
The ex-Captain of Navy, Morgan.
Shown to have misused its military position and to have made suffer its fellow-citizens,
he will be transported to the general headquarter of the Navy to face the Court-martial.
Our duty is to be used as escort and to deliver it to the guard of the Vice Admiral Garp.
I am the Captain of Navy, Morgan “the logger”!
You incline in front of me!
I can nothing make,
neither for the Cour martiale nor anything else.
I will have just to let it leave.
I suppose that it has what it deserves.
You know?
I respected my father.
My father was…
what I wanted to be.
But…
It went too far, hein?
Shit.
Why?
Do He, you think that my father will be carried out?
Eh well, I…
Possible that I can nothing change to what occurs.
Which father…
Helmeppo-San…
Everyone on the bridge!
Keep with you!
Garp…
It is the Vice Admiral Garp.
Garp the Terrible one!
This man is the Vice Admiral of the General headquarter of the Navy, Garp the Terrible one.
The man who sailed on Grand Line!
A hero of the seas!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Thank you to be come in person.
We entrust Morgan to you.
Not, you cannot, Helmeppo-San!
Vice Admiral Garp?
Stop!
VICE ADMIRAL GARP!
THE FARM!
I hear you.
I have not slept for 5 days.
We wish you good luck in your mission!
I reached a new record of eaten donuts.
Hein?
Not to sleep will not stop me,
I am with more than 842.
But I would prick a p' tit nap well now.
Old croûton nut.
MORGAN!
The Vice Admiral Garp represents the authority of the General headquarter of the Navy!
Do He old croûton, you do it dead?
Not a gesture!
If somebody moves the least muscle, I reduce this Zatsuyou in parts!
Dad!
Please, made not that!
Helmeppo-San is your son!
My son?
I do not need this shit!
I want just my freedom!
And to have it, I can put an end to his life in a blood bath!
Dad…
HELP me!!
Too much late, band of larvae!
Helmeppo-San!
Prepare you to draw.
Charge the gun! Aim!
Target:16° on the right - Distance 8263.
Loans?
Please, wait!
What does it make?
You will be made kill!
Go down from there!
Please, do not draw!
My friend…
My friend is on this boat!!
Release.
Not question!
Then I will kill you.
Stop, Zatsuyou!
You go too far!
NOT! Helmeppo-San is my…
my…
MY FRIEND!
Bandage imbeciles. They fight between them.
Your career is finished.
I will prefer returned being to give up my friend!
Please! Allow me to catch up with them!
Cretin!
Return!
You do not have any chance to catch up with them!
Let leave it.
It is a simple idiot…
or…
Your orders, Mister?
With all this foutu din, you awoke me.
Vice Admiral Garp!
It was thought that you had died!
Hein? Was somebody killed?
I had to miss that while I slept…
Where is the victim?
It was me?
I am free!
Look at!
The world will be prosternera again in front of me!
Today mark the first day of the new Kingdom of Morgan!
Now, mets the course in the west!
What do you make?
I asked you to change course.
Not question!
I cannot any more support it!
It protected us from his life!
It knew that if it were returned, its dream would fall to water!
And in spite of that, it protected us.
Even me!
Dad, I will stop you!
Come!
What a cretin you make!
With which believe you to be addressed, hein?
What can make an useless ver de terre like you against me?
I suppose that I will have to reward you for your obedience.
Now, it closes!
Your mouth!
Salt old!
Good blood!
Learn your place,
poor wretch insect.
I will not become your slave!
I am the only one to decide how I must live!
Be not made illusions!
What can make a poor wretch larva like you all alone?
He is not alone!
You!
Morgan!
Return without making stories!
As a soldier of the Navy, I put to you with the stops!
Pitiful! Pitiful! Pitiful!
It does not matter how much larvae as you will present yourselves!
If you oppose me,
I will kill you all!
I am afflicted, all that because you wanted to save me.
About what you do speak?
One is friendly, not truth?
Coby…
And I already made my decision…
I will live to carry out my dream!
And to carry it out, I will fight!
I will fight…
If I die by beating me, that suits me.
You want to die so much?
I do not want to die!
Not before becoming Naval officer!
But…
if…
if I must die…
If that arrives…
If that arrives,
then I will die by beating me!!
The recreation is finished.
Ah! Coby!
Good blood! Shit!
Salt dumb!
Coby coward!
Coby!
Insects as you are not even worth the sorrow to be killed.
Request so that one is re-examined never again!
Morgan!
I let to you escape, this time!
But one day,
our ways will cross again,
and this day, I will capture you!
Prepare!
It arrived because of my lack of vigilance.
We are also guilty to have allowed the prisoner to escape.
We beseech your forgiveness!
For their actions, these deux-là will be returned definitively.
Which despairing duet.
It does not matter where I go,
I must take my responsabilities.
If I give up you with your fate,
you will cause only problems.
I do not have the choice.
Come with me to the General headquarter from the Navy.
Vice Admiral?
You will take them with you?
At the General headquarter of the Navy?
I cannot?
If… Of course that you can.
If you do not want to you two,
you can leave now.
No complaint will be retained against you for what occurred here.
Is necessary to as say, as it was one day rather special.
And thus we left for the place where Luffy-San was:
large sea…
Sea known under the name of Large Line.
I will re-examine it certainly a day!