End of anger!
To cross Red Line!
A cemetery of dragons…
Not…
Not!!
Ryuji said to me that if it turned over to the nest of the dragons, it would be better!
That cannot be a cemetery!
Apis…
Ryuji was stray Sennenryu.
Luffy?
During 1000 years, it was all alone.
But then Apis became his friend.
Apart from the 1000 years that he lived,
it is the time passed with you Apis that he cherished more in the world.
Luffy… You can include/understand what the dragons say?
About.
Do not tell conneries.
But, I know what he said!
Liar.
Ryuji, liar…
It is a nest of dragons.
The nest of the dragons was found,
then opens the eyes!
Speak to me!
You will be better!
Ryuji did not lie.
He said that Sennenryu was to turn over to the nest of the dragons every 1000 years
to reappear.
Ryuji would be…
Look at over there!
A Sennenryu baby!
Out of my way!!!!
Be to you you still there?
Ouais.
A little more and I would have drowned.
Admire.
This place is splendid.
Isn't this marvellous?
It is the source of the elixir of youth…
Ryukotsu!
But with of Sennenryu calcified,
it is impossible to make an elixir.
Indeed.
But you forget the herd living of Ryukotsu which is there.
By the way,
I am tired of this useless battle.
Why this treasure would not be divided?
Not question!
You do not wish the eternal life?
I am not interested.
Liar!!!
There is not only one man who is not frightened by death!
And for you and me which ate a Fruit of the Demon,
the border is very thin of this world with demise!
It is impossible that you would not be frightened by death!
It is what you believe…
But if this type is exposed there,
he will die with the smile with the lips.
I see.
Then very well!
You can sit down there and look at,
while I only assert Ryukotsu for me!
Not!
Remain in your place, small plague!
Apis!
Usopp!
Would not be so carefree, Apis!
I owe it even if it is imprudent!
It is a place crowned for Sennenryu!
I will protect this place…
for always!!!!!
You want to always prevent me?
Then you all will die here.
Luffy!
It is with me.
But, Luffy!
I promised.
I cannot about it any more?
Would not be if defaitist!
Our goal yet was not achieved!
One will go to the nest of the dragons, not truth?
I do not want to hear any more of “I cannot about it any more”!
You know that I am right.
You do not have to worry for Apis!
It is all that you can do, man-rubber band?
And now,
ultimate technique of the kamaitachi.
It does not matter where you will hide,
you will not be able to escape from it.
I wonder whether you will be able to support it.
It is foutu.
Is Luffy in danger?
Luffy…
I will not flee to hide!
Poor idiot!
I will cut you of pieces!
It is what it…
and…
I gained!
One succeeded!!
It is what all that?
They really exist?
Then it was not a legend?
I suppose that it will be réengloutir again like before.
When will that occur, Sennenryu will set out again, hein?
This Sennenryu baby will go elsewhere also, I suppose…
Then, would you like to pass to the house to taste my famous butaman?
Oh, one would have really liked,
but one must refuse.
We are pressed a little, you see.
One is it?
I wanted to test…
Thank you for the proposal, but one must leave.
Oh, as it is damage.
That would have taken three days to prepare them.
And meanwhile, I would have told you the history of the royalty of Lost Island.
Oh, one already heard this history.
Super!
Full sail towards Large Line!
Do Apis, you want to come?
I spent much pleasant moments with you the guy, I would like
but I must remain here on this island.
I want to learn some a little more on our habits with Grand-Père Bokuden.
And just like our ancestors who protected Sennenryu,
I will protect the nest from the dragons.
I will wait the day when the babies dragons will turn over on the island.
Wait one minute…
The next time they will return in…
It would not be in 1000 years?
Do not say anything which could ruin its dreams.
I know that I will not be able to see the babies dragons when they will grow,
but my children, or their children will be able.
And we will protect this island forever!
You are odd!
You them guy you made odd tricks the every day, not truth?
It is true?
Goodbye, Apis!
Apis! Do not forget me!
The honest warrior of the seas, Usopp-Sama!
Bye Bye!
Everyone!
Made attention with you!!
You too! Make attention with you, Apis!
Bye!
Bye Bye!
You believe that Apis will go well all alone?
Apis will manage.
It is perhaps small,
but it is crafty one and courageous.
She will go well.
You are right, Nami-San.
It is perfect.
Ouais.
Is Apis our friend, not true?
It is certain.
You did not want to leave with them, Apis?
If I had left with them, I should have followed their road.
Out, there are things which I want to make here!
I am about to do something of incredible.
If I had not met Luffy and his crew,
I would never have thought that I could have protected this island.
I would have even thought that to protect it was impossible.
However when Luffy and its crew took Ryuji with them to seek it,
they never believed that impossible.
If you really believe in your convictions and that you fight until the end,
you can achieve anything.
It is that which they taught me.
They said that to help their friends they put all their heart at it.
They risk their lives for that.
And now, I am me also become their friend!
Then I will give all that I have!
He fell asleep…
He, could you help me to achieve my dreams?
Thank you!
Allons-y!
While speaking about that, if you intend to protect Lost Island,
you will need to learn from the things on our ancestors.
Let us start with the first king.
That is enough, I do not need to hear it!
Apis, return by here!
Stop!!
Wait! You must listen to me.
Nooooonnnnn!!!!
Apis!
Nami-San!
With the report/ratio my love!
I see enormous clouds mortals right in front of,
with a storm right in lower part.
I suppose that we returned on our road.
We should see Red Line soon.
One goes finally worms Grand Line!
He, Sanji!
One goes there!
Stop that!
Afflicted…
Zoro!
But…
One goes there!
is the chart correct?
Stop that!!
Look at that.
I had heard rumors,
but it is also written here on the chart.
If it is true, then the entry of Large Line is a mountain.
A mountain?
You want to say that one will run up against a mountain?
Good blood…
I also thought that it was madness, but…
there are channels drawn along the wall of the mountain.
That means that one must climb it.
That seems amusing!
About what you do speak?
Even if there are channels,
it is impossible for a boat to climb a mountain.
But it is what the chart says.
Of course!
It is impossible that Nami-San is mistaken!
You stole the chart in Buggy, not true?
You have really confidence?
Zorooo!
I with this blasted rudder helps!
Sanji-Kun, Usopp, do you want will help?
I do not manage to think with this din.
Sanji, come to help me!
Yes, Nami-San!
One goes there!
What?
The current is too much strong!
Do Usopp, repeat to me that?
I said that the current is too much strong!
The current…
I included/understood!
Included/understood what?
One must really climb the mountain.
You did not already say that?
Look by here.
Listen.
There is no doubt, the “light which us guide” is indicated here.
Here on Red Line, Mountain Reverse.
He! I am supposed to do what here?
You see the channel here?
If a high tension current coming from one of the quatres oceans runs out towards this mountain,
the current quatres will climb the mountain, will meet at the top
and will run out directly in bottom towards Grand Line.
After Reverse Mountain “Winter Island is”,
the currents which enter in collision with Red Line circulate of bottom towards the surface of the ocean.
If we do not manage to enter the channel,
the Vogue-Merry will be crashed to pieces on Red Line
and the boat will be destroyed.
There will remain nothing any more but remains on the ocean.
Included/understood?
I see!
Then it is a Mysterious Mountain, it is that?
I suspected well that you would not have included/understood anything.
In any case, this boat follows already one of these currents.
Thus if one manages to preserve this direction,
one will be able to succeed in assembling Reverse Mountain intact.
Nami-San, you are incredible!
I never heard that.
Boats which climb mountains.
I heard something.
On the Mysterious Mountain?
Not.
Only that half of those which tried to return on Grand Line died about it.
Then I know that it will not be easy to return there.
Sanji-Kun, the sail please!
Immediately, Nami-San!
Luffy, moves your bottom from here!
He!
I can see Reverse Montain!
What?
It is immense!
The entry towards Large Line.
Then it is Red Line, hein?
You cannot even see the top beyond the clouds!!
One will be made aspire!!
Seize the rudder!
Let make me!
We have it!
N-Nami!
Where is the entry?
If one quickly does not change a course, one will sink right in cliff!
This crack in cliff…
Nami, which do we have to make?
Maintain the course!
Be sure for you?
Do it!
Is Nami, it the entry of the channel?
Perhaps…
Unthinkable…
Water climbs really the mountain.
Do you ensure that one passes between these gates, Ok?
If it is not the case,
the boat will be tiny room of pieces!
We derive!
More towards the line!
On the right, on the right!
On the right?
Ok, with starboard all!
The rudder!!!
Luffy!!
My hand catches!
One succeeded!!!!
And now, straight until the top!
Super!
He, I want to see that too!
Incredible!
Dirty bastard!
The type of the fruit of Okama…
Bastard, you are still in life?
You never give up?
The farm!
You cross me for the last time…
Because of you my dream to obtain from Ryukotsu is foutu!
But I will not let that finish like that!!
I will have at least the pleasure of empocher the 30.000.000
Go maintaining!
What do we have to make?
If it uses its kamaitachi here,
one cannot know what it will cut!
There is no place where to go…
Well!
Not only one among you cannot pose the little finger on me!
Ah! Of Ryukotsu!
Bye Bye!
Oh! One did not think of that!
Now that it is an anvil,
it will be able to annoy us never again!
Even if it could swim,
the current is agitated too much!
That it is my Nami-San!
One arrived to the clouds!
Incredible!!
One is above the clouds!
Look at!
The top of the mountain!
It is the top!
Yahoo!!
Mihawk is here…
Readier of All Blue…
A chart supplements…
To prove that I am the bravest pirate…
I can see it,
the largest ocean of the world…
Large Line!
And some share at the horizon,
One Piece awaits us!
Ahead!!!