It is not an exit!
It IS an ENTRY!
It IS the CELESTIAL ISLAND!!!
Heso.
Yes, excuse me!
I stop immediately!
Is nobody wounded?
AND YOU THEN?!
It is not easy to take in hand!
Nami-san! You are the best!!
Oh my god! Here are which is surprising!
I have evil to believe my eyes of them!
How can it control this trick?!
He!
Where did Nami-san pass?
Father, goes it
to leave itself there?
Yes, Conis-san… I
am not quiet either.
What?
What? Does Y' have a problem?
It is in Skypiea a prohibited necessary where,
no matter what it arrives, no one should not penetrate.
One should never put the feet at it…
And why that?
It is a crowned ground.
A crowned ground?
This ground is called…
[Note:Upper Yard =
The higher garden]
The Field of God, “Upper Yard”.
The prohibited ground sacree! The Field
of God and the Celestial Judgment!
God saw over there?!
Where one never must
to put the feet?!
Yes.
Euh, by “God”, you
please say God?
Does God live on the celestial island?
Yes. Skypiea is its Field, it is
directed by Very Powerful God, Eneru.
Very Powerful God?
Eneru God knows absolutely all
from what occurs in this world.
Absolutely all?!
It observes us, all the time.
Q-what?! All the time?!
Even now?
Of course.
Hein?! It observes us
in this exact moment?!
Pfff… God?
Don't Zoro, you believe in a God?
I know anything of it. That it
exist or not, I don't care.
I am never interested there.
But good, I do not have anything
against those which believe in it.
Therefore, this God who
live in Upper Yard…
You have already
considering, Conis-chan?
Not! I never saw it!
We cannot go in Upper Yard.
Never…
Crowned ground, Upper
Yard, is prohibited.
There is thus a ground
firm on the celestial island…
It is true all that?
A place where it is necessary especially
not to put the feet, hein?
He, Luffy!
With what are to you in the train
to think there, brothel?!
Listen to what it is
saying to us!
“One cannot go there” means only you
do not have ABSOLUTELY to go over there, Luffy!
It is true?
A place where it is necessary especially
not to put the feet, hein?
It is well that? A place where it is necessary
especially not to put the feet, hein?
There it will want to go, it is sure…
But even if one should not go there,
Will God forgive us not if it is done?
He is sympathetic, not?
Not… enfreindre a rule
of God is a sacrilege.
Good Ah? Ben so much worse then.
He will go there even if
God does not forgive him!
But which are the consequences if
one enters this Upper prohibited Yard?
E-and well…
And well?
We think that one
does not return alive from there.
O it does not return alive from there?!
V have you fear for
Isn't Nami-san?
Let us request so that it
too much does not approach Upper Yard!
NAMI-SWAAAN!
One goes there! One will seek Nami!
DO NOT MOVE! ONE COMES TO SEEK YOU!
You really count
to go to seek Nami?!
NAMI-SWAAAN!!
All that you want is to go
at the place prohibited, not true?!
NAMI-SWAAAN!!!
What?
These trees are immense…
I never saw anything of tel.
From how much centuries are it old?
They all are so much…
One does not even see the summit of it!
I am sure.
A treasure is certainly…
… some share by there!
It is within reach!
There is somebody here.
One is there almost! Grouille!
Ca came from there.
He, Luffy! Allons-y!
One second. I eat initially.
And if something arrived at Nami-san
while are to you eating?!
Forget puffs out it! One
returns quickly in any case.
Go what. One second…
Conis-chan, one can await it
like that all the day.
Said to us just how
us to return in Upper Yard!
But…
One is not sure that it
that is to say really gone over there…
And then…
One should not especially attract oneself
the anger of Eneru God.
Eneru God with the alarming air…
Eneru God…
God, hein?
It would be said… that it
nobody on board has there.
Traces of claws…
They were attacked
by something?
I am sure!
A treasure is certainly…
some share by there!
An extraordinary treasure is here!
It is within reach!
I feel it!
L it shell spoke!
We are there almost!
Grouille!
It is a shell, not? It cannot
not there to have somebody inside…
Listen, if one keeps this newspaper,
one day it will have value!
This shell… can
to record the voices.
Not! I want to set out again!
J-J' am afraid. I feel it…
The anger of God!
It is what this noise?
It is…
God!
They were killed…
By God…
I should return. They is dangerous.
It is to better move away
as much as possible from here.
The Help!!
Go! Hoist the veils!
Cape on the place where it is necessary
especially not to put the feet!
Ah, excuse me! For the moment,
the wind comes from opposite!
With this wind, you will spend a time
considerable to reach Upper Yard!
All my excuses!
What?!
Considerable?!
Ca would go more quickly if your boat
used the energy of Dials.
I am sorry.
“Considerable” wants
to say how long?
I do not know… Until
what the wind turns…
It is thus that? Considerable, hein?
Nami is surely in danger without
large Usopp-sama to help it…
Doesn't Papi, y' have a faster means?
If one grouille not,
Nami will be of return!
But if y' does not have wind, one cannot…
He, Luffy! You thought
thus with that since the beginning!
About what you do speak?
Salt lying…
Dumb…
He is with me!
It is what that?
I hear noise.
What is this…?
Give up!
Speak for you! It
with me that one is!
Out of my way!
You even!
Q - What
happens…?
This forest is well agitated.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
A place was finally found dangerous where to go! I will not wait until the wind changes direction!
He, Luffy! Do not say to me that it is…
… the Waver old man very broken!
It left!
What a cretin!
You see! You do not want to listen to me?!
Ahh… I run…
What does one make? He runs again.
Let us leave it!
Brothel, be to you really
heavy with your conneries.
It is thus that your Waver old man?
It, isn't this is really worn?
One found it in the sea of in lower part.
If that does not disturb you
not, do I can examine it?
I can surely repair it.
You can repair it, papi?
I am engineer into Dialo-nautical.
Serious? Quickly then…
… it repairs!!!
Eneru…!
It is my prey!
Did Ah ouais? You want
what one fights for him?
I do not see there an objection.
It is perfect to kill time!
What unimportant remarks!
You will be used as meal with my dog!
What a spectacle!
A duel of weak weaklings!
It is you the weakling!
Q-what?!
What?!
He! I helps!
Take me along with you!
To take you along with me?
But there is only one place!
I from another island
celestial to seek a treasure!
But it does not matter!
I beg you!
I do not know if it will go…
I do not know!
I will go up even if I must kill you!
A guerilla!
D-God…
Shit…!
Eneru?!
How oses you to touch in Vearth?!
The Hydroones, quickly!
Extinguish this fire!
The Island of the Angels
Lovely Street
Company, greet!
Heso!
Organizes of Skypiea
- White Berets McKinley Captain
Everyone, heso!
They are the White Berets.
It occurred something?
General advertisement, be on your guards!
Today, several people have
penetrated illegally in Angel Beach!
It would seem that they are seven!
The White Berets are in alarm
maximum and seek these criminals!
If you are vigilant
locate somebody of suspect!
Be vigilant!
You did not have the impression
what it spoke with somebody?
A guerilla. He is
party, moreover.
He, Ho!
Make conceal this foutu dog!
It had to beseech its pity.
But… why Eneru-sama
does it intervene itself?
What good is it to have sent to us?
Ca wants to say that time was past.
Was time past?
The new clandestine ones
have just arrived.
Still?
A crew of seven individuals coming from
Blue sea at summer announced by the Amazon old woman.
Seven individuals coming from the Blue Sea…
He speaks about us?!
“Of clandestine”?
You discharge tax of immigration of 1
Billion Extols each one and go your way!
It is the payment.
It is because one does not have
paid the tax of immigration?
Oh not!
Types of this boat…
And the man of presently…
The clandestine ones…
But then, we will undergo
same fate us too?
Pas la pains to disturb us
for seven people only.
Moreover, seven it is not
divisible by four.
What occurs, brothel?
Who are they?
It is what this place?!
I must quickly return
and to prevent the others!
This place is dangerous!
How you find, Usopp? Look at!
Mine also is ready!
Look at to me that! My speciality
they is the spit portraits!
Incredible!
The spit portrait of which exactly?!
This trick…
… I will explode it!
Brothel! It is the portrait
spit of anybody, Long Conk!
Not! Stop! What a horrible thing!
You can repair it?
I never saw this model before.
Try to repair it, please!
Afflicted, if I do not examine it
sufficient, I will not be able.
In any case, I count on you.
I will try to dismount it.
Papi… It is which these?
Suspect boat! Do not move any more!
It is which these?
Why they crawl
like that towards us?
No idea!
It is… surely of the perverts.
Hein?! It is thus that a pervert…
Company, halt!
Heso!
Hello. Heso.
Brothel, but of what
you speak, the guy?!
Who are they?
Of the perverts.
You are the seven clandestine ones
originating in the Blue Sea, isn't this?
We are here for you
to inflict the Celestial Judgment!