Who dares to rub in Franky Family?!
Return to me the money!
“To me the money”, say you Return?
Does that want to say that you are a man of Straw hat?
It is him, Aniki! I wanted to know if a man of Luffy to the Straw hat were so strong that!
But it is only one weakling!
Ca does not concern you!
Oops!
I appreciate your courage to want to bring back only the money, but I cannot you leave it.
Return it to me.
It is…
It is the money which we will use…
To repair our boat.
With this money…
We will be able…
We will be able to finally look after the wounds of Merry!
I you… will not leave it!
With the help of a companion!
The attack against Franky House.
Why so much of rage?
You seem to adore this boat.
It does not matter the state of your boat.
This money is with us henceforth.
Unfortunately, in this world, to conceal with the pirates is not a crime.
It is probably of the dirty money which comes by far.
Then, gives us.
If not, you can go to beg the Navy. You will be alone to make you capture.
This time, the unlucky person, it is Luffy with the Straw hat.
Because of a poor useless servant…
Incompetent to protect his money correctly.
The guy, you of him occupy!
I will do a little shopping with all this money.
I will give myself pleasure.
Wait!
HISTSU KUSHI
Remember this, Length-nose:My name is Franky.
If you want to survive in this city… Never cross my way, some is the reason.
What you made?! Leave me!
A poor weapon like that one hurt?
With more, Length-nose!
Thank you for the 200 million.
Wait! Return it to me!
Return it for Merry!
Return it to me!
Return it to me.
Return it to me, please!
I must have patience until the return of Robin.
If I find myself wedged, I will have problems.
I am not reassured.
At all events, I will protect this boat and the 100 million.
I count on you,
the guy.
St-stop!
If I remember well…
It is the place about which Nami spoke.
Included/understood? The street of the market east here.
Then you will borrow this channel for the moment.
There, Usopp is here.
Of agreement.
Another Nami-san thing,
The reference mark of the disassemblers of boats, Franky Family?
Usopp!
Usopp left.
Be sure for you? One is at the good place at least?
I AM NOT LIKE YOU, WHORE! Your mouth!
Usopp!
What you ace known as?!
What?
Look at, blood.
This cretin started from itself.
Do not say to me only it…
Usopp…
Luffy!
What you insane? From where you come like that?
Shipyard.
I tried to jump like the naval engineer to seek Usopp.
You are well?
I failed to forget! The guy, it is horrible!
Usopp was made choper with the money!
Ouais, I know.
Oi, we are not far from their cushy job.
Usopp was made tabasser and they stole the money.
It had to feel responsible… and had to only leave to the meeting Franky Family.
Then all our excuses for today.
Which heading that one.
We do not even know if it has it or not.
I hope that they will show me a little more respect, I must remain discrete by here.
It is Kalifa.
Nmaaa, enters.
Otsukaresama, Iceberg-san.
Do you want to drink something?
Yes…
I would take a little tea today.
I made some.
Maaa, I was sure, Kalifa.
I am grateful to you.
Mr. Kogi always leaves from here while being furious.
Which was the subject of the discussion?
They seek a thing which I hold, then they continue to make me proposals.
It of important, isn't this is something?
Such a thing. I always denied to know anything about it.
These people are tiring.
It breathes, Chopper?
It is frozen…
But he did not die.
They is good, it will be left there.
Remain here…
Usopp.
One will shave this hut immediately.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Oi, buy to puff out!
One has money, much of money!
Now, one is stuffed of money!
When I was young, I often made the decoration of the houses of people.
Thank you! You found my binoculars!
Yosh, I will tell you the time where I fought against a monstre marin on Calm Belt.
They was largest of all!
I have 8000 men at my sides!
They took all the money,
Nami.
How will I tell that with the others?
Bottez them the bottom…
the guy.
I play that.
Look at, you lost.
Go, will buy more provisions!
Buy all the store!
There is money!
Whore, you will see! I will put a beating to you while returning!
How, that it occurred?!
There is somebody over there!
Who be you?!
It is…
Luffy with the Straw hat!
You returned to seek the dough? Imbeciles!
Look at how much one is.
What do you hope to four?
But now that you are there,
Give us your settings at price.
It is the captain of this poor Length-nose.
They did not understand that they did not have any chance.
Come, I await you, dead losses.
GOMU GOMU NO…
What you insane?
They is punches? Even a warship could not anything against this armor!
It is delirious!
If you want to play, I will reduce to you out of pulp!
GUN!
It transpierced its giant armor!
Oi!
Wait a little, the guy!
Listen to what one has to say!
To say…
Di…
Draw with the gun!
SANTOU RYU!
KARA SUMA!
Battle song of the demon to the three swords.
… The boulets de canon are out of steel, are to you with the current?
Guns too!
They are… They are insane furious!
We break! We by the door of behind break!
Assume a little bit…
when you must fight.
PARBLE
KICK E
One cannot pass any more by the door of behind!
Windows… By the windows!
RUMBLE
HORN NOT!
ROSEO COLONNADE!
At-At-At-At-await a little, the guys!
It is the money which you want, hein?!
The 200 million which the greenhorn kept!
Ca fears, the money is not there!
Our chief, Franky-aniki, left to make shopping with all the dough!
And we do not know by where it left!
Ca is not used for nothing foutre the brothel, the 200 million will not return!
Zambai!
Close it.
One of fout.
Yes,
it is too late now.
The guy, one will not leave only one crumb of this place.
And us with?!
Baka, seized again!
It is us, Franky Family,…
Who will not leave a crumb of it?!
Show them!
The Speciality of Franky House!
Fire at will!
Here they are! With the attack!
No pity!
Destroy all that falls you under the hand!
They are only four!
It is what this noise? A fire of artifices?
Ca comes from Franky House.
Still them? What do they still prepare us?
And well…
They listen to us!
Oh cherished, they cannot play in silence.
Never, they will include/understand.
They is good, that did not last a long time.
It is splendid…
day.
Does one have to continue Franky?
But where?
Good, they do not seem to know where is the money.
Even if one ends up catching this Franky,
he will have already very spent.
What will one make?
While remaining here, one can await it still a long time.
Oi, I finished first aid!
We will transfer it onto a stretcher, then come to help me please!
Ca is not used for nothing to chatter longer.
In any case, let us turn over to the boat.
Nami-san remained all alone.
It misses Robin-chan, too.
There is also the problem of the boat.
Oi, Luffy!
About the boat…
I made my decision…
It is time to separate from Merry…