The war of Arabasta!
The city of the dreams:Rainbase
With the kingdom of the Oases.
Three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
In a howl of sadness, this desiccated ground sinks from now on in an enormous wave of agitation.
To stop the madness growing in the kingdom of Arabasta,
princess Vivi hurries to catch up with the army rebels in order to dissuade them.
However…
I want to beat this refuse of Crocodile!
If one stops the rebels, Crocodile will it stop?
Try to risk our lives at the same time as holds it!
We are your companions!
Say to me.
Where is Crocodile?
Vivi made its decision!
You all.
Luffy-San rightly.
I had a reason.
We must go where Crocodile is.
Ouais.
It is certainly the best thing to be made.
Super, and not of turning to nut this time.
Ah yes?
Where is this dumb of Crocodile?
Let us see…
Here the Alubarna capital, where my father controls.
Here the road which Alubarna will borrow the rebellious army to attack.
Therefore, one has just to beat Crocodile before they are there.
And Crocodile…
… is there.
Rainbase.
Rainbase?
While going towards North, one will be there within one day or more.
Hey, I already said you to stop with your “Aaah”!
Close it! It is easy to say for you who voyages to back of camel!
Ouais, lets go up to us too!
Woman-camel!
Nami-camel!
Not badly!
Chopper, you have just been beaten.
Yes, will be necessary that I involve myself.
Vivi will, be there water with Rainbase?
Yes, this place is very prosperous.
The city was saved by the rebellion and is recognized for its casinos.
Casinos!?
Do He, He, of what you think?
There remains at least a merry city in this kingdom.
“Da Lady” means “Not question”
Nan!
I said not!
Give the-me!
Go! Just a mouthful!
It gave it well to us to drink it, not?
Ossan spent one night to be dug for this water!
Then one will not drink it of only one blow, moron!
Can't Waoh, you remain quiet a little?
Of course that I can!
But it is hard!
VERY HARD!
I can take one step more.
Of… of water…
Then one arrives at Rainbase or not?
Luffy-San.
Thank you.
I would never have been so determined without you.
Give me to eat.
After having exploded Crocodile, you will give me to eat until I die about it.
Yes, I promise it to you!
Katorea - Camp of the Army Rebels
Please, Kohza!
Let join the rebellious army to me!
Not question.
Why not?
I have the right to join the rebellious army, not?
I hate the King!
Let fight to me with you!
Falafra, shows him.
It had that during a battle by protecting me.
You want to throw an eye with the infirmary and the cemetery too?
I…
AI NOT FEAR!!!
The King stole the rain, the cities are dry and much of people died.
My friends are falls ills!
It is the fault of the King!
I want to fight too!
I am not afraid to be wounded or to die!
Then returns at home.
Because you are mistaken.
Everyone is afraid and nobody wants to fight.
Then why do you fight?
One does not want to fight.
But it is owed.
It is what the country wanted.
I insane that you understand or not.
Release!
I said to you to release.
THERE IS NO PLACE FOR the CHILDREN!
What doesn't go, Kohza?
To howl on a kid, that does not resemble itself.
He resembles to me, when I was small.
Ca irritated me.
I did not change much.
Do you have the weapons?
Not, that takes more time than envisaged.
Send a message to our troops in each city.
As soon as we have arm, we will attack Alubarna into simultaneous.
Your Majesty, it is nothing any more but one matter of time before the rebellion does not attack Alubarna.
We must attack as long as we can it!
THE FARM!
Not question!
You want to fight like kids or what?
You are struck, you strike?
But in this case, the kingdom will be in danger.
And then?
Since the incident of Dance Powder,
there is no more doubt about the fact that somebody wishes to destroy this country.
Without knowing do its identity, you want to exterminate your people?
It is what would destroy this country.
You understand? A country it is people.
But there is no idea of the identity of that which scheme all that.
If it is waited until it destroys the country gradually, it will be too late!
Your Majesty!
Not question!
understand me.
The King will not let to us attack.
One can remain both nothing to make.
So only Igaram-San was there…
Does Igaram take a short leave?
Igaram-San must have joined Vivi-Sama.
To discover the identity of the plotter.
Or can they be well?
Chaka-Sama! Pell-Sama!
What is there?
Karu is of return!
Karu?
Majesty, this letter…?
It is without any doubt the writing of Vivi.
Majesty, you want to say that…
Did Karu come to deliver this letter of Vivi-Sama?
Father, all that is writing is the truth.
The man who upset our country and brought suffering and destruction to us…
… is not other than Crocodile!
Igaram fell vis-a-vis Crocodile.
He died.
Crocodile…
I relied on him, because he is member of the government…!
Who could the suspecter have wanted to reign on our country?
Igaram-San is…
It gave its life to protect Vivi-Sama and our country.
And now, I am with people who gave me a capacity without limits.
If we can continue together, something will change in this country.
A glimmer of hope is there.
Arabasta will be surely saved.
Believe in us, father, please.
Vivi.
It is written that you also risked your life in the battle.
Karu, you are courageous.
You are wounded?
Show to me.
No matter what it arrives now…
… this left arm proves that we are companions!
Chaka!
We know the enemy, now.
Joined together soldiers for the battle.
One should not leave the efforts of Vivi reduced to nothing and the unpunished death of Igaram.
We will immediately tackle the base of Crocodile with Rainbase.
Wait, your majesty!
Even if one leaves now, Rainbase is far from here!
Moreover, Crocodile is regarded as the defender of the people!
Forgive what I will say,
but think there.
If one attacks Rainbase now,
the rebellious army will jump on the occasion to attack and occupy the palate.
If that arrives…
And then, if the palate falls to the hands from the rebellious army?
I said it presently to you, a country it is people!
If the royal army is devastated,
if one beats Crocodile,
the country will reappear with the hands of its people.
But if we remain here to discuss the army rebels…
… that which will laugh the last will be Crocodile!
Your Majesty…
You went so far…
If we are likely to stop the army rebels…
If we can beat Crocodile, I of it will be satisfied.
Our adversary is one of Shichibukai.
Crocodile is not insane.
This battle will not be completed without sacrifices.
Chaka!
Convene your officers for a conference of war!
Pell!
You leave in front of and make a recognition of the enemy camp.
Majesty.
It seems that this time still we underestimated this man.
What a incredible will!
We will leave to fallen the night.
Majesty!
All the soldiers will walk on Rainbase!
One is there.
One succeeded?
Rainbase?
One is there!
Crocodile!
YOSH!
I WILL EXPLODE You the MOUTH, CROCODILE!
Then it is that, Rainbase.
Do Hey, you think that Baroque Works knows that we are there?
It is possible.
One met Mr. 2 while coming here.
It is more advisable to be said than they know than we are there.
And then?
They will recognize us.
One will not be able to run to hide in Rainbase.
WHY NOT?
Because if they find us in first,
one will not be able to put the hand on Crocodile.
The assassination is their speciality, after all.
OUAIS! LEAVE, CROCODILE!!!!!
Did you listen, stunned!?
It does not matter which tries to stop us.
I will protect Nami-San and Vivi-Chan!
You can call me Prince, both!
Prince.
I WILL KILL YOU, DUMB!
Prince!
Water!
Close it, you two!
Above all, I need water!
ME TOO!
Water, water!!!!
Wait, Luffy!
Ah! Take money with you!
Colonel Smoker?
You think that the pirates of Straw hat will come in Rainbase?
Surely.
Just a feeling.
ONE CAN FINALLY DRINK WATER, USOPP!
Water!!
There is something which does not go in this country.
As if a shade hid behind all that.
Excuse me.
Excuse we, can one have water, please?
Water! Give us the barrel!
Five! Five barrels! Five!
But you are sure that Baroque Works is related to the pirates of Straw hat?
Here.
All that I know…
… it is that this Straw hat is after Crocodile, one of Shichibukai.
Ca it is water! Name of god!
Sacrament good, this water!
One should hurry and bring back some to the others!
I will make a turn.
One does perhaps not should have sent these two zigotos for that.
It is not hard, they can do it.
You believe?
They surely will run while bringing problems with them.
One would make better prepare.
COURSE!
OUAIS!
TAKE THE BARRELS!
Shit!
Join the men, Tashigi!
They are continued!
Yes, Colonel!
How much does one owe you?
If they are your friends, it will be necessary to pay for them too.
O- Yes, sorry for the disturbance.
What the Navy fout here??
How I would know it??
Continue to run!
They are made courser by the Navy once again…
I hope that it is a joke????
Then why it runs by here?
But Tony-Kun did not return from the toilets!
Then let us leave it!
He can take care of itself!
THE GUY, THE MARINE EAST!!!
BECAUSE THEY FOLLOW YOU, JERK!
ONE WILL CATCH YOU, THIS TIME!
These goods with nothing are good to run, at least!
One would not have
to run in the city,
if not Baroque Works will see us!
I believe that it is too late.
Then there are not the choice!
Allons-y!
What?
In Crocodile!
From agreement, Vivi?
Yes!
You see this building with the crocodile on the roof?
It is the casino of Crocodile, Rain Dinners!
Then it is that…
It is there that Crocodile is!
One would make better separate!
It is a beginning of plan.
Well! One finds oneself over there!
Yes!
At Croco!
They separated!
Do not let escape!
Come me to seek, Smokey!
Be courageous for you!
But do not believe to be able to run without end!
It was right…
Shit!
Ah it is really pretty.
Where are parties?
Odor of Luffy!
Odor of Zoro!
But Sanji left by there!
What occurs?
MOVE OF!
Stop!
Mr. Bushido, they arrive by here too.
Look at, it is well them!
Kill them!
The Million Works Baroque!
Tiger in front of, wolf behind, hein?
Passes in front.
Grouille!
O- Yes!
Usopp!
Take care of Nami-San!
What?
I will deal with these.
Of agreement, shows them who is the Boss!
Sanji-Kun!
Leave!
One breaks!
Without this dumb of smoker, you are only small fry.
My condolences.
I hope that Mr. Bushido will draw some!
Not good enough!
Still test.
Roronoa Zoro.
One still meets.
This voice…
Ca makes a lease that I seek you.
To attack the innocent ones does, what that want to say?
I have my reasons!
And looks at, I do not want to fight against you.
Our duel finished in Logue Town.
Not it is not it.
We did not really cross iron!
It resembles to him, it resembles to him too much!
DECREE TO RESEMBLE TO HIM AS MUCH!
What you say?!
You continuous to insult me?
I will not forgive you your spite!
Shit, it is the only one which I cannot fight!
Wait!
Dumbs!
Remain here!!!!
Nooooooooooon!!!
No the problem, it is well them!
I have… I succeeded!
Super, Usopp!
Look at, it is there!
The entry of Rain Dinners!
It built it in the middle of a lake!
Didn't the others arrive yet?
Well! Aim and draw!
One will start with these deux-là!
ENEMIES!!!!!
Zoro!
You stays not with Vivi?
If!
It is not there?
It perhaps already entered!
One would owe magner then.
Luffy!
You stop!
Moku Moku is with him!
Hey, allons-y!
Everyone inside!
To go where?
It is here, not?
THIS REFUSE!!!
Oh? Vivi and are its pirates downtown?
Yes, the Million has just taught it to me.
Let enter them.
Yes.
CROCODILE!
I WILL EXPLODE You the MOUTH!!!!
With the next episode…