The ocean which recovers the world
is divided into two by a continent called Red Line.
The current which makes the round the world tour calls Grand Line.
Gold Roger, the Lord of the Pirates, hid there
its treasure, One Part,
some share on this road.
Since, pirates ventured at sea.
It is one enthralling time.
The pirates make float their emblems.
It is at that time
that we become acquainted with a young pirate,
of which here adventures.
Go…
Shanks, takes me along with you when you set out again at sea.
I want to become too a pirate me.
Why?
Why not?
Luffy, even if you could swim very well,
you could not become pirate.
I can fight too.
My fist is as powerful as a ball of revolver.
Ouais, it is that…
Stop making fun you!
Luffy still likes the toys.
At his age, I did not leave the house, me.
I am not any more one kid, I am an adult!
Calm yourself, thus take a fruit juice.
Thank you.
And you say that you are adult?
Te insane step of me, Shanks!
Afflicted to disturb you.
Look at to me this band of goods to nothing.
We are gangsters of the mountains.
But did not fear, us did not come to plunder the city.
We came to seek rum.
I am afflicted, but there does not remain to me any more rum.
It is strange, these pirates are however drinking some.
I served the last barrel to them.
Really afflicted, but one very drank.
Afflicted.
I give you this bottle if you want, it was not open yet.
My head is put at price to 8 million Berrys,
this bottle will not seal my thirst.
Ah it, the ground is soaked now.
I am afflicted, Makino-san.
You have a sponge?
I will do it.
You like to do the housework, one would say.
Then deals with that too.
We do not have anything to make here,
one from goes away.
Goodbye, band of idiots.
What took to you, Capitaine!
You were made ridicule!
How can you laugh?
Why didn't you fight?
Even if they were more numerous…
Which kind of men are you, to laugh when one humiliates you?
You are not pirates!!
I include/understand what you feel,
but it is only rum.
Useless to be irritated for that.
I cause you more!
In this moment, I had believed that Shanks was a coward.
But in fact,
I had not included/understood the way of acting of Shanks,
for this drink history.
What do you want?
Are Oh, you in anger because of what I said?
Yes, I require excuse!
You will regret it. Goes in hell!
Luffy!
Save it!
I suspected well that it occurred something.
Then they are still these gangsters of the mountains.
Captain.
Luffy.
Isn't your fist as powerful as a ball of revolver?
The farm!
I advise you to leave before somebody is not wounded.
If you still approach, I explode you the head, species of coward.
I said to you not to approach more, if not I make you jump the brain.
It is a bet.
I say that the gun is a bet on the life.
What do you tell?
I say simply that a gun is not made for bluffer.
You killed it!
Species of dumbs.
Us?
Stop saying stupid things.
You really believed that you had gained?
We are pirates, you know.
Listen to me well, the gangsters.
Whether you sprinkle me rum, or spit on my hat,
I can laugh at it.
But…
If you dare to carry the hand on my friends…
Shanks.
I occupy myself some.
Do not underestimate us, gangsters!
If you hope to beat us one day, come with an army!
Super…
Good-bye.
Shit, I did not even can card-index a punch with this dead loss to him.
Shit!
I am sorry, but you are useless for me now.
Release!
We are grateful to you, Luffy.
Makino warned us,
it is for that we came to beat us.
He, does not cry, you are a man!
But Shanks… your arm!!
My arm does not have importance,
since you are in life.
Shanks refused at sea to take it along with him,
because of its brittleness
and of its lack of force.
But Luffy had seen its size,
and it decided to become like him.
You leave?
Yes.
We remained a long time here. You only will feel?
Yes, but I will not wonder any more to take myself along with you.
I will arrive there all alone, with becoming pirate.
In any event, I will not have taken to you with me.
You believe yourself able to become pirate all alone?
Obviously!!
One day, I will gather an invincible crew
and I will find all the largest treasures of the world!
AND I WILL BECOME THE LORD OF THE PIRATES!
You want to become stronger than us?
In this case…
I entrust my hat to you.
This hat is very invaluable for me, then take in care!
One day, I will recover it.
Hold your promise.
I count on you, Luffy.
The adventure begins one decade later.
I slept well!!
Go!
Show them what the crew of Arbyda is able!
I am called Monkey D. Luffy. Enchanted!
They is super good.
One is on a pirate boat?
Not, not that one.
It is a boat which Arbyda-Sama wants to plunder.
They is good.
There is no canot de sauvetage here?
If, undoubtedly.
Mine was taken in a swirl.
A swirl? And you are always in life?
Ouais, I am astonished myself by me to be left about it.
Kobby, that made a long time.
Is it well?
I do not know.
But such as it is, it must work very hard.
I do not arrive at knowing if it is simply timid or obstinate.
You do not have any will?
You are the kind of anybody whom I hate!
Allow me
to enlist me in the Navy, please!
I drive myself station that you will give me, I am ready with all.
I want to enter the Navy!
Many sailors were killed by pirates.
It is not part of pleasure.
Then…
I accept your request!
Yes!
So long, Kobby!
Keep with you!
You have chance to have a friend like him.
Yes!
Do not make any you for him, Kobby has notch.
That will go.
One day…
One day one will be re-examined, Luffy-San.
In spite of what opposes a pirate and a guy of the Navy.
Then thus did that occur?
Nami?
It is really not believable.
Ouais.
I always took care on Zoro and you.
What?
I detach you if you unite with me.
I seek companions to train my crew of pirates.
I refuse!
You want that I unite with you?
What a good joke!
Which evil is there to want to be pirate?
The pirates are refuse, I refuse.
However…
It is said that you capture the pirates for the money.
That they say what they want,
I am the quiet aware.
What I want to do,
it is to achieve the goal which I set.
It is true?
But I decided that you would be member of my crew.
It is not with you to decide!
You are always like that.
Let finish to me front.
Then you were like that front?
I do not see a difference.
It is very interesting.
Fire!
You…
Luffy-San!
Straw hat!
Take again-that!
I however said it to you, that I was very strong.
It is not human normal,
he surely ate a Fruit of the Demon.
A Fruit of the Demon?
I intended to say that which ate some obtained capacities surpuissants.
I agree to become pirate.
I decided to pass on other side, to fight the Navy.
But I warn you…
I set a goal to reach.
A goal?
I want to become the largest fencer of the world!
And if I do not arrive there,
then I will commit suicide.
One goes there, Zoro!
Burst!
Not question!
Nice!
Thank you.
Please, Capitaine.
You are monsters both.
Do not be to you badly either, to have infiltrated a military base.
It was cake.
There does not exist any place which I donot can infiltrate.
It is true.
It was you on the boat of Arbyda?
One met over there, I remember it.
I burglarize the boats, then I travel everywhere
with my chart of Large Line,
and I will become rich.
My goal is to pile up 100 million Berrys.
Do a chart, you can sail?
Of course, I am the best.
Super!
Would that say to you to join my crew?
Really?
Ouais, I train a crew of pirates!
Not!
I hate over all the pirates.
Zut, I…
Did Nami, what take to you to do that?
Excuse me!
You believe that I will let pass that?
You spent time of them to save me!
Do not say anything!
I carried myself.
I do not want to become pirate.
You excite yourself easily.
They are pirates who killed those that I liked.
Ah, I include/understand…
Catch it!
Oh not!
You…
Behind you!
He, He!
Then one is caught some with a girl?
Zoro!!
You are wounded?
Thank you, Zoro. One would never have arrived there without you.
It is nothing.
They is super!
Nami, join us!
A super team will be trained.
I do not want,
unless you do not give up piracy.
How could one drop a job so well, is not this Zoro?
It is clear.
But we are still far from the goal.
I am hungry!!
You underestimate the sea.
Then do Nami, you unite with us?
Be heavy for you!
You do not have the Nami choice.
It will make very to achieve its goal.
Go, I am not so terrible!
Good Ah?
It is not serious.
In any event, I will not drop.
I want to become the Lord of the Pirates, it is decided!
I want to become the largest fencer of the world.
Which band of idiots…
What is there of so funny?
I will crush you!
What do you make?
Stop immediately!
These young people took the sea to achieve their goals and their ambitions.
They move towards Grand Line.
What awaits them over there?
Nobody knows it.
I will become the Lord of the Pirates!
Nevertheless, these young people are on the way!
Why do you hold as long as that to become the Lord of the Pirates?
There is a reason?
Not, not really, but…
But?
I promised it with somebody,
on this straw hat.
I see…
Good, ahead!
Worms Large Line! On the way!
These 20 minutes were quickly passed.
But now, you them spectators, you have an idea of what is One Piece.
I am always caught blows.
But you have a super technique of saber,
the Slash Demon.
They is super…
Pas le rice, the Slash Demon.
Another thing?
Afflicted, but it is a secrecy.
Let us hope that will not remain secret too a long time.
You will see…
If you want to fight, you gained ace!
Stop your gamineries.
Why the pirates like do so much to fight?
We need other team members.
One needs a cook and a tireur d'élite.
And a musician.
Why would one need a musician?
The pirates appreciate also Article.
Art of living should not be neglected.
It is quite true.
All will be well, one is strong.
Which is the report/ratio?
None.
Finally in short, I made my decision.
I will find One Piece costs that costs.
Watch for my adventures!
The series starts to become interesting.
With the next one!
Do not forget us! Goodbye!
I will become the Lord of the Pirates!!!