At the time of the final combat of Davy Back Fight,
Mugiwara Dangers gained an unhoped-for victory!
My… Noro Noro Beam was used for nothing…
Super! Super! Super!
It is brilliant…
Really brilliant…
All's well that ends well.
Ouais.
And now, the so much awaited decision…
Who thus will Luffy choose?
Chopper! Return!
Iyan… Choppy!
Thank you…
I am so happy…
Do not cry. One could not lose.
Well well…
In this Davy Back Fight full with tears and sweat…
The pirates of the straw hat succeeded
to recover their Chopper fellow-member!
The tournament shows a tie!
Wait, wait, wait!
In the world of the pirates, a tie that does not exist!
There are only the victory or the defeat,
not true straw hat?
What do you want to say?
And if one formed another part of the Three-Corner Range?
It is stupid or what?
Why one would still play his rotted play?
It… It… It has… It accepted!
It is what I wanted!
Idiot! Cretin! Weak!
It will be the last time, I promise it to you!
One must still fight?
There are not the choice, since it accepted the combat.
It perhaps had an idea.
It would be well the first time.
Perhaps that he seeks to enlist a naval engineer.
HOWLING SERVICE!
THE BALL WITH THE PIRATE PRISONER!
A new Three-Corner Range will be played.
Comprising a play of ball where all
the members can take part!
This play must count six players in each camp
You will have to fight face to face.
A player cannot take part any more
twice with the tests.
To change the composition of the teams is prohibited.
This time they will take to me, it is sure.
Not, it is me whom they will take.
They made ego an idol.
These deux-là is not wanted.
He… Why?
Too much soft, and too alarming.
Well, the first test…
“Hit and Deadball”.
As usual, I state you the rules.
Two balls will be concerned.
You will use these balls for touching
the adversaries which will be on the ground.
All those which will be touched will be eliminated.
They will not be able to thus return any more on the ground.
You lose the part when all your
players on the ground were touched.
You choose your players of
ground or of out-field freely.
But, a player of out-field does not have the right…
to enter on the ground,
even if it touched many people.
I see…
It is a little like the ball with the prisoner…
For more details, read the payment carefully.
The payment?
Which large book…
Exact, Hit and Deadball…
is the play more regulated Davy Back Fight.
In the course of time, its rules changed gradually,
to create a play with the very strict laws.
That is not used for only they are
strict if you do not respect them!
You arbitrate as that arranges you in any event.
Not, not, not… Look at the first page well.
Arbitration regulations…
Go against this payment and…
you will be decapitated.
Decapitated?!
What a horror!
Indeed.
Moreover, our arbitration body has
more than 50 years of experience
With the four assistants, they are five referees in all.
It would be said that one will have a honest combat.
The crew of Foxy has just aligned his team!
What a seen splendid!
Compared with them, the small faiblarde team
straw hat seems handicapped.
As always they are only Sept.
Useless to point out it!
The moment came.
The setting concerned will be done by a double interval.
That two players of each team advance!
Zoro, I want to do it!
I count on you.
Jump of all your forces!
Oooh! The doctor changed appearance!
It seems that he has superhuman capacities…
It should not be taken with the light one!
Iyan… It is what that?!
It does not have anything any more nice!
How the part starts!
One had them! Go, shootez them!
One goes there!
Chopper!
Aim head of puzzle!
Oyabin attention!
Is Oh, it already eliminated!?
Shyaaa! One beat Oyabin!
It is except, except!
What!? The shooting was perfect!
Article 20…
“The face does not count!”
What?!
Shit!
You are well, Oyabin?
Do not laugh, Hamburger-san!
It is our chance.
Touch the most possible world.
Of agreement!
I will touch them all! We will gain all!
You all, dispatch you to flee!
… Do not draw too extremely…
Equip with Foxy…
Eighteen players in less!
Super!
Incredible, they touched each one nine players of a blow!
Even score, hein?
Sanji cheer, Zoro cheer!
Excuse me…
Fantastic, nine of a blow.
Yosh, in my turn!
Equip with Foxy…
Ten players in less!
Ten players, record to be beaten!
Wah! Still a skewer of eliminated players!
The team of Foxy is finally in possession of the ball.
This time, it is my turn!
Go Chopper! Be given to bottom!
Yosh, I included/understood!
Ooooh! Hamburger succeeded in saving to them his!
Now, the team of Foxy has two balls!
It is the hour of the counter-attack.
Played well, Hamburger.
Give the ball to Big Bang.
Go ahead Big Bang!
Align to them all!
If it touches me, I died… I will die!
Ah not!
Oh, it is…
Length-nose and twenty-two players of the team of Foxy…
are eliminated!
Are Usopp, you well?
I succeeded in with me leaving there alive…
And guesses which with the ball?
By boxing the attack of Big Bang,
Usopp carried many other players with him!
There remain nothing any more but two adversaries.
Many people were made beat.
That is badly.
How will they be left there?
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
MUGIWARA-TEAM
Does Oyabin, what one make?
Does what one make?
As long as the historian is there,
I cannot use my Noro Noro Beam.
It is time to use it!
Really? “It”?
Completely. “It”.
Oh there there! Hamburger has been just made touch!
Played well, Robin!
The head does not count!
If, it is specified that the head counts…
page 103, subparagraph 54.
It rightly.
Does not obstruct us more!
You want to be made decapitate?!
I am sorry…
What a control, this Robin!
It thus succeeded in memorizing
all the payment in if little time?
Impressing, Robin!
But I yet very did not read.
Yosh, it remains nothing any more but one about it.
Sanji-kun, draws to him above!
Well, Nami-san!
San ji-kuun…
Do not draw…
Give us this ball!
Here it is!
Thank you.
You me leashes to touch you with?
My small rolled up eyebrow.
Touch me, strike, done me what you want!
But what you insane, Sanji-kun!?
Oooh! Sanji the womanizer
was passionately made burst the head!
It is the second elimination for
the team of the straw hat!
Cretin of mellorine!
He is without hope.
But in any event, there remains nothing any more but Oyabin.
One did not gain yet, it can always overcome us.
Indeed!
It is what that?
It will use the weapon Multi Item of Hit and Deadball!
Operation…
gun “Sight of Elite”!
He the referee, that goes completely against the rules!
It is thus that the Sight of Elite.
Do not say to me that you ace already heard of this trick?
They spoke about it in the payment,
but I was unaware of that it was that.
Exact, in accordance with article 322,
the Sight of Elite is the only authorized weapon.
It is true this lie?
Too much cool!
I want the same one.
It is merdic!
He, that is used for nothing your trick,
you nevertheless will lose!
Ah yes?
Is porch, all ready?
Yes, Oyabin.
It left!
Shit!
It is soporific, close the eyes!
It still uses this perfume.
It is the moment, Oyabin!
Received.
Revenge!
That the eyes are closed or not…
does not have importance for a true swashbuckler.
Extraordinary! Incredible!
The epeist Zoro sliced the ball into two,
with naked hands and closed eyes!
Iyan!
Zoro of the team of the straw hat… expelled!
Why!?
Article 645…
“It is interdict to destroy the ball!”
New ball for the team of Foxy.
What?!
As it is damage.
Ah, which damage.
Zoro the swashbuckler is eliminated!
Zoro is…
fact of excluding from the play.
Epeist of shit!
You were made eliminate before me, the cook.
That starts to become interesting.
It is of both against one.
Attention here me is!
Try to touch me!
Me too.
Super high-speed, level five.
Try to avoid that.
Iyan, Choppy!
Chopper was sacrificed to make this splendid stop.
How is it?
Doesn't the face count, hein?
VI… Face?
It… It was touched with the face?
It is very difficult to say.
It is too hairy.
Referee!
You are a sailor, not true?
The ball touched its face!
If you do not recognize his courage to him,
more the sorrow to claim you marine!
That does not count! That does not count!
What?
More to claim me marine?
I cannot let them say that!
The decision is essential itself…
That does not count!
But!
But?!
Even if the face does not count,
you left the limits of the ground!
Oh not, it is outside, unfortunately!
This small catch in the so large heart…
Chopper is unfortunately eliminated!
But you are inevitably a large sailor!
Choppy!
You are well, Chopper?
Yes but…
I am eliminated…
Let to me occupy itself some!
Thank you, I owe you that, Chopper well.
Do not say that to me…
That does not give me pleasure of the whole!
Be really good for you, Choppy!
Now, I want you more than ever!
I will not leave myself it!
Maintaining it is against one.
There remains nobody any more other.
It is final confrontation!
I will not want you,
simply, dispatch you to lose!
No matter what it arrives, I will not lose!
But what do you tell?
Look around you before saying
a trick which you will regret.
Here it is finally!
Swing-low of combat!
Prepare!
It is what that!?
He the referee, made something!
There are too many balls!
There is no rule prohibiting the use of twenty balls.
I knew well that were to you with the team with Foxy…
Fact of shitting! We will be always disadvantaged,
unless having our own referee.
Do not worry you Luffy!
Only you and Oyabin have the two good balls.
The others do not count!
Oh, it is true!
What does it have that?
It has the brain in puzzle, too?
The brain in puzzle…
I see, then I will smash you you and your funny head.
Here me is!
Iyan, by here!
You ace too stretched your arm…
How everyone mixes!
One mixes! One mixes! One mixes!
Oh not!
One does not know what a any more ball is the good one!
One mixes! One mixes! One mixes!
Then, which is the good one?
If you discover it after it
touched you, it will be too late!
The farm! I have only to catch up with all the balls!
What a arrogance!
I did not believe so bad player.
The guy, draw!
And now, the final blow…
Luffy, attention!
Luffy, take it in full face!
You are really démoniaque!
Excel!
Super!
Luffy with the straw hat… expelled!
But why!? The face does not count!
Article 999.
“It is interdict to swallow the ball.”
It is written in the black payment on white.
It is exact.
It is written in the last page.
Impossible… that exists, a similar rule?
And the winner of Hit and Deadball is…
The crew of Foxy!!
Idiot!!