The Prehistoric island!
Shade hidden on Little Garden!
I wonder whether it will snow.
But it is impossible that it snows!
Of course how it is possible!
You stays deadened you cannot thus know.
He. It reneiger, isn't this goes?
Eh well nothing is sure, but
this first part of the ocean is single.
The 7 magnetic fields emanating of Mountain Reverse affect all in the sector.
Then we must remain vigilant.
It is rather rare to have a voyage as violent as at the beginning.
But this sea is more difficult to sail than any other in the world.
The gold rule is never not to take this sea with the light one.
He, sailors!
Loans for a round of my Special Drink?
Dry bottom!
He Usopp, manufactures to us fishing tackle!
Fishing tackle? What a good idea!
Well!
I will make soft foods of fishing really not very ordinary!
Not, not.
Not like that…
You like that?
Delicious, not true?
Incredible!
In bottom, Karu!
Cool! Cool Méga!
How can they act of the kind?
Here is the tien.
Go! Go! Go!
Let do them.
If a storm approaches, they can what make.
They do not want to die, you know.
Eh well, I suppose it,
but they are not even with the aguets!
You should not be also anxious.
Not on this boat.
Aglou! Aglou! Aglou!
What a idiot, this Karu!
Eh well, it is enough releasing…
He the guy, look at!
It is a dolphin!
It is nice!
GIGANTIC!
It LEFT!
Allons-y!
Ouais!
Well!
Ensure this line!
Let make me!
These guy…
FULL SAIL!
Perfect! One tankard the wave and one draws from here!
Nami! How is the course?
Wait one moment, I check.
Turn the rudder of all your forces!
With your orders!
No the doubt.
One is aligned perfectly.
Our next destination is…
this island!
Then here it is,
the second island of Large Line!
Mr. 3…
What is there?
Wait one second.
All the other teas really insipid are compared with Earl Grey.
I am bored.
You do not stop saying that you are bored, but you also hate to work.
As long as orders were not received,
as much to release themselves and benefit from it, not truth?
To have pleasant holidays like that
fact part of the privileges of an Agent Officer.
And still a thing…
Stop using my code name as a public.
People will finish by knowing that I am Mr. 3.
Really?
And by the way, during these last days you did not do anything of other but to look at this foutu paper.
What can that be well?
Orders of the chief.
WHY DIDN'T SAY It EARLIER to YOU?
Then Mr. 5 was beaten…
If that had been Mr. 2, I would have been happier.
Thus one would have been promoted.
The defeat of Mr. 5 is not astonishing.
This man was a cretin who believed too much in the superiority of his capacities.
There is nothing more useless than a man having the capacities Demon
but which is not enough malignant to use them effectively.
A professional criminal uses his remarkable intelligence to arrive at his ends.
Perhaps that one could teach them something,
as what they is to put at back the largest criminal organization.
Then here Little Garden.
It is not “little” whole good blood!
It is definitely less nice than the name…
An unexplored territory would be said…
A jungle in a wild state!
One will have to pay attention.
I still think so that Miss All Sunday said.
But your bad luck comes
road where the Log Poses leads you.
The name of the next island is…
Little Garden.
My expensive, even if one does nothing to stop you, you will never arrive at Arabasta.
You all will be destroyed.
Does C-C-Ca mean that there will be monsters?
Who knows?
Let us pass to the following island without making stopover here!
But there is need of time to regulate the Log.
Y' has that, and it is as high time as we make some provisions.
One did not succeed in supplying us at the last city.
I see a river mouth in front right!
Really?
Yakiniku = Korean Barbecue.
I hope that there will be a Yakiniku restaurant!
Would there why be here a good blood of it?
You ace not known as which one did have need for provisions?
I wanted to say that one needed ingredients!!
You ace really that a chick-pea in the head!
But to make stopover is dangerous.
I want to say, look at these plants.
They are not on any book of botany which I read.
How it is nice!
Who me?
NAMI-SAN, OF COURSE!!
What is it?
Do not worry you.
It is surely a p' tit bird.
And it is right a normal jungle.
Y' has anything worrying.
What is there?
NAME OF GOD, DIRTINESS Of BIRD!!
A lizard?
I ask for myself which taste that A.
It is that the kind of noise which one hears in a normal jungle?
Ca resembles an volcanic eruption!
A tiger?
It is monstrous!!
What?
What did it arrive to him?
It is not normal.
It is at all normal!
How a tiger, the king of the jungle, can bathe in its own blood?
Good then, it is decided, we will not make a stopover on this island!
We just will have patience on the boat and will wait calmly until the Log is ready.
Yes!
Then one puts the veils from here as quickly as possible.
Yes!!
One must hurry to arrive at Arabasta, not true?
Bento = Box of Japanese meal
Sanji, a bento!
A bento?
Yes, to hold me in form!
A ton of meat and without crudenesses!
A bento of pirate!
Ca feels the adventure with full nose!
He you, wait one minute!
Where do you believe to leave like that?
With the adventure!
You want to come?
The adventure! The adventure!
It is useless… I cannot stop it.
It is too excited.
You laugh, not true?
The monster which killed this enormous tiger is always in nature!
Sanji, a bento!
I heard you.
Give me one minute.
He, that done anything if I do leave with you?
Not, not of problem! Allons-y!
Do not say to me that you will go with him?
Eh well, if I remain here sitted, I will finish by me making pimpernel.
I will be quieter thus while it is waited until the Log is ready.
You cannot!
Luffy does that all the time,
but for you they is very dangerous!
The adventure! The adventure!
All will be well!
Karu will be with me!
It is so surprised that it lost the voice of them.
Well, Vivi-Chan, I will prepare you a special bento made with love!
Can you also put some cocktails for Karu, please?
Of course!
Let make me!
Well!
A bento of pirate and a special cocktail for Karu!
You are ready?
Ouaip!
Well, one left!
Perfect!
On the way!!!
We will be soon of return!
It has tripe…
Wednesday miss.
You expected what of other of somebody who infiltrated an criminal organization?
Good, I have time to kill.
I will make a turn.
A TURN?
He, Zoro!
Wait!
One is with course of puffs out.
If you see something of edible, brings back it.
Ok, I included/understood.
I will drive out something which you will be unable to catch all alone.
Await Zoro!!!
I heard what you said.
Bastard, you believe that you can bring back something of larger than I will be able it?
In the thousand.
A contest of hunting.
Listen. Gaining will be that which will have brought back the most kilos of meat.
You want to say tons?
You will make less the boasting one when our preys are aligned.
I think the same thing.
They all are similar.
Why do they all have to follow the same way?
I include/understand exactly what you feel.
Do not cry, I am on your side.
They gave up us…
It is what I was going to say!
But, wait one minute…
Q… What is there?
N- N N Nami?
It is not that one…
That one, either.
He! He, He! Nami? Nami!
What do you seek good blood?
I remember to have read it in one of these books.
What?
Little Garden.
What is there?
He, looks at! You see this trick?
One would say a squid with a shell.
A squid shell.
An ammonite would be said.
It is a squid shell.
I have the impression that one observes me.
Ca must be my imagination.
Do Oh, you want to play with me, filth?
It is what this thing?
Is Ca eaten?
Let us see seeing… It was which?
I read it recently.
What did I make some?
Why does y' have a king of the seas who walks on ground?
A DINOSAUR!!
A DINOSAUR?
Then… that must be one of the prehistoric islands!
This island remained still with Old Dinosaurs!
Because of the difficulty of navigation of the islands of Large Line,
diversities of the islands seldom mix the ones with the others.
Each island thus developed its ecosystem which is clean for him.
Therefore, there are islands which contain civilizations which are more advanced,
and there are islands which remained isolated during tens of thousands of years,
and which kept their original state!
The unforeseeable climates of Large Line make this possible!
This island really remained with Old of the Dinosaurs!
INCREDIBLE!
Luffy!
DO NOT GO UP ON TOP!
Usopp!
What? What is there?
You found the book?
Be tough large bastard for you.
Santouryuu = Style of combat with 3 swords
A follower of the Santouryuu combat?
It is terrible! This island is…
Is this island?
What?
I believed to intend Nami-San to call me…
For the inhabitants who live here,
the island is like a small garden.
Little Garden…
It is as that which one calls this place.
Chief of forwarding, Louis Arnote.