You bastard... What the heck are you doing???
What do you mean?
We've come to get Nami back.
Oh yeah, where are Usopp and Johnny?
Usopp!
That's right, we can't be wasting time here!
What happened?
He's been captured by Arlong!
If we don't hurry he'll get killed!
He's dead!
What?!
Usopp-aniki is dead.
He's been killed...
By Nami-aneki!
REUNITED!
USOPP TELLS NAMI'S TRUE STORY
Is that the truth!?
Yeah, it's horrible...
That woman's a witch!
In order to obtain some hidden treasure
in Cocoyashi Village for herself,
She was kissing up to Arlong!
And for that purpose, she killed
without even thinking about it.
She's a rotten-hearted low-life!
We've been fooled all this time!
Bastard!
Say that one more time and I'll kill you!
Stop it Luffy, this has nothing to do with Johnny.
You don't have to believe me,
But I saw it with my own eyes!
I saw what she did to Usopp-aniki!
You're making up crap!
There's no way Nami would kill Usopp!
We're friends!
But I...
Who's friends, Luffy?
Nami!
Why did you come here?
What are you talking about?
You're my companion.
I came to get you!
How annoying.
Nami?
Friends? Don't make me laugh.
You're more like a pathetic group
of cooperators, don't you think?
Why you... I saw it with my own eyes.
How... how dare you kill Usopp-aniki!
And your point is?
You wanna try killing me to avenge him?
What!?
I'll tell you one thing.
Right now Arlong wants to kill
''Roronoa Zoro and his posse.''
All because Zoro went and did something stupid.
You guys may have these monster-like powers,
But you're no match for real monsters.
Hang around this island long enough,
and you guys will be killed for sure.
Well...
It doesn't concern me though.
Her cool look is still so charming!
Hi Nami-san!! It's me, it's me, remember me?
Lets go on a cruise together!
You stay out of this! You'll just complicate things!
What did you say!?
My love is always a hurricane!
Hey! Listen to me when I'm talking!
Where is Usopp?
At the bottom of the sea.
Why you! Quit your bullshit!
Do swordsmen attack women too?
Roronoa Zoro?
What did you say!?
You don't even know what's
going on so don't interfere!
After an emotional loss,
of course you're irritable.
You'd better watch what you say.
Mind your own business, bastard.
Aniki's! Don't be bickering at
an important time like this!
That's right.
If you're going to fight, do it off the island.
You outsiders quit sticking your
nose into this island's business.
You still don't get it?
The only reason I got close to you guys
is for the money, nothing else.
Now that you guys have nothing,
you're no use to me.
I'll return the ship.
So why don't you go find a navigator
and head to the Grand Line.
Go find One Piece or whatever...
Just get the hell out of here! You're a bother!
Goodbye.
Nami.
Luffy-aniki.
I'm going to sleep.
Sleep!?
Right now? In the middle of the road?
I don't feel like leaving the island...
I don't care what's happening here...
I'm a bit sleepy...
I'm sleeping.
Aniki...
Then...
DO WHATEVER YOU WANT!
GO AHEAD AND DIE!
Hurry, hurry!
What's the big deal?
The marines... the marines are here!
The survivors of Gosa Village successfully
got in touch with the government.
The marines are here to rescue us!
You see!?
We're going to be saved! We
can finally escape this island!
So that's the Arlong Park I heard about from rumors.
You know it's the end of the world
when pirates settIe down like that.
Listen up men. Our duty today is to
rescue survivors from Gosa Village,
which has been destroyed by Arlong and his gang.
But I think...
That our duty to justice does not allow us to pretend
as if we didn't see this grounded pirate castle.
Does it?
No sir!
We shall eliminate Arlong and his gang.
Prepare to attack!
Yes Sir!
Marines from the 77th fleet?
Yeah, that's what it says.
That's a new face.
Someone go negotiate with the person in charge,
and tell them not to make any unexpected moves.
If they don't settle for 2 million,
go ahead and erase them.
They shot at us right away!
Arlong-san, watch out!
He chewed up the cannon ball.
That's a scary set of teeth.
Arlong-san, about the negotiations?
No negotiations.
All right let's go!
Attack!
Down with the marines!
Chu, hold up guys.
We don't need that much force
to take out some trash. Chu.
We'll go get them.
To pick a fight with us in the sea,
they've got to be stupid humans.
Three of our main fighters, this
oughta be a great fight.
That ship won't last three minutes.
How strange.
Sir, that bomb seems to be a dud!
One more time! This is to signal battle.
Our enemies are mermen so
don't let your guard down.
Yes sir!
Man down! He's from the merman gang.
Attack!
Hold it right there!
You're from the Arlong gang eh?
I am general Purin Purin from the marines, 77th fleet.
We're a pretty famous marine fleet.
If you're not looking to die, you should quietly surr...
General!
How dare you attack our general!
Attack!
What's this shock?
Could there be a merman under the ship?
Sorry to bother you guys.
We just removed the rudder from this ship.
General!
What'd you say!?
Are you ok?
Don't worry about it. I missed his vitals.
This is a big ''if''....
But what would happen to the sea, if we moved
a boulder in the middle of a current?
What!?
Moving a boulder?
But that's impossible!
All right. Right around there Hachi.
General! A whirlpool appeared right in our path!
The rudder isn't working!
What!?
I toId you already, we removed the rudder.
The next stop for this crippled ship will be...
The bottom of the sea.
It can't be...
This is reality.
We can't escape from Arlong's reign.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Thanks for the work.
Nah, we know everything about the
winds and the currents in this area.
It was no sweat.
With our power and knowledge, we
have no adversaries in the seas.
And also the map Nami drew for us.
We moved the boulder looking at it.
We could even easily tell the currents.
It's a really well made map.
If we make Nami draw up maps for the whole world,
we could be kings of the sea forever.
Damn it. Nami is irreplaceable as a
member of the Arlong kingdom.
What a pity.
Pity?
The deal is if Nami saves 100 million beli,
She gets Cocoyashi Village and is free to go.
Is that for real?
Are you really going to let Nami free to go?
Really for real?
What a waste!
I have no choice.
That's my deal with her from eight years ago.
I keep my promises made over money
even if it means my death.
That's me...
Hey, Zoro-aniki,
what the hell are you thinking!?
You're the target of Arlong and his gang,
you know! Why don't you run away!?
Now that we know Nami is that kind of low-life,
there's no reason for you to stay on this island!
Reason to stay on this island?
There is a reason.
He's still staying here.
Are you saying that even you're thinking
of getting Nami back as a partner?
I don't care what happens.
He decides who becomes our navigator.
Aniki...
Okay,
I understand.
Although it's only been a short while,
Our job to bring you guys here is done.
I'm with him.
I don't want to die in vain.
Okay,
Take care.
Well then, until we meet again...
Aniki, you guys take care too.
You guys too.
Hey.
Why was Nami-san crying back then?
That woman... crying?
She was crying in her heart.
Keh.
What? Crying tears of guilt for killing Usopp?
You're serious?
You seriously think Nami-san killed that long-nose?
Back then...
For my business,
I have no other choice!
Back then,
Nami made it look like she stabbed me
and stabbed the back of her own hand!
If she didn't do that for me,
I would have definitely been killed by Arlong.
What should I do?
The man, Usopp, can't take being
saved all the time like this.
Anyway, I'd better find Zoro quick.
Is that Zoro right there?
Yes! It's him!
''Nami didn't kill him...''
Is that what you want to say?
Isn't that right?
I dunno.
I made that little servant lose it once already.
She may have just killed him in a fit of rage.
Little servant!?
WHATS LITTLE ABOUT NAMI-SAN'S CHEST!?
Is that all you think about?!
He's still alive...?
Nope. I think he's dead now.
USOPP!!!
DID NAMI DO THIS TO YOU!?
No, uh, sorry.
That was him and me.
IT WAS YOU.
Luffy, you're here.
Yeah, a little while back.
I'm here too, nice to meet you!
I'll kill you someday!
Hey, you're still fine even after that?
Shut the hell up!
Oh yeah, you were killed by Nami right?
Damn him, Johnny was lying after all.
Actually,
there is some truth to it.
It's more the opposite.
Nami saved my life
You made quite a mess.
Nami.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Just came by to rest.
If you made a mess every time you came to rest, I'd go nuts.
And would you open that treasure map,
If there was nothing wrong?
There was just something that made me angry.
Them, eh? Who are they?
You met them?
Yeah, the guy said something 'bout being a captain.
He seemed like a liar though.
I heard,
When you were traveling with them, you
were happy and had a great time.
I haven't seen you happy for years now.
So tell me, who are those guys?
I promised you could talk to me
about whatever you want, right?
I was supposed to forget about those guys.
I was supposed to have erased them from my heart.
Yatta! I'm done!
Damn it. Nami won single handed again!
Hey Luffy. Why are you still holding so many cards?
I had a feeling that more is better.
Idiot! Learn the damn rules already!
All right then lets make the rule that more is better.
Okay then it's decided.
But...
You can't decide the rules!
the more I tried to erase them from my memories,
The more I remembered them...
Crap! The water's leaking in!
Quick! hold it!
Leave it to me!
Hold on!
For an instant...
I forgot the fate I brought upon myself.
What the hell do you think your crew are!?
I thought that if I could,
I would stay with these guys forever...
I see.
Of course she'd be upset.
Somebody actually came for her.
Friends huh?
To her,
that's the most...
difficult word of all.
So Nami bluffed the ''killing me
off'' part so I could escape.
I think there's a reason for her
being with the mermen pirates.
Of course.
So what do we do now?
Rush Arlong Park?
Hold on!
Before that we should ask Nami
for a better explanation!
Either way, it's useless.
No matter what you guys do,
Arlong's reign won't end.
Nojiko!
Who's that?
Nami's older sis.
Nami-san's older sister?
She's so pretty!!
What do you mean, ''It's useless''?
Do us a favor.
Don't meddle with this village's business anymore.
Leave Nami alone.
I'll tell you the reason why.
The reason?
You mean why she stays with the mermen?
Yes.
Once you hear the reason,
you must leave this place.
All right, then tell us the reason or whatever.
I'll pass.
I don't care about her past.
Where are you going?
A walk.
What do you mean, a walk?
You're not going to listen to the story?
Yeah, I'll pass.
What's with him?
Don't mind him. That's just what he's like.
We'll listen to the story.
Although it probably won't change anything.
I'll listen too.
I want to understand what's going on here.
Me too, I want to know everything about Nami-san!
He's sleeping.
Don't sleep if you said you'd listen!
I see.
No wonder Nami is torn.
A marine ship arrived?
It's the marine's 16th fleet.
Maybe they were sent by headquarters
to see about the 77th fleet.
I'm commander Nezumi of the marine's 16th fleet.
Bring forth the village leader Genzo.
I'm Genzo, commander.
You, huh?
Escort me to Nami's house.
Nami?
What business do you have with her?
All you have to do is escort me.
We have to go back eight years to start the story.
Back when we were still young.
She lived in this village.
Nami and I will never forget her.
Her name was Bellemere.