(The following episode is based
on Manga ch.7: "Romance Dawn,
The Dawn Of Adventure" and Ch.8: "Nami")
What a great harvest today.
We robbed so many treasures,
Mr. Buggy won't scold us.
Hey, look.
What's wrong with that ship?
Oh, there is a woman.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Ah.. am I dreaming?
I never thought that I could
meet anyone over the sea.
Though I don't know who you
are, please give me some water.
Would you please give me some water?
I can give you all my money if you want.
Please help me.
Ok, we can help you.
But we have to make sure
what is inside your box.
Sorry.
I can't open it.
Really?
If you like, I can give them all to you.
And that ship.
Ah, our ship.
Thief! You lied to us!
There are some black clouds over the
southern sky, and some cold front.
I predict the storm is coming soon.
Careful, the little ship
is easy to turn over!
Bingo!
Goodbye!
I'll take your treasures!
Don't run away, you thief!
We will remember you!
"Luffy's Past!
Meet Red-Haired Shanks"
"Luffy no Kako!
Akagami no Shanks Toujou"
I am so hungry.
How soon will we be on land?
I don't know.
Just follow the wind.
Are we there? No, but we will be.
Someday.
You want to be a pirate king, but you don't
know any sailing skills. Isn't it strange?
Why? I am always following the wind.
So you also earn money
by roaming over the sea.
I don't remember having told you I
earned my living by earning prizes.
I am on the sea for a man.
Then I got lost.
So I have to earn some money
by catching those pirates.
So you are lost.
Shut up! YOU are lost!
Shanks.
It has been with me through many
battles. It's very important to me.
Luffy, I will never give
it away, even to you.
Bring me with you next time, Shanks.
I want to be a pirate, too.
How could it be possible?
Why not?
Luffy, even if you are a good swimmer,
you can't be a pirate.
I can fight well.
My fists are also very good.
Really?
What do you mean?
Anyway, you are too young.
Yes, you are about the
same age as my children.
I am not a child! I am a grown man!
Ok, don't be angry.
Come on, drink some juice.
Ah, thank you.
Kids are kids, easy to cheer!
You are wicked, Shanks!
Don't laugh!
Stingy Shanks!
Excuse me.
Those people are all pirates,
they all look so funny.
Welcome.
We are mountain men.
Don't be afraid, we are not here to rub.
We want to buy ten bottles of wine.
Sorry, we are sold out.
Why, it is strange.
Those pirates are drinking; do
you mean they are drinking urine?
Sorry, but we don't have any wine.
I am really very sorry.
Look like we drank too much.
Sorry.
If you don't mind, take this one.
It's not opened.
I am worth 8 million belly's. One bottle
is not enough. Don't look down on me.
Ah, the floor is wet.
I am sorry, Makino.
Let me clean it.
Ah, I can clean it.
Looks like you enjoy sweeping.
Enjoy yourself well.
It is meaningless if
there is no wine. Let's go.
Goodbye, cowards.
Are you ok, captain? Did you get hurt?
Ah, it's ok. I am fine.
Our captain is so poor.
It is ridiculous.
How can you laugh?
Don't you feel ashamed?
Why didn't you fight?
Even though they are so many!
You are not men to
laugh at such a thing!
And you are not pirates either!
I can understand how you feel.
But it is just some wine.
You don't need to be that angry.
I don't want to talk to you!
Are you stuffing yourself, Luffy?.
Leave me alone!
What are you eating?
Is that the box?
Did you eat the things
in the box? > Yes.
Spit up, spit them all out!
What's wrong, Shanks?
What is that?
You ate the "rubber fruit"!
Rubber fruit is called "Devil Fruit."
After you ate it, your
body would become rubber!
You won't be able to
swim after eating it!
No!
You little bastard!
I was drinking happily.
Are you tired of living, kid?
You dog, apologize now. How
can you look down on Shanks?
What did I say to make you so unhappy?
You just said it! Apologize now!
Mayor!
Did you see those pirates' faces?
You didn't even say a word.
You are such a coward.
Pirates are all cowards.
All they can do is play cool.
Stop it!
Ah?
Don't look down on
Shanks and his friends!
They are not cowards!
Stop, Luffy!
You can't look down on Shanks!
You bunch of stupid mountain men!
You are too impolite, kid.
So far no one can live
if they irritate me.
Wait a minute.
Let go of that kid, please.
I don't know what Luffy did,
and I don't want to fight with you.
If I have ever offended
you, I would like to pay you.
Please, give that kid a chance.
Mayor.
Indeed elders are more
polite and knows the norms.
But it is useless this kid is finished.
Because he made me really angry.
It is your fault, monkey!
You are in big trouble.
I'll let you say you're sorry in hell.
Luffy! >Please, give him a break.
I wonder why the bar is empty?
Aren't they those pirates?
Captain!
Shanks.
Pirates, why are you still here?
Are you still sweeping?
Luffy, I thought your fists
are more powerful than guns.
Shut up!
I don't know why you are here,
but get out before you get hurt.
If you come any closer, you
better watch your head, coward.
I told you not to come any closer.
Or I'll smash your head.
You are risking your life.
You're going to pay
for this with your life.
What you are talking about?
I mean, you cannot scare me.
What?
They started it!
Really nasty!
Nasty?
It is so naive.
You think this is a game?
Those in front of you are pirates.
Shut up! It is none of your business!
Listen, mountain man...
Even if you throw wine or food
on my head, or you spit at me,
I will laugh it over
as if nothing happened.
No matter what your reason is,
I won't spare those guys
who ever hurt my friends.
Shanks!
You won't spare us?
Ridiculous pirates! Kill them all!
Charge!
Let me handle it one is enough.
Don't be arrogant, mountain man!
If you want to fight us,
send over a battleship.
Sweet.
Wait, this kid irritated us first!
I heard your head's
worth a lot of money.
Damn you!
Smoke bomb!
Luffy!
Oh no, I let him go! Luffy is kidnapped!
What can we do now?
Calm down! Stupid head.
Let's look for him together
we will find him soon.
I can't stand this guy.
I can get away easily.
They would never imagine a
mountain man would go out to sea!
Let go of me, you stupid monkey!
Go to hell!
Stupid kid, YOU go to hell!
You irritated me first.
Bye bye.
Damn him!
Those guys are garbage.
I can't even beat them.
Damn him!
Sorry, it is pity that
you are useless now.
What? What the hell is that?
Help, help!
Shanks.
Get out.
I want to thank you, Luffy.
Makino told me.
You challenged them because of us.
Don't cry, you are a man.
Shanks...
Your arm!
Sorry, but it is just an arm.
I am glad that you are safe.
Are you leaving now?
Yes, we have stayed here too
long. It is time to say goodbye.
Will you get lonely?
Yes, I will be very lonely.
But I won't ask you to take me.
Because I decided to
be a pirate by myself.
I won't take you with me anyway.
You thought you can be a pirate?
I can!
Someday I will find my
partners as good as yours.
And to find the best
treasure in the world.
I will definitely become a pirate king!
You want to surpass us?
Here.
I leave this hat to you.
This is the most important
thing to me. Keep it well.
Someday, I will come to
you and get it back...
when you become a good pirate.
A deal is a deal, Luffy.
Hey, you are daydreaming again.
That hat is important, isn't it?
Yes.
Thanks, Zoro.
Ah, I am so hungry.
There's a bird.
Let's eat the bird.
How?
Watch this
GOMU GOMU NO!...
ROCKET!
What a genius.
Help!
Idiot, what are you doing?
Hey, stop now! The ship
over there, please stop!
Somebody is in danger at the wrong time.
I am busy! Save yourself!
What did you say?
You are quite skilled.
Do you want us die?
Stop the ship.
We are underlings of "Buggy the Clown"!
We want this ship.
I didn't know you are the famous
"pirate hunter," Master Zoro.
We are very sorry.
You made me lose my partners.
Sail forward in full swing.
Yes.
By Luffy's capacity, it should
be no problem to be on land.
To take it seriously,
buddy, what should we do now?
You are right.
Our treasure and ship
are stolen by that girl.
If captain Buggy knows this...
What is this "Buggy" that
you are talking about?
Haven't you heard of "Buggy the Clown"?
Never.
He is the leader of our pirate ship.
And he is one of the people
who ate the "Devil Fruit".
He is very terrible, to put it simply.
Great! I finally got it!
Wait, stinky girl!
Thief! Give us back our map!
We've just grabbed it! It's
the map of the "Grand Line"!
Damn! If we can't get it
back, we must die miserably.
I don't want to die
under the captain's bombs.
Captain Buggy.
Some unknown object is
above the sky of the harbor.
Shoot it down!
What?
Somebody fell down.
Where did the bomb come from?
Thank God I'm alive.
What a strange journey this is!