It is that!
I NEVER HAD THINK Of THAT!!
Davy Back Fight, the final match.
The intense combat enters the captains…
is finally with its apogee.
Luffy!
I will fight for my companions…
UNTIL DEATH!!
PROUD COMBAT!
THE FINAL DECISIVE ONE!
It was still raised thanks to its incredible will!
Luffy with the straw hat!
With each time it is with ground…
Luffy.
With each time it is with ground, it is raised!
It IS WHAT YOUR PROBLEM, BROTHEL?!
Luffy!
It has evil to hold upright!
It suffocates…
What a man!
But its eyes always shine and it is raised unceasingly!
By regard for his/her companions!
Yes, it is that Davy Back Fight!
My eyes are full with tears! I see there nothing any more!
Luffy!
It is too much!
Dumbs!
Luffy! Luffy! Luffy!
Crowd acclaims Luffy!
Y-a it already have before a rival
able to hold head in Oyabin like that?!
The guy…
WHY YOU ENCOURAGE the ENEMY?!
Oyabin… Oyabin…
Oyabin! Oyabin! Oyabin!
Look at well, that will be finished soon.
You cannot flee with this kind of displacement.
Shit, it does not have even enough any more of force to flee!
I cannot see Luffy in this state any more!
Now, I will finish some.
Oyabin attacks!
Initially it slows down the boulet de canon…
By using the speed of the boulet de canon…
My megaton will undoubtedly put KB to you!
Here it is! The ultimate attack of Oyabin
“the overlapped boulet de canon”!
It will complete it with Foxy Fighter!
Luffy! You received the ray a little earlier than the ball!
Dodge it as soon as you can move!
I can move!
Straw hat was released from the effect of the ray!
Useless!
You will not go nowhere!
Luffy! Caution!
Take that, it is a gift.
It is finished!
All the attacks were right of Straw hat!
Luffy!
He! Doesn't Ca go a little too much far there?
I… it… it… it was still raised!
How?!
I gained.
WHAT?!
YOU HOLD HARDLY UPRIGHT!
If you do not give up, I will strike you until
what you can be raised never again!
INCREDIBLE!
It is the most violent exchange which
one saw during the combat!
Luffy, smashes it!
Beat it!
Incredible! What a incredible rain of blows!
What?
It was what that?
They do not move any more.
Straw hat is with ground…
NOT, the only one which bulge is Straw hat!
How is that done?
Shit.
Why?
Oyabin!
A mirror!
A piece of mirror fell
hand of Straw hat!
It was wedged in my cut afro.
That comes from the mirror of your part to the idiot.
Dumb!
Impossible…
Still eight seconds…
It is possible that…
Sept.
What?
Six…
Oyabin!
Five!
What you made?
To go, let us hope all together!
Four!
What?
Ouais, that with the funny air!
Three!
Two!
One!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
MUGIWARA-TEAM
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!!!
Géniaaaaaal!
Luffy!
Oyabin!
Oyabin flies away with far!
Yatta! Yatta! Yatta! Yatta!
It landed…
Out of the limits!
Davy Back Fight, final match.
The heroic battle enters the two captains…
The legend of Oyabin with its 920
consecutive victories is finished.
The winner of the combat is…
I will not lose any of my companions…
SAME IF I MUST DIE ABOUT IT!
LUFFY WITH THE STRAW HAT!
Yatta!
Oyabin lost.
Foxy pirates against…
Oi, do not remain there sitted, one must go to save Oyabin!
Ok, I occupy myself some!
the crew of the Straw hat.
I will do it!
Move from there!
I go there too!
Under the orthodoxe rule of the Three-Corner-Range,
the tests of Davy Back Fight are finished!
Oyabin!
Whore, you frightened us!
Toi~.
Does not touch it like that!
It is seriously wounded, stunned!
You frightened us.
Especially with this Afro Power.
Nami-san! The capacity of the afro is immense!
Ah! It awakes!
H… H… hein?
Play… and play?
I believed that I had gained.
It was a dream?
Worry you, you gained ace.
Such an amount of better.
Do not worry you, I supervised you.
Liar…
When I think of it, I would not have any more any
raison d'être pirates if I left this crew.
Oyabin! You should avoid moving.
Hey Straw hat!
Bastard! How oses you
to destroy my record of invincibility?!
Oyabin!
Played well, brother!
Yo, Oyabin!
Oyabin!
Be to you idiot or what?
Like the rule says it…
hurry and take 500 men!
Yes, the last transaction must be decided.
Chopper and Robin!
Thank you… I… I am so happy…
, I hold return this to you.
Initially it chose these deux-là of course.
Who will be the following? Chosen!
Give me the pirate flag.
WHAT?!
It is impossible!
You hope to seize our pride?
I do not want the sail.
You without, isn't this cannot sail any more?
What a compassion!
But, the symbol is above.
One will be able to use it never again.
Stop talking cock and take all!
Ok. Then I will take just the symbol.
I will make new.
I will thus not need to take your veil.
Straw hat… you are too…
Finished!
Which horror…
They seem to appreciate!
BURST!
Wait a little!
There remain to you always 497 novel members to be chosen.
I want anything else.
The rules are the rules.
You must choose 497 moreover of them, it is all.
Hein? I do not have the choice?
Be to you idiot? Of course that not!
Luffy!
Isn't the orders of the captain are undeniable?
Yes, in this case…
Ah, I see.
What? What?
I see, I included/understood.
Thus I will choose…
You there!
Me?
Yes, of you until…
to you.
Me?
Does Ca make how much?
There are 500 members.
If there remains only Oyabin,
Hamburger-san, and Porch-chan…
Oh, that made to pile 497 people, Luffy Captain.
Yosh! It is decided!
Winners, the crew of the Straw hat!
Davy Back Fight is officially finished!
The new crew of the straw hat is trained!
But one cannot sail on
Merry with so much of people.
Ben, one has that to sail with
sexy Foxy and to follow them.
Ouais, it is not badly.
What do you tell?
Sexy Foxy is MY boat!
“Your boat”?
You cannot sail with if
large ship with only 3 people.
Impossible.
It is impossible.
Very well, the guy!
Make good voyage, former Boss!
Does not catch cold!
Do not forget to brush the teeth!
Oi, Straw hat!
You will pay me that…!
How long will they still amuse us?
Yosh, my comrades!
I will give the first mission to
new pirates of the Straw hat!
Achieve it with brilliance!
Would be sure!
Gomu Oyabin!
You ARE TRANSFERED!
Transfered?
Ouais, transfered.
Isn't the orders of the Captain are irrefutable?
You can turn over to your first crew,
head of puzzle or no matter who.
In any event, you are transfered!
It is all.
Former Boss, await us!
One is always of Foxy Pirates.
They are like mercenaries.
It would be said that it is finished.
Do not worry you, they gained.
Well, well. I will not use any more stilts.
Let us find the village, it does not matter
the number of years that will take to us.
You!
I have boot to them the bottom.
You are amoché enough.
It is always like that.
Thank you.
I see, it is thus for that you accepted the challenge.
Lastly, you would have accepted in any event.
He, it is malicious that!
What occurs?
Be to you which you?
I return you the question!
This… This thing spoke!
It is not “this thing”,
it is a taaaaaaaupe.
“Do Taaaaaaaupe”, you want to say… mole?
I' m has champion!
Yes!
Still an odd guy…
Which kind of champion?
Content that you it requests!
I am the champion of digging of holes,
who personally defied old the tenant du titer.
You have just destroyed the house of Ossan with
stilts, what makes of you a champion?!
Ossan with the stilts?
You see? It is a taaaaaaaupe.
Ittonto, soon I will try the record
world of the largest stilts.
It is far, but I will return in 2 or 3 days.
With this mole, you will not be alone. Will Ca go?
Of agreement, but tries to return
with the championship!
Of course, I promise it to you.
It could be that you would be…
It is me.
Large father!
Ittonto!
I missed you! I missed you so much!
You ace really grown since the last time that I saw you.
Afflicted you to have anxious.
They is the peeeetit-wire of ossan?
It is with the words “I want to re-examine Grand Father”
in my head, which I started to dig.
But rather quickly it became my
objective to be the best digger.
And, champion?
Aim at the ground!
Be to you exactly like Ossan with the stilts…
Oh? Really?
One does not compliment oneself!
Say, if you are the hole, you would have
to be able to join your village not?
You ace of the Ossan chance.
Ah, I do not know how you to thank.
Do not make any you.
Thank you with you, Born-san, I completed my true objective!
I will never forget what you did for me!
Thank you!
Take care of you!
You too. I wish you good luck.
Well, allons-y…
Was Nami, the Log reloaded?
Yes, they is good.
In this case, allons-y.
Ouais.
As quickly let us find an engineer naval as possible!
Yosh, the guy!
Quickly let us find an engineer naval!
OUAIS!