Sandai Kitetsu and Yubashiri!
New sabers of Zoro, and the Staff sergeant
Meitô: a blade of named
Shigure: Rain of Fall
Wadô Ichimonji: the direct Way towards the Harmony
Mono Oowaza: Great Achievements of Skill
Saijô Oowaza Mono: Creations of Supreme Skill
Ryû Waza Mono: Good Parts of Skill
Sandai Kitetsu: the 3rd Trenching one of Demon
Nidai Kitetsu: the 2nd Trenching one of Demon
Shodai Kitetsu: the 1st Trenching one of Demon
Yubashiri: the Snow-covered Step
Ouah, this city is immense.
Many pirates are supplied here before moving towards Grand Line.
I will buy good material to me.
I am sure that one can unearth much good things to be eaten here…
And much of pretty girls too!
Me also I have something to buy!
Good Ah, Zoro, and how?
Well, I will throw an eye with the bracket.
Burst!
My glasses! My glasses!
Is He, it that which you seek?
Afflicted…
It should be refunded to me!
You fall well.
You can say to me where is the bracket?
Follow the direction indicated by smoke.
Let us raise our glass to its health!
With the eternal Lord of the Pirates!
This type with the straw hat,
it is Monkey D. Luffy!
It is here that the Lord of the Pirates died…
Here that the Âge d'or of the Pirates started.
The last vision which the Lord of the Pirates had before dying, I want also to see it!
Well, a little grimpette!
Colonel Smoker, where do you go?
With the bracket.
I want to see it… The place where the Lord of the Pirates died.
It is there that it will be.
You speak about Monkey D. Luffy?
100 of our men are ready to capture it.
Loans to be fought until death!
You do not pigez or what?
I will only go, that will be enough.
He!
He, kid.
What?
I am a little there occupied.
It is well you? The most required criminal in any East Blue?
I am called Luffy.
Does Y' have a problem?
I am here the captain of the base of the Navy with Logue Town, Smoker.
I come to stop you!
Ah, to stop me?
I refuse!
I will install for Grand Line and will become the Lord of the Pirates!
The Lord of the Pirates?
Therefore, how I could make me stop here?
Then you will have to beat me.
If you do not arrive there, you are not likely any to enter Grand Line.
It is the rule here.
Thus all will depend on you, if you have courage to fight against me.
I must overcome you if I want to go in Grand Line?
Then I will beat you!
Thus test.
This type… is a man-rubber band!
Shit! My feet are wedged!
Moron! What you insane?
It is not my fault, they are my feet…
Yes! I am free!
Too much slow!
You, you would be worth 30 million Berrys?
I do not even need to use my capacities of the Fruit of the Demon.
My fists will largely be enough.
I arrive!
I was pilot what here did without 20 years ago.
This guy who had the pride and the ambition to be the Lord of the Pirates, in his last moments.
You, the Lord of the Pirates? Do not make me laugh, you are not even able to reach Grand Line.
It is useless, even if you manage to raise you.
Bah, how knowledge as long as I didn't test?
Allons-y!
Oh not!
Ouahh! Am plantéééééé to me!
What is it that this kid?
Ah! I finally found you, my dear Miss!
Shit, I made error.
Thank you, so long.
But however…
It is really cracking!
Thank you for your purchases!
Can He, I have that too?
What does it still manufacture him?
As envisaged.
According to the charts, it passed well by here.
The hour of our revenge finally sounded.
You think of being able to finish some with him?
Obviously!
That which will die is…
Swelled… It is you?
Captain! There…
Ouah, I flew bloody far…
And it was which this guy initially?
What will I make now?
I have well time… for a small nap.
Does He, that go?
He died?
Where you go?
You broke my glasses, not?
But I said to you
that I was going you to refund them.
You do not seem to have much money.
And moreover, you seem to hide something.
I do not have money, it is true…
Rings around your eyes…
They say that you are somebody who apparently, did not eat days since.
Your mother is very sick,
or you left your wife
leaving only to nourish five children?
Euh…
I do not force myself to answer myself!
Is, it is to me all.
… Navy?
Hold!
Our caretaker resigned this morning.
As long as you will work for the Navy, you will not have any money worry.
Which chance, you don't believe?
You insane of me?
Why should I work for the Navy?
You want to flee?
You take the kindness of the others for acquired?
Therefore, you want to say that you are concerned less poverty with
your heart that of that with your hands?
Euh…
Staff sergeant, it is the hour of the exercises!
Well, do of tone better, agreement?
Staff sergeant?
I bought full with businesses.
Still a last shop…
Navy?
Pfff! Why do I do that?
Is Zoro… in the Navy?
One will make as if I had not seen it.
Shit! How one can do something with that?
Three brushes, it is better after all…
You! What do you make here?
I know it!
It is him, Zoro, the hunter of pirates!
Why does it clean our grounds?
It belongs to the crew of Monkey D. Luffy!
You are in a state of arrest!
Good, I do what now?
What did it occur?
It would be said that they were attacked!
Their attacker fled!
“Money for the glasses”?
Which shock…
Shit!!!
It is really the spit portrait of Kuina. And moreover,
it is a fencer who uses a katana.
It would be said that the world is really small…
In any event, I do not think any more of re-examining it.
I want to buy katanas.
Well, well, well.
Welcome.
Take your time to look at.
Has this shop existed for 200 years, you knew?
I have 100 OOO Berrys.
Sell to me two katanas.
Hein? 100.000 Berrys for two katanas?
Is Pfff, this type mown or what?
For 50.000 each one, you will have only rotted sabers.
That will be always better than anything.
I do not have much money in any event.
“That will be always better than anything” than he says…
That must be an amateur…
This saber…
He, He, He this ka… katana…
I p… can… the v… see a dryness… second?
Why are you nervous like that?
Go, show!
Which odd type…
I do not manage to believe in it!
Oh… Ohhh… The calm one.
They is not the every day that a beginner brings one of famous “the Meitô” in my shop!
It is necessary that I speak calmly.
This katana is in sorry state,
but I want to give you some Berrys of it well.
I give you 200.000 of them Berrys.
Thus that will make you 300.000 Berrys,
and you will be able to buy three katanas with 100.000 Berrys.
Hein? What do you tell?
Well!
I… I give you 250.000 of them.
Not? 300.000?
500.000 then?
Whatever the sum which you will offer for this katana…
Very well! You gained ace! 650.000 Berrys!
I included/understood, are to you a businessman!
I buy it to you for 800.000 Berrys!
Hello!
I come to recover my Shigure.
It is ready?
Ah! I am content.
You do not have anything!
Somebody was introduced into the base of the Navy presently!
And then you disappeared.
I believed that it had arrived to you something.
It is what its problem with that one?
I am reassured.
But, since you are well,
that wants to say that you rejected the charity of your next while preferring to flee of an honest work.
Your money.
Take it again!
I refuse to accept money of a person who acts like that.
And then I already repurchased myself glasses.
Ahh! This katana! Not possible!
It is Wadô Ichimonji?
It is Wadô Ichimonji, it is that?
Wadô?
Keep silent yourself! Keep silent yourself!
What a splendid completion!
No the doubt, it is one of 21 Oowaza Mono!
Here! Look at that.
This sword is worth more than 20 million Berrys!!
But… why somebody as it has you one of famous Meitô?
YOU!!! You said to him!
What you interfere yourself,
you sabotage my business!
To sabotage your business?
Excuse me.
I said something that one did not have?
Came to you for your Shigure, hein?
Here it is! I sharpened it.
Take and releases it!
Why suited you by there?
It is what your problem?
I… I am sorry.
Pfff! This small idiot you ace saved the setting.
This sword is indeed Meitô.
A sword which an amateur as does not deserve you to carry.
The katanas in these barrels are to 50.000 Berrys.
Take two and leave my shop!
Why is it put in this state?
You… really the sabers, isn't this likes?
Since you carry three from there…
That makes me think of this bargain hunter…
An bargain hunter, hein?
He is very famous. He is called Roronoa.
I heard this name much.
Yes, everyone in East Blue
knows its reputation of large fencer.
But it is a demon!
To use a katana as means to earn money, it is unforgivable!
Which funny of time when the evil is so powerful.
The large fencers all of the world are is pirates,
maybe of the bargain hunters.
All large are Meitô of the world between their hands, you knew?
The katanas cry.
Must Bah, they have their reasons, you do not believe?
It is necessary to live with its time.
Lastly, I swear on Shigure that
I will become a large fencer and will involve myself to improve!
And then I will travel of share the world, and I will recover Meitô of the hands of these gangsters!
12 Saijô Oowaza Mono legendary.
21 Mono Oowaza.
And 50 Ryû Waza Mono.
Even if I must leave the life there!
You want to recover that one too?
Is Wadô Ichimonji, it well that?
Eh! I did not want to say that I wanted to have all Meitô!
It is right which I do not support that they are between bad hands.
Hein? This katana…
This katana… perhaps that…
Yes, it is that! Sandai Kitetsu.
It is Sandai Kitetsu!
Its predecessor, Nidai Kitetsu, was one of Oowaza Mono!
And Shodai Kitetsu was one of Saijô Oowaza Mono!
Mister!
You want to really sell this katana for only 50.000 Berrys?
It is extraordinary!
It is an exceptional saber!
You, you should take it!
Its value is estimated at nearly a million Berrys.
It is a super business!
Not question!
I do not sell it!
It is well what I said.
This sword for 50.000 Berrys,
I found that odd.
Not, it is not for that…
It is cursed.
You knew it?
Not, I feel it.
Kitetsu are excellent katanas,
but they all are cursed.
All the fencers who used Kitetsu during time,
knew fine tragedies and mysterious deaths.
You will not find anybody who wants to use Kitetsu because all their predecessors died.
I wanted to remove me from this dirtiness because of the curse…
I… I am sorry!
I did not imagine this so terrible thing!
I will not have had to interfere me.
I like it.
I take it!
Be to you… Be to you nut? If I sell it to you and that you are made kill, it will be of my fault!
It is you that are nut!
Sell it and then it is all!
Ché… Darling!
What do you say that?
My chance… or curse of this sword…
Let us see which of both is strongest!
Not!
Stop! Its edge is exceptional!
You will cut yourself the arm!
I take it.
Do He, you want me to choose another of them well?
Euh… Yes!
With… Wait!
The sleeve covered with a long mosaic, enamelled in black.
The blade, the wire slicing like a razor.
Ryû Waza Mono, Yubashiri.
My shop is not very large,
but it is best the katana than I have.
I do not have the means.
I already said it, not?
I do not have money.
Not, the money forgets.
And I do not want money either for Kitetsu.
I excuse myself to have wanted to mislead you presently.
Too for a long time I did not cross a true fencer.
It is said that a katana chooses its Master.
I will request so that the chance remains with you.
Y' does not have to say, three sabers, it is well better.
Eh well, eh well…
I do not manage to believe that a skinflint as the saber of our family gave you.
Which evil is there so that a man transmits his dream to another man?
Very well, then leave the refuse now!
Yes!
I do not return from there…
I am able even more to raise me.
Ahh! I slept well.
Well, ahead!
I turn over to the bracket!
You found it?
Not, not yet.
Be sure for you that you saw Straw hat?
Yes, no doubt!
Very well, continue to seek!
Ouais!
But where is the bracket?
Straw hat… Straw hat…
Is Ahhh, where it?
Is Ahhh, where?
Dumb…
It is by where?
You seek what?
Where is the bracket?
By there.
Thank you.
AHHH!! It WAS…
Find Luffy!
It owes planquer some share here in Logue Town!
Yes!
I did not already say you not to howl,
that stops my thoughts.
It is not kind with planquer.
That will go, I will find it.
Colonel Smoker, that did occur?
Tashigi, where devil had you passed?
Co… Colonel, the aggressor…
You are awaked.
I am reassured.
You are well?
It was Roronoa Zoro.
One was attacked by Zoro the hunter of pirates!
Zoro?
Why would it have attacked you?
It is necessary that I capture it.
It is necessary that I find where is the bracket.
The last vision which the Lord of the Pirates had before dying, I want to see it!