You... insignlficant bug!
Waiter boy!
Even if you're equipped with hundreds of weapons,
You still might not be able to defeat the one 'spear' he has.
At least...
That kid...
Has no hint of hesitation.
Is it that he has what it takes to survive?
Or does his conviction mean he refuses to die.
Conviction?
This is your grave!
What?! My Great Battle Spear!
What did you do it?!
I gave it five punches in a row.
Your spear's useless now.
Why, that bastard's not bad at all.
Maybe we can pull this one off!
This is no good!
He broke the Great War Spear?
But being hit by those huge blasts,
His body won't be able to take much more.
OUTCOME OF A DEADLY BATTLE!
THE SPEAR INSIDE!
You get the picture now?
This much space should be plenty for me.
This much space will be enough to pulverize you!
What?
That thing of yours.
That spear's all broken.
It's nothing but a bomb-on-a-stick now.
Its power has halved.
You think so?
Yeah!
Bomb-on-a-stick, eh? That's not so bad.
Its power is sufficient to blast you outta here.
You're all battered up. Looks
like you're barely making it.
No, I'm not.
Behold!
Since you dared to defy the great Don Krieg,
You are sentenced to death!
I'm not gonna die, so there!
Hey! Over here!
You li'l monkey!
Die!
Stupid bastard.
No use!
How many weapons does this guy have?!
GOMU GOMU NO...
GATLING GUN!!!
What in the world is that?
His arms have multiplied!
Hey! Waiter boy!
That a boy!
Useless!
Against this metal armor,
your punches are useless.
It didn't even leave a scratch.
GOMU GOMU NO PISTOL!
Don!
Cut this crap!
Boring! Boring!
This is absolutely boring!
How could this armor possibly break with only a
few hundred punches from this little monkey?
I think I'm almost there.
He's gone!
Over here.
Listen,
with the best-crafted equipment, the greatest
power, and most powerful weapons,
You'll be acknowledged to be strong.
A very powerful person!
And that'd be me!
GOMU GOMU NO...
That's totally useless!
You can't do much with persistence alone.
BAZOOKA!!!
It's no use!
This is the limit of your strength.
What?!
My invincible armor is breaking?
But it's too late.
You're done for, Hammerboy!
It's a trap! Run!!
Waiter boy!!
Having what it takes to survive...
Refusing to die...
GOMU GOMU NO...
What?!!
BAZOOKA!!!
Great! Yeah!
You're great, waiter boy!
I WIN!
You wish, damn brat!
He's still alive!
Oh no.
You can't run away from this iron net?
The sea is below us!
It's clear who the victor is, hammerboy!
I'm always the one who has the last laugh!
That's our Don for ye!
Get rid of him!
Yeah!
No problem, 'coz my hands and feet are still free.
Why don't you just stand down?
Why all this?
What?!
This time...
It's really over!
GOMU GOMU NO...
SLEDGEHAMMER!!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Don Krieg's defeated...
How can he be defeated? How?!
Way to go, waiter boy!
Great!
That guy did it!
Awesome!
Is this for real?
But that was Don Krieg!
He's just too powerful... He's something else!
What's all the ruckus?
You're up now?
He's defeated.. your Don has lost.
What?!
If you've got the time to space out,
why don't you go and rescue him?
He's not going to resurface, you know.
What?!
Those who gain powers from the devil
fruit are cast away by the sea,
becoming deadweight in waters.
What'd you say, old fart?!
Why didn't you say so earlier?!
I'll hold you responsible if anything happens!
Where is he?
Hey, hang in there!
Aren't you the one who refuses to die?
Isn't that what you believe in?
I'm not gonna die.
This isn't my grave.
Damn it.
Zoro!!!
If you already knew the outcome
why didn't you give up?
It's simple! Just let go of your ambitions!
All of em...
I don't know.
I'm not sure why myself.
But if I were to take even one step back,
I believe that all those important oaths, promises,
and many other deals 'til now,
Will all go to waste and I'll never be able
to return before you, ever again.
You still can't do much against
the one 'spear' he has.
Someone who'd hold that same spear
for his own foolish reasons.
All Blue!
Hey, waiter boy!
Don't you dare die on me now!
Don, what's wrong?!
Why's the Don..?
Don Krieg lost?
No way...
He's the King of the East Blue.
That man... that man...
Even if you say so,
See for yourself!
The armor he's so proud of is shattered to bits!
This is a must see!
Won't you have a look?
He's the only man I've admired.
I always believed that he's the best.
Hang on a sec, bud!
The poison will spread all over
your body if you move about!
Lie down!
That'd be fatal!
Don't say we didn t warn you!
Waiter boy!
You can't die, you hear?!
You've got things to do, don't you?
Hey, you can't just die!
Waiter boy, say something...
Say something already!
Waiter boy, don't die!
Why you...
You're such a pain in the butt.
I'm the strongest.
It's me! It's me who won!
No one can surpass my powers!
Don, not that!
Hold him! He's unconscious!
Don't do that, Don!
I have to win with my power!
I must win!
I'm the strongest man!
Don Krieg...
We've lost.
Commander!
Let's retreat and start all over again.
Thanks for everything, Sanji-san.
Come here again, wont' ye?
Sanji-san,
Give him this message for me when he gets up...
Tell him that we shall meet again at the Grand Line.
But, you..?
I've given much thought into it.
It's the only thing I want to do.
I'm not sure when Don Krieg's ambition
became mine as well, but...
I may only have a few hours to live.
It's kinda weird for me declaring my decision,
just because I'm running out of time.
But this time, I want to do what I want to do.
Trusting my instincts.
Then I won't have anywhere to run anymore.
What loyalty do I have to Don Krieg?
I've just been using Don Krieg's name
as a shield so I could run away.
When your mind's made up, you eventually
pay less attention to things like,
Being scared of a strong enemy, or
how not to get yourself injured.
That's what he taught me.
Patty! Carne!
Give him the ship we use to get supplies!
What? Are you serious?
Why should we give the pirates a ship?
How are you expecting us to get our food, idiot?!
That's right!
People like him should just go swim in the sea!
Shut up and just get it already!
Fine!
You don't have to shout at us!
We're getting it! We're gonna get it!
Hey, it's sinking! It's gonna sink!
In the past, I used to worry about every little detail.
I feel so dumb for doing so.
See ye.
I'll be taking this.
I don't have to return it, do I?
Nope.
Try if you dare, bastard.
Hey! Remember now!
For this is the fighting sea restaurant, Baratie!
What an annoying bunch.
They're really nice people.
Next time we meet,
I wonder if they'll let me join 'em again?
I don't know if I'll even get a chance to.
I want to be free!
Bellemere-san!