Laki!
What are you doing?
You're going to die if you just hang there.
Is this stuff worth dying over?
Kamakiri!
Yeah, I was just going to bring this wood over to the ship so i can repair it tomorrow.
And were you planning to swim across?
Those huge sharks are still lurking in there.
Look at this.
This is the topography of Jaya, 400 years ago.
Wow, a skull!
It looks like a skull!
Well?
Kamakiri...
What about your injuries...?
I can still fight!
You're right. If there's any time to take out Upper Yard, it's now.
In today's battle, the effects of Satori's absence were clear.
Tomorrow morning, we must attack again, Wiper!
GOD ENEL APPEARS!!
AUBADE TO THE SURVIVORS
C'mon, Zoro, please.
Just for a little bit...
Why do I have to go with you?
How old are you?
If you're scared, just hold it 'til morning.
Yeah but i really have to go,
but i dont want to die...
That's what im thinking...
Oh, you're so cold, Zoro!
Idiot...
Aw, jeez...
What's that sound?
There shouldn't be anyone on the ship...
The mist's so thick I can't see...
Gh-Gh-Gho...
What's with him?
He said he was gonna take a piss, and now he's sleeping out here?
He's hopeless.
Gh-Gho...
Gh-Ghos...
Quit dreaming!
Gh-Gho-Ghost!
Gho...st!
We...
It must be to talk...
...with your bottom lip inside your mouth!
How careless...
Didn't i tell you?
Enel-sama summoned us here...
...because you let Wiper escape!
It's nothing to panic about.
No Shandian will escape from me again.
That is their fate!
Heh, that's nothing but a lame excuse!
If only Enel-sama...
...had left all of the duties to me,
We would have been victorious this very day!
Gedatsu.
An idiot like you could never do that.
WHAT!?
Let me warn you two.
Otherwise you will lose control of your Mantra...
....and repeat Satori's faillure.
You're the one who needs to learn humility, Ohm!
Defeating Gan Fall is nothing to get cocky about, Shura!
This looks like fun!
God, the Priests have arrived.
Open the door.
Not again.
What are you doing?
You are absolutely disgraceful.
Shut up!
With these two fools in my way...
...i'm never able to unleash my full power!
If i was allowed to guard the island by myself,
I could work much better!
You talk pretty big!
I should teach you a lesson about the limits of your full power!
With the Truth of Sorrow...
The Ordeal of Iron!
A bore! Your Ordeal means nothing!
My Swamp presents the greatest Ordeal!
Would you like to try it?
Gedatsu-sama.
If you persist in doing that, you will tire yourself.
Please cross your arms and place your hands on your elbows.
How careless!
Enough!
God is before you!
Before us?
Then where exactly is He?
Didn't He summon us here!?
Just where is Enel-sama...!?
Caught you by surprise!
I am God.
(''ware ga kaminari'' - ''I am lightning'')
I'm right here.
You need more training.
I do not desire any failures akin to which befell Satori.
What was that for?
Indeed.
Making light sport of us...
Is that why were summoned here?
I was bored.
But sit down.
You three do not seem preoccupied by the Blue Sea dwellers.
Enel-sama, if this is about Satori...
He was still inexperienced.
With that absurd Ordeal of Balls.
And that is why i call you pitiful, Shura.
Gan Fall is alive.
Impossible!
I finished off Gan Fall myself!
He has yet to fully recover.
He and the Blue Sea dwellers seem to be along quite well.
A tenacious old man indeed.
But what do those Blue Sea dwellers want?
What they want...
...is Gold.
Gold?
How did they learn of that?
This island used to reside on the Blue Sea.
Of course, they will move tomorrow.
And the Shandians will renew their attack.
Here on Upper Yard, you each have your own area to govern,
Tomorrow, I will open all the land to you.
You may work your Ordeals anywhere you please.
And disregarding the rule, you may conduct yourseleves in as violent a manner as you see fit.
Why grant us so much power so suddenly?
Because it's already been completed...
The Maxim, that is.
It's about time we finish off this island and set out on our journey...
To the World of Dreams.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
To think that these children could defeat Satori...
That will make Enel their enemy.
And Shandia will not let this chance pass by.
Enel...
What is it that you want?
The effects were indeed clear.
Today, we will invade God's Shrine!
And then, Enel...
Look! It's just like i said!
Someone must have been here!
The Going Merry's...
...been repaired!
I saw it!
I knew it wasn't a dream!
You're right.
Even the broken mast's been repaired!
Indeed.
It must have been quite a chore simply standing up something this heavy.
But, I'm sorry to say...
He did a piss-poor job of it.
There's a nice guy out there!
There was someone here.
I saw him!
But, who would come all the way out here to fix our ship?
The only ones on Upper yard are us and our enemies.
But, he took off the Flying Model, Usopp.
Yeah.
That's what's even stranger about it.
Hey, how did the guy fixed it...
...know what Merry was supposed to look like?
He knew she didn't have a comb, or wings, or tail.
Who did you see, Usopp?
It was a dream. There's nothing else it could have been.
Oi, hey!
What are you guys goofing off for?
There's a lot to do.
Doesn't it bother you, Nami?
What?
That someone repaired the Going Merry.
It would be one thing if it was destroyed.
But since it's all fixed up, what's the problem?
Are you gonna go through the trouble of finding this guy so you can thank him?
Well, no, but...
How did he know?
Hey, Merry, can you hear me?!
Listen up.
It's time for usopp-sama, the chief of Operation,
Get Merry off the Sacrificial Altar, to make his appearance!
Watch me closely!
I'm the vice-chief of Operation Get Merry off the Sacrificial Altar!
They're gonna be relying on me!
What are you going to do, Usopp?
Yosh!
Chopper!
Aye!
Launch!
GO!
Yeah! He did it!
Chopper, floor it!
Awesome!
You're awesome, Usopp!
Usopp...
It didn't work...
Don't worry about it, Chopper.
Besides, I've prepared a secret plan for this very occasion!
Really? What kind of plan?
There's huge Skysharks swimming around here, right?
Yep, yep!
There's scores of them!
What if we used their power?
The Skysharks' power?
Right!
They're really strong!
I can speak to that!
There's something I'd like you to do.
Sure, whatever you say!
You can count on me!
I'll do anything.
Yeah?
Well said!
Usopp!
Does... this mean... that I'm...
The hungry Skysharks are gonna try to eat you!
I'm the bait!?
No, no!
I don't wanna be the bait!
HELP!!
Let 'er rip, Sanji!
Yosh!
Come and get it, Skyshark.
NO!!
DON'T MOVE!!
MOVE!
Yosha!
Yes! Yes! Usopp, banzai!
Yeah, it was nothing!
NO!!
Alright, look at the map.
The route the exploration team will be taking is...
...directly south.
Here to the right there should be some ruins.
Beware of all the enemies along the way and bring back the gold!
You make it sound easy.
If it involves investigating ruins, I'll gladly do it.
What about you?
You keep talking about gold and more gold and you're not gonna come?
Of course not!
It's scary there.
She wants the gold, but she's not willing to risk anything to get it!
Nami's strange! A real weirdo!
You say something?
Meanwhile, we'll take the Merry through the island.
It's be dangerous for us too.
We'll be heading towards the coast as fast as we can, so...
Let's meet here!
And then we'll escape from Sky Island!
We'll become a rich pirate crew!
Alright!
All the meat I can eat!
Escape...
That sounds great!
DON'T MAKE ME THE BAIT!
Look!
The Weather's perfect!
We're on top of the clouds, so yeah.
So, we'll all meet safely on the east coast!
Yosh!
Let's get going then!
Aye!
Who will encounter my Ordeal of String?
The Shandians?
Or the Blue Sea dwellers?
The festival is starting.
It shall be magnificient.
Today is a great day.