To deliver princess Vivi!
Pirates of Luffy on the departure
Bandage the bastard ones!
It was which them?
It is…
What a force!
Incredible.
Now,
our combat is continued!
Yes!
Stop!!
I do not believe in it!
What you made, brothel?
You have chance that the girl is unscathed!
You know that you failed to cost me 1 billion Berrys?
You include/understand?
You there…
About what do speak you?
Why did you save me?
Ah yes.
We must speak about it.
What would you say to negotiate a contract with me?
A contract?
Stop beating you!
Crowned Zoro!
Why you did not say it to me?
I believed that you had become insane and that you all had killed them
just because they had not made you your favorite dish!
Is species of cretin, it what you would have done?
Eh well, does not worry you any more for that!
You two, the farm!
Therefore, here is our offer.
We want 1 billion Berrys to escort you in full safety over there.
You how these guys are strong, isn't this saw?
It is a good deal, you do not believe?
Impossible.
You have my gratitude to have saved me the life.
Thank you!
Why not?
Is not this is to you a Princess?
It is right a small billion…
You know the country named Arabasta?
Not.
It was a large pillar of civilization.
A ground of peace.
It was a long time ago.
A long time?
And now?
A civil war is preparing.
These last years, a call to the revolution was launched.
Citizens began from the acts of insurrection
involving the country towards chaos.
But one day, I heard the name of a secret organization:
Works baroque!
I discovered that they were responsible for the incentive to the rebellion.
Moreover, beside that,
I could not get any information to me.
Then, I spoke in Igaram, which deals with me since my childhood.
The old man with the hair chikuwa?
Chikuwa = Kind of fish roller
Chiku? yes, it is him.
I decided to infiltrate Baroque Works.
I thought that by doing it, I would learn some more on
those which draw the strings and which were their plans.
You ace of the testicles for a Princess.
And? you discovered their intentions?
The assertion of an ideal nation.
Igaram-San already said it to me.
It could be…
Yes.
They tell that a “ideal Nation” is their goal.
But it is a lie.
Their real intention is to go up on the throne of Arabasta!
I must turn over in my country to say the truth to the people,
and to prevent them from joining the rebellion!
If that continues…
I include/understand.
Then here what occurs.
All has a direction finally.
If a civil war is close,
the money must be rare.
Then which is the thinking head?
True identity of the Boss?
Do not ask it to me!
But you know it, not?
Do not ask!
I cannot say it to you!
If I say it to you, they will track you too!
Indeed, that is not wanted.
And of course, to try to capture a whole nation…
Isn't Ca must be a super guy extremely?
Yes!
Whatever your force, it is not possible to believe that you will be able to touch it.
One of Shichibukai…
Shichibukai = one of the Captains Corsairs
Crocodile!
It is which?
You have just said it?
Is He, it what this otter and this vulture?
Afflicted! Afflicted! Afflicted! I am sorry!!!
One of Shichibukai will continue to us now!
She said “Shichibukai”!
Not badly!
What will arrive to us?
I am sorry!
Ca slipped out of my mouth!
To be sorry will not change anything for us maintaining!
Now, you mingled us with all that!!
We arrive just on Grand Line and us here are tracked at died by Shichibukai…
Why me?
There is bowl, one will fight one of them soon.
Does I wonder what it resemble?
Your mouths you two!
Even if that were not long, very glad to have made your knowledge with all!
Where you go?
They did not see me yet, therefore I release!
Hahaha! You are gifted!
Not! Now, I cannot even flee?
I am really sorry!
These guy are enough cools.
In any event, where would we be flee?
In any case, three among us were added with the list of died of Works Baroque.
It is if exciting!
I have economies… Approximately 500.000 Berrys…
You do not worry!
Do not fear…
Do not fear anything!
I have a plan!
Igaram!
It is for what to make this clothing?
Old man, you would mislead no matter whom while carrying that!
My God! I am surrounded cretins!
Vivi-Sama, listen to me attentively.
The information network of Works Baroque will receive soon this report/ratio.
Once they will know that we are those who know the true identity of the Boss,
you what will arrive, isn't this knows?
A thousand of hunters will be after us.
Therefore I got dressed like a Princess.
I will leave with these three factitious headstocks
and I will make course directly on Arabasta.
It is us that?
Lures.
Once they will have started to continue me,
Vivi-Sama and yourselves will be able to leave in full safety for Arabasta.
Wait one minute!
Who said that we would take along the Princess some share?
We still do not have a contract.
To take along the Princess?
What does that want to say?
You did not listen to them?
The old man wants that one brings back it to it.
Is Oh, it of that they speak?
Ok!
Crocodile will try to kill us!!
This Crocodile, it is really so strong that?
It is one of Shichibukai.
Therefore, as a pirate elected by the government,
it is not any more on their list of settings at price.
But before this decision, its head was worth 80 million Berrys.
80 Million?
They is four times the price of Arlong!
Stop it!
Will you accept?
Ouais!
Ca seems funny.
You have my deeper gratitude.
Well, now, me Vivi, I will leave…
The old man, you are like it!
Like which?
Now Princess, give me Eternal Pose.
Does Eternal Pose?
You never intended some to speak?
I will explain you:it is a version solidified for the eternity of the Log Poses.
The Log Poses guides you from one island to another,
But Eternal Pose never forgets the magnetic field of the island on which it was regulated.
It should eternally point towards this island.
And this one points on Arabasta.
With that you will arrive at Arabasta.
Vivi-Sama, after having marked some pauses,
you direct quickly towards Arabasta.
I never did it myself,
but I am certain that you can follow the Log two or three times to arrive there.
And now, I leave the Princess to your care.
Of course!
Igaram.
I think that the tour will be dangerous.
Please, made attention on the way.
Iga…
You too.
We should re-examine us on our premises.
The safety of our country is between your hands.
Well, it left.
It was a sympathetic old man, not?
Yes, we can count on him.
Impossible!
It is not possible!
They are already there?
It was a man well!!
Nami, the Log!
They is good! It is already regulated!
It catches!
Go to the boat!
Vivi! Vivi!
Quickly!
If they see us here, all that will have been used for nothing, not?
Ca will go!
One will bring back for you at home!
You see these guy?
They do not have the air like that of it…
Oi Luffy! Take the two others!
But they saved any East Blue!
I will seek the boat!
Just with them four!
Ok! I go there!
What does Baroque Works represent for them?
And Crocodile?
Shichibukai does not have any chance!
One goes there!
What you insane brothel, Luffy? He!
You will break me the nose!
Release to me brothel!!
What you insane?
Hurry Vivi!
Karu is not there…
What a idiotic!
To make the lure.
He, I have them!
Go up, one is ready to leave!
Hein?
The guy you still sleep…
We do not have time to seek it for the moment!
But I cannot leave it all alone here!
But, you know…
He! What is there?
She says that its duck asshole is not there!
She said that it should have come when she whistled it but it did not come!
That one?
You were all this time there?
It was already on board when I arrived.
If we sail on the river, we will lead to the sea.
We will be able to get under way more quickly.
Allons-y!!
Mr. Bushido!
About how much hunters do speak we with the Juste?
I do not know!
Baroque Works has approximately 2000 employees.
And I intended to say that there are other cities like this one in the surroundings.
Good blood, 2000 people?
Does He… the boat move?
You are finally debouts?
Wait! Let us remain another night!
Yes!
One had fun so and the girls were so nice!!
When will we find a city also brilliant?
Slow down brothel!
We are to pir…
It is not even yet the morning!
They still do not know what occurs…
He! Explain to them…
Oh… It is done!
It was fast…
Yes, I jumped the tedious details!
We soon will leave the island.
Cool! Fog!
It will make soon day.
Eh well, it is a good thing to have escaped with your prosecutors!
It is sure!
Made attention with the hollows not to burst the hull.
You can count on me!
Was Euh, it you Luffy?
Pretty boat.
Who it is?
You! You are…
I saw Mr. 8 it does not have there a long time,
Wednesday miss.
You killed Igaram!
Even if it is you,
what you insane on my boat?
Who are you?
What you made here?
Miss All Sunday!
Miss All Sunday?
It of which number is the partner this time?
That of Mr. 0.
The partner of the Boss.
That of Crocodile?
Then it is malicious?
It is only authorized to know the true identity of the Boss…
We followed it to know who it was really.
Or to be more precise,
I let to you follow me.
Oh, it is nice.
I knew it!
And thus, that which informed the Boss that its identity was uncovered,
it, isn't this was you?
Correct.
Then, it is malicious!
Remain apart from that.
Which are your intentions with the Juste?
Who knows?
But you were so serious in connection with that,
I just had to cooperate.
A Princess who thinks that it can become the enemy one of Works Baroque and save her country.
It is so ridiculous…
Close it!!
He, Sanji.
An idea what does without?
Not! Not exactly…
But it would be said that the adorable one
Miss Wednesday is in danger.
Could you not point these dangerous things on me?
Impossible!
Oh!
A Fruit…
A Fruit of the Demon?
What?
Which kind of capacity is this thus?
Ouah, seen from here, it is a splendid woman!
Really, do not be so in a hurry.
I do not have any order in this moment,
thus I do not have any reason to fight with you.
Then, you are thus famous Capitaine with the straw hat?
Monkey D. Luffy.
He! Return to me this hat!
You want to fight?
You are not the welcome here,
then releases from our boat, pétasse!
Which bad luck…
You them pirate collecting a Princess that Baroque Works wants dead.
And this Princess is protected by if small number of pirates…
But your greater bad luck
is the road towards which the Log carries out you Poses.
The name of the next island is…
Little Garden.
My expensive small,
you will not arrive whole at Arabasta even if we do not do anything.
You will be destroyed.
I of insane!
Return to me this hat!
Yes bouffonne!!!!!
Be to you a kid or what?
To move so quickly towards its tomb,
doesn't that seem to you so horrible, band the insane ones?
Eternal Poses…
With this, you can avoid Little Garden.
This needle indicates Nanimonaishi very close to Arabasta.
As none of our members knows this road,
you will not be followed.
What?
It helps us?
Why do you do that?
It is obviously a trap.
I wonder.
What do I make?
I do not want to accept something of this kind of it…
But, if I must sail on this boat,
then to take the surest road would be best.
It is what still this trap?
Cretin!
Es you completely idiot?
It has just said to us that it was the best way!!
And if it tried to help us? Then what?
You do not decide a road of the boat!
Oh, as they is unhappy.
It exploded the old man chikuwa,
I hate it!
Eh well, I do not hate those which have a great mind.
If you survive,
we will be re-examined.
Not!
One goes there Banchi!
What is it that?
It is still a monstre marin?
Not, it is…
It is a tortoise!!
It is an enormous tortoise!
This woman…
I do not include/understand what she wants to do!
To try to include/understand is a waste of time.
Yes, we have already people like that on board.
He! Can somebody explain me all that?
I do not know what occurs!
Oh Miss Wednesday, you belonged to the crew now?
He! Does somebody explain me?
We have an ostrich now?
He… What does it occur?
Would you like to eat something?
That somebody explains me all that!!
I see.
I did something of inexcusable but I must always show my capacities.
Ca will go!
Your deadened knight awoke,
and I will make my duty to ensure your safety.
Whore… I am glad to have slept!
Are Nami-San, you jealous?
At all.
I wonder
if all will occur well for me on board your boat.
I do not want to be a ball.
What do you tell?
Thanks to you, we all are put at price.
If you did not want to be a ball, it did not have to be said initially to us.
I am sorry.
Hein, Luffy?
Oh, I am hungry!
I do not believe that he is concerned with it…
In any case, we know our next stop.
Little Garden!
Is well there to be?
Who occupies himself some?
Allons-y, partners!
Yes!!
Yes.
We keep in mind…
Little Garden.