Crocodile of Sands VS Aqua-Luffy!
Fights in Mort, Round 2
You cannot save this country.
Good voyage, Princess.
Crocodile!!
Luffy-San!!
Straw hat!
Luffy is alive!
I will finish this combat.
Once and for all!
When are wet to you, you cannot change into sand.
You ace fear of water.
It is for that you stolen ace the rain.
Now, I will burst you!
We beat!
Rise!
Crocodile!
Go, upright! Vermin!
What do you say?
Will a bomb explode in 10 minutes?
Yes! With 16:30 precisely!
16:30?
If this bomb explodes, it will destroy all in a radius of 5 kms!
It is what Crocodile said!
A radius of 5 kms! Ca wants to say…!
… how the rebellious army and the royal army will be both destroyed!
This dirty Croco of shit…
Q- What do we have to make?
It is necessary to find the bomb planters!
And to stop them!
Bomb planters?
How to find them?
In only 10 minutes?
There are not time to think of that!
But, listen, if the ray of destruction is of 5 kms,
they must be distant from at least 2,5 kms, not?
Not, I do not believe!
They are probably very close to the place!
Q- What?
If they are here, they will jump with the others!
It is well the kind of Crocodile.
To sacrifice its own men?
What a salts bastard!
One would make better hurry!
You were found, Princesse Vivi!
Your death will save to us a large promotion!
Billions!
Less than ten minutes…
...com well of seconds for these?
Hey, hey! Not enough to have even time to discuss it!
2 seconds!
One leaves in front!
Go ahead!
Deviated from my way, cretin!
Exactly what I was going to say!
One separates!
It is necessary to leave this whore of sand cloud!
Only 10 minutes!
Well! Quickly, it is necessary to go there!
Ouais!
It is really… the ultimate limit of time!
The destiny of this country…
… will be sealed…
… in 10 minutes!
You think of being able to beat me?
Ouep, you can change more into sand.
I am impressed enough that included/understood you that with the threshold of death.
But there is still a basic difference which you will not be able to overcome.
It is the level of Shichibukai.
And then, that done no matter what you would be one of Shichibukai?
I will become…
Shichi = 7 Hachi = 8
… Hachibukai!
Who is this boy?
A pirate.
Perhaps that you are not with the current…
but it would seem that the Princess has escaped accuracy with death.
Then it is him which brought back Vivi here?
Ca is not used for nothing!
I do not have that to dodge your attack.
And even if you are covered with water,
my hand can always drain the water of your body!
M- Shit! It can still do that!
It who me it said ace, isn't this is you?
To succeed in having a perfect command of the capacities of the Fruit of the Demon…
… can make invincible.
… and…
Crafty person!
Still this attack?
It did not pass far…
You really think of gaining by always using the same technique?
Ouais!
And how!
I had envisaged that since the beginning!
I will cover you water!
Which foreseeable plan…
The barrel! The barrel!
How you have the pitiful air, Luffy with the straw hat!
You can nothing make without this barrel.
It would be said that nothing changed since our last combat!
It is right.
Up to now, nothing changed.
And now?
I am more same as front one!
Is it insane?
AQUA LUFFY!
Shit! An escape!
Is this kid… serious?
I feel…
I believe that one is not supposed water drinking as much.
Does it include/understand really the situation?
Stop your conneries, kid!
Not!
It is no matter what which call you “conneries”?
My body…!
I am always serious!
Then, it was how?
Croco of sands!
Incredible!
Wounded crocodile…
… by this boy?
It is not the moment to be filled with wonder, Mr. Cobra.
Now, you will lead me…
… at the place where Ponéglyphe is engraved.
Why do you need some?
Do not put stupid questions.
You have just with me to lead to it.
Your chance probably turned.
The countdown… is finished.
Release from there, Nico Robin.
Unless you do not want to also be drained.
I… lost any patience.
Nico Robin?
Well, as you want.
Listen well, Straw hat…
All the stones of the ground will be reduced in crumbs.
The grass is desiccated!
Q- Q Q What??
J- I fall…
I failed to make me have!
This bastard!
He aspired all water with his hand!
Do you think of being able to block my capacities, Aqua Luffy?
If it is the case, you are mistaken seriously.
The capacity of sand rests in its capacity to drain any thing.
Look at!
My right hand drains all that it touches.
Indefinitely…
Stone!
Even the statues change into sand!
The ground… dies!
My sandals too!
All that touches this hand…
… dies!
Where are they?
And where they hide?
More that 8 minutes!
One can still find them in 8 minutes!
No matter what it arrives, it is necessary to prevent this bomb from exploding!
Without what, more than one million people will die!
A bomb with a ray of destruction of 5 kms!
One is not speaking about a small bomb of shit!
Would they be in it?
Shit!
Go! In 8 minutes, Alubarna will be nothing any more but one heap of ruins!
In 8 minutes, we all will be died!
There are not time to panic!
R- Look at!
Ca must be that!
There are only 8 minutes to find the way until up there!
He!
And shit!
Summers you… a rebel?
Pas le time for the courtesies.
Thus rest a little!
Ca is there! It is that!
Not! That one is very covered with foam!
No sign of them!
Where are they?
Nothing which resembles a gun!
Why?
More that 7 minutes!
I must stop it!
At all costs!
Nico Robin? Is this your true name there?
What can that make well?
I do not see in what that looks at you.
20 years ago, a young girl of this name became tristement célèbre in the whole world.
Why would it re-appear now?
The only thing that you have to make, it is me to lead to Ponéglyphe.
They to trail by here, isn't this is dangerous, Miss Navy?
Let pass to me.
I am in a hurry.
I will not authorize it!
A wounded soldier told me what occurred here, in Alubarna!
Do you know which is the person that you retain?
It does not matter which it is!
I hate any person related to the Government.
If you do not let to me pass…
I do not intend to let to you slip by!
In this case, I will have to kill you.
Wait, Marines!
It does not matter what arrives to me!
The place of the palate, where the rebellion burst…
… will be destroyed by an explosion with 16:30 exactly!
You must prevent it!
What!?
It is in 7 minutes!?
The lives of a million people are concerned!
But…?
In this case, we must help you and prevent the explosion!
Wait!
This woman is…!
IN POSITION!
Release from my way!
A special capacity!
I had specified that I was in a hurry.
Do not cause me longer!
Staff sergeant!
This woman, it is Nico Robin!
I am sure!
Colonel Smoker had ordered to me to find his sheet of research!
This woman….
That made 20 years that there is a beautiful reward on its head!
I remember even article of the newspaper.
The incident, during which six vessels of Marine combat were run,
… had been caused by a eight year old young girl!
The Government had declared it very high threat,
and a premium of 79.000.000 Berrys for its capture offered.
After that, it disappeared without leaving traces…
Stop your chatterings!
Will you let me pass?
Or do you want to die?
Which is your choice?
The advantage of the number is not of any utility against it…
Sergeant! Take along all the men on the place and find this bomb!
But, Staff sergeant!
Go!!! There remain only 6 minutes!
Yes!
Now, let leave it!
I said to you to release from my way!
It was right!
He did not joke with his right hand.
The garden changed into desert.
Where is party?
You too much much pushed me with end…
Failure.
Cro- Co…
Once again, you lost.
Luffy with the straw hat.