Here are pirates of the desert!
The man who saw free
With the kingdom of the Oases.
Three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
In a howl of sadness, this desiccated ground sinks from now on in an enormous wave of agitation.
On the way of Yuba, where the seat of the rebellion is…
Luffy and its friends find themselves confronted with incredible obstacles in the desert.
Y makes hot…
Water…
I am afflicted, Zoro.
This heat is really too heavy…
Forget that. It is nothing.
Nami-San! Where are you part??
Nami-San is always beautiful, even now!
What is there, Luffy?
To travel is easier with you, Matsuge!
But you think that the others are well?
They will find us while following our traces in sand.
A TSUNAMIIII!!!!!!!
Hein? What arrives to him?
A TSUNAMI WILL STRIKE US!!!!!
He! What you ace, Luffy?
I knew it. I knew that it was not an good idea.
About what you do speak?
I said to him not to do it, but he said that he was too thirsty,
he thus tore off a cactus which he found on the way.
A cactus?
Ouais. Just there.
Those which resemble balls.
Oh not! Not these!
They are Mezcal cacti!
They cause hallucinations!
What?!
It IS TOO LATE!!
ONE IS COOKED!
Very well! I will strike it!!
I will return the demon from where it comes!
It is not good that!
Anesthetic!
Played well, Chopper!
Then?
Did you see Nami and Vivi?
Luffy?
What?!
Shit.
One is completely lost.
One does not see any more the traces either.
When I think of it, I did not see Ace since an end of time.
When did it disappear?
It was surely lost all alone.
I swear you, which empoté brother…
It is we who are lost!
And by your fault!
What doesn't go, Usopp?
You did not hear a noise?
A PIRATE BOAT!?
It is…
They have Nami and Vivi! … and the camel.
What?!
Eh, Luffy!
Wait!
And there shit, one will have to go too!
Ouais!
IEA!
Aah, I am burst too much.
It was what this noise?
I would not do that.
Afflicted, guy.
My throat was so dry that I could not say where I went.
If not, you do not have a little water, the guy? Water…
Didn't Eh, come to you to save us?
I just came to have a little from water.
Luffy-San, saves us.
I believe that they want to eat Matsuge.
One can eat this trick?
We, the pirates of sands of Barbaro, have a thing to say!
To say?
“There is nothing which does not move in this desert and which is not edible.”
I already ate tricks which were by ground!
You soon will have badly to the belly!
Bah, I will pay attention.
Curious kid!
You are rather odd too!
Let us eat!
WHY!?
I am the Captain of these pirates of sands of Barbaro, Barbarosa.
You, isn't this is Luffy?
I excuse myself for the hard treatment which your companions underwent.
You thus said that you were hungry?
Ha! Do not worry you for that!
How you say!
But, Captain…
There is no board on the boat to repair the great chechmate.
And without the great chechmate, we will not have enough power to advance.
It rightly! It rightly!
What does one have to make?
This rate/rhythm, that means that one will die in the middle of this desert!
Ca means that one all will die!
One all will die in the middle of the desert!
Us, pirates of sands, naps all born on board this boat of sands!
And we will die on this pirate boat of sands!
And which thinks of not finishing these days on this boat?
Yes! Yes! We will die on this boat!
We will die on this boat!
It is what the problem?
Yes, if it is our destiny, that it is thus!
We, pirates of sands, will not defy the winds of sands!
I had said to you not to do that.
But if we make the voyage to the oasis of Melias, we will be able to restock ourselves with drink.
Where is this oasis?
I will make a turn there.
Hein? Eh well you see…
The displacement of sands was strange, recently.
They would be too dangerous for a foreigner.
It is my responsibility.
I will do it!
I see! You will do it?
Bring back to us wood in these sledges of sands.
They resemble more boats than with sledges.
Zaba and Rasa will show the way until Melias to you.
Shaved?
Ouais, Rasa is the best navigator of sledges of sands on our boat.
With which want you to make team?
I would be well myself!
Wait two seconds.
According to all that you have just said to us,
it seems that this work will require a certain force.
Perhaps that I should go there with you.
Beautiful throw!
Shaved!
The others seem to be foreigners…
… but you are of this kingdom.
Be perspicacious for you!
You must know a little bit how this sledge of sands functions.
Isn't this?
Vivi-Chan cannot make such a dangerous thing!
Ouais! It is too hard!
Very well, I come with you.
Thus this trick slips on sand?
How one makes use of it?
I will direct the sledge.
I already did it front.
It is not quite different compared to a boat, not?
You must just draw this trick…
I… I am of return!
STOPPED LOSING YOUR ENERGY TO MAKE IDIOCIES!
Luffy-San, rests there.
I think initially that you must do that…
Good luck.
Zaba, one goes there!
Ouais, Shaved!
Ca occurs super!
If this sledge were borrowed, we would be in Yuba in one nothing time.
The sledges of sands are difficult to control!
It would be difficult to use to make all the way, in any case!
Then how is that made that you can do it?
When I was small,
I was accustomed to using a sledge of sands, I had one in gift of it!
Good, what will one make while waiting?
If one were made a camel!?
We adhere!
I joked!
It did not feel that like a joke.
Do He, what you foutez!?
Ho, Shaved! Idles!
Hoooooo, Vivi! One is attracted inside!
They is moving sands!
If we engulf ourselves in sands,
we will never leave from there!
Shaved, you did not go there a little extremely?
If the chance is with them,
they will be left there and they will catch up with us.
You know this girl?
Yes.
How could I forget it?
You hold out, Vivi!?
At this speed, one will not arrive there!
Not! It is too late!
Vivi, clings!
In spite of its appearance, Luffy always sometimes happens to be left there.
Ouais.
But what worries me more, they are the whims of this desert.
Whims of the desert?
Yes…
The desert is honest.
With same a light change of the climate or according to the hearts of people,
its nature can change.
To change according to the heart of people?
What is it that?
Okashira! It is them!
Okashira:Owner - Boss
They arrive!
Everyone at its station!
Quickly!
You want to put yourself across my way, you too?
Look at to me all that!
Who are they?
It is a band of robbers of the desert.
They survive while stealing us.
A pathetic group.
Nowadays, the country is ready for the war.
They prepare to attack us.
Look at as they are alone!
Today, one will do them!
Good the guy!
Do not let only one of these jackals escape alive!
Ouais!
Quite known as!
Quite known as!!
Do these types think that they are in a tavern or what?
We live with far in the desert!
Will it choose us, we them pirate Barbarosa or these least that nothing!?
We will fight and let the desert decide our destiny!
Morons! Morons!
There is no chance that the desert chooses you!
It is what that?
Large ball of manure in sight!
Large ball of manure?
It is what this trick, still?
In fact insects roll a giant ball of manure through the desert.
For a few years, more than 100 people have lost against this ball of manure!
Okashira!
At this speed, it will touch our boat in little time!
Leave the-me!
Thank you, my guests.
I LEAVE YOU IN LIFE FOR THIS TIME!
YOU HAVE CHANCE!
And one applauds well extremely…
Shaved, you exaggerate!
They did not catch up with us!
Let us leave them!
If we still wait and until they do not arrive,
we will know that they were really bad.
They were caught up with!
This room is completely covered with sand.
Formerly, it was a prosperous city.
You were front here?
The people of this city were those…
… which gave me a small sledge of sands like proof of their kindness.
It was strong a long time ago…
When my father the King made the turn of the country,
I accompanied it and one stopped in this city.
I waited.
The King said that it would return.
“If something arrives at this oasis, I will come to your help.”
“Even a small voice of this country, I will not be unaware of it.”
You!
I recognize you! It was thus you!
Although he said that, he gave up this oasis.
Everyone had to leave.
But in spite of that, I waited here.
I awaited you.
I believed in you.
But… the King never came.
And of course, you either.
But, the same incidents occurred in the entire country.
The King was solicited the every day and tested…
I do not want to hear your excuses!
In the middle of this immense desert, I waited, only!
During this time, I did not distinguish any more to raise it to lay down sun.
Until the day when Barbarosa collected me…
Neither the heat of the sun midday, nor cold after laying down it sun…
I did not feel anything any more.
I was in life, but it was odd.
Only the words of the King resounded in my head.
Even now, I do not include/understand.
They were so painful.
What did I wait on this ground?
What maintained to me in life?
Hatred?
Anger?
An impossible hope?
What was it?
That it is said to me!
I am sorry…
I am sorry that you had to wait…
They fled the tail between the legs!
Good, sorry but we cannot give food, of water, or wood.
It is hard to be a pirate of sands, not?
All those which live in the desert have the same problems.
A long ago, I thought that the desert belonged to each one.
But when I reconsider there now…
I say myself “Shit, which ridiculous thought!”
I started to think that perhaps it did not belong to no matter whom.
And because it does not belong to anybody, we can really live freely.
I wonder whether it is similar for the sea.
Perhaps…
You and your band will have to discover it by yourselves.
I see them! We are of return!
LUFFY!
OR ES YOU?