Good-bye the island of the giants!
Let us leave for Arabasta!
It was hot in it.
It is all that you could do?
Now, can you say where I am?
How you have…
known where I was?
Instinct!
He!
Look at that! Over there!
There is a rainbow! A rainbow!
It is sincere even when it cries!
It is like being under a gross chute d'eau.
I include/understand… Brogy Master…
Dorry…
You… Why?
I believe that I disappeared.
Mr. 0?
If I remember well, wasn't this the name of the Boss of the enemies about which Vivi-Chan spoke to us?
Therefore, the man with the other end of this Den Den Mushi is…
Den Den Mushi:Snail Phon
One of Shichibukai!
Ca makes a few days that I did not give you your orders.
What does it occur?
Mr. 3…
Ca must be the owner of this Den Den Mushi.
I see, I include/understand the situation.
It is the den of the enemy.
And this guy named Mr. 3 continues Vivi-Chan to kill it.
Whore…
I do really not should have gone to drive out outside!
They may find it beneficial to be left there.
What is it that this silence?
I asked you a question?
Did you eliminate princess Vivi and the pirates from Straw hat?
Yes, mission accomplished.
I got rid of these bastard which knew your secrecy.
Therefore, more need to continue them now.
I see. Good work.
Unluckies move towards your position.
They will confirm the success of your mission and will carry out a delivery.
Unluckies?
A delivery?
A eternal poses for the kingdom of Arabasta.
You and Misses Week Golden delicious must turn over to Arabasta.
It is the moment.
We will begin the most critical part of our plan.
More detailed instructions will await you Arabasta.
It is which these deux-là?
He! What does it occur?
Oh… nothing, really…
Brothel!
You try to kill me, hein?
Try to see, otter of shit!
And you you would have just
to stop that immediately!
Giant chicken of shit!
What did it occur?
It was what this noise?
It was nothing…
One of these bastard of Straw hat was still in life.
But that goes, I completed it.
You rest reassured.
Living?
You said to me that you had finished your mission.
It is not what you said?
Yes, but…
I thought of having done it, yes.
But this bastard was more coriace that envisaged.
In other words, you gave me a false report/ratio.
Euh… eh well…
If you want to say that like that…
But this time, I am sure to have finished some with him.
You do not need more to send someone else, Ok?
In short.
At all events, you direct towards Arabasta.
It was surely… because of your weapon.
Its weapon?
Of course!
After 100 years of use in their duel,
even the weapons of Elbaf are not able any more to cross as much.
It is a chance…
An incredible miracle!
He, Brogy.
You hurt me.
I am so content that you would be alive, my dear friend!
There is no miracle.
It is normal.
It is stranger than these weapons are still intact after 100 years of combat.
And it is similar for them.
Today is one day splendid!
I thank our Elbaf God!
Oh Brogy.
You seem happy to have had the chance to cut out me and to estourbir me.
Cretin! Do not say that!
Do not strike me my wound!
You seek the brawl, dumb?
Yes!
I will pulverize you!
Ouahou!
Too much extremely!
Incredible!
Why do you still fight?
I put an end to the transmission.
It would be a shame which the Navy has wind of that.
I will recontact you way in which you received your orders until now.
It is all.
Made quickly, Mr. 3!
Miss All Sunday!
What is there?
Send Mr. 2 to Little Garden.
Make lay out it of Mr. 3 on the road between Arabasta and Little Garden.
It is rather hard of your share, not?
Mr. 0 Crocodile…
We have enough personnel.
You oppose so that I say?
Not.
I am the orders.
Ca will be arranged immediately.
The line is cut.
Good,
it is which these guys?
It is what?
Then it is that the premium on our heads?
I had completely forgotten.
But the reason first of their arrival on the island, it was me…
IEA!
You will close it?
It rightly, Vivi!
Why do you worry?
You want a senbei?
Senbei = rice Cookie
Where did you find that?
Yosh! It is the moment to make Senbei party!
But that will not be a party if there are only senbei.
Really? One can clink glasses with nevertheless, not?
Does somebody want you?
Kanpai!
He, you waste them.
Whore, not to respect food like that…
Do ball, what you make?
Who said that I will not eat them?
He! You can always eat them!
But you balanced them!
What is there?
Nothing, just an insect bite.
Eh well, to wait one year so that the log is regulated on the next island, they is rather serious…
You are right!
There is no what to laugh!
We have a debt towards you.
It must be possible to express you our gratitude.
Ok giants-Ossan, made something for our log!
The log is the only thing on which one can nothing make.
Naaamiii-Saann!
Vivi-Chaaannn!
He you, balls!
Yo Sanji!
Isn't everyone is well?
I am so content!
This cretin never showed himself to help us,
and it has the base to be shown now?
What is it that?
Es you Mr. 3?
Do He, how you know for Mr. 3?
Ouahou! Nami-San!
You are always also stimulative!
You want to burst?
Eh well Nami-San.
You will catch cold like that.
Hold, mets that.
Thank you.
Eh well, I have just discussed with Mr. 0 on Den Den Mushi.
The Boss? You spoke to him?
Yes.
There was this species of odd hut in the middle of the jungle.
It would be said that it confused me with Mr. 3.
Therefore, I played the game and I said to him that I had killed you.
Isn't Ca wants to say that he believes us dead?
Why one can leave when nobody does not seek us?
One cannot leave?
There is something to make still here?
And after, I left myself the troubles to bring this to you.
What?
It is a eternal poses for Arabasta!
One can sail!
Allons-y, Capitaine !
Thank you very much Sanji-Kun!
During one moment, I believed that all was lost!
No the problem!! It is nothing!!
If I had known that you would be so content…
Yosh! Everyone!
Senbei party!
Doesn't Ca go Luffy?
One cannot make of Senbei party, it remains about it only three!
What?
In any event, there are not time for that!
Allons-y, Capitaine!
There are not time to lose here!
Zoro, He dumb!
You our contest of hunting, isn't this did not forget?
Not. And I gained, moreover.
I had a large rhino like that.
A rhino?
It may find it beneficial to be edible.
Of course.
A contest of hunting?
Ca points out something to me.
Well, large-Ossan and large-Ossan.
One must go there!
I see.
You have the air in a hurry.
It is damage which you donot can remain with us.
I hope that your country is healthy and except.
Yes, thank you!
With more!
Do not die any more!
One day, I will go in Elbaf!
Wait to see it.
Mine is really larger.
Ben yes, of course.
I will be a honest warrior of the seas!
Our friends from go away.
Yes.
We cannot let them leave like that.
This monster always lives in the sea of the west.
Is Dorry, how your wound?
Eh well… I will not die about it.
My axe and your sword soon will reach their limit.
You are sad?
Yes, I am it.
I fought with this axe during 100 years.
But…
For these small human, I will not regret it.
Therefore, it is decided!
Look by yourself!
Mine is larger!
But looks at!
My lizard gains!
Do your eyes have a problem or what?
My rhino is much larger!
Who is concerned with it? Both have the air goods.
Your mouth, moron!!
Your mouth moron!!
Look at them!
The tien is not also large!
The tien is not also long!
Mine has much more meat!
This meat is dégueu!
Bastard, it is not true!
Until when you will continue?
It is not as if one of both could hold on the boat.
Cut right that which one needs. We are ready to leave.
Yes, Nami-San!
He Usopp!
You you can see that I gained, not true?
Hein, I of insane.
Can't you say that there is equality?
There is no equality in a match.
And you dispatch go up!
Yes!
All sails outside!
They said that if one continues by there, one arrives on the western face of the island.
Didn't He, one can have taken more meat?
Cretin, if one takes some more, it will be rotted before it is eaten!
Do you try to make run the boat?
Oh, giants-Ossan!
They came for our departure!
For all the small human ones which came on this island,
the imperative reason for which they did not reach the following island is in front of us.
You took care on our lives with honor.
And thus, we must make similar,
whatever the enemy who presents himself.
The honor of a friend should be tarnished at no price.
Trust us and continue right in front!
Whatever what appears, do not change a trajectory!
Of agreement!
What is there?
What did you include/understand?
One goes straight no matter what it arrives!
It is one goodbye.
We will be re-examined.
Without any doubt.
Look at that! In front of!
Therefore, you appeared, Mangeur of islands.
We will force you to let them pass,
on the name of Elbaf!
What is it that?
It is what that?
A poisson rouge?
A giant poisson rouge?
Where had I already heard of that?
Turn the rudder!
Quickly or we will be swallowed!
Usopp, hurries!
I cannot!
One sinks right in front!
Isn't this, Luffy?
You bet?
You are insane?
This thing is not like Laboon!
I know.
Calm yourself.
Hold, take the Senbei last!
I do not want any!
One must make half-turn!
We all will be…
Nami, stops.
Luffy!
One these guys, isn't this can trust?
Yes.
Really?
We really will direct we right towards the interior of this monster?
It is too late! One cannot stop any more!
Eh well, you grew well, Mangeur of islands.
Monstrous Poisson rouge!
It is not only its size which is surprising.
There are also the size and the enormous length of the “islands” which it lays after having eaten,
like this called giant shit Nanimonai Island.
I remember when we landed on one of these things by thinking that it was a continent.
Last happy days of our adventures.
To look at points out these days to me.
Only the snake with the tasks of blood we cannot bore!
Contemplate strongest of the axes of the tribe of the giant warriors of Elbaf!
Straight! Straight!
What do you say?
One was already eaten!
Straight! Straight!
Hakoku!!
Hakoku = the nation of the warriors