Aboard the Going Merry, Nami's team was sailing toward the east coast of upper Yard to escape.
At the same time, on their way to defeat Enel at God's Shrine, the Shandian warroirs encountered Priest Shura.
Wiper and Shura clashed in what became a climactic battle!
Why did you throw away your shield and weapon!?
Are you insane!?
Don't tell me...
You can have it...
if one shoulder is all you want.
An Impact? That's not egough to kill me!
No, 10 times that energy!
REJECT!
Wiper! are you trying to kill yourself!?
Just try and use the Reject Dial one more time!
You'll blow your body to pieces!
What about my body?
Isn't this what you would call resolve?
If that's all you're thinking about, you'll never beat them!
I'm going ahead!
Fine! Do what you want!
But I'll at least pray for everyone's safety!
Okay, guys, watch yourselves!
We'll meet at God's Shrine!
In the Upper yard Survival, currently...
...1 has fallen...
...and 80 remain.
I guess they were without divine protection.
Meanwhile, the four members of the Straw Hat Pirates' exploration team have also set out.
Their objective is to reach the ruins of the ancient city where a fortune in gold resides.
From the Sacrificial Altar, they headed directly south.
Directly...
...south.
FIERCE SKY BATTLE!
PIRATE ZORO VS WARRIOR BRAHAM
Third verse!
Hold it!
The islands in the east~
What!?
No, I have nothing to say.
And i don't feel like listening to your idiotic prattle.
I'm just going to eliminate you!
What!?
If that's all, you should've said so.
The Priests and guerillas here use some strange tactics.
I've been at a disadvantage in all of the battles so far.
If i have to beat someone from a distance, I have something i can try.
HAWK WAVE
That'll work on the second-rate flunkies...
It's not ready yet...
But, I'm going to test it.
The Flying Blade Attack.
No! No, no! Help me!
Leave me alone! Quit chasing me!
It's Shandia!
It's the Enforcers!
I...
...shouldn't have come!
The forest is getting a bit unruly.
These appear to be a homes built away from the city.
They're being swallowed by the forest as well.
I wonder if the city ruins themselves are still intact.
A woman?
This route leads to God's Shrine.
Going any farther is forbidden!
Come down from there at once.
You have no idea of the historical importance these ruins hold, do you?
You dare to sass me?
Do you have something to say? Why are you here?
By God's divine word, the Shandians and you Blue Sea dwellers are to be cut down by my Axe Dials!
6 FLOWERS
TWIST!
What a cruel thing to do.
Had enough, Enforcer!?
Looks like the others were taken out.
Damn! These Enforcers are becoming a real problem!
Go right, go right, go right...
That's one of those Blue Sea dwellers Wiper told us about!
I'll eliminate him!
A guerilla?
He means business!
Die!
Dunno what your reason is...
What the hell is with you guys?
Please, forgive me!
I surrender! I surrender!
I lose Just, please, spare me!
Again!?
hey, you! If you're not a priest, then stay out of my way!
I'm in a hurry here!
That bastard...!
What are those shining pistols!?
Where'd he go!?
You're a tough nut to crack.
Sorry. I've underestimated you, Blue Sea dweller.
Don't worry about it. I should apologize too.
I thought you were just a second-rate flunkie.
He didn't even take a step!
They said there were different types of Wavers.
Are those skate-shoes of his one of them?
He moves his body using gusts of air.
And those pistols of his shine when he fires them!
I keep losing sight of him.
Where'd he go?
TIGER
Three katana?
HUNT
Bastard!
A Blue Sea swordsman who can't use Wavers or Dials...
...will never be able to beat me.
Do you know what this is?
What?
MILKY DIAL!
Air battles aren't just about jumping from cloud to cloud!
An eel!?
If i cooked and basted this guy, he'd make quite a meal.
I screwed up!
I'm an idiot!
He's already quick and nimble in battle...
and i let him get my leg!
Right now, I gotta do something about those shining pistols!
That's it!
The effectiveness of those guns is pretty exaggerated!
Too bad for you!
Check out these goggles!
Your shining pistols won't work on me anymore!
Give up while you still can!
Those don't look like sunglasses.
Busted!
Seems you don't like my Flashguns.
A swordsman must rely on timing to survive. You can't expect to beat me.
I don't know your reasons for coming here.
But, as long as you are on this land, you will be considered our enemies.
Now, surrender and die!
Your leg must be causing you considerable pain.
You make it sound serious.
I let that eel distract me and got myself shot.
That proves I still lack concentration.
Okay, this looks like a good chance to try that technique.
Should i give it a shot?
Running away?
Sight.
Hearing.
Smell.
Taste.
Touch.
Tought.
And unto the six mortal senses...
Good.
Evil.
Neutrality.
What nonsense is that?
And further unto each, Purity and Corruption.
The 36 earthly desires of this world.
I am facing the muzzle of a cannon at you.
You are a pistol.
In timing and power, my weapon surpasses yours.
You did well, but...
You're going down!
A cannon?
Has he lost his mind?
How could he have a weapon like that?
Have you seen...
...the Flying Blade Attack?
What a joke!
ONE-SWORD STYLE
36-POUND CANNON
That hurt.
This was nothing personal.
I'm not one to die just because someone says so.
I'll accept the challenge,
Survival.
Damn it...
I don't even know where i'm going anymore...
Guys!
Luffy!
Zoro!
Robin!
Maybe i've been standed here to die...
I wonder if i'll go to Heaven when i die.
Maybe Doctor is waiting there for me.
No, i can't think about things like that.
I'm a doctor! And doctors don't think about dying!
I wonder what kind of place Heaven is...
Wait a second.
Isn't this Heaven?
Huh?
Where did all these ruins come from?
Maybe the others are here!
I'm so smart i amaze myself!
Oh, I must be the first one here!
It must have been my nose!
I'm first!
A tanuki
(raccoon-dog: has shape-shifting powers in japanese folklore)
GOMU GOMU NO...
FUUSEN!
That won't work on me!
GO
GOMU
GOMU GO
GOMU GOMU
GOMU GOMU NO...
FUUSEN! (balloon)
Why, you... dirty son of a...
Sanji-kun!
Sanji!
Oi! Sanji-kun!!
Hang on, Sanji!
W-What's wrong!? C'mon, Sanji!
Hey! I can't hear his heart!
It can't be!
A rather foolish man.
Even when i hadn't come here to hurt you.
Then why have you come?
What a cold greeting.
It's been six years, hasn't it?
Former God, Gan Fall.