Sanji-san, leave this ship, please.
I don't want to kill you.
I'm not leaving.
PEARL...
CROSS!
I'm the one who stole everything from that old man.
So that I could live...
His power...
His dreams...
This restaurant is the old mans treasure.
If I...
If I don't place my life on the line as well,
I won't be able to repay the old fart!
GOMU GOMU NO...
Stop it! Don't interfere!
AXE!!!
The Coldhearted Devil-man.
Gin, The Pirate Fleet Battle Commander
The Fin...
The Fin is destroyed!?
That guy...
Is he planning to destroy the ship?
Gin!
Blow his head off!
Hurry up!
B... But...
He's the one who gave us enough to feed our men!
Gin, you bastard.
Hey.
I wasn't fighting back at you.
I only destroyed the Fin.
You bastard waiter boy!
What are you trying to do?!
Sink it.
WHAT!
I'm going to sink the ship.
Are you joking?!
Bastard! I thought you were
gonna say something else!
Are you for real, you shit!?
But if I destroy the ship, they
can't get what they want.
And what do you know about this!?
What do you know about the immensity
of my debt to this place?!
So you're going to die for it?
Are you stupid?
What did you say?
It's not about death!
Dying isn't paying him back!
That's not what he put his life on the line for!
He saved you so that you could
live, yet you want to die!?
Only a weak person would act like that!
Then what the hell do you suggest!?
Oh, both of you.
Stop arguing.
Fighting amongst yourselves at a moment
like this is just laughable.
But you can't do anything regardless now
that we have a hostage in our hands.
How unfortunate for you that to have
to face us, the Don Krieg Pirates.
Now let my Fire Pearls,
Burn you down!
Gin!
Why? Gin...
Sorry, Pearl.
Just stand aside.
Gin.
You're betraying me?
Forgive me, Don Krieg.
This person saved us.
I don't want him to die like this.
At least...
Let me finish him with my own hands.
Have you lost your mind?
My pirate fleet 'Battle commanding officer'?
Owner, are you ok?
Owner, get a grip of yourself!
Battle commanding officer...
So he's not a regular crewman.
He broke the shield of the Iron Wall Man.
What a frightening power!
Look! Did you see how successful my
'decoy strategy of threat' was?
Stop lying!
Do you really want to destroy the ship?
Sanji-san!
I wanted you to get off this ship so
that I wouldn't have to hurt you.
But it doesn't look like that's gonna happen.
Yeah.
I won't go.
This restaurant,
I won't give it to you even if it costs my life.
Then at least, let me kill you with my own hands.
I can't make this right or wrong.
Thanks.
Eat shit.
The same for you, Straw-hat guy.
Not necessary.
Because I won't lose to a bunch
of weaklings like you.
You bastard!
How you dare talk to our commander like that?!
Calling him weak to his face!
We are the Don Krieg Pirates!
The strongest in East Blue!
Don't you mean, the one with the most people?
Looks like you hit 'em where it hurts.
...Definitely.
We'll kill these guys ourselves!!
Back off!
Don Krieg!
But...
When a guy gets flustered because
someone calls him weak,
It's proof that he recognizes he IS weak.
Let the outcome determine the weak and the strong.
I'm still here.
So don't make a fuss.
Aye!
Gin.
You're responsible for killing that cook.
That insolent Hammerboy,
Leave him to me.
I understand, Don Krieg.
Hey, kid!
I'll show you the power that conquered East Blue.
I don't care if you've eaten a devil fruit.
You will come to understand
such a thing is meaningless.
You never shut up.
I want to kick your ass. That's it.
Shall we start now?
You just wait right there for me.
You arrogant...
That guy can't tell strong from weak.
This time that cook will be finished!
If Gin takes out that weapon... he's serious!
They call him the Devil-man.
No matter how his opponent pleaded for mercy,
he would always kill him without any hesitation.
A Devil-man. A human with no feelings.
I'm sorry, Sanji-san
You can't defeat me.
We'll see, small fry.
Take this.
Sanji!
Didn't I tell you?
You can't defeat me.
Farewell.
Just disappear from this world.
The commander is really great!
Kill him, Gin!
Sanji!
Die!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
That cook defeated Gin with only a kick!?
Even Gin can't defeat him?!
Idiots.
What have you seen till now with those eyes?
Gin is the Devil-man I praised!
That's why I gave him the position
of battle commander.
Soon, he will show his abilities.
Is Sanji alright?
How could he be?
Including the fight with the Iron Wall Man,
he's received 5 or 6 heavy hits.
This is nothing great.
You Octopus...
Battle commander... that's all you've got?
Why's he looking over there?
Ok!
I'm gonna use this opportunity to kick his ass!
Don't be so zealous!
You bastard!
Are you going to fight with me or not?
Fight with you?
Is it necessary?
I use methods to kill people.
It is a human's power.
Remember that, stinky monkey.
What?
You better be careful messin' with the monkey!
Sanji!
Yahoo!
That guy is severely injured now!
Kill him!
Damn it! If only the Iron Wall Man hadn't hit him!
He's already been hit 10 times by that steel ball!
This doesn't hurt a bit, small fry.
I'm beaten...
This guy is really strong.
Prepare to be finished.
I have played enough.
What's this? Mercy?
Are you joking?
Gin-san!
Sanji!
He can't take it any longer.
His body can't even withstand the
reaction from his own attacks!
Great!
Kill him, Gin!
Shit.
I can't.
What the hell?
I... Don Krieg.
I really...
I CAN'T KILL THIS MAN! DON KRIEG! !
Gin.
I really...
I really can't kill him.
What did you say?!!!
Because I... I...
I am...
For the first time...
This is worse, I won't accept mercy!
Take it away!
Don't be so tough, just eat it already.
To me, any hungry person's a customer.
Sorry, I can't pay for it.
I understand better than anyone else
the feeling of starving to death.
You can die for your dignity.
But, isn't it that after you eat and
survive, and see tomorrow?
Delicious.
So delicious. It's too delicious!
I thought I was going to die.
I thought I was a goner.
Delicious, so delicious.
This is my first time eating something so good.
Good, ain't it?
I'm sorry, you're gonna get in trouble...
Because you let me eat for free.
There's no evidence now, is there?
This is the first time
anyone has ever been kind to me...
That's why,
I can't kill this man.
Anytime!
I know.
I don't plan on ever betraying you,
I don't think anything we've done so far is wrong.
I respect your strength, and am grateful to you.
and I'm very happy that you praise my
strength and let me be the commander.
That's why I do whatever you say.
And I'll still do it in the future.
But...
I simply cannot kill this man!
Don Krieg...
I beg of you...
Couldn't we just leave this restaurant alone?!
You bastard!!!
Not only do you disobey my orders,
But then you tell me what to do!
Do you wish to die so much?
I'm very disappointed in you.
Didn't I always say,
That I detest those feelings of principle?!
The rest of you go to one side.
Don! That...
MH5
The poisonous gas!?
What?
Poisonous gas?
Put on your Masks!!!
Or else we'll all be killed!
Put on your masks quickly!
What the hell kind of weapon are you gonna use?
Using that kind of weapon! You bastard!
Don't you know the consequences of using it!?
Stop babbling over there!
This is a battle.
The purpose is to win.
Treacherous? Despicable?
Don't you agree that this is acceptable?
Winning is the goal.
The method doesn't matter,
only the goal is important.
I don't care what consequence
the poisonous gas will bring.
As long as I win.
That is strength.
Damn bastard.
Throw away your mask!!!
You aren't one of mine anymore.
You must die.
I won't let you shoot that poisonous gas!
Stop interfering, Hammerboy.
Damn it!
Gin.
I've never heard such cowardly words.
I'm gonna destroy him.
Do not mock Don Krieg!
He's the strongest man alive!
And it's impossible for you to win.
You idiot! Open your eyes!
That guy's trying to kill you!
Of course.
For me to talk about my feelings,
Is to betray the role I have.
That's why...
That's why this is an obvious consequence!
Gin!
Why? Why?
You realize at that end, eh?
But it's too late.
Die together with that cook.
POISONOUS GAS...
M
MH
MH5!
Dive into the sea!
Owner! Into the restaurant, quickly!
I'm borrowin' this.
Sanji, Gin. Use it!
Waiter boy!
Now for mine...
ARA?! Everybody has submerged!