Gold bells and birds.
Ca was to be them
symbols of Jaya formerly.
No idea…
I wonder whether it is not only one
part of a larger unit.
It is a Bird of the South…
and he lives precisely here, on this island.
And is its cry odd?
Ouais, like writing in the newspaper.
In old times, one was useful oneself
birds of the South aboard ships for…
GOOD BLOOD!!
What!? What there is?!
It is necessary to capture one of
these birds! Immediately!
Hein? Does it like?
This sparrow? But why?
Listen to me well.
Tomorrow you will face
Knock-Up Stream!
You will have to go full South.
But how you count
you to return there?!
Once at sea, it will be to you
impossible to locate you!
I see…
It is true that our objective is not
not an island but a point on the open sea.
No compass will be able to help us.
You will need
assets of this bird.
I had wind of the tragedy
history of Montblanc to the tavern.
I had of it the tears with the eyes, Cricket.
I find the fruits
labor of the others…
… particularly with my taste.
You know how one calls me?
The Hyena!
The dreams are never carried out?!
Bellamy VS Saruyama Allied Forces
HERE THEY ARE! DODGE!
They are damaged these
mantes religious!
AHH!! The SCOOP!
It IS WHAT THIS DRILL OF SHINGLE?!
It is him!
What him?!
It would be said that the Bird of
South controls the insects!
The sparrow? Small beasts?!
I hear it.
Does Ca come from where?
What?
I hear another noise.
Up there!
It is what that? Rocks?
They déboulent right on us!
They are not droppings of dung-beetles?!
Not.
They are insects!
LADYBIRDS!
They are enormous! IEA!
Ca does not finish any!
You do not have any enough of you
bring back, band of stupid locusts?!
Go, release from my way!
You believe yourselves of size?! Hein?!
It is heard, but it is not seen.
A slug!
Balance to him salt! Salt!
Sanji! Puts to him a jumped kick!
Ok…
HOW IF It WERE POSSIBLE!
Dissatisfaction
to run!
Let explode them to me!
Not, Luffy!
These bumblebees are poisonous!
Fireflies!
It is pretty!
AHH! COCKROACHES!
PIGS!
If it is the brawl which
you seek, you will have it!
Do not underestimate them
Allied forces Saruyama!
Kill them!
Give us gold!
And perhaps that one will save to you!
Afflicted to disappoint you…
V-old man…
saru lunge!
[Note:Monkey attacks]
The children would not have
to play with this kind of instruments.
And Ben, that made a long time that I had
not done a little exercise of night.
spring snipe
It is well our Bellamy!
How you find the capacities
Hamper Hamper of the Captain?
[Note:Hamper = Spring]
You remainders without voice, hein?
Ok, now transfer to me this waste!
And how that jumps!
It is too for
Allied forces Saruyama.
Anything else that an old man
and a pair of enormous monkeys!
It was found, Bellamy!
Ca must be that!
Look at to me that!
Ca it is beautiful gold!
And there is still!
It is brilliant!
What a lucky find!
You do not have the right of
to touch with this gold, dirty punks!
Right?
I will show you
what a are our rights!
BIG CHOP!
Imbecile…
You made not the weight!
Why one would need
rights to fly of the treasures?
Hein, old man?
Push yourself, Patron!
hak44} voc
{\ fs15 \ alpha&HFF& \ T (710,1260,1, \ fs40 \ alpha&H00&) \ T (760,1260,1, \ fs40 \ alpha&H00&)} so {\ fs15 \ alpha&HFF& \ T (1060,1880,1, \ fs40 \ alpha&H00&) \ T (1380,1880,1, \ fs40 \ alpha&H00&)}nar
[Note:Havoc = Devastator]
Species of enf…
Wait, Sarquiss!
I will complete it myself.
Still that?
Capacity of the fruit Hamper Hamper…
SHOUJOU, COURSE!
spring}
{\ fs15 \ alpha&HFF& \ T (3630,5510,1, \ fs80 \ alpha&H00&) \ T (5510,6010,1, \ fs80 \ alpha&H00&)}snipe
SHOUJOU!
Owner! Gold was found!
An ingot in the shape of bell!
There, look at!
Ca sticks with the log book!
He speaks about a bell!
Allons-y!
Embark gold!
It would be time to grow, old man.
The Gold City forever existed only
in the head of Norland, the liar.
If you want to become one
pirate of the New Era,
you should make you with the idea that
the dreams are never carried out!
The Gold City exists!
He, Ho! You will ransack
this small house!
Wait a little, kid!
A femmelette which does not have enough tripe
to face what she does not know…
… appears to me badly placed
to speak about piracy.
You can repeat that?
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
No the chance.
One did not even see only one of them.
Us if, but…
Y had small beasts everywhere
and one did not can approach some!
Course, moron!
Brothel, one is not even able
to catch a bird with us seven?
Put you there all, the guys!
You too.
I can run more!
“You will not catch me
never, band of nazes! “
It was what that?!
Came to you up to now for us narguer?!
Brothel…
I will clean up you!
If I cannot see it…
Papi! There was the bird…
Papi Head of Diamond!
Masira!
Shoujou!
But how it occurred?!
Shit, which did that?!
He, spins to me a knack!
Ok!
LOOK AT!
Vogue-Merry!
How that could arrive?!
Who dared to do that, Bordel?!
Who?!
Die… plate…
Papi!
He, Papi! You are awaked?
I am really sorry!
We were there, but us
did not can anything make!
But, it…
There remains to us still time.
We still have time
to repair your boat…!
Wait, Papi!
Say to us initially what occurred!
Not, it is nothing. You
in made not for that!
Ca does not have any more importance.
Important it is… You have…
Cheer. Played well, you have
caught the Bird of the South.
It is perfect.
Luffy!
Gold was…
… stolen!
It… It is nothing.
You do not occupy of that!
What counts, it is that you…
What that wants to say?!
Owner, you last ace ten years of your life to ruin you
health while plunging each day for this gold!
And now, you…
Close it, kid!
It is not serious.
It is our problem.
Measuring rod?
Us, members of Alliance
Saruyama, let us have obligations.
Your boat is not in state
to sail for the moment!
We must repair it
before the lever du jour!
We will not block your voyage!
Listen, I promises you
to send on the celestial island!
Owner…
He, Luffy!
The emblem of Bellamy…
A knack?
Not, that will go.
Luffy, not! Do not try anything stupid!
There remain to us only three
hours before raising the veils!
If I go along the coast,
I would arrive at the city
from this afternoon?
Yes, completely.
He, kid!
Where you go?!
You would not owe you
to interfere our business!
Do you know with whom you…
If you want to stop it, take that!
G-kid…
I would be of return
before the lever du jour.
Ah, it left…
I will feel one
little dehydrated after that.
Good Ben, one would say that it
no more only one drop has there!
Not, indeed.
O God of Drink,
thank you once again!
I do not believe that there exists, but good.
Oh, the newspaper!
Let us see seeing…
I of mande which are them
bad news, today.
Hein? Am misled to me.
It is right research opinions.
Whore, this city
is really nut!
I have my snap of it of
all this rabble!
They are dirty the pétochards
from this afternoon!
They did us well marrer
with their history of celestial island!
It should not be worth more than 30 Million.
Hou there there! I believe
that I picolé a little too much!
Let us see that…
1…
10…
100…
1000…
10.000…
100.000…
1.000.000…
10.000.000…
My God! I drank really too much!
1…
10…
100…
1000…
10.000…
100.000…
1.000.000…
10.000.000…
100.000.000!
Three hours, Luffy!
If you did not return before…
we will lose our only chance to go
on the celestial island and it will be your fault!
It has to plunge the every day without leaving it
time with the bubbles to dissolve in its organization.
It is right a duel with
that which ruined my life.
Afflicted…
I am really sorry…
We were there, but us
did not can anything make!
WHAT A DUMB!
They were too funny these
two macaques, I swear you!
Especially the mouth in blood
and completely exploded!
Pleurnichant snot with the noses!
“Patroooon!”
If it is so important in your eyes,
z' have that with protecting best!
Not true?
What a loose!
Would not be too hard with them!
Vis-a-vis Bellamy, anybody
the least chance would have.
After all, the head of our Captain
is put at price to 55 Million Berrys.
CA FEARS!
That there of so important is
at this hour of the night?
This afternoon…
these guys who were with the bar…
Bellamy!
Be to you still there?!
Than you are better
cars from here immediately!
Be to you…
Be to you in danger of death!
What do you tell?
In danger? Me?
100 Million…
60 Million…
Exact! Guys of this afternoon…
They have both a premium
higher than holds, Bellamy!
You will be made kill!
You pleasant! One has
interest to slip by from here!
One is foutu
mouth of this hard to cook!
Perhaps that it
do not point out us!
One cannot remain there!
It is the first time that I see
somebody with a premium of 100 Million!
Ho, Ho, Ho, Ho!
Bandage morons!
You flippez in front
two bits of paper…
You do not have the eyes in
face of the holes, or what?!
You saw their chief, not?
I am there.
You ever heard
to speak about this kind of pirates?
Guys who make their characteristic
faked research opinion.
Pirates who bluffent
to become famous.
Only one glance on their posters
is enough to make fade their enemies.
With final, they have the fun so much
to fight that they deflate.
They lose before even to have fought.
Exactly like you maintaining!
You saw what it
was worth your own eyes!
You made pity!
It is true!
Jitter that it us
has foutu, this dumb!
As always, Bellamy rightly.
Is really necessary to have made the worst atrocities
to deserve a premium of 100 Million…
It is strange which one does not have it
ever seen in the newspapers!
Ouais!
I ever intended to speak
of this “Straw hat”!
Oh, I see!
It made me well go!
Go! Still a toast!
Kanpai!
[Note:Kanpai! = Health!]
BELLAMY!
OR YOU HIDE?!
I heard my name.
He!
One precisely spoke about you.
You want something?
Ouais!
The gold returns which you stole
in Papi Head of Diamond!