The wishes of the despairing people are
being crushed beneath the dry cloud of sand.
Some peoples looking for hope, some
peoples hope for a little chance...
Their resolves have gone
astray, and in the confusion,
The Curtain of History has
been drawn on a tragic climax.
Nami has been battling against the Toge
Toge abilities of Miss Doublefinger.
Although she seems to be at
an insurmountable disadvantage,
Nami has gradually begun to understand the
power of Usopp's invention, the Clima Tact.
Meanwhile, Crocodile
appeared at the Palace,
And has finally revealed to Vivi and Cobra
the final objective of his evil ambition.
Secret of the Royal Family!
The Ancient Weapon, Pluton.
What did he mean?
Pluton?
What is he planning?
Pluton.
It is said that with one shot, it has the power to
wipe out an entire island and all of its inhabitants.
A weapon bearing the name of a God, the
most fearsome ancient weapon in the world.
And it lies dormant
within this very country.
An ancient weapon...?
This country harbors
something so terrible?
Father, did you know of this?
The secret passed down
through the Royal Line...
That has been my true objective
since I began this venture.
With it, I will create the world's most
powerful military nation upon this very land.
Then everything you've done
has been for that ambition!?
When I become King of this country.
I'll have no problem recruiting
pirates from far and wide.
As I gain power, I will surpass
even the World Government.
A country out of a dream!
The World Government will
never allow you to succeed!
I know, that's why I need...
...the ancient Pluton.
I don't care how you
came to hear that name,
But not even I know where it is hidden.
I am not certain if it is in this
country or even if it exists at all!
I see. I thought that might be the case.
I've already planned
for that possibility.
The uncertainty of its existence
is undeniable, even to me.
Audacious fools.
Crocodile is holding
Cobra-sama captive inside!
We must rescue Cobra-sama!
We need the full force of the
Royal Army! We must get inside!
But... with those hands sprouting
from the door, we can't break it down!
If we don't do something about
those hands, we'll never get inside!
If everything moves according to plan,
In 20 minutes, the Rebel Army
will reach the Palace Square,
And a battle will ensue.
And then, in one half
hour, at exactly 4:30...
I've arranged for a giant bomb
to be fired into the square.
Are you insane!?
The bomb will generate a
blast five kilometers wide.
I'd imagine your lovely scenery
is going to change quite a bit.
If you do that...!
Both the Royal and Rebel
Armies will be obliterated.
They will fall and their war
will be over for all eternity.
You should be happy.
You've worked so hard to
see this rebellion end.
Destroying the Palace is
far too crude a method.
It's so much more efficient to
annihilate them all in one fell swopp.
How can you do this?
WHAT HAVE THEY EVER DONE TO YOU!?
You...!
You...!!
Vivi-sama!
Worthless.
Stop this!
What can you possibly
gain from doing this!?
Vivi-sama!
Now then, Mr. Cobra. I'll
ask a different question.
Where is the Poneglyph inscribed?
Poneglyph...
How do you know about that?
If I tell you where it is...
No...
I will take you there.
Papa...
The words of a wise and
benevolent ruler, Cobra.
You're a clever man.
Vivi-sama.
I cannot stand this any longer!
Remember, Nami,
The Clima Tact draws its
power from your intelligence.
In your dire moments,
use your head to survive!
That's our real weapon, right?
Heat Ball, Cool Ball...
I can use their individual
characteristics and combine them to attack!
That's the Clima Tact's power!
And last of all,
Tornado Tenpo!
This is your weapon's final feature!
Tornado Tenpo...
No human opponent will
survive a hit from this...
BUT!
You can only use it
once, so make it count!
If you miss, it's over!
If I miss... it's over.
You mustn't look away
from your opponent.
You've got quite an interesting weapon.
But without having any actual
fighting ability behind it,
It's nothing more than a toy.
And if you're trying to kill someone,
the only things suitable are...
...weapons!
That's what you call them.
If I stand still, I'm going to die!
The final attack, Tornado Tenpo!
I have to-
G-Give that back!
I can't be killed by this little toy.
I bet a wool sweater would
generate more electricity than this.
You won't know until I'm done!
Give it back!
I have to think...
This one-shot Tornado Tenpo...
I just have to create an opening
so she won't be able to dodge it!
I think.
What can I do by combining the three kinds
of bubbles and this country's arid climate?
If there were only a little
more moisture in the air...
Moisture...
That's right! There
was a rain technique!
A water show?
She's lost her mind.
No dammit! I have a plan!
Oh come now.
I'm getting bored of
your little party tricks.
The party's getting exciting.
Let's start the real fun.
An urchin!
You'll be as full of
holes as a bee's nest!
That doesn't look like a bee's nest.
The wall's smoldering!
As gratitude for your
little show earlier,
I'll let you see something interesting.
Now's my chance!
The hot air should absorb all
the moisture and rise higher.
It'll collide with the descending
cold air and rapidly cool off...
...causing the misture to condense!
Then...
Didn't I tell you not to look away?
Whaaat, these wounds are nothing.
I'll... keep fighting... till I die.
Even if my arm torn from my body... even if my
nose is shattered into a thousand pieces, I'll...
Don't talk so much or you'll
start bleeding internally.
Yeah, yeah, I know...
So you guys made it through alive.
Sanji!                            Sanji!
You're all beat up...
So? How was your fight with Mr. 2?
You need to ask?
My goggles!
You got them back for me!
Thank you, Sanji!
You're so thoughtful-
AHH! OI, WAIT A SEC! THEY'RE BROKEN!
You jerk, these are the
lastest model from North Blue!
Do you have any idea how
much they mean to me!?
Oi, look over there.
Listen to me...
Those must be the reinforcements
for the Rebel Army...
They're still coming?
Looks like it.
Vivi-chan might be the
only one who can stop them.
Ah, shit!
Vwo!
"Vwo"!?
Hey, where the hell have
you been hiding, Eyelashes?
Let's hurry to the Palace!
We might still be
able to help Vivi-chan.
Gotcha.
Oi, Usopp! Come on!
Right...
Oi, Eyelashes, let me on!
Look, look! Can't you
see the condition I'm in!?
Eyelashes, stop! LET ME ON!
Godness, looks like the only thing
you're good is running away, honey.
That's right, the bubbles...
There it is!
It's kind of small...
but I made a cloud!
What are you talking about?
It's not enough, I
need to make it bigger!
Enough of this!
You...!
So? Ready to die yet?
I should ask you.
What a bluff.
Unforgivable.
What!?
Today's forecast calls for comfortable
himidity with a slight breeze.
Expect a sunny day accompanied
by high atmospheric pressure.
With the exception of one area...
...where mirages and whirlwinds
have been cause for worry.
Beware of tornadoes!
Tornado Tenpo is your
weapon's final feature,
But you can only use it once.
If you miss, it's over!
If I miss... it's over.
Tornado Warning!
I'll decide this, with my final attack!
I've always wanted to fight like this!
For that sweet girl's sake...
Nami-san...
Please don't die...
Try risking our lives along with yours!
WE'RE YOUR NAKAMA!
What?
So it turns out you do cry.
You're the one suffering the most,
And you want to beat the hell
out of him more than anyone.
It summons the clouds!
It causes the rain to fall!
It even makes the winds blow!
My miraculous Clima Tact...
...will decide this match!
I'll use my ultimate attack! For Vivi!
Are you alright?
Your left leg is causing
you quite some pain.
You can't even stand
up anymore, can you?
This... is nothing!
This doesn't hurt! It doesn't even itch!
Do you even know mow
much she's been through!?
Compared to that...
Giving up one leg, or
two legs, or three legs...
...IS NOTHING!
Now taste this.
What...? What...?
What? What!?
The doves tied me up...!
I did it.
I did it you guys. Usopp, Vivi!
Ah-hah.
I finally remember your ugly mug.
I vaguely recall...
...a bounty hunter
well known in West Blue.
Am I right?
They called you a truly magnificent
and notorious assassin...
But you're just someone's dog.
What are you fighting for anyway?
Little dog of Crocodile.
Did you lick his hand so you
could get a good treat from him?
Bastard.
You fight for money.
Pride also has a bill.
Get ready to pay it.
So your body is as hard as steel.
If I can't cut steel, then
I can't cut you either.
As you say.
Striking and cutting
attacks will not affect me.
I see. That's a pain in the ass.
And since I can't cut
steel, I can't beat you.
Then what will you do?
Well!
I'll pity you.
What?
A predicament like this
is just what I've needed.
I've been itching for a chance
to get one step stronger.
When I beat you...
I'll have become a
man who can cut steel.