Ground of God, Upper Yard.
The nightmare of made Survival
always rage on the territory.
Nico Robin reaches finally
Shandora, the City of Gold…
while Chopper faces the Priest
Ohm in the higher ruins.
Unfortunately, it is overcome.
It is possible no to survive
with the Truth of the Pain.
The chance of survival is of 0%.
Ordalie of Iron!
Where is the exit?!
Now, in the ruins
in top of Giant Jack,
four survivors are on
the point to start the combat.
Old ruins would be said.
He well, it one is crowned band
the hard ones to cook that we have there.
He, pass to me gold!
He well, which sadness.
None among you will escape
in my Ordalie of Iron.
If one of you is put in
through my road, I kill it!
You will say to me where
find Eneru and my holy guard.
It is what this connery of cave?!
He well, gentlemen, you seem all to have to make, but to achieve your goal,
you will have initially to survive!
Climb Giant Jack!!
Confrontation in the higher ruins
Despite everything, moment that
God had predicted approach.
None you will survive.
Predicted?
If you had not answered your desires, your lives would have been longer.
Your wounds will make you
to include/understand the gravity of your crime.
I suppose that you are one of
these Priests with the service of God.
I insane steps badly of
what God could predict.
I soon will find gold.
I do not have anything to make with you.
This also is not authorized.
To perish under my Ordalie of Iron is
the only exit which you will reach.
I will save you.
Nothing more than of stupid chatterings.
Allons-y, Holy.
Make them what it you will like.
It is our target, Pierre!
The Priests of Eneru must be
destroyed before continuing!
This foutu python followed me
all length up to now.
Whore.
It is unbreakable, but
that rises and that turns.
This cave is odd!
Each one of you…
is dedicated to die!
This dangerous weapon me with the air.
Ignoramus of inhabitant of the Blue Sea!
You and your crew, do not be
arrived at the sky that yesterday.
You do not have the right of
to take anything!
I have my snap of it to hear you
to repeat what one can do or not.
What occurs in
sky does not concern us!
I am well of agreement!
I should have completed you as of the beginning!
You are nothing more than one parasite!
Burst!
This guy is stronger than I thought it.
BURST!
It is true. This thing has
hooks filled with venom.
And now, of the hooks behind?!
How a dog can it
to move like that?!
It is called Holy.
I inform you that I draw up the animals
sky. I am the Celestial Stockbreeder.
When they are animals, I them
teach much more than the discipline.
I learned how to him to be held on two legs and I made of him a true boxer!
And there you will be able to taste!
Do not do of it a little too much to you?
Gan Fall…
In spite of your defeat against Shura,
you still did not include/understand?
I believe that it is time that stop you
to make toy with your lance, old wreck!
I will not release taken!
I must discover what
you manigancez, imbeciles!
Would not be so haughty and arrogant!
Even if you discovered it,
A type in your kind would not include/understand
nothing for God!
Follow them, follow them
! Catch up with Shandia!
What, what?
It is what these “meh” which I hear?
Goats?
They are the Soldiers!
One will die if they catch us!
What? Soldiers?
Troops of Eneru!
It is necessary to leave from here!
Wait a little! I announce you that…
One does not even know where one goes!
It is what?
Giant Jack!
The Sanctuary of Eneru
is perhaps up there!
The Sanctuary of Eneru?
Wiper!
What?
Wiper is up there!
It is alive!
They approach Giant Jack!
Do not let them reach
the Sanctuary of God!
Leave us quiet!
This whore of snake.
It does not release the business!
He… Chopper!
He! How it occurred?!
I see. His/her companion of the Blue Sea.
He, looks at where you go.
It was what?
Barbed wire?
It is its Ordalie?
Chopper!
He, Chopper!
Answer me!
Why you came here all alone?!
He!
Which damage.
They are Iron Clouds.
Light like clouds,
but hard like iron.
They can spout out of Milky Dial.
I installed of them several in
corner, each one with its own detonator.
If you steps on one
they, Dial will start.
In this zone, you do not know
sites of the switches.
I do not even need to attack you.
Half of what arrived
to this animal comes from me.
The remainder, it is him even which
started in Ordalie.
You wish to avenge it?
Not, I do not like too me
to beat for such a reason.
Oh? Your answer impresses me.
But…
I am just a little out of me.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
SKYPIEA-FANSUB
I am sorry. This is
good place, Conis-san?
This is the coast where they
are given go?
Yes, Father. It is what Nami-san said.
But the situation is
rather embarrassing.
We must keep
their boat, now.
We must make our possible
to defend it until their return.
Must I make sound the trumpet
to make flee the danger?
Very good idea, Father!
Ca will give us courage!
It is perfect.
Suu, can you make
the guet by over there?
Nami-san, which kind of promise?
It is right so that all occurs well.
Luffy and others
went in the forest.
We agreed for
us to find on the east coast, then…
it is over there that we go.
I wonder whether they are left there.
The forest is so dangerous.
I hope that they are
all healthy and safe.
They are well!
They belong to our
crew. They will be left there.
Go!
I will look after them costs whom costs!
Hold good, you two!
I hope that everyone is well.
I consider it regrettable that the island
celestial is thus.
All with the Sanctuary of God!
We have a chance of
to take the head of Eneru!
We will not leave you
to reach the Sanctuary of God!
It is Giant Jack!
Climb it!
I you beg Wiper of it,
do not use any more Reject!
Soldiers, you gather! Us
let us must stop Shandia!
Wiper, you should not defy Eneru!
Eneru…
No matter what one does, one
cannot overcome Eneru!
It is well.
You all, thus climb
with the higher ruins.
Over there, you will fight to survive.
There will remain only 5 about it.
The words of God are irrefutable.
Stop, Wiper! I am…
You are what? You want to make me believe
how you are not our enemy?!
Eneru and you, you are
similar in our eyes, Gan Fall!
Es you unable to hear reason?!
Be made foutre!
Burn Bazooka did not kill it?!
Of what its scales are made?!
Ca is enough! Ca is enough, stupid cave!
It is my chance.
The more it moves, the more
it leaves openings.
It was what?
It is characteristic of people of
Blue sea. You did not expect it.
This sword is too
made Iron Cloud.
In other words, this blade…
is in fact an expelled Iron Cloud
by Dial embedded in the handle.
It tracks my preys,
where how they are!
You include/understand now,
epeist of the Blue Sea?
It is a kind of whip. I included/understood.
You, epeists of the White Sea,
be only one band of acrobats.
Holy.
We will fight separately.
The higher ruins… go
soon to suffer some damage.
My faith.
Even if the Master of the Skies is here.
We will fight with you, Ohm-sama!
The guy…
It would seem that apart from us…
Ouais, he remains only us.
We will help you with
to reach Eneru, Wiper!
I know! I will dig
to leave from here!
The python…
It enough!
Stop!
Leave us quiet!
Nami!
Aisa!
Young girl!
Stop them!
Aisa, what you insane there?!
Nami, why you are assembled?!
Are Zoro, where the different ones?
Wiper!
What you plot,
inhabitants of the Blue Sea?!
Aisa, deviates from it!
One is saved.
Demon! Wiper, species of demon!
Girls, why
did you come up to now?
Why?!
Because there was this gigantic…
… snake…
What a cretin!
Aisa!
Wiper!
You were distracted and have
lowered your guard. Idiots.
Forget the others!
There is nothing any more with
to make to save them.