The pitiless combat died!
Luffy VS Crocodile
With the kingdom of the Oases.
Three years were passed since the last drop of rain.
In order to find hope during this time of disorders, the inhabitants decided to take the weapons.
Luffy and its crew were victims of a trap tended in Rain Dinners.
But thanks to the intervention of Sanji,
they finally managed to escape.
Colonel Smoker was saved drowning…
… and allowed Luffy and its crew to escape.
The kingdom of Arabasta in ruin, or will reach fall a durable peace?
The sand glass of the destiny counts the number of second remaining.
They flee!
Continue them!
They are there!
Catch them!
Colonel!
You do not continue them?
Not, I am tired.
Tired?
Yes.
Well!
Stop the continuation.
They will not have them.
Order the gathering.
Contact the general headquarter.
Ask them to requisition all the men-of-war near the kingdom of Arabasta…
… and that they immediately travel towards this country.
Reinforcements?
But, Colonel…
I do not know if our superiors will like the idea to send as many boats right for some pirates!
Since when I deal with my superiors?
Oh… Yes!
Immediately!
He!
Return!
Stop!
Here me is!
Ouais, it is this road.
The odor of the perfume of Nami becomes increasingly strong!
He! Me known as step which one will run like that until Alubarna!
Oh, Matsuge!
Where did Matsuge leave!?
While thinking of it!
There is many stables in this city, not!?
Let us find some horses!
But, the city is filled men of the Navy!
Do not worry you!
Look at over there.
He! Everyone!
A CRAB!?
Chopper!
It is a Mobile Crab!
Ca with the good air!
COOL!
Brilliant! Super! Terrible!
Impressing! Cool!
Go up!
One can go up above!?
Glad to meet you!
It does not look at us a little oddly?
You still brought something of narcotic with you.
It is a friend of Matsuge!
Matsuge was born in this city,
thus it has everywhere full with friends in the neighborhoods!
But they all are perverse…
Nutcase!
The Mobile Crabs remain hidden in sand so much a long time…
how they are regarded as legends, but there is of it a front us!
It is rather fast, not?
Everyone, you hang well!
Yosh! Caution!
One left!
Stop! Chopper!
It is him!
This dumb…!
He, Luffy!
What a idiotic!
Luffy-San!
And the others must continue you to advance!
ALL WILL GO WELL FOR ME!
You ensure that it arrives over there without risk!
Bring back Vivi at it!
Made blunder!
Made blunder, hein?
Imbecile…
He!
One goes there, Chopper!
On the way towards Alubarna!
Yes.
Included/understood well.
ONE GOES THERE!
Have-await two seconds!
He! He, Zoro!
You will not leave it here!?
Aren't He, a little cruel for you!?
Be to you cruel sacrament but…
you will protect me better now!
Why do you do all that for me!?
ANSWER me!
LUFFY-SAN!
All will be well, Vivi!
It will be left there!
I am more anxious for him!
Once Luffy chooses its enemy…
… it is never left there unscathed!
Listen, Vivi.
It will deal with Crocodile.
Time that the rebellious army manages to attack.
Time for this country is counted.
If the royal army and the army rebel meet,
it will be the end of this country, the kingdom of Arabasta.
And if you are the only one who can stop them…
then you must remain in life, it does not matter the price to be paid.
Henceforth, no matter what it arrives to us…
… that does not have any more importance!
M- But…
Vivi-Chan.
You founded this combat.
You left your country a few years ago,
to defy an organization of which you did not know anything.
In any case…
you cannot say but you any more engagements only, from now on.
V-Vivi!! Born does not worry you!
I… I… will protect you!
LUFFY-SAN!!
LUFFY-SAN…
WE WILL AWAIT You has ALUBARNA!!
… WILL AWAIT You…!
OUAIS!
She east flees, not?
Princess Vivi.
In any case, the Agents in Alubarna are already ready to receive their orders.
Come into contact with them immediately.
I find…
… that your small horse-gear lasted long enough, Luffy with the straw hat.
You know it well…
Although it is weak, it will still try to save everyone.
It is always sad because it cannot support to give up somebody.
She even wishes that this rebellion finishes without any death.
Without any death?
It pacifist stupid there and limited many like that.
Those which do not know the truth of this battle.
You are of agreement with me, not?
Ouais.
But as long as you will remain in life,
it will fight to its last breath.
It is for that I must…
… to stop you here!
It is more than pitiful.
You are nothing more than one idiot.
You are a perfect example.
Those which conspire with others die because of that.
I left a hundred like that of it behind me.
Eh well…
Does Ca show that are quite stupid for you, not?
You find that funny?
Perhaps that I should kill you too.
Nico Robin.
If it is what you think,
made as you want.
And what did it arrive at your promise not to call me by this name?
Where do you go?
I go from this step to Alubarna.
Which imperceptible woman.
I grant 3 minutes to you.
After that,
I will not have any more time to play with you.
I grant 3 minutes to you.
After that, I will not have any more time to play with you.
A problem?
Not. Ca will suit me very well.
Let to me say a thing, Luffy with the straw hat.
It does not matter how you fight.
Somebody as will never arrive to you…
Listen, Luffy with the straw hat.
Your pitiful attacks are like punctures of mosquitos.
Ca is not used for only you continuous.
Somebody as will never arrive to you…
You! Dirtiness! Dumb!
I burst you!?
Stupid Croco of sands!
I said to you that it was useless.
You, dumb!
It does not matter how you fight, elastic man.
Somebody as will never arrive to you at me…
… Beats…
“BEATS”!?
What try to you to say!?
I find that I had fun long enough.
Luffy with the straw hat.
I always fought seriously!
But there… Good blood!
I am not even able to touch it!
It disappears all the time.
You and me…
… sums of the pirates of different classes.
Beautiful dodging…
If that had touched you, you would have regretted it.
What!?
The desert was split into two!
According to the way in which you use and improve the Fruit of the Demon,
it can become an incredible weapon in a battle.
I am not as these cretins who are glad to have only capacities.
You will regret being to you found on my road…
What?
Hein? What? It is what?
Sand!
He aspires to me!
You never heard of moving sands?
The desert is a convenient coffin.
No tomb is necessary.
Sand is grabbed by an underground river.
Thanks to my capacities, I can determine his exact place.
Combatant in the desert, nobody in this world can hope to beat me.
This rotten sand…
… will not be sufficient to bury me alive!
Dumb…!
As I cannot strike you,
I will capture you in the place!
Friend = Net
You do not want to listen to me?
It is useless.
Muchi = Whip
Am I obliged to always repeat the same things?
Release me, dumb!
My arm!
My arm! My arm!!
A mummy would be said!
My arm was transformed into a mummy!
It is because of sand.
He aspired all the water contained in your arm.
I should perhaps aspire all the water of your body and kill you.
So to speak, here a first impression of the desert.
It is not very funny!
It is that!
WATER!
Useless.
It is not useless!
This water…
… was given to me by Ossan with Yuba after it spent all the night to be dug!
Ossan = Old man
Luffy-Kun…
Take this with you, please.
You know what Ossan said?
Yuba will never be destroyed by only one grain of sand!
You persist in continuing?
DECREE TO PLAY WITH MY NERVES!
Die…
… with the “cordial” ground of Yuba.
Your 3 minutes are past.
I had warned you.
I do not have more time to play with you.
Sand is quite dry today.
A tempête de sable!
In the sky, in the South!
Evacuate!
Wait! The wind blows towards the South!
It should avoid us!
Colonel Smoker!
It is…!?
Vivi! Doesn't something go?
There is a tempête de sable above Rainbase!
It is him…
Luffy…
Listen, Luffy with the straw hat.
Here the dominant winds always blow of North towards the South.
If…
… this small tempête de sable moves towards the South and grows bigger,
where do you think that it will strike when it will be beautiful and large?
Towards the South?
In Yuba.
Why!?
You! Why do you do that!?
Stop that!
Look at, a breeze of wind coming from the South rose…
Ossan does not have anything to see in it!
Dirtiness!
DECREE, DIRTINESS!
DECREE! FILTH!
DECREE!!
It is useless.
Drop.
Once this storm took speed,
even me, I would be unable to stop it.
Stop of you foutre of me!
Yuba is finished.
Stop it! Immediately!
For which take to me you?
Beginners who only make tell it like you…
there is full.
Luffy with the straw hat.
Here on Large Line…