Wealth, Fame, Power.
The man who had acquired everything in this
world, the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The final words that were said at his execution sent people to the seas.
My wealth and treasures?
If you want it, I'll let you have it.
Look for it, I left it all in that place.
Men now, chasing their dreams, head towards the Grand Line.
The world enters the Great Age of Pirates!
I can see the Gates of Justice, but can I get across on a regular boat?
Anyway, there's no time!
I've gotta try something!
Here I go!
Pirate-niichan!
What are you doing?!
Sanji-kun.
Were you really unable to win?
Did you really fight properly?
Your opponent was that woman, wasn't it?
You're soft on women, aren't you?
I'm sorry about the key.
That's not it!
I'm just saying that you could die because of your stupid way of chivalry!
Are you still gonna honor it, even when you end up like this?
What are you gonna do if you die?!
It's not...
...like I wanna die.
However, I've been raised to never  kick a woman.
That's why...
...even if I die, I will never kick a woman!
You're so stupid.
You idiot!
Oi! What are you doing, Nami?!
If running away is also against your way of chivalry,
then at least throw that away!
To die without a cause is a different story entirely!
Leave that woman to me...
And also,
I've changed my opinion about your way of chivalry.
Did you just say you love me more?
She didn't say that!
I'm not as nice as that guy.
Me neither.
Looks like we'll get along well.
Yoyoi!
Hold on now~!
That octopus guy!
I won't! I won't let you escape~!
Nami, go get that woman.
I'll deal with this guy!
Got it!
Yoi! Yoi! Yoyoyoi~!
I won't let you get in the way!
Kokutei!
CROSS
Why you little~!
You, again~!
Your opponent will be me!
Come on!
The Silent Owl's Miscalculation! My Cola Is The Water of Life.
Geez! There's no way you can cross the ocean with a boat like this!
Are you stupid or what?!
But, you...
Robin's been taken to that Gate!
I have to hurry, or I won't be able to bring her back!
I should be able to reach that building in front.
Hold on, what are you gonna do?!
Wait, pirate-niichan! Calm down!
If I can't get across the ocean, then I have no choice but to fly across!
We came here to tell you...
...about a way to get to the Gates of Justice!
What the hell is this place? A basement?
It's the ocean's underground passage.
To get to the Gates of Justice, you have to go under the ocean.
Is that right?
Alright!
Wait! Do you even know how to get there?!
You're really amazing, you know?
How did you know about this?
Earlier the guy with Lucci came through here laughing really loud,
so we just followed them!
Guy with Lucci
If they don't know the entrance, there's no way they can follow us!
They're such fools!
Lucci and the black-haired neechan went through the doors, too.
This door, right?
It's a pretty hard steel door.
You know how to open it?
The guy with Lucci was touching something around here, so....
It must operate with the keyhole over here!
But, there's no key....
You guys, stand back.
What are you gonna do?
I can get to the Gates of Justice from here, right?
Gear Third!
It opened...
Alright! I'm going then!
Why did you become so small?!
You're so funny, pirate-niichan!
Alright, we still have more work to do!
W-Wasn't there a really loud noise just now?
Is it my imagination?
No, that can't be it.
Perhaps it was the sound of one of the pirates destroying the door...
What?! How could something that stupid happen?!
You mean that thick steel door?
First of all, there's no way they could have found it.
No, they should know.
A child and her pet were following us, so...
Wh-Why did you know and still not stop them?!
An order...
...wasn't given to do so.
What are you saying, you idiot?!
You should be able to decide something like that by yourself!
Don't you know what could happen if we leave them?
What is it? Oi?!
Does that mean someone's heading here now?
It seems so, doesn't it?
I'M SCARED!!
Hey, shut up!
Oh, it's me.
Listen, Lucci!
Your assignment and first priority is to protect my life!
You got that?!
You have to eliminate every single person who gets in my way!
Going against me is nothing but treason against the World Government!
They deserve to be demolished!
What's with that face?
You don't have time to be worrying about others, Nico Robin.
Hell is right in front of you!
Lucci!
Hurry up and bring her.
Good! I'm back to normal!
Hold on, Robin!
That pigeon bastard!
I'm definitely gonna kick your ass!
Sanji-kun's defeat is...
Well, it's his own fault.
But, what the hell was that?
What's up with this woman?
She's got some guts, doesn't she?
Damn, I have to hurry up and refill my cola.
He zips around so fast for a big guy like him.
Chapapa...
I'm over here.
Seems like you're fast at running away.
Chapapa.
I don't even have to take any of the punches that you're so proud of.
FRANKY TRIANGLE JACKER!!
Chapapa.
I'm not gonna take...
...your stupid sideburns!
Damn you!
Weapons Left!
Damn, I'm almost out of cola.
Gotta hurry to the kitchen!
Wait, you bastard!
Damn it, you dodged it!
You sure are one first class coward!
Chapa...
What did you...?
What's wrong, coward?
You're not running away this time?
You bastard!
You just pissed me off with those words!
Try taking this, my murder strike!
It's faster than the Shigan, and an extremely heavy punch!
Jyugon!
Chapapa...
A tiny punch like that won't work.
Strong
Tekkai!
Hammer!
You have such a weak punch.
Jyugon!
Yours is just a flabby-ass punch.
No, yours is a flabby-ass punch.
Then that makes yours a paper-like punch.
Yours are just norakura pants.
Pants?
That's not a punch!
You're  just pants!
You stupid bra!
Shut up, you sock!
Learn your lesson!
Bastard!
Fundoshi!
Fundoshi = Japanese thong for men
Chapapapa~!
Move, you bastard!
Shut up, frog mouth!
This is great! I'm in the kitchen!
They do have one! A huge refrigerator!
That guy...
He's probably got a gorilla Devil Fruit.
Damn it...
Three minutes have already passed.
I used the Rumble Ball too quickly.
What should I do?
Yoyoi!
Withdraw your life from the third world~!
This is the finishing strike~!
Yoyo-!
Bastard!
Great, it's got a lock!
Chapa! Kumadori!
Yeah! I've locked him up!
You bastard!
Oi, wait up you gorilla!
I have business with that refrigerator!
CP9 and the hooligan!
I'm Franky! I'm an ally!
Who's a gorilla?!
You're slow!
Listen up!
Just like Luffy, I haven't forgiven you.
The reason why Usopp left us was...
It was all because of you!
Give me back Usopp!!
But, you guys were just together...
Forget about that for now!
Don't you wanna save Nico Robin?!
I wanna save her!
Robin!
Then get three colas from that fridge and give them to me!
With them I can power up!
I'll finish these assholes off in an instant and take their keys!
What kind of idiot becomes stronger with a cola?
Leave me alone! I do!
You guys...
How long do you plan on doing your stand-up comedy?
And on top of that, you wanna have tea during a fight?
That's impolite!
Jyugon Oogi (Jyugon's Secret)
Hukuro Dataki! (Owl Hits)
Chapapapapapapa!
Beans' Left!
What the hell is that?!
This is bad!
That's right, he's on our side now.
I better do what he says.
If I open it for an instant and close it, he won't be able to come out.
Open!
Yoyoi!
The door has been opened~!
Good!
Franky!
You saved me!
FRESH~!
What the...?
Freshness is the best!
Oyasai punch, go!
Oyasai Punch = Vegetable Punch
Jyugon.
That was vegetable juice!
Who says 'Freshness is the best'?! Damn it!
Give me a cola!
You weren't just thirsty?
Yoyoi!
The door~!
Here!
Thanks!
You've got a good heart, haven't you?
Now...
Here I sit!
The work in the fields is done for the time being.
Let's just cool down and stop the fighting!
Just have some tea!
Tea will give you power!
You freaking dumbass!
He's so amusing.
Oi!
What's up with that 'I wonder what would happen
if he drank something else?' face?!
Bastard!
There's nothing else, deer!
It's not a matter of how you feel?
I only take cola!
That's cola!
There's no doubt, it's cola!
You're my savior!
I don't know what's going on, but I won't let you do what you want!
Rankyaku
Franky!
SUPER~!!
Chapapa...
What is it?
It's not as if anything will change just because you drank some cola.
Guard yourself.
Chapa!
You idiot!
Are you gonna hit me with another of your weak punches?
Strong Hammer!
Dobeba~!
AMAZING~!!
Sorry about that.
Up until now, my punches were...
...definitely weak, just like you said.
Zoro-kun, any ideas on how to get these handcuffs off?
Yeah.
Let's just do 'rock, paper, scissors', then cut off one of our wrists and...
What the hell are you saying scary things for?!
How could we do that?!
You think so?
Then I have another idea...
I don't wanna hear anymore!
Next time, One Piece: Zoro Bursts With A New Technique!
Zoro's New Sword is Sogeking?
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!