What is what does not go, Usopp?
The money… the money disappeared!
Ah! Over there!
Thank you, my guy!
Wait, enfoiréééés!
One succeeded!
You stop!
Franky Family.
These bags… are with us!
Money… money!
Galley it Company!
And the splendid N°1 Dock.
Wait, Paulee!
You will not escape to us, this time.
But I had asked you for a new time!!
It is…
It is Paulee.
It is still continued by its creditors.
Return to us our 200 million!
Afflicted, Nii-san! I will take care well of it!
Heeey!
It is you who them ace given the money?
And then what still! They stole it to me!
What?!
Give us the money!
As I already said, I do not have a round for the moment!
Your problems do not concern us!
'Silvering, they insist.
Over there, one will yagara bulldozer.
ROTION
Engineer de Galley it Company!
Please excuse me, but I must borrow your will yagara a few moments!
ROUND
Shit! He still fled!
And well, so long!
One will make “mumuse” another time!
Shit!
And well… You arrived at the good moment.
Thank you my God.
It of your employees, isn't this is one?
Completely.
Thank you!
This money is with us!
Hein? Money?
Oh, that…
Oii, return!
This jerk! I go the choper…
I will go there!
A pigeon?!
It is the valet de chambre…
Apparently, it is timid…
This floor needs to be changed.
What you insane?!
You do not worry! As soon as I throw an eye in it, I will give all to his place.
Have-have-have-have, oi, oi, oi, detaches me!
But what you insane?!
I will not escape!
I said to you that I had included/understood!
Release to me the ear!
For once I put the hand on a little money.
You will see, Lucci!
Do not settle your debts with the money of others, idiotic!
I FOUND this money!
And you think that I will believe you?!
I fell on this will yagara bulldozer by accident!
They return.
One leaves oneself there well, Usopp.
You let it make?!
200 million Berrys, it is much of money!
Ouais! Then, why you did not do anything?!
Because this pigeon said “I will go there”.
Nmaaa, I am sorry…
We deal with idiots among our members.
If you had caught it, that would have annoyed me.
Well, let us leave side Franky Family and forget all that.
Admittedly, but…
Ca hurts…
Did He, where pass the types badly equipped with presently?
Franky Family is a group of disassemblers of ships.
Disassemblers? They however did not have the air of honest workmen.
But they are also bargain hunters.
They track the pirates who accost in the city and generate the combat.
These people sow the disorder.
If they leave gaining against the pirates whom they accosted…
They also destroy their boat.
They disassemble it and sell the parts in good state.
Such is the business of Franky Family.
Which cowardice. And what do they make of the crew?
Nmaaa… For most covetous, a reward is always good to take.
They however do not have the air very strapping men.
They are only subordinates.
But do not underestimate Franky, their tapi chief in the shade.
Whore, it was less one.
Oi, you are well?!
I am healthy and except.
Oi! Where is the crew of Straw hat?!
They are surely still with the dock n°1.
We bring back it for you, Iceberg-san!
Stop! My ear!
Afflicted disturbance, Lucci.
A thing is sure, this cretin poses many problems to us!
It goes back to speaking!
Go, excuses itself, Paulee!
This pigeon speaks too much much!
It would be said that he speaks in the place about the type.
At all events, we found our money.
Is He, it with you?
I bring back it for you.
Ah, Thank you!
If you want to thank me, you ace that with me to give 10% of them.
Please it excuse, customer.
Its passion of the play him because much of debts.
It loses the reason as soon as it is about money.
Of agreement, but how you make to speak?!
Jerk, you cannot it close, Lucci?!
I will not forgive myself!
Punishment
But why it takes that so much with the serious one?!
Hung with a wire
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
IPONRI
How is it?
Nmaa… It is always similar.
Look at that!
It deadened the shock of a hand!
Its fingers are embedded in the ground!
It is what these fingers which it has?
What does not go with the naval engineers, here?!
Oi, you with the glasses!
Hello! Do not only forget…
That which caused you and humiliated, it is…
The PIGEON!
I of insane.
That which struck me, it is Lucci!
It struck you because the pigeon could not do it.
Oi, the pigeon!
He, assumes you when you must fight!
Say something!
You in redemandes?!
You of ace have enough?
Stop that, Paulee!
Good, excuse us for these nuisances.
I am Rob Luc… nonon… Hattori, the pigeon!
Here Rob Lucci! He works here!
Charmed to meet you!
He is expressed like human now.
I included/understood!
You are ventriloque!
Really?! Then it was you which spoke presently!
You are very strong! I would never have guessed!
Stop, it does not have nothing extraordinary there.
It is an eccentric unable to speak directly to people.
Wait! Who is this woman!
It is what?
What a dépravée!
You show too much your legs!
There are only men on this work place!
It is what this getup?!
Paulee, calms maintaining to you.
You also, Kalifa!
You do not have shame to still wear this clothing?!
How much time will have I to repeat it to you?! Puts long pants, pants!
What?
Long pants?
It is zarb, him too!
Nmaaa… Ca is enough.
Start by opening the door, one goes there.
In any case… This door is giant!
The opening is manual?!
How these two insane can open it alone?
Ca moves!
Nmaa… When they work on a building site,
their competences of engineer are sufficient for five people per dock.
Kaku, that you saw presently, is one as of theirs.
It is a world of carpenters.
Made not attention with all these not very common personalities.
They are really zarb.
Ah, it is open.
Preserve the money close to you henceforth.
Although there are no pickpockets inside.
Of agreement, please excuse my errors.
Oi, Luffy!
Protect me, ok correctly?!
Yosh, I know! You ace that with me to entrust them!
I am not convinced.
Trust me!
Here, in the dock n°1, the main activity of Galley is it Company.
One deals here with the most difficult work.
Come, enter inside.
Enooorme!
Seen from here, this shipyard with the really brilliant air!
Ouais.
They build an enormous galleon!
Who is the customer?
There are full craftsmen.
Come… by here.
Oh, it is Iceberg-san!
Oii, the owner is there!
Hello!
Owner, could you throw an eye on quality of these boards?
Of course, I arrive in a few moments.
[Otsukare:nobody have just completed a work]
Otsukaresama, Iceberg-san!
Maaa, Otsukare. Is all well?
Yes, all occurs for best!
Ca then?! Ice-ossan is very popular here!
Obviously. In this city, only competences count.
Many shipyards were undertaken in the past.
Seven shipyards were in competitions.
At the sides of the craftsmen, it astonished by share its knowledge in naval construction.
The company which gathered the seven manufacturers of boats…
Was called Galley it Company.
Its competences and its enthusiasm for joinery did not change since.
Never the craftsmen will forget this respect which they have for him.
And because they are proud their competences…
They will resist eternally vis-a-vis the pirates and the government.
Thus is this place.
Oi, Ossan!
It was said to me that you were an excellent naval engineer! You want to become pirate with me?
What you tell?!
Insolate!
Ola, ola, it is always like that.
Excuse it.
Nmaa… You do not have a naval engineer on your boat?
Ouais, one came here to repair our boat and to find a companion moreover.
And well, we have many engineers…
But I do not know if one of them would like to join a pirate crew.
If somebody wishes to join you, I will not prevent it.
Really?! Now that you said it!
Why not you, Ossan?
Nmaa… I cannot. I am the mayor.
Ca does anything!
On this subject, is there really a woman of the name of Nico Robin on your boat?
Yes, of course! She is even super intelligent!
What is there?
Does Y' have a problem with Robin?
Not.
He, Ossan.
I can see this boat more closely?
Of course, that is equal for me.
Thank you!
It is really brilliant!
Rather as that, take your time, gently!
If there were a gun like this one on board, Merry would be…
Ahh! A half-culverin!
[Culverin:Canon transportable of the end of the Middle Ages]
It is so long! Ca shines!
I will like so much to test it at least once! !
It is the moment!
Would this be copper?
It must be expensive.
Would they let to me test it?
But wait!
We have 300 million Berrys now!
We can easily buy one of them!
But where did it pass?
Where did Robin leave?
By there.
This odor…
It is well what I thought!
I wonder who was this guy camouflaged with Robin?
It was perhaps Chopper, after all?
Sanji!
Chopper.
Kaku…
Where were you?
In expertise.
Ah, the person of presently.
Did you throw an eye on our boat?
Yes, I did it.
Iceberg-san, finally I find you.
I included/understood the problem… How is that presented?
It is that…
Luffy, go down!
Ouais, I arrive immediately!
What, it is true?!
You will regret it if you lie!
I am a professional, I do not lie.
Where is Usopp?
He trotted himself by over there presently.
Oi, you!
Isn't these bags are with you?
These are the bags whose Usopp was to be occupied. They are with us.
Thank you.
But, where Usopp passed?
While dropping all this money…
Money?
Ouais, it there 200 million Berrys inside.
200 million Berrys?!
Ouais it is that! So long!
Ca, it is sure…
Then, how long that will last?
We can pay as long as you will want.
One has full of money.
If possible, one would like something of more robust, with more guns, and more rapid.
Could you also add some decorations on wood?
And to remake the interior of the parts, too?
A bronze statue too!
As graaaande as you can!
Good, wait…
You return without doubts of an enthralling voyage.
Ouais, one flew then one fell from the sky…
Climbed mountains, and even taken in ambushes!
Full with tricks happened.
It is for that a repair of quality is wanted.
It is not to laugh…
It is what I see.
The wounds of the engagements are too deep.
Does that want to say that repair will take much time?
Not.
To be honest, your boat…
Is not reparable, even by us.
Is the skittle broken or what?
Ouais…
It is seriously damaged.
It is not possible…
But until now, we always could sail without problems!
Even if we repair it best than we can…
The chances to reach the next island are of…
Zero.
Merry…
You…