One was hot…
Thank you…
Look at, even the large table of information which
was anchored on the ground was made carry by the waves.
What a force!
The speed of the waves of this Aqua Laguna…
is abnormal!
I see!
Thus had Sanji gone to the station?
Before continuing Umi Ressha,
it is necessary at all costs to find Luffy and Zoro.
Yosh, it is included/understood.
Help us, please!
The guy! I count on you!
JERRY AURORA FLICKER JAB !
DROP KICK!
Which waste of time.
SKEWER!
Where are you, Straw hat!?
Please, answer!
Hey, look at-look at-looks at!
Ah, the pirate big sister!
Hey, looks by here! Y' has a trick there!
A trick?
Wouldn't this be Straw hat?
Your Lord of the Pirates?
What?
This imbecile…
He, you? Where you like that run?!
Does not go in the low city!
You want to die?!
Aqua Laguna arrives!
Return!
It is terrible! The pirate girl descended the staircases!
He, return!
The sea will absorb you!
Wait!
Does not go in the low city!
Do not continue it!
Paulee-san.
Y outward journey with several will not change anything.
But…
It is the sea which faces us.
You would finish drowned.
If it occurs anything, I will intervene.
You, you do not move from here.
It was thrown in the low city!
That fout tokens.
Then Straw hat is over there.
The HEART OF NAMI SHOUTS!
REBIRTH OF LUFFY!
How can it still run?
Which girl…
Imbecile, it is not the moment to be amazed!
Oï! Return immediately!
You will drown you!
A sea anemone…
Sea anemone…
A sea anemone which exceeds of a chimney…
Why a sea anemone?
Sea anemone…
Wait, the reindeer! Remain here!
Zoro!!
Nico Robin very dropped to negotiate with the CP9.
Because with you, it would not have
ever been able to carry out its dream.
I could authorize the 6 members of the crew of the Straw hat, me excluded, to leave this island alive…
even if I must for that awake
the weapon and to destroy the world.
Robin, wait!
One will fight against no matter whom!
Robin!!
Be brilliant for you, pirate big sister!
What a unconsciousness!
It is too late!
Look at the sea!
The wave is already there!
Good blood! They will die!
One can nothing any more make!
Zoro!
You hear me? It is me!
Chopper?
It is useless, I cannot advance more.
LUFFY!!
HEY!! BUT WHAT YOU INSANE?!!
Gnaa- Gnami! It is you there dirrière?!
Gnii- Oï! You hear me well?
It is standard Li with the pigeon which has me jity until there…
Then semi ji am found wedged here!
DECREE TO MAKE the IMBECILE
IN ONE SIMILAR MOMENT!!
WHILE YOU PENDOUILLAIS,
ROBIN WAS MADE REMOVE!!
To save our lives, Robin chose…
to sacrifice his!
While delivering itself to the government, Robin received in
exchange the promise which it will not attack us.
I do not have nowhere where to go, and nowhere where to return.
Not, it is finished.
We will be re-examined never again.
It knew very well that it
would be carried out if it were delivered.
Then Robin…
we had lied well…
Oh thank you…
Do not worry you!
I will not let Robin die!
Look at! Look at this wave!
Is it is what this delirious!?
It is thousand times larger than usually!
He! They is really serious there!
He the pirate! Drop and breaks!
The reindeer!
I do not arrive there!
How you found yourself wedged in it Zoro?!
Stop drawing!
What one makes?!
The large wave is too much close!
That exceeds me…
He… wait a little… say to me…
Would not have you Kitetsu by chance?
Hein? The saber? Yes, I have it!
How you know it?
I feel it, only him…
Because it is cursed.
Then you had kept it to me.
Thank you… it slips by to me, grouille!
Flee quickly!
In height! Climb highest possible!
Too much late, they will not arrive there!
He, the pirate!
You will be carried!
AQUA LAGUNA!!
It is what that?
Good-bye.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
MUGIWARA-TEAM
Aqua Laguna is too much large!
It is what that?
Too much late!
What?!
It exploded all the building!
Zoro!
Deviated, Chopper!
But it is which these guys?!
One goes there, Nami!
It is what that?
Cling, Zoro!
The low city…
Shit!
He! Look at!
It is them!
Super! Brilliant!
Well, they are in safety here.
The waves cannot go up high any more.
Cheer the guy!
You are too strong!
THAT ALL BATTERED UP TO NOW!!
And the crew of the Straw hat?!
Would Aqua Laguna have absorbed them?
Not! Look at!
Paulee-san!
Shit!
Not yet, run!
Sink at the high city!
Quickly!!
The large bridge crumbles!
Which monstrous wave…
Incredible! One is in the high city…
and one is not even in safety!
Look at, the sea withdraws itself.
Obviously!
It will strike one second time…
then third once…
with the same force!
It is necessary to be put at the higher shelter!
Good blood, which band of cracked…
Thank you. You saved us, Mister with the cords.
That fout tokens! It is thus that Aqua Laguna?
I still tremble about it…
If the waves were so strong each year,
this island would have disappeared for a long time.
This one was exceptional.
You are really fantastic!
You had chance of you to leave there.
Granny head of shark!
You were also on the island?
Of course!
If I had been right in the middle of the sea,
I would have died drowned!
He, Mister the Pirate!
You super stays! The “Badaboum” too!
Ah yes.
YOU WANT Me TO CHOKE OR WHAT?!
Cretin… it disappeared… on my head…
Hein?
With the Zoro fact. Why tested you
to escape the waves too you?
You stays in bottom?
Hein? Ben, nothing important…
It was wedged in a chimney.
Wedged in a chimney?
Zoro be really too null for you!
But how you ace makes your account?!
It IS NOT the SORROW TO PLAY IT to YOU YOU!!
You are really too idiots you two!
And where are Sanji and U…
Where is Sanji?
It is true. I have many things to say to you.
Also listen, Zoro.
I could not dream of more beautiful occasion.
I have the exceptional authorization to call upon five vice-admirals and ten men-of-war, Buster Call.
Thanks to Ao Kiji, the CP9 received the right to make use of it.
Isn't this, Funkfreed?
The woman that the government
world sought during 20 years…
Nico Robin, fell easily
in the hands of the CP9…
Just like the man who holds the plans of Pluto,
the apprentice of Tom, this foutu Cutty Flam!
The world is however immense, but both only
people able to awake the old weapon…
are on board Umi Ressha, and move towards me.
A weapon so powerful that it could
to destroy the world… will fall into my hands.
It is time.
I am there, Robin-chwaaan!!
Your chevalier servant arrives!
Then was Nico Robin sacrificed for us?
Yes.
The other cock and Usopp are with it.
What does one make, Capitaine?
What good is it to reflect?
One takes a boat and one continues them!
There are not really the choice.
Allons-y.
Let us save Robin!