Battle with the Giants!
Open the Second Door!
One Piece Treasure Sweepstakes! The first letter is...
The way to win will be explained at the end of the show!
That's why you should wait here for five minutes and then bash into the Main Island with the Rocketman!
We'll go fight first and open a passage so that the train can pass between the Main Gate and the Main Island Gate.
You Straw Hats should try to avoid unnecessary battles and concentrate on just following the CP9.
Yeah, I got it!
What the hell is he doing all by himself!?
That guy doesn't understand the plan at all!
Damn you pirate!
I'll hurry in first, so...
Let's meet again some other time!
See ya!
Don't let them open the gate!
Shit!
Scram! You're in the way!
Let's break through!
We breached the first one, the Main Gate!
Hey, Sogeking...
Hey!
That hurt, oi!
It's about how I make this cold air tact function, you see.
Let me see. Eh, don't ask me!
Everyone... I wonder if they're all okay.
Sit quietly and wait, Chopper.
We've got enough to worry about with our captain.
I still haven't gotten enough sleep...
Let's take care of them quickly and get back to sleep.
Oimo!
G-Gi-Giants!
Oi! Straw Hat Luffy.
How many nakama did you bring with you?
Enies Lobby has over ten thousand soldiers!
Yeah. I'm alone.
Open the way!
We won't let you pass through this gate!
If you don't go back home obediently...
...we'll crush you down!
Don't be scared! Franky-aniki is just behind those doors!
Show them a fight that won't shame aniki's name! Franky Family!
Don't fail!
Let's clear the way for the Rocketman!
Force the gate open!
I won't let any of you pass through that gate!
The Destroyers!
Everybody!
Damn! How do they dare do that to our main forces?
Go!
What?
Zanbai!
Kiwi! Mozu!
Galley-La!
Sorry, we're late! It took longer than expected to get Sodome and Gomorrah on land!
Zanbai! The Destroyers were...
I understand.
We don't have the time to treat them!
In order to get to where aniki is, we must open those doors no matter what happens!
Let's go!
Yeah!
We'll destroy this guy's sandals. Mozu!
Roger. Kiwi!
Kaashii!
Tilestone!
Nailing complete!
You...!
I'll crush you!
Kaashii!
All right!
Bastards...
Guys, let's go for another round!
How are things over there?
At this moment, in front of the Main Island's Gate, Kaashii and Oimo are supposed to be facing the enemy.
There shouldn't be any problem in my opinion.
Is that so?
Did you capture the Straw Hat who entered the Main Island?
Ah. Err...
As for the estimation, it's approximately four hundred.
Four hundred?
What are you talking about?
I mean the damage report.
Ahh? The damage report!?
You're saying over four hundred soldiers have been beaten!?
Another hundred just added to that...
No, excuse me. I will do the correction.
Of course you will.
The soldiers aren't that weak!
Do you expect me to believe that so many have fallen!?
If there are victims, report them precisely!
Yes, then I'll make my report. For now, the victim count is around five...
Niiiin-!
Five people!?
You mistook it for five people!? Geez, can't you even report properly, damn!
Five...  hundred people...
It looks like Straw Hat Luffy is running around the island without even fighting.
Mah, that's evident!
Capturing an idiot who would face so many soldiers at once is only a matter of time!
You did a good job.
Chief, Lucci's party has just arrived.
They're back?
Let them enter!
It's been a while, Chief.
Wanted for the incident in which government officials were attacked eight years ago...
Here's the criminal Cutty Flam.
As well as the criminal who is wanted for causing that incident twenty years ago at Ohara, located in West Blue,
where Marine battleships were attacked...
Here's Nico Robin. We brought them here without any delay.
Those two are waiting on the other side of this door.
It's great that you came back!
Lucci!
Kaku!
Blueno!
Kalifa!
That's sexual harassment.
Just by saying your name!?
It's been a while, Lucci.
Seems like your impudent face hasn't changed a bit.
Same goes for your stupid features, Jyabura.
What?
Won't you two just let it go? What's with the fighting when we just returned?
Yoyoi! That's right, stop this, you two!
Isn't this is our first meeting in five years!?
Chapapa...
Chapa...
CHA!
PA!
I knew you'd do it right at the start.
Fukurou.
An armed soldier's strength is around ten dourikis. As for you...
Let's see, let's see. What's your strength?
First, Kalifa, 630 dourikis!
Blueno, 820 dourikis.
Kaku, 2200 dourikis.
Lucci...
4000 dourikis!
Four thousand you say!?
Oi, are you saying this for real? I've never heard of such a douriki!
It's true! Everyone got stronger, chapapa!
I know Jyabura and Kumadori's strengths too, so I understood who's stronger!
Oi, that's not fair Fukurou!
Leaving Lucci aside for now, what does the fact that I'm losing to Kaku mean!?
Chapapa! Kaku became stronger too!
Oi! Don't get cocky, Kaku!
The Teawase is a technique to measure your physical strength level only!
In a real fight my Devil Fruit power will count too! Don't forget that I'll never lose to you!
Think of it as you please. I hold no interest in such matters.
That's right. Don't pay attention to the talk of a stray dog.
Who's a stray dog, Lucci?
You monster cat!
Stop this for a bit, you two.
He's acting quite violently, that Jyabura.
At this moment, the fact that Jyabura got dumped by the office girl Gyatharin is the hot topic of the Marines on the island!
So that's the reason.
Ho-Hold on!! Why does everyone know about that!?
I talked about it on the Main Island, chapapa!
It was you?
Geez! Don't start fighting over a stupid ranking list.
All of you guys, since you finished the rokushiki training, you are already far surpassing a normal human's strength!
Five hundred dourikis are easily enough to consider yourselves superhuman.
Chief has got nine dourikis. He's the only one, chapapa.
Don't say that, it doesn't matter! I'm just the Chief who gives orders!
Plus, I've got my special sword with me!
We all knew about the Chief's weakness a long time ago.
O-o-o-oi! You shouldn't be so blunt about it, Kalifa!
That's sexual harassment.
Eh!? Because I replied?
Chief.
Wh... What is it?
It's sexual harassment.
My existence is!?
Yoyoi! Kalifa, how rude of you!
Chief! Let me open my stomach to take responsibility for this!
Seppuku!
I can't die...
I already told you to kill yourself!
Could it be? Is it you who stopped me from dying?
My mother in heaven!
Is that how it is!?
Is that so? Your mother is...
Jyabura, can you understand my feelings?
Yeah! I, who have always been rude to you, understand it well now!
The feeling of losing someone important to you!
Mother!!
Gyatharin! Was I not good enough?
Chief...
What is it?
It's over. The skit.
Right...
Anyway, you've done a really good job on your five year long mission.
Not to mention Nico Robin, you even brought back that abominable Cutty Flam with you.
Well done!
Hearing this good news, people from all over the world will praise your talent.
Can you understand how proud I, as your Chief, am feeling of you at this moment?
That's right! It's not like a reward for this job, but I have something to give you.
Mah, we'll put that aside from now.
For now, let me meet with them.
With the whole world's hope.
Guys, the time has come!
It's getting late, how about we go?
Those guys should have opened two doors by now!
Let's charge in!
Samurai-man! I'll leave that barrier to you!
I'll take care of it.
It hurts!
Hurry up! We don't have a lot of time! Open the gate quickly!
Don't falter! Go for it!
Where is this place?
This passage is hard to walk in!
Whoa! It hurts!
Just you wait, Robin! Don't think you're leaving the crew that easily!
He came out!
Immobilize him!
The Chief calls for you. You two get inside.
We're done for! The Main Gate was closed!
Worrying is unnecessary.
Leave it...
To luck!
Leave it to luck!?
Next time, One Piece: The Means of Escaping is Opened!
Fly through the Sky, Rocketman!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Here's how you can get your present!
Write the four letters that appeared in the show, your address, your full name, your age,
your opinion of the show and you may win a lot of prizes!
The last keyword is... this!