Remain there, Robin!
The discution is not finished!
If, it is it.
We will not be re-examined any more.
Luffy, hurries to catch up with Robin!
Robin!
From where does this force come to them?
Who be you?!
We are the CP9.
This mission is a business of state.
We will not let to you interfere.
It is time of déclancher the fire. We must hurry.
As long as one is there…
I would like to show you something.
A fruit of the demon!
What a kind of fruit?!
Lucci, you…
The fruit Neko Neko.
[Neko = cat]
Model Leopard.
A man-leopard.
Enormous!
What…
THAT WANTS TO SAY?!
End of the crew of Straw hat?
Terrifying model leopard!
With fire!
Oi, you awake all!
Is whore, they the pirates who did that?
There are still many people inside.
And Iceberg-san?! It is still on the floor?!
Allons-y!
Dispatch you, the others! Etteignez fire!
It would seem that the incendit was declared.
Man-leopard or not…
I you will not let raise the hand on Iceberg-san!
Ca becomes complicated! Zoan “carnivores” are extremely violent one!
Indeed, standard Logia, standard Zoan, standard Paramecia.
All have their own characteristic.
That of Zoan, it is the increase in the physical force.
The more one involves oneself, the more one dvient extremely.
The Zoan type is the best for the close combat.
The farm!
I insane of what a filth of monster can say!
There is no time to us.
We must eliminate you before making us surprise by the flames.
Iceberg-san!
Lucci, the workmen arrive.
It does not matter, they will not arrive up to now.
RANKYAKU
Behind! Very collapses!
Nami!
Chopper!
Paulee, which do you make?
I will leave you from here, costs whom costs.
You will not be able with your wounds!
Stop, Paulee.
Do not call me by my name like that!
Release from my way!
Whore!
Why you, the guy?!
I have…
At least, I had…
ALWAYS BELIEVED THAT YOU WERE MY COMPANIONS!
You are well only.
The guy with the pigeon!
Straw hat!
SHIGAN
Luffy!
Insane the camp of this island!
Whore!
TEKKAI
Zoro!
You too.
Grandmother, Grandmother! A giant fire!
They are the offices of Galley it. They make really horrible things.
Too bad? It is somebody who put fire?
And well, I do not know.
But I have a bad presentiment.
I hope that Iceberg is well.
My faith, if this thing had not existed…
Testimonys of pirates do not have any value.
And this business will remain irresolute.
Iceberg-san, you have beautiful being a large naval engineer…
Or even a large mayor…
A citizen should not be opposed to the government.
Let us see the other apprentice of Tom, Franky…
Or rather Cutty Flam, to take the sketches of the Ancestral Weapon to him.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Is everyone outside?
One cannot return any more inside!
Check all if it does not miss anybody!
Is Oi, where Iceberg-san? You saw it?
Did not say to me that it is still inside!
It is inevitably well!
The engineers are with him. It cannot be there!
The guy, seek in the neighborhoods!
This girl belongs to the crew of Straw hat. No doubt!
Would it have jumped of the window?
It was made surprise by the flames and could not escape any more.
What does one have to make of it?
Whore, which they have fact is horrible.
One will make him acknowledge where are the different ones!
We all will catch them and will deliver them to the navy!
Was Blueno, Franky in your bar?
Yes, but it had left to research Straw hat.
I see.
It cannot remain in place, that one.
On the other hand, there are some who will have much less chance.
Look at.
Listen well, Straw hat!
There is tankard the Length-Nose!
Ouais, one had it!
If you do not want that one transforms it into sardine…
Baka! How much time should I repeat it to you?
You must say:“If you do not want that it finishes at the sea-bed”!
Tea!
SEA!
Cretin, you me listenings never!
Most important, it is that Straw hat includes/understands, not?
He will include/understand anything by saying that!
You will be made botter the bottom by Aniki.
“If you do not want to see it running at the ocean floor, go to the warehouse, under the bridge! On behalf of Franky!”
How that!
It will be made burst, if it is pointed.
Who waits who? And at which place?
Be to you which, you?
One is occupied! Break!
If you hold with the life, you have three seconds to answer.
It is what this joke?
Do you know at least which Aniki one speaks?
What do you want to say by “the warehouse, under the bridge”?
Is Franky over there?
It is what your problem with Aniki?
You must to initially say us!
You gave up your companions of East Blue for your boat!
Why do you cry?
Baka! One does not cry! Baka!
It is right which… You split me the heart to want to protect your all alone boat.
We do not cry! None us cries!
What do they have?
At all events, you include/understand or not?
We are not any more companions!
Then…
Such an amount of cruelty. I will sing this ballade:
“Broken Friendship. Rupture of the Wind of North.”
Yay, Aniki!
You foutez yourselves of my mouth?!
Oi, still not of tea? I am assoifé.
Yes, a moment.
I am burst through chialer.
Even if I did not chialé.
Here is, Aniki. It is a little hot.
Thank you.
Of agreement, I included/understood, Nii-chan.
THAT BURNS!
Calm yourself a little!
Afflicted for all, Aniki.
You should take some, you too.
Would be honnète, you must us want of it with dead since one you ace taken your 200 million.
Especially if that finished in argument between you.
Do not make any you for that.
Resentment is not used for nothing.
Spoken well, I include/understand.
However, the 200 million…
I very spent!
I go you foutre a beating!
Let us go, does not irritate you like that.
But with as much of aggressiveness…
You believe that I can pass sponge?
To have demolished my house, Franky House.
More all wounds of my men.
BANDAGE JERKS!
Aniki!
Your anger returned!
Good, much things did without, but Nii-chan…
One will calm both a little…
And to take measurements which settle.
It is “which is essential”.
They is “which is essential”, Aniki.
Good, one of fout.
What will you make all alone now?
Now, you do not have nowhere where to go.
Then one will deal with you.
Become one of my men!
I love you well.
Not question. I do not intend at all to become desossor.
Even if I left the crew, I remain a pirate.
You will hear:“Honor of the Pirate”.
Yay, Aniki!
You still foutez yourselves of my mouth?!
I think of future, guy.
I of insane, me.
You could not go to slacken you elsewhere?
Does the high tide arrive this evening, not true?
Ouais, and it is for that.
We must help each other when Aqua Laguna arrives.
In the neighborhoods of midnight, the houses of the first two floors will be under water.
This moment, there should be nobody close to the shore or in the streets.
If you leashes your boat here, that will go.
Oh, thank you.
It is very pleasant.
Baka! They is good, are with collects to you so much!
But doesn't that disturb you to have to undergo this high tide every year?
We took all the practice to take refuge each year.
The problem, it is that the level of water does not cease increasing every year.
The low city which you see…
At summer built on the ruins of an old city, several hundred years ago.
A long time ago, the island of the shipyard and the low city formed only one.
And now that it is immersed, it is called the Quoted Watery one.
The streets became channels.
In fact, it is not the level of the water which goes up, but the ground which goes down.
If that continuous, it will become impossible to live downtown.
I see.
This splendid Watery Citée is not perfect.
But if that becomes too dangerous, you will have only to change island with Umi Ressha.
One can say that.
But Umi Ressha was installed there are a few tens of years.
Before that, it was very difficult to cross the ocean.
Naturally, there was not as much traffic on the island.
The inhabitants were done with the idea…
That this isolated island would run one day, the city and all that goes with.
But a thing made disappear concerns…
It was Umi Ressha, “Puffing Tom”.
Henceforth, everyone can cross the ocean without log, it is a revolution.
Then it was thus.
Umi Ressha is really enthralling.
Toilets 7 were restored…
All that thanks to the great Tom genius, which invented Umi Ressha.
This man all saved us.
Aniki!
Help us…
I will pass the hello to your Aniki.
We know where it is.
Allons-y.