You gave up your companions of East Blue for your boat!
Why do you cry?
Baka!
One does not cry! Baka!
It is right which…
You split me the heart to be wanted to protect your all alone boat.
We do not cry!
None us cries!
What do they have?
At all events, you include/understand or not?
We are not any more companions!
Then…
Such an amount of cruelty. I will sing this ballade:
Broken Friendship. Rupture of the Wind of North.
Yay, Aniki!
You foutez yourselves of my mouth?!
Aniki!
Help us…
I will pass the hello to your Aniki.
We know where it is.
Allons-y.
Onii-san, the tea is ready.
Made a pause.
Ah, sorry for the disturbance.
I would take some after having finished that.
Ca hurts!
Ohhh, have!
Then, Onii-chan.
Answer my question…
What will you make after having repaired the boat?
What?
One of course will set out again with the adventure
and perhaps to turn over in my village of East Blue.
It will not be a voyage around the world…
But for a boat which surmounted Grand Line,
the return will be triumphing.
The hand on the heart, I go…
Not, you cannot turn over on East Blue.
It is too much far.
Aniki.
I threw an eye on the boat when we brought back it.
He, stop you!
What you will make in Merry?!
Remove these cords! Put back the boat!
If you damage Merry, my 8000 men will not tolerate.
You listen to me, dumbs of désosseurs?!
You go morfler if you do not listen to me.
I am the Master of East Blue, the children are afraid…
By hearing my name, Captain Usopp!
You do too much noise.
Do not grip me, you…
The farm.
Ca hurts!
Afflicted, I excuse myself…
Forgive me…
Your boat is foutu.
The estimates of Galley were true for it.
As a desossor, I advise you to dismount it.
Get stuffed!
I will help you in the stages of disassembling.
What you tell?!
Wait, until you will make?
Stop!
Aniki!
I say to you just that I want to help you to dismount the boat.
Stop your conneries!
I will not let myself make!
Merry is MY boat!
Not, it is not…
Nothing more than one boat.
What?!
I presently asked you what you would do after having repaired the boat.
If you did not hope to risk your life on sea with this boat…
I would not have put the question.
But….
Since you say to want to turn over on East Blue with this boat…
I must stop you…
Onii-chan.
This boat will not even be able…
To reach the next shore.
Listen,
a boat…
Is born with the promise from…
“To sail from one bank to another.”
What means…
A boat which cannot reach other bank…
O-oi!
Stop!
A boat which cannot sail any more…
IS NOT ANY MORE ONE BOAT!
Aniki!
STOP!
The preferred man of the boat!
Tears of Usopp!
Species of dumb!
Do not touch in Merry!
Stupid jerk!
IF YOU DO NOT WANT TO INCLUDE/UNDERSTAND…
NOTE YOUR OWN EYES!
Afflicted, Merry.
I will repair you immediately.
Immediately…
I will continue…
Still…
And still…
I will repair you!
Always!
Oi, drops, Length-Nose!
You saw the hold, not true?
The skittle is broken in the center!
The slats are detached, the frame is foutu too!
With this hull, all will yield to the first wave!
It is not a poor amateur as you who will arrange the things!
FIRM MT MOUTH!
I DO NOT WANT ANY MORE TO HEAR You!
STILL A WORD AND I YOU BOOT THE BOTTOM! DUMB!
Whore!
I knew it already…
Hein?
What you ace known as?
To be…
Honest…
To be honest, I knew all that!
I knew that…
MERRY WAS FOUTU!
I…
Knew.
When I heard the results of the examin…
I understood that what it had occurred this day was quite real.
Initially…
I believed that it was a dream.
I thought that such a stupidity could not take place.
But this night of full moon, in this misty forest…
I heard the hammering of a hammer out of wooden.
Ca came from the boat, and there was supposed over there not to be nobody.
I had noticed…
That the noise came from the boat.
The fog was thick…
But I am sure over there to have seen somebody…
Who hammered with a wood mateau.
And…
Without knowknowing which it was…
Incredible!
The boat had been badly repaired in the morning.
The torn off mast had also returned in its place.
But what I did not include/understand…
Was that which had done that,
knew the original configuration of Merry.
Despite everything the made modifications,
Merry had returned to its initial form.
It was a mystery…
But however, of the words trotaient me in the head.
I do not know if that came from me…
Or if it were him which had spoken.
You do not worry.
I will still hold out.
Ca can appear stupid…
But I think that it was…
Merry…
Its incarnation.
It is what I thought.
It probably knew that the boat had reached its limits…
And had appeared in this form for us to say it.
Here of what I thought by hearing the results of the examin.
You must take to me for insane.
You summers not obliged to believe me.
Aniki?
That I you croive or not…
It resembled a sailor with a wood hammer, hein?
Why…
How do you know it?
You know what, Onii-chan?
You saw Klabautermann.
Klabaru…
Klabautermann.
A legend which is transmitted from generation to generation in the sailors.
A spirit which lies only in the boats which are maintained carefully.
In fact, it is an incarnation of the boat.
It holds a wood hammer in its hand and carries one waxed of sailor.
When the boat is in danger,
it runs around the boat to inform everyone.
It is said that it sometimes saved sailors.
But it is the first time that I intend somebody to affirm to have seen one of them.
More the sailors deal with him,
more the boat is grateful.
This boat was to want to take you along towards the next island no matter what it arrives.
You think that this boat was happy…
To have met a crew which he wanted at all prices to transport…
And to appear under human form?
Merry.
I include/understand.
Then it was you…
Who spoke this time to me.
Merry.
But that surprises me.
You fought with your companions in spite of the bad condition of the boat?
It is not so simple only that.
The men do not include/understand anything!
They are stupid!
It would seem that somebody arrives.
If there is somebody outside,
that can be only Zanbai and the others.
Why don't they pass the side sea?
It is true.
Usually, they use the entry top.
Perhaps they bring back Straw hat?
It is true,
I had forgotten that you were used to me as soft food to attract Straw hat!
They will not come. They are not any more my companions.
I said it to you.
Why they do not enter?
Ok, ok, we will open.
Ok, ok, made not such an amount of noise!
Onii-chan, turns over to see your companions.
I cannot.
I defied the captain.
And the problem of the boat is not regulated yet.
What do you understand by “regulated”?
All is regulated if the boat cannot sail any more.
Leave it to me and I will occupy myself some, you will not have with you to make some.
As I said, I think that best for you would be to dismount this boat.
Pas la pains to insist! It is my problem!
I want just to help you to regulate your problem, thanks me!
To thank you? You pleasant?
You do not include/understand?
It is also a problem for the boat!
The day when this boat, which will have loved you at the point to appear under human form…
Will run in the middle of the ocean while transporting you…
Oi! It will be able to never rest in peace!
It will never reach beyond.
Then, you would be able to let die a companion?!
Do not say that, that does not have anything to see!
Of course that not! It is similar!
Guy! You do not include/understand anything!
Mozu!
Kiwi!
But which it is?!
Excuse my intrusion.
These two women did not want to let to us enter.
Engineers of Galley it!
What you foutez there?!