The exit is close!
One directly will be propelled outside!
What? It is not true!
Yosh! Umi Ressha is there!
Go the guy! One goes there!
Jump! Sodome, Gomorrhe!
Straw hat!
All the members of Franky Family are with your service!
Brilliant!
It is of King bulldozers of higher class!
I wanted to also to join me to you.
These types which took on board your friend…
with me also because they are my enemies of
are taken with the life of Iceberg-san.
And then I have still many things to say to them!
Well, then…
Franky Family and engineers of Galley it…
There was small different downtown.
But now, we have a common enemy.
They is bad!
I said it to you.
My job was right to put the train on the rails.
Nothing can stop it now.
He, Luffy!
Now that we all go in the same direction…
there is no reason but one fights separately.
Listen! We are allied!
The guy! It is not one
large wave which will stop us!
One all will achieve our goal!
It LEFT!
Now, the guy, made
something against this wave!
Open fire with all the guns available!
I DEAL WITH CANON!
Franky Family! Do not move back vis-a-vis vagueness!
Prepare the guns!
Let us not waste time!
Pleasing more!
Ah, the baby Den Den Mushi sounds!
It is surely Sanji-kun!
What did it occur…?
Here too!
They all were overcome!
TO STRIKE THE WAVE!
THE POWERFUL COMBO OF LUFFY AND ZORO
Oï! You over there!
Yes, T-Bone Captain!
How were you made this wound with the arm?
I was made prick by an insect.
I scraped and that bled.
They are not good! We must stop the hemorrhage!
Use this while waiting.
Not! Do not use your invaluable cape!
That should go now. When one of my
men bleeds, that makes me nausea.
T-Bone captain…
I request so that the world is in peace each day.
Its head makes really fear.
Captain!
What do you have says?
J I did not still say anything.
If there is something which I can do,
even if I must leave the life there…
Not.
All officers of coaches 6
and 7 were made massacre!
And the two criminals also disappeared!
How?!
It is not known if there were an intruder or
if they are escaped by themselves!
It is terrible…
We must save the life of our men!
Defer the situation to all the coaches!
Yes!
Nami-san! Nami-san,
do you hear me?!
Yes! It is you, Sanji-kun?
It became a dangerous hair here.
Dangerous?
Sanji-kun! What a is this voice?!
He! What it occurs, Sanji-kun?!
Oï! Oï!
Ah, all that because of an idiot!
I-idiot?
E-Encore! What it is?!
- Will Ca go?
What occurs?! All is well, Sanji-kun?!
- It is inevitable.
- It is inevitable? Oï…
- Which is an idiot?!
Not… because of two idiots…
Takes that!!
As I expected it, one
cannot create opening!
Not, it is not finished!
Move back all! Made place with
special gun of Franky Family!
Target, Aqua Laguna!
FIRE!
Super Canon Scrap!
Shit! Flancher is not necessary!
Continue to draw!
Bring more ammunition!
Of agreement!
Concentrate the shootings on only one and even not!
Draw on the same point!
Give your maximum.
The rails can, more or less, rise
with the top of surface…
but they cannot pass Aqua Laguna.
If it directly is struck,
even Rocket Man will not resist it.
Will one die?!
This is why I said to you to prepare.
Quoiii?! Us too?!
I thus see… Robin is still…
Moreover… it would be said that you have fun.
He, Sanji-kun.
The reason which pushes Robin to be acted thus…
and our situation…
THE FARM!!
Listen, Sanji-kun.
I very will say to you in connection with what hides behind the actions of Robin and our current position.
Listen attentively.
One goes crasher!
Oh not! One died! One will die!
Stop groaning and continue to draw!
Open a way!
Oï, Luffy.
Ouais. In us to play, Zoro.
Oï! You do not stop drawing!
What you will make
One will draw…
a boulet de canon.
It is what the double of 108?!
216.
216, it is long and hard to say that.
It does not matter.
What they are making?!
What they intend to make with
naked hands and with sabers?!
They said that one was to continue to draw.
What you make?! Let us cover them!
Yosh… then 300!
One will strike the wave!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Yosh… then 300!
Ok!
One will strike the wave!
Sanji-kun…
They thus did it.
ONE… ONE PASSED!
AQUA LAGUNA WAS PASSED!
I believed that I was going to die!
Oï! Nami-san, all is well?!
Ouais, it is a miracle.
That it is well!
You are not pirates of shoddy goods!
They are frightening like enemies…
but as allies, there is not better!
STRAW HAT!
I was really persuaded that one was going to die.
They are incredible.
You do not slacken, the guy.
The storm yet was not passed.
From now on, nothing is feared!
It was funny!
Straw hat…
Be impressive for you!
It was superhuman!
Oh, sorry.
Luffy, come here!
It is Sanji-kun.
Yo, Luffy.
Ah, Sanji!
How does that occur for you? How is Robin?
Robin-chan is still captive.
Nami-san have just explained me the situation.
Ouais, I very heard.
I see.
Ah, therefore it is that.
Them foutre goes a beating.
Oï! Luffy, would not be ridiculous!
Say to him to wait until one arrives!
Oï, cook! You hear me?!
In this train, has full with dangerous type there…
That will go.
Zoro…
What did you want to make?
When you known ace that Robin had lied and that it
had let itself capture to save us…
You would have remained without anything to make?
Useless to try to stop it.
Finally, you are not so stupid that.
Oï, Marimo-kun! You worry for me?!
In your dreams! Cretin!
But unfortunately…
when I learned the reasons from the choice of Robin…
even an order of the captain…
could not stop me!
Why you broke it!?
I had full with things to request from Straw hat!
Hein? How I could the knowledge?
Should to you have said it earlier.
Why I should have said that?! Do not be unaware of me!
I ignore you…
I hope that they are well.
Granny! Made in kind make the train faster!
Faster?
Ouais! More rapiiide!
Calm yourself, the train already acquired its top speed.
And from now on, one cannot any more stop it.
It is thus what occurred
since I left the crew.
Robin-chan does not know anything in connection with the condition
of Merry or combat between Luffy and you.
Robin-chan sacrificed himself for us six, included you,
so that we all are healthy and safe.
It did it for us.
What a sad history!
Why you chiales?
Cretin! I chiale not!
Fact of shitting! Why?! Nico Robin with the reputation to be a démoniaque woman and without heart!
Then why this sentimental history of friendship?!
Robin-chan is just there.
It does not matter the situation, I will help it.
Franky, the leader of Franky Family, goes you
to give a knack, guy with the rolled eyebrows!
To be honest, I have also a reason of
to save Robin of the claws of the government.
But it is especially because tone
history tore me the heart!
Oï! Allons-y, Length-Conk!
I…
I do not come.
That does not relate to me any more.
And then, if our enemy is the government
world in person…
I do not want to be implied, and…
you will find Luffy and the others, not truth?
There is no more no reason so that remains with you…
especially after my ashamed behavior
and all the hard words which I could say…
I am sorry for Robin…
but for me…
I do not have any more any reason to help it!
I left the crew!
Hello.
O-Oï! How that, hello?
But where hope you to flee?!
That will go.
Leave it.
Which head of mule…
Find quickly!
There should be indices!
That… that will go!
Please, that preserves you!
Wanze-san!
Terrible things occurred in the train!
The farm! Terrible things occurred HERE!
Nero-san! The criminals are escaped!
How does that do without your side?
Nothing suspect?
Me also, nothing to announce.
I see.
Ah! I found them!
Ah shit!
METALLIC STAR!
Who is there?!
Your friend explained me all the situation.
It seems that you wish to save an young woman.
I do not need another reason to help you.
Let to me fight with your with dimensions!
My name is…
Sogeking!