Coach n° 7
T-Bone captain.
It is impossible that they are hidden in a so small coach…
Good evening!
They are there!
They are on the other side of the door!
Criminals and a third located intruder.
I hate the indirect combat.
Chokkaku Senkou
Bone Sowaru
Di… disappeared!
It is not true!
They took down us.
WHAT!?
Shit! Bastards!
You do not lose anything to wait!
Already too late?
On this Sirs,
take guard with the monstres marins and good voyage!
Good-bye!
Coach n° 4
Wanze!
Insane the, insane one, Wanze!
Sift! Wanze!
If you want to cross this coach,
you must overcome me initially!
You hope to stop us?
I will stop you! Sift!
If, by chance, it occurs something during
the mission of this convoy in Umi Resha, I am there!
If you want to release the criminals… Initially try to beat my Ramen Kenpo!
They took down the last two coaches?
What do you manufacture?
All my excuses.
Our best soldier, the T-Bone captain, is also in the detached coaches.
Then, which is the situation of this train?
Yes. Without counting the engine, it remains in all the 5 coaches.
But the soldiers of Coach 5 all were beaten.
There remains only Wanze in Coach 4…
And Nero in Coach 3.
Also, Nico Robin in Coach 1, and people here present in Coach 2.
It would be said that the enemy is not stupid.
But the only problem in this situation, it is that Franky was released.
Our mission is to escort Franky and Nico Robin in Enies Lobby.
This put aside, that some of them burst
or that it arrives to us something,
That does not affect the mission.
Then, did you identify the enemy?
Yes. Initially there are the two prisoners.
One of them carries an odd mask.
There is also a fair man in costume (ndT:under heard costar-cravatte). Thus three people in all.
It is probably a companion of Straw hat like the Long Nose.
Their objective is of course to recover Nico Robin.
And Franky their ready strong hand.
Lucci, do I have to supervise Nico Robin?
Pas la pains.
Concentrate on recaptures of Franky.
To recover Nico Robin…
For them…
It is completely impossible.
Sanji VS Ramen Kenpo !
Fights Chiefs!
Coach n° 4
At all events, let me deal with him
You, you go to the following coach.
Do not forget that it is our plan to help Robin.
It is impossible.
You… I… do not rez… no one… it… share!
I mix and I wet the flour…
It will remake ramen?
Ramen Beam!
Needles!
Caution!
Stop that!
One passes by above!
Ok.
With… then Sanji-kun, good luck.
Sift!
They are flee so quickly!
But it is quite as useless!
Because in the following coach, there is Nero.
Even if it is new, it is an assassin of the justice of the CP9!
They died!
Nero adores to kill.
Sift!
Flanchet Shot
So at least one knew in which coach is Robin,
one could be easily introduced there while passing by the roof.
What is this you cards with marmonner? Dépèche to climb, Geso King!
(ndT:Geso = Squid)
Who calls you squid?!
Squid?
Ca…
Hurry a little, octopus species!
Speedo-kun!
I have an idea.
Listen with your heart.
To flee without stop do not make advance the things.
Do not oblige me to repeat that I am in a hurry.
Then I go there!
Ramen Kenpou:Menkiri
((ramen kenpou skate cut noodle on fire))
Fire-Skate!
Ca hurts!
While dodging me, you gave me ten kicks.
Twelve blows.
Do not say to me that you are super strong!
It is right you who is super bad.
Oi oi! “super bad” you say, even my father me forever known as that!
Stop!
It is insulting! I am Wanzeee!
In fact your strange rolled up eyebrows give me the tournis.
Put besides, you are rather gifted.
YOU ES BADLY PLACE TO SAY THAT MY HEAD STRANGE EAST.
Sah! They is good.
You will include/understand why I was choose for this mission of escort.
Ramen Kenpou Ougi
((ramen kenpou technical ultimate))
To beat noodles! To beat noodles to finish…
What is it that?
An edible combination of combat of dream!
Men' S Formal Follows!!
(conventional noodle combination)
Its-its-saaa!
The advantage of Ramen Kenpo is to use noodles freely.
Dumb…
He plays with food since presently.
Special speed, power, blows… I am completely different from presently.
(ndT:repetition of “presently” - _-)
I will show you a force of another level!
Stop speaking and brings itself.
Jerk, I will make you eat all these noodles then are held ready.
And?
Be to you which you?
I keep the third coach.
Using 4 styles, novel member of the CP 9.
The weasel of the seas, Nero.
Shaow!
Then what…?
I cannot even kill you.
You are an invaluable criminal.
Oh, Onii-chan!
What you make on this roof,
Instead of waiting inside?
One never knows.
You could be malignant and pass by above.
Shaow!
You are rather careful kind.
It is important to remain on its guards.
By the way, it is what this trick behind you?
What a low blow!
Ca suits me!
I am the boss of the gangsters of my city.
Hein?
Where did Luffy pass?
Do not know.
“Do not know”?!
What one makes if it fell to water?!
It is not possible.
It was there still a minute ago.
Not true, Chopper?
Hein? Yes.
It is not an answer!
I worry because a person who is supposed being there it is not.
It east can be wedged in the chimney of Rocketman.
Ouais, like me when…
Chopper, dumb!
Await us, Robin!
And Usopp…
Try out the world of Ramen Kenpo!
More power, you speak.
Its-its-saaa! Eat that!
Ramen Kenpou Tonkotsu Spank!!
(tonkotsu = piece of pig for ramen)
It is right the fist of a greenhorn become larger.
Its-its-saaa! Wait a little!
I… I am wedged!
Hopper!
Its-its-saaa!
Imbecile! You were made have by my Ramen Kenpo!
A leg and an arm stuck in the ramen! Which error.
You dared to strike me presently!
Why you take the giddiness, jerk?!
You still tried to spin me the tournis with your eyebrows!
You will pay it!!
Its-its-saaa!
Make shit!
My arm and my leg are wedged!
In this state, I cannot not counteracted.
((Human noodle Press))
Drunk Men Near!!
It is not finished!
Still!
Finally released.
Its-its-saaa!
Me under regard not, imbecile!
It is my Ramen Kenpo of insane, of insane!
If I attack I will stick myself in the ramen.
I should not touch this ramen.
In here still!
Ramen Gyouza Set Clapping
Therefore, there is one place to aim.
Escalope
Ramen Beam!
Its-its-saaa!
I do not have weak points!
I observe you since presently.
Your style of combat uses only your feet.
If you cannot be useful to you about it, you can nothing make!
Its-its-saaa!
Useless, useless!
No matter what you make, you will stick yourself to my combination!
Try to avoid that!
Ramen Kenpou Fukumen Spank!!
(snap double-noodle)
1.4 mm pasta, fedelline.
Lifting?
Ah! My noodle fists are of pieces!
Usually in a combat, I use neither hands, nor knives,
because it is crowned for a cook
But since that one is in a kitchen…
and that you make use of food…
it is another history.
You are more awkward than I thought it!
Senmen Muchi!!
(whip of 1000 noodles)
You are played it cool, small pretentious!
An amateur who doesnot can cook do not should handle the knives of the others!
They are different from the knives which a rabble as uses you!
Afflicted to be pretentious.
It is not to excuse me
But I will show you
the sentence “special couteau de cuisine”
of a cook of first class…
Shaow!
Soru
Strong Hammer
Kami-e
Rankyaku
Shaow!
Fresh Fire
Soru
It is what its problem? It jumped to the sea!
Geppou
How did it can leap in the open air?
I really do not include/understand!
Why Rankyaku did not cut it?
There is something of odd with its body, shaow.
Jerk…
with the Juste…
what you are?!
Long nose-kun?!
Why are you there?