Wealth, Fame, Power.
The man who had acquired everything in this
world, the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The final words that were said at his execution sent people to the seas.
My wealth and treasures?
If you want it, I'll let you have it.
Look for it, I left it all in that place.
Men now, chasing their dreams, head towards the Grand Line.
The world enters the Great Age of Pirates!
Bastard...
Are you messing with me?!
No, I'm impressed.
But if you're in such a rush, then I'll show you...
Witness my new-found power.
It's falling apart!
Oh, no!
I only meant to be half beast, but I became a full giraffe!
THERE'S A TALKING GIRAFFE FALLING DOWN!!
Kaku! Your new power is so hilarious!
A wolf?!
What is this place?! A zoo?!
Damn you all!
Enjoy the fighting powers of the Devil Fruit's ability!
Rankyaku!
Wh-What the hell?! Something's coming!
Amane Dachi! (Rotating Cut!)
This is bad!
Get down, Usopp!
I Won't Kick Even If I Die! Sanji's Way of Chivalry
I see...
The length...
In other words, a longer reach.
Your new power adds to your centrifugal force,
thus making your blade even more accurate and powerful.
Wh-What the...?
Oi, nothing's been broken.
Take a look at the ceiling.
The ceiling?
Huh?
I can see the sky...
Wow...
I wonder why...
Oi, you don't mean that he actually cut through the Tower of Justice?!
This is dangerous!
How pathetic.
Letting your emotions overrun you in a fight.
Shut up, already.
I happen to like this giraffe form.
I love giraffes.
Yeah...
I got it, I got it.
No matter how much sharper your blade may have gotten,
that doesn't scare me even one bit.
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ouch! Stop it Zoro!
S-Stop! Stop it, Zoro!
That hurts! What are you doing?!
Why are you pulling on me?!
Huh? Pulling?
Wow, we're completely stuck.
Yeah, so it seems...
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?!
IT'S NOT MY FAULT!!
It's because you ran into me!
That's because you were just standing there during his attack!
Just hurry and take these cuffs off!
What are those morons doing?
I don't know...
In conclusion, right now we're in exactly the same situation as Robin.
Then, the key is...
One of the CP9 members have it,
and the only way to get it is to beat them.
That's impossible! How the hell can we fight like this?!
Our prey got stuck together.
Alright, Jyabura.
Just stand back and leave those two guys to me.
Hey! Are you trying to take my prey away from me?!
Then what is it?
You saying you wanna fight together?
I'd rather die than do that.
Same goes for me.
Oi, you guys!
Tell us the number on your handcuffs.
Number?
In order to know which key belongs to which handcuffs,
each pair and their keys are labeled individually with a number.
If we have the keys to those handcuffs,
then we can unlock them for you.
Huh? Really?!
Number... The number....
Oh, here it is! It's number two!
Unlock it please!
Not it.
Mine, neither.
Too bad.
What the hell?! After getting our hopes up!
Damn it...
So that means that one of the other three CP9 members have it.
Oh well...
Then, whoever gets the kill first wins.
Guess that's all we can do.
WHAT?!
Whoa! What's with these stairs?
They're cut and out of position.
Something must have happened from that impact I felt earlier.
Is this building okay?
Oi, are you guys okay?!
Zoro!
Sogeking!
Oi! Chopper!
What?
They're waving...
Looks like they're having fun.
Oi~!!
DUMBASS!!
LOOK AT THE HANDCUFFS!!
GO FIND THE NUMBER TWO KEY!!
Huh? Key?
Key?
What the hell is this?
I thought there was gonna be a bridge or something.
That's one huge whirlpool!
I can see the Gates of Justice, but can I get across on a regular boat?
Anyway, there's no time.
I've gotta try something!
Here I go!
HOLD ON!!
ROBIN!!
Yeah! Yeah!
We found out how to get to the Gates!
Let's go tell everyone!
That was close!
What's this?
Gee = Sound Effect for Staring
Gee~!
Th-This is...!
It couldn't be...
Here!
What the...?!
We did it!
We found another secret passage way!
Yeah!
Where the hell are we?!
Help! Help me!
Pirate-niichan!
What are you doing?!
I see.
The keys and the handcuffs both have numbers.
What?
If you guys are stuck like that,
then I'll just fight them both.
Don't be stupid!
There are two of them!
If you get beaten,
then we'll still be cuffed and end up being killed like this.
Please! You're our only hope!
Hope?
That doesn't make me happy!
Damn it!
Sanji, Nami, or Franky.
When one of them gets a hold of key number two,
bring it here immediately.
We're counting on you!
The one who'll get the key the quickest...
...is probably Sanji.
I'll look for Sanji.
I'm their only hope!
I've caught you now~!
Let go of me!
Yoyoi!
Just give up already~!
Die~!
I don't even stand a chance against him.
Franky~
Tekkai!
Boxing!
Soru. (Shave)
What's up with your punch?
You're no ordinary human, are you?
No matter how much you harden your body like steel,
my fists are made of real steel.
Not now!
This is no time to be drinking tea!
A spell!
I was put under a spell!
I was almost swallowed by a high tide, called a 'trap of love'!
You've had three cups already.
Shut up, you witch!
I'm not falling for any more of your traps!
The CP9 members that insulted Robin-chan so horribly on the Sea Train...
I'll never forget that!
Now...
Give me your key!
Too bad.
I guess you're in a hurry.
Go ahead.
Please help yourself to the key.
Where is it?
I don't know.
It's on my body somewhere...
I wonder where it's hidden.
Why don't you search me?
e& WITH PLEASURE~!! e&
You've made a bad start.
I'm such an idiot...
If you're looking for Nico Robin,
she's getting closer and closer to the Gates of Justice as we speak.
But, for her, I guess we should say that she's getting closer to hell.
I already know that.
That's right, Robin-chan's life is on the line.
If you get in my way, I won't hold back, even if you are a woman!
Just hand over your key before you get hurt!
Shouting isn't going to get you the keys.
You don't have to think of me as a woman.
I haven't lived in such an easy world.
As long as there's an order to eliminate,
all I have to do is take your life.
I'm not giving you my life.
The thing I want...
...is the key to Robin-chan's handcuffs.
Then it's okay that tea time is over?
Soru! (Shave)
Your power is definitely that of a superwoman.
I've got you!
Got one shot in.
You...
How could you do such a thing?
I guess that's what they call 'getting yours', don't you think?
You damn little brat!
Getsu Pou! (Moon Walk)
He's fast!
I just stomped you to the ground.
You've already lost!
Now, the key...
Shigan! (Finger Gun)
Rankyaku!
What a boring man.
Yet you call yourself a pirate...
How utterly spineless.
Oi! Shut the hell up!
Give me the key!
I'm through with your obvious threats.
Would you like me to do something fun?
If you don't attack, you will not survive.
He's not coming after me.
That's good.
If he caught up with me again, I'd definitely be dead.
I just have to escape...
Seimei Kikan! (Life Return)
Yoyoi!
Yoi! Yoi! Yoyoi~!
Damn it!
Now, now~!
Shall I just...
...blow you away now, or choke you to death~?
A cold wind blows on this nature!
A peaceful death that couldn't wait for the sprout of spring~!
At least once, allow a blossom of lovely red flowers!
To scatter them around is my obligation to human nature~!
When you go to the other side,
when you see my deceased mother...
Please, let her know...
that I am... I am well,
and killing~!
Now die~!
Now, now, now~!
No!
Haru Gin Jyou! (Spring Brew Emotion)
Kokutei!
Roseo! (Cherry Blossom)
Nami! Are you okay?!
Chopper...
Thank you, you saved me.
What is that?
Does he have a Devil Fruit?
I don't know...
His hair moves like an octopus, I couldn't do anything at all.
Anyway, now's our chance, Chopper.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Why?
If we don't beat him, the key...
This key?
I stole the key without him noticing, but I couldn't get away from him.
Do you know everyone's situation?
Hey, Nami.
What number is that key?
Number?
It's three.
That's not it.
What's with this number?
Something just fell down.
Is this...
...a doll?
It's not.
Sanji?!
Why does he look like that?
Sanji!
Oi, what happened?!
Why's your body like this?
Are you okay, Sanji-kun?!
SANJI!!
I'm sorry.
I lost.
I couldn't get the key...
Hold on, Sanji.
I'll fix you up right away!
I never thought that Sanji-kun would be defeated.
Sanji-kun.
Were you really unable to win?
Did you really fight properly?
Your opponent was that woman, wasn't it?
You're soft on women, aren't you?
I'm sorry about the key.
That's not it!
I'm just saying that you could die because of your stupid way of chivalry!
Are you still gonna honor it, even when you end up like this?
What are you gonna do if you die?!
It's not...
...like I wanna die.
However, I've been raised to never  kick a woman.
That's why...
...even if I die, I will never kick a woman!
You're so stupid.
You idiot!
Oi! What are you doing, Nami?!
If running away is also against your way of chivalry,
then at least throw that away!
To die without a cause is a different story entirely!
Leave that woman to me...
And also,
I've changed my opinion about your way of chivalry.
Did you just say you love me more?
She didn't say that!
I'm not as nice as that guy.
Me neither.
Looks like we'll get along well.
Oi! Don't you wanna help Nico Robin?!
Hurry up and get me a cola!
I haven't forgiven you yet!
Forget about that and hurry up!
With a cola, I'll be able to power up!
Who's stupid enough to become stronger with a cola?!
Leave me alone! I do!
Just watch, I'll finish him off in an instant!
Next time, One Piece: The Silent Owl's Miscalculation!
My Cola is the Water of Life
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!