Does one have to continue Franky?
But where?
Good, they do not seem to know where is the money.
Even if one ends up catching this Franky, he already very spends.
What will one make?
While remaining here, one can await it still a long time.
Ca is not used for nothing to chatter longer.
In any case, let us turn over to the boat.
Nami-san remained all alone.
It misses Robin-chan, too.
There is also the problem of the boat.
Oi, Luffy!
About the boat…
I made my decision…
It is time to separate from Merry!
Fights with the moonlight!
Tears of the pirate boat!
Oooi! Usopp is awaked!
Really?! It is brilliant!
Which relief.
Oi, Usopp!
Robin-chan did not return yet.
Cretin, will not cause us more concern!
Ouais, you is nutcase to be there gone all alone.
Estimate yourself happy to be in life.
Reflected before acting.
You did not make the weight!
I bring only troubles to you.
Afflicted…
I am really…
What a shame! The guy!
All our money… I… I…
He, wait, calms itself!
I included/understood, releases me!
But, all the money that we had finally collected is…
Usopp, you must still rest.
Ca is enough now, do what Chopper says you.
Then it is what I thought…
We will never find the money.
In fact, one will know nothing as long as this Franky will not return.
I include/understand… I am sorry.
It is not serious if we do not find it, we always have 100 million, then do not worry you.
If, it is serious!
Nami.
Afflicted.
Not, it is nothing.
On this subject, Luffy…
The ship, which will become Merry?
Will we be able despite everything to repair it with this 100 million?
After all this time, we can finally repair it in this famous shipyard.
We will be able to repair it completely and to make it more robust…
It will be able to then sail again.
Isn't He, 100 million Berrys, that enough?
With what you do think, Luffy?
And well, with that…
Usopp, we decided to change boat.
Afflicted to have taken this decision in your absence.
But the decision was made.
Merry helped us much…
But the voyage with this boat stops here.
In any event…
In the catalog of Ice-ossan…
There is full with other boats which we can buy.
With 100 million, we can treat to a larger boat of occasion.
Wait…
Wait, wait…
He… It is a joke, not?
He, look at, Chopper believed there.
Our captain is not if defaitist.
Say it to him, Nami.
What? There is not enough money to repair it?
It is because they took the money to me?
We do not have enough any more of money, it is that?
It is that, Luffy?
A boat of quality is inevitably expensive, it is normal.
Not, not, that does not have anything to see!
Then it is what? Say to me!
You want to make me Peter leads?
Of course that not! The money does not have any importance!
Then it is what? Stop with your conneries of change of boat!
Oi, stop both! What good is it to dispute?!
You calm before speaking!
I cannot calm myself with such conneries!
He, the hour is serious but it is not worthwhile to be irritated like that.
Yes, Usopp. You must rest, your body will not support.
I of insane!
Ca returns nutcase to me to see this captain making decisions with the light one.
Pas à la light! I suffered before making this decision!
How can you suffer and finally decide that?!
Except me that of the sight!
What you make?!
What a horror!
Oi, Luffy! If it is not because of the money, then it is what, Luffy?!
Say to me!
Go, why you do not say anything?!
Do not occupy you of me, and say to me!
Say it! But I hope that the reason is valid!
Merry is not any more…
What did you say?
You included/understood very well.
Merry is not reparable any more.
Never…
I will not have said such a thing if it were not the case!
It is THIS boat, this boat on which we are in this moment even!
Yes, this boat is about to run!
What do you say, Luffy?
It is the truth. It is what they said to the shipyard.
They said that it would not even reach the next island.
I see… One would not reach…
You returned, convinced by people that you hardly know?
What?
It has is enough that famous engineers say that to you…
Awake!!
This boat on which we travelled so much all this time…
A companion who resisted the waves and the combat…
Hope you to let it die here?!
It is that which you want for this boat, Luffy?!
Usopp, that is not used for nothing to shout so extremely.
Remain apart from all that.
The conversation is not finished.
Usopp.
What do you decide then?
We do not have a naval engineer in the crew. It is for that one asked them to throw an eye there!
Then they is good, one does not need more to require anything of them!
I will repair it myself, as I always did.
One makes like that since the beginning.
Yosh, I will start immediately.
Oi, come to help me.
Oi, await Usopp.
Ah yes it is true, it misses boards.
Let us buy some with the shipyard.
One will have job.
You are not naval engineer, Usopp!
He, Luffy!
I know, and then?!
It is to have the opinion of an engineer better!
But I do not rely on engineers who would drop a boat like that!
Usopp…
What wants to say that we must protect our boat ourself.
I…
WILL NEVER GIVE UP THIS BOAT!
You become nutcase?!
You were influenced by a band of engineers!
People whom I knew…
Would have relied on the force of Merry…
Rather than to listen to these balivernes!
To drop like a poor old man.
And to believe captain… do not generate the good decisions?!
I badly judged you, Luffy!
He, wait, Usopp. Luffy also…
Keep silent yourself, Nami! I made my decision!
I will not change an opinion!
We will change boat no matter what you say!
We will leave from here without Merry!
Firm! I will not let to you make!
Listen, Luffy…
It is not by trailing the feet as that one leaves oneself there!
I cannot leave from here while giving up a companion!
Anything, a boat is not the same thing!
It is similar!
Merry is alive and still has forces!
You are in a hurry probably already to have your next boat!
Oi, the guys, remain calm!
Ca will not arrange anything to be irritated like that!
DECREE CA IMMEDIATELY!
Luffy!
Do not imagine you that you are the only one to spend a dirty moment!
One feels all the same thing!
It is not question of changing boat!
Of agreement, then if my decision is not liked…
You have only to leave this immediate boat…
Sanji!
Bandage cretins.
You ridges what, there?!
One calms oneself! Did not say anything!
You included/understood, Luffy?!
I am sorry.
I did not want to say that…
Not, they is good, Luffy.
You let speak your heart.
What?!
You do nothing but progress, by throwing the useless companions.
If you give up Merry…
Give up me with.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
You do nothing but progress…
By throwing the useless companions.
If you give up Merry…
Give up me with.
Oi, Usopp, do not say stupidities!
Not, I am serious. I reflect there since one moment already.
Gradually, I understood that I anything was not compared with your superhuman force.
Today, I was unable to protect a little money.
Henceforth, I am only one ball for you, the guy.
You does not want the weak one among you, isn't this?
Luffy, you will become the Lord of the pirates.
But your ambitions are too large for me.
When I wanted to leave at sea, you invited me.
What do you tell? Hurry to go up.
We are already companions, not?
You are my only bonds of fastener.
When our opinions do not agree any more, we should not travel any more together!
Oi, where you go, Usopp?!
Ca does not look at you.
Ca does not concern you any more.
I…
I leave this crew!
Usopp.
Impossible.
He, await you what Luffy?!
You hope to let it leave?! He!
Catch up with it! Quickly, seek Usopp!
Ca is not done only it leaves like that…
After having travelled all this time together?
Isn't Usopp, an invaluable companion?
SEEK IT!
He Luffy.
Aren't you the captain?
Why you do not say anything?
Usopp!
Wait, do not do that!
He, is turned over!
Oi, return!
Do not leave, Usopp!
Please, return!
Luffy.
Luffy, I cannot remain any more in your company.
Afflicted for all these troubles that I brought to you.
The boat is your property, since which you are captain.
Then engagements against me.
Monkey D. Luffy.
ENGAGEMENTS me!
Do He, what you tell?
This evening, 10 hours, I will return.
Then we will fight for Merry.
I would beat you and will recover Merry.
And…
This moment, we will not have anything any more to say to us.
What is there? Stop making the idiots!
Why friends should fight?!
If one grants a little time to the problem, everyone will be calmed.
Usopp has right summer irritated by the conversation.
One cannot retrogress after such a discussion.
Of course that if!
If you will excuse yourself and speak to him, very will arrange itself!
I already said you…
It is too late.
Why?
Usopp is not insane at the point to risk its life for a small argument.
And if one cannot regulate that differently…
There are not the choice.
If you include/understand, go T.
Luffy.
As I thought it…
Did Franky Family come here during the day, not?
Hein? About what you do speak?
Why didn't you deal with them as long as it was still time?
Usopp would not have been made attack.
You would have better done of you to charge some rather than to go to make shopping!
As a cook, I need to buy the necessary one…
It is not the moment to discuss on top!
I intended enough to shout for today.
You do not beat any more for what it occurred.
Nami-san.
But it is this cretin…
Chopper, you have…
Run after Usopp?
I wanted to continue his care…
But it threw me.
Usopp rented a room in a town hall.
He said…
“We are not any more companions, turns over to the boat.”
All these good moments spent together appear to be transformed into lies.
In addition to that…
If something arrives at Robin…
I am afraid well that the crew…
Fly in glares.
The crew of the Straw hat.
Maaa, I do not remain places this evening from there.
It is 10 a.m. Usopp arrives.
The guy, do not go down from the boat!
Included/understood?!
It is there!
Usopp!
You came without fear.
Do not regret anything, it does not matter what it occurred.
Here the duel which you asked!
Of course.
Give all that you ace. I will overcome you.
I know already how I will beat you.