Wealth, fame, power.
The man which acquired everything of this world, the Lord of the pirates, Gold Roger.
It's last words during its execution posed people to take the sea.
My richnesses, my treasures?
If you want them, I leave them to you.
Seek them, I very left over there.
The men, pursueing their dreams, ventured on Grand Line.
Le world now entered the golden age of piracy!
GEAR THIRD
It is open…
Good, I go there.
Why are you so small?
Good, I am become again normal!
Wait, Robin!
Salt dumb of pigeon!
I go you botter the bottom!
[Secret Attack of Jyugon]
JYUGON OUGI
[Multiplication of the owl]
FUKUROU DATAKI
Chapapapapapapa!
[Left Bean]
BEANS LEFT
It was what, that?
Oh not!
It is true, it is of our with dimensions.
I should listen to it.
Cola!
No doubt, it is cola!
Be to you my saver!
SUPER!
Chapapa…
What thus?
It is not cola which will change you suddenly.
Take guard.
Chapa?
Cretin.
You still hope to strike me with your poor blows?
STRONG HAMMER
Oh not!
ENORMOUS!
Afflicted.
Until now, my blows were…
… really poor. You were right.
Does Sogeking become the new saber?
Zoro emerges with a novel method!
In the fact, Franky.
It is time that I explain you.
Zoro and Sogeking are prisoners of a pair of shackles of Pierre Marine.
What?
Then one can nothing make without this key number two?
Indeed.
What a band of cretins!
Good, I see where is the problem.
Chapa!
I am really in bad temper.
Chapapa!
It is coriace, not?
It was raised.
Sit down and admires.
FRANKY
[Canon devastator]
DESTROYER HOU
I hate to twist the shoulders like that.
Then, do not do it!
Chapapa!
Imbecile.
For me which controls Rokushiki,
The balls never reach me.
But you would make better give up,
You are not likely any to escape my Franky Destroyer Hou.
Because it is…
… of the balls with homing device!
Des balls with homing device?
Pas possible!
Les balls locates the enemy and continue it?
C' is the first time that I hear parler. of it
Mais it is which this guy?!
Wait!
C' is you which must follow it?
I said to you to wait.
Chapa, that to make?
Whore!
It still disappeared.
Where are you?
Pas la pains to seek me.
I control Rokushiki and I am an expert of Soru.
In addition to my displacements with speed of light,
I am quiet a such owl, tracking his prey,
Achieving the perfect murder.
An owl?
Never my target sees me to its last breath.
He is funker there.
He had not envisaged that.
Bandage dumbs…
I was never humiliated kind.
I am member of the CP9!
SORU
[Steel Ball]
TEKKAI DAMA
He, pay to!
Whore, it is the ocean below.
Franky!
Oh not!
If the current involves it,
It will fall into the fall from water.
I can nothing make for him in the ocean.
Franky! You will arrive there!
Chapapa…
Even if I fall into the fall from water, there remains to me Geppou.
That fears…
I can nothing make.
The current is well too strong.
I will not have enough air.
I must go up.
Chapapa!
Continuous to run!
Yoyoi!
This voice…
Would it have opened the door of the refrigerator?
Thank you for the meal.
It grew bigger!
You puffed out as well as that?
I do not want to burst here.
I am close to the ravine.
I fall! I fall! I fall!
[Butterfly]
FRANKY BUTTERFLY
Chapapa! I will not let myself make!
GEPPOU
[Wild animal]
JYUGON
Dumb!
Chapa!
[Left Weapons]
WEAPONS LEFT
[Sheet of paper]
KAMIE
SLIME
Chapapa…
Was whore, it what that?
It was less one.
Oh not, that craint.
Je must leave là.
Canon de Cola 1,5 liters!
COUP DE BOO
You include/understand now?
You cannot anything vis-a-vis Rokushiki with your capacity.
STRONG HAMMER
KAMIE
Will visit the water falls!
[Powerful Right-hand side]
STRONG RIGHT
Take-that!
Chapa!
Release me!
I cannot carry you with Geppou on only one foot.
One will fall.
Ouais, I count there well.
But before you tombs, bring back for me on the dry land.
Or you prefer to fight now, while carrying me?
I know that it is not careful.
But I do not have anything to lose.
One is in the same kneader.
Let us turn over on the dry land.
Well, it is that…
Well, well!
Let us turn over together on the dry land.
Chapapa!
But once in top, I will put a term at this combat.
Oh! You believe that?
Chapapapapapa!
Because henceforth….
I know how to finish with you of a blow of it.
Really?
Me also, Fukurou-kun.
Chapa.
Robin! Robin!
You hear me?
Nous will save you costs which costs!
Je you have it promis.
Quoi that it arrives, I you ramènerai.
ROBIN!
Where is the key number two?
Zoro-kun!
I can about it more, I am burst!
Carry me.
And then what still!
RANKYAKU
SHIGAN
You insane what?
Dumb!
While launching this attack, it is me whom you aimed.
Anything.
But if you want to fight, not concern.
I have some enough that you trail in my legs.
What thus?
I was going to say the same thing, salts vegetarian!
He not, I like the meat too.
You would make better turn over to ruminate elsewhere.
I suppose that the confrontation is inevitable.
Very well, then remains here.
I will finish some with the preys.
I do not have any as a a long time.
Wait!
I want well that one fights, but you me leashes the preys.
Very interesting!
Zoro-kun!
Who is strongest according to you, a giraffe or a wolf?
Does that interest you?
Not really.
It is true?
You would like to see them fighting?
Not, I said…
Let make me.
The prognostic one of the largest hunter of pirates,
And of the epeist of the crew of Luffy the pirate is…
Really?
Then you think that the wolf is stronger?
Obviously.
What thus?
Is the giraffe strong too?
Oh, I see.
The “Amanedachi” of presently was impressive, it is that?
You saw just.
The wolves are crafty ones.
But they are not so strong only that.
Dumb, you irritate me!
You want to fight immediately?
Well, well!
It is our chance, Zoro-kun.
I included/understood.
One will benefit from it while they fight between them.
You want téchapper while they fight?
He! You understand that now?
Does not reveal our plans to them!
You failed to make you have.
The preys have priority.
Zoro-kun!
How you ace which been able to do that?
You come from foutre my plans in the air.
In any event, this plan was not terrible.
Here the plan of survival number two!
Zoro-kun, you do not say anything this time.
A giraffe or a wolf, I wonder who am coolest.
The force is not enough.
Really strong somebody, must have the class and be cool.
Which that could be…
On top, there is no doubt.
What do you want to say?
The wolves are stronger and much more cools.
About what you do speak?
Those which the children in the zoos like more,
Are not the wolves, but the giraffes!
For this reason the giraffes are more cools!
I suspected it, you do not reflect more than one horse.
I am not a horse, I am a giraffe.
It is our chance, Zoro-kun!
This kind of pretense will not last a long time.
Then you have another idea?
[Janken: Japanese Pierre-Sheet-chisel]
One plays “Janken”, Sogeking.
The problem is there.
It is possible to get rid of these shackles.
It is what the relationship with Janken?
That which loses…
… the hand is cut.
How you can say a similar thing?
I did not finish my explanations.
Thus that which will be released…
… will leave with its hand to give it to Chopper…
… and it will be able to fix then.
One is not headstocks!
Would not be stupid!
I have another idea…
I do not want to know!
Let us pass to the serious things.
It is when you want.
Gaining has the preys for him all alone.
What…
Perfect, Sogeking.
Remain quite right.
You are my saber!
I want a lawyer!
One day, I will stick a lawsuit to you!
What will you make, now?
Hurry to deposit me with ground.
Like that, I will be able to you foutre a beating.
Pas la pains to harp.
I will make so that you buckle it good once for all.
Fast ultra spinning top!
TEKKAI DAMA
I will propel you on the lathe by the centrifugal force.
I see…
I will surely not leave there alive.
[Centaur]
FRANKY KENTAUROS
Chapa?
I hold you by the legs.
Like that, you lose any freedom of movement.
How that?
Even if you do that, you cannot
nothing against this centrifugal force.
Not inevitably.
Gauge 70 mm, Canon de Cola 0,2!
Small…
COUP DE VENT
It countered the force!
The spinning top stopped.
Whore!
That is enough!
One is soon on the dry land.
Take-that!
Gauge 70 mm, 1,5 max Power Cola!
COUP DE
You insane what, dumb?
Give up!
COUP DE
VENT
SUPER!
I want to save Robin.
Afflicted, Doctorine.
Soon in One Part: Unverifiable!
Rumble prohibited of Chopper.
I will become the Lord of the pirates!