Length-nose-kun.
Try to dodge that!
Ramen Kenpo Fukumen Spank
Note:fukumen spank means “double noodle smacking”.
Usually in a combat, I use neither my hands, nor my knives,
because it is crowned for a cook.
But since one is in a kitchen…
and that you make use of food,
it is another history.
Let to me show itself…
technique of a cook of first class.
Special Houchou Sabaki
Note:special houchou sabaki means “special handling of the couteaux de cuisine”.
Dumb…
What is this qu…
But be to you which brothel?!
What doesn't go, Ramen Kenpou?
Where did your promptness pass?
Cursed would be you! Salt shameless.
Although you would be only one criminal!
My fist-noodles are of pieces!!
I am…
an onion!!
That is not used for nothing to continue the combat.
Admit your defeat and lets pass to me.
To admit my defeat?! How if I were going to do that!
Who said that I was overcome?!
I am have CP7, Wanze!
Unfortunately, I know the importance of this mission.
Your friend Nico Robin was pursued by the government during many years.
One will not let it leave so easily, idiot!
Ramen Kenpo
Note:menkui knocker means “hammer of noodle piles”.
Menkui Knocker
With onions, initially to cut the stem and the root without touching the heart.
The taste is preserved…
while cutting them systematically.
Stop! Does not approach you!
Note:ramen beam means “bar of ramen”.
Ramen beam
Weeding
Although you would be only one cook of third class which plays with food,
I nevertheless congratulate you for maintenance on your knives.
Franky VS Nero
Duel on the roof!
Note:Hoshi Shield means “Spangled Shield”.
It is Hoshi Shield.
It is what this body?! It is not human!
Still fire!
Note:master nail means “main nail”.
Master Nail
Still flown away… I do not include/understand how…
One can nothing make there if the four styles do not go.
I do not control Shigan yet…
I thus will have to use some tricks.
Yosh! It is my chance to advance to the next car!
He! wait, bastard!
I can blink eyes even more.
You were well made have.
Note:beans left means “remaining beans”.
Beans left
Too bad.
Exactly…
what I provided that you make!
IEA!!
That went.
This bastard!
Note:ouche finger means “finger which makes sore”.
Ouche Finger
Soru
Shit,
he noticed.
Rankyaku
That passed very close to me.
Which flexible type.
Then your weak point…
it is your back, hein?
Me also I included/understood how you think.
It is nothing any more but one matter of time before this combat is not completed.
Wait before taking the famous person!
If I do that, I will not have any more weak points.
Invincible Franky
Invincible.
What say some to you, stupid weasel?!
What should I say to him?
What does that want to say?
Why are you there?
How did you come here?
I cannot answer, you pose too many questions.
Good, we calm.
Ah…
A little coffee?
Do not talk cock!
How…
Charmed to meet you. I am the King of Snipers, Sogeking.
To make short, I came to save you.
Length-nose-kun…
And there is not only me.
There is Sanji-kun and named Franky the gangster which fight in the train.
I benefitted from it to come here.
Moreover, Luffy-kun and the others follow us with another Umi Ressha.
With a whole group, apparently.
I looked by the window before coming here.
But the four in the preceding car had the very dangerous air.
The ideal would be to save you before Sanji-kun does not meet them!
Let us let us go both!
What doesn't go?
You do not have to worry, I very envisaged.
Note:okutopa-Kutsu means “shoe-octopus” (or suction cup).
Here your okutopa-kutsu.
If you put them at the hands and the feet, you will be able to climb by the window and to stud yourself in Umi Ressha.
Go, before they see us.
Wait.
“Wait”?
Why that does it occur thus?
I clearly did you my good-byes.
I will never return in the crew!
They know all why…
you said that.
Ice-ossan of the shipyard very explained.
It is well?
Not,
even thus,
I will not return with you.
About what you do speak?
You still do not include/understand?!
They are not as weak as you think it!
They wanted to speak to you before you do not make this stupid market!
You should have spoken to them about it front!
You think that they will be content…
if they sacrifice a friend right to save themselves?!
Now that they know why you left,
they will follow you until in hell…
and all your enemies will destroy!
You still do not know what a kind of Luffy man is!
It is you who do not include/understand!
I did not ask to be saved!
Remain apart from that!
What?!
Why this din, Nico Robin?
What doesn't go?
Now that Enies Lobby is in approach,
you cannot remain calm any more?
Even if you cry over your own destiny,
your life will not be saved for as much.
It is nothing.
Was C-C' what that? It is suspect…
It would be said that it of changed there something into it…
It is right my imagination?
I said that it was nothing.
Then please, leave me.
But what does she play?
A rabbit?
Oï! Stop that-shaow!
Stop talking cock and fight sérieusement-shaow!
Upright!
Supervise your language, stupid weasel.
I do not joke.
But finally, you ace not of chance.
You ace really not of bowl.
You returned to me furious.
This week I am in SUPER form!
He, frérot…
You know the monster which one calls Centaure?
That which is semi-human, semi-horse, it is that-shaow?
Where do you want to come from there?
Hentai!
Note:hentai means “abnormal character here”. (Pun with the other translation:transformation.)
Abnormal character
Critical situation
Me known as step only it…
Note:Franky Kentaurusu means “Franky the Centaur”.
Franky Kentaurusu
It is the reverse! Your body is with back!
Do not criticize before to have seen its power.
Why one still does not see Bashing Tom?
Puffing!!!
He, Luffy! Return inside!
You have just changed clothes and be already very soaked to you!
They is good! It is my seat!
Gomu gomu No….
300 pound…
CANON!!
GIFT!
Splash!!
More Laguna!
STOP PLAYING, BAND Of MORONS!!
One is bored.
Prepare your weapons or another thing, idiots!
Ben… euh… will be necessary that I speak to them presently…
Oï, the guy!
I see a train right in front of us!
It is Puffing Tom!
It is not a little too early?
Let pass to me!!!
Will shit… what arrive to us?
There is not any more an engine. All that one can do is to wait.
One pitches!
But will somebody help us with this storm?
There are not any more other choices, if nobody saves us.
Oï, everyone! Something arrives by the back!
Really?
A lifeboat.
Not, in fact,
it would be said that it makes use of the rails.
Not possible.
There is one Umi Ressha in the world.
And it was impossible to leave Water 7 after the last train.
Well…
Then…
What approaches?
Oï!
It is Umi Ressha, but there is no engine! There are only cars!
It is stopped on the rail!
What?!
WHAT SE PASSES?!
It would be said that they were detached.
Sanji and Usopp are perhaps on board!
Franky Aniki, too!
They is bad! At this rate/rhythm, one will strike it!
Granny-san, brakes!
No chance that they go.
Made something.
One will be crushed!!
Nyaaa nyaaaa!!
Luffy, which do you hope to make?
I will see what there is inside.
Gomu Gomu No…
Rocket
Something flies.
Yosha, I did it.
Qu-Qui you are brothel?!
Oooï Sanji, be to you there?!
Usopp…
Oooï, Sanjiii!!
Oooï!!
Are Z' there?
Me known as step that it is…
It IS LUFFY WITH the STRAW HAT!!
Oooï!!!
You are there?! Sanji?!
Sanji…?!
Close it!
Straw hat, you do not have nowhere where to flee!
Where is Sanji?
Is Qu-Qui it?
Sanji, it is a companion with me!
This guy is not known!
I see…
With more.
FIRE!!
Straw hat left!
He says that they are not there… while one draws to him above…
Then there is only of the guy of the government inside.
And what do you hope to make?
If it is not moved, it will longer remain us to live.
It is Umi Ressha after all!
One will be made propel in the airs.
Not, one will explode if it returns us inside!
STOP!
It is with the tower of Franky Family now. One will bone it right before striking it!
Yosh! One will help you!
The guy, one has job!
OUAIS!!
Oooï, Zoro!
Oï, Roronoa, it calls you.
Cut it. That obstructs.
Ouais.
“Ouais”, which he says!
It will strike us!
STOP!
Ego in a world of ruins.
I will cut it.
Nitouryü Iai
Note:Nitouryü means “Style with 2 Sabers”.
Iai is art to leave a saber, to cut its opponent and to arrange the saber very quickly.
Rashömon
Note:Rashömon means “door” in old dialect of Kyoto.
He, the guy! If you continue to make similar tricks, warn us front!
You intended me to say to him “Cuts it”?
It was not thought that it would really cut it!
But one would have been crushed if it had not cut it!
Yes, but… one was to prepare.
It is monstrueusement strong and yet it is not the captain…
They are impressive!
Frankly, you are incredible!
I did not know that there was second Umi Ressha.
To this pace, they surely will catch up with them.
So by misfortune, the criminals whom one captured were to be saved…
That will not arrive!
This man is between…
first Umi Ressha and them!
It is true!
As long as the Navy has this man,
our justice will not flanchera!
Yosh, it left!
Nitouryü Iai!
Rashömon!!
He, it is not you the train?!
Why?! Do it to you!
, Do it to you!
Not question! I do not want to be destroyed!
You must be made destroy!
I do not want!
Oï, the guy!
It is not finished yet.
It is what that?!
It is a King of the seas.
He is enormous…
Sashimi!
Note:Sashimi is a Japanese traditional dish containing believed fish.
It is cut into two!
Roasted Poisson!
Really enormous…
Rocket Man with the tiny air at side!
It is right in front of…
that which sliced it.