Wealth, Fame, Power.
The man who had acquired everything in this
world, the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The final words that were said at his execution sent people to the seas.
My wealth and treasures?
If you want it, I'll let you have it.
Look for it, I left it all in that place.
Men now, chasing their dreams, head towards the Grand Line.
The world enters the Great Age of Pirates!
Sogeking.
Make that flag burst into flames.
Roger that.
My new weapon, the Great Pachinko.
Going by the name of Kabuto! Closely behold its power!
No way...
Done.
Are you out of your mind!?
Don't think you'll be able to survive having the world as your enemy!
YOU WANNA BET!?
Robin!
I still haven't heard it from your mouth!
SAY YOU WANT TO LIVE!!
Robin...
Robin!
Live...
I thought wishing for it was forbidden...
Nobody would allow me that...
The sea is vast.
Someday, without any doubt,
nakama who will protect you will appear!
If I'm really allowed to declare my wish...
Then I...
I WANT TO LIVE!!
TAKE ME OUT TO THE SEA WITH YOU!!
I love you guys!
Damn it!
Let's go!
The drawbridge is lowering!
Looks like it went well on those guys' side.
That's great.
Robin!
We absolutely will save you!
The drawbridge is lowering!
Go, Straw Hat-san!!
Damn you, pirates!
We won't let you!
Prepare the mortar cannon!
Stop the drawbridge even if you have to blow it up!
Yes!
The drawbridge stopped!?
They're getting in our way!
What is this!? Damn it!
Who was it!?
Oi, pirates!
Kokoro-san?
I can hear everything. Why are you wasting your time there?
Wasting our time? But the bridge is only half lowered...
Jump into the waterfall with all your heart!
The seatrain...
Heh!
What's with that "Heh!" while smiling?
Let's go!
I wouldn't have taken you with me anyway!
As if someone like you could become a pirate!
I will!
Someday, I'll gather nakama who won't lose to this crew,
find the greatest treasure in the world,
and I'll definitely become the Pirate King!
When I was a kid, I swore to gather nakama and become the Pirate King.
To the pirate who protected me...
You're already my nakama.
Robin...
Just like the pirate who protected me,
I'll protect you too!
Pass some here, oi!
Then take me on your next voyage, Shanks!
I want to become a pirate too!
As if someone like you could become a pirate!
Why not!?
Luffy, no matter how well you can swim, you can't become a pirate just like that.
I'm strong in fights too! My punch is like a pistol!
Ah, is that so?
What's with that tone!?
Basically, Luffy's just a kid.
You're the same age as my kid you know.
I'm not a kid! I'm an adult already!
Don't get so angry.
Here, drink some juice.
Thanks!
See!? You're a kid!
That's dirty, Shanks!
Stop laughing!
What!? Damn you Shanks!
Sorry for intruding.
Oh, so these are the so-called pirates.
They all have such idiotic mugs...
Welcome.
We are bandits.
We didn't come to break havoc in this bar...
Sell us some sake.
We need ten barrels.
I'm really sorry.
We're short on sake at the moment.
This is pretty weird.
These pirates are drinking something, is it water?
As I told you, the sake you can see is everything we have.
We did something bad.
We drank all of the sake.
Sorry.
If this is alright, you can have it.
The bottle cap is still on.
The bounty on my head is worth $8,000,000...
A single bottle of sake is far from being enough.
Don't underestimate me.
Now the floor's completely wet.
I'm sorry about that, Makino-san.
Do you have a dry cloth?
Ah, I'll do it.
It seems you like cleaning up.
With this, it'll be worth doing it.
If there's no sake, then there's no need to discuss this.
Let's move out!
Seeya, cowards.
Are you alright?
Captain-san, are you injured?
No, I'm alright. It's no problem.
You really were done over by that guy, boss!
How ridiculous!
Why are you all laughing!?
Wasn't that uncool!?
Why didn't you fight him!?
No matter how numerous or how strong they are,
you're not a man if you laugh after something like this happens to you!
You're not a pirate!
It's not that I don't understand how you feel...
But they only spilled some sake.
It's not worth getting angry over, is it?
I don't care anymore!
Gobbling it up, Luffy?
Shaddap!
What are you eating!?
Was it this box!?
Did you eat what was inside this box!?
Spit it!
Spit up everything you ate immediately!
Wh-What are you doing, Shanks!?
What was that... just now?
What you ate was the Gomu Gomu fruit!
The Gomu Gomu fruit is a Devil Fruit!
You become a rubberman after eating it!
And you inherit a body that is unable to swim for the rest of your life!
NO WAY!!
YOU FREAKING IDIOT!!
You disturbed us while we were having fun drinking sake...
What's the big deal, brat?
Shit! Apologize!
How could you make fun of Shanks and the others!?
Did I say something that stayed on your mind?
You did! Apologize!
Mayor-san!
Did you see the faces of those pirates from earlier!?
What a pathetic guy, he wouldn't let out a word of complaint after having sake spilled all over him!
Pirate crews are a gathering of cowards.
They're pitiful.
Stop it!
Don't ridicule Shanks and the others!
They're not cowards!
Please stop it, Luffy!
Don't take Shanks and the other for idiots!
You moron bandit!
Your choice of words was quite bad, brat.
No one has survived pissing me off up until now...
Ah, please wait!
Please release that kid!
I beg of you!
I have no idea of what Luffy did, and I've got no intentions of going against you.
If an apology won't do, we'll pay you!
I beg of you, please spare that boy's life...
Mayor!
As expected, elders know the ways of this world very well...
But it's no use, this brat won't be saved.
He pissed me off, you see...
The bad ones are you, mountain monkey!
What a hopeless runt...
Repent for your actions in the other world!
Luffy!
I beg of you, let him get away!
I was wondering what was happening since the bar was empty.
Ain't it the bandit from earlier?
Captain-san!
Shanks!
Pirate... You're still in this village?
Were you trying to clean the whole village all this time?
Luffy.
Wasn't your punch as strong as a pistol?
Shut up!
I don't know what you came here for, but it would be better for you to run before getting hurt.
We'll blow your head off if you get any closer, coward.
He told you not to get any closer,
or I'll blow your head to pieces.
Bet your life on it.
If you're going to use that pistol, bet your life.
What are you talking about, you bastard?
I told you this wasn't a kid's toy.
He did it!
What unfair jerks!
Unfair?
Stop talking naive trash.
Are you planning to fight us after this?
The ones standing in front of you are pirates...
Shut up!
We don't have any business with you anyway!
Listen well, bandits.
I don't mind having drinks and food spilt all over me, nor being spit in the face...
I'll just laugh about it.
However...
Whatever the reason, I won't forgive anyone who hurts my friends!
Shanks!
You won't forgive me?
You pirate scum...
Guys, slaughter them!
I'll do it, I'll be enough.
Don't get too excited, bandit.
If you wanna measure yourself to us, at least bring a battleship.
So strong...
Wait a sec!
This brat started it all!
You've got a bounty after all...
SHIT!
A smokescreen!?
Luffy!
I escaped from right under their noses.
They'd never think a bandit would escape on the sea!
Shit!
Let me go, stupid mountain monkey!
You should just die!
Idiot, you're the one who's going to die.
You pissed me off after all...
Farewell.
Shit, shit!
They're nothing but scum, but I couldn't even lay a hit!
Shit!!
Sorry about that, but you're useless now.
W-What the hell is this!?
Come back!
Someone help me!
Shanks...
Get lost.
Thanks, Luffy.
I heard everything from Makino-san.
You fought for us, right?
Oi, don't cry!
You're a man, right?
But...
Shanks!
Your arm!!
That's a cheap price, it's just an arm.
I'm glad you're safe.
You're leaving, right?
Yeah.
We docked here for a long time, but it's time to say farewell.
You'll miss us, right?
Yeah, I guess I'll miss you.
But I won't ask you to take me with you anymore.
I decided to become one by myself.
A pirate...
I wouldn't have taken you with me anyway!
As if someone like you could become a pirate!
I will!
Someday, I'll gather nakama who won't lose to this crew,
find the greatest treasure in the world,
and I'll definitely become the Pirate King!
Oh? You're going to surpass us?
Then...
I'll entrust this hat to you.
It's my precious hat.
Take good care of it...
It's been ten years since then.
I set out to the sea and became a pirate.
I'll protect my nakama just as Shanks protected me!
Wait for us!
Robin!
D-Don't worry, Luffy-kun!
I-I'm by your side!
Your voice is quite unstable, isn't it?
I-I'm shaking from excitement!
Okay!
Then let's wipe out these World Government jerks already!
And save Robin-kun at all costs!
Next time, One Piece: A Man's Way of Life!
Zoro's Techniques, Usopp's Dream.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!