On the false sketch which we found…
While looking at attentively, one sees signatures.
“Tom”, “Iceberg”, “Cutty Flam”. And at the end, the name of the companie, “Tom' S Workers”.
But I already heard this name some share, “Cutty Flam”.
Cutty Flam, the second apprentice of Tom, is always in life…
Who more is, in this city…
UNDER THE NAME OF “FRANKY”!
Go, passes first! Cut out the door and sinks!
Go ahead!
THAT IS ENOUGH! DO NOT GIVE ME ORDERS!
WHERE IS ROBIN?!
Luffy!
Luffy?!
Robin, I find you finally!
Oi, Luffy! Where had you passed?
Robin, they is good to re-examine you!
Wait! What does it occur?
Let us go, go…
Iceberg-san.
What…
WHAT It IS THAT THIS BROTHEL?!
Paulee! Why didn't you flee?
It is what all that?!
Then… It is them… which wanted to kill you.
WHY ARE YOU EQUIPPED LIKE THAT?!
Oi!
Kalifa, Blueno, Kaku, Lucci, stop your conneries!
Return, Robin!
Confrontation with the CP9!
It is true!
They are the carpenters who accompanied you, not truth?
Now that you say it, I recognize the Nose-Square.
Then the assassins were infiltrated!
Does Ca want to say what?
Paulee, actually, we are spies of the government.
Then, we if we excuse ourselves, isn't this will be forgiven?
After all, we are companions, building boats at your sides.
If you do not manage to believe in it, do you want that I strike Iceberg with the face?
Stop your conneries. You made some enough like that.
The voice of the mask of buffalo resembles much holds.
Species of jerk…
YOU CAN EXPRESS YOURSELF NORMALLY!
Insane steps of me!
Stop, Paulee!
[finger killer]
Doesn't Ca have is enough to you, presently, Paulee?
Oi, encordé!
Why…
You…
No imprudence.
Our techniques exceed the human understanding.
After a long drive, our body became the equivalent of a weapon, the “Rokushiki”.
[Rokushiki = six styles]
That which it control has a superhuman force.
Stop with the casinos.
Imbecile, I had chance today, then it is my round!
Blueno, of beer, more beer!
No problems.
Whore, Kalifa, still equipped like that!
Stop, Paulee. You have only with step to look at it, not?
Why you…?
It is not serious.
We were to kill you in any event.
It is sad, my friend.
Lucci, stops!
You, that stops!
GOMU GOMU NO…
TENKAI!
GAtTLING GUN
What? Ca did anything to him!
Fact of shitting.
SORU!
It disappeared.
SHIGAN!
Luffy!
A normal man would have died with this blow…
Rubber servant boy.
What do you make, Straw hat?
You tried to kill it, not truth?!
Isn't he your companion carpenter?
Previously, yes… But now.
Be to you really a treaty!
But that done anything.
In any event, I promised to him…
That one would burst those which tried to kill Ice-ossan!
Why combine to you with Paulee?
Because me also, I have hope to regulate with you.
Oi, Robin! What you insane with these people?!
If you want from to go away, gives us a good reason!
Yes, they said that they were government!
Then, why?
You are really obstinate.
I bade my farewell with Cook-san and Doctor-san.
They did not say to you?
Of course that if! But I cannot accept that! Why, Robin?
To achieve my goal.
A dream which will never become reality if I remain near you.
To achieve this goal, I would sacrifice anything!
Then it is for that you made show your own companions.
Which is this goal?
You do not need to know it.
You will not be able to reason it.
This woman is…
Sure Es you of what you advance, Nico Robin?
Do you go counts of what you do?
Nobody authorized you to speak!
Quiet remainder!
Iceberg-san!
I will not let anybody bar the road!
Oi, Robin! What you insane?!
Be serious for you?
Robin, what it arrives to you?!
Es you really our enemies, Robin?
Please excuse me, but one stops there.
Now, we must find somebody.
We do not have time.
We have anything any more to make, neither here, nor with you.
Kalifa, how long still?
Two minutes.
You were not warned…
But in two minutes, this fortress will be absorbed by the flames.
What?
To erase all unspecified traces, fire is very effective.
If you do not want to die flarings…
You would make better leave quickly.
But if, of course…
You of it are able.
They want to finish some with us.
Nico Robin is on their side.
Luffy, do you accept the departure of Robin?
OF COURSE THAT NOT!
Do not howl.
Soon, the flames will be spread in several rooms.
But the culprits are the pirates.
Here what it occurred.
Dumb!
You act like cowards while making wear the hat to the others.
Our reputation is tarnished already well enough like that.
Good…
I leave first.
Ah, make as you want, you finished your mission.
Wait, Robin!
I am not agreement!
Good-bye.
Robin!
Do not let it leave! Nico Robin!
Where you go, now that you were found?!
Release from my way!
TENKAI!
Why their body is so hard?
Our over-trained body…
Can harden a such iron carapace.
But to box the blows is not our only strong point.
I YOU AI KNOWN AS TO RELEASE!
KAMIE!
[Kamie = sheet of paper]
In spite of its size, Luffy does not manage to reach it!
It is as nimble as a sheet of paper!
Robin!
Wait!
You…
GOMU GOMU NO…
GUN!
It still disappeared!
Our legs is so fast, it is as if one disappeared.
GENPO!
We can strike the air to float.
It flies! How?!
Moreover…
RANKEN!
A sharp blow?!
You, drop you!
Why?!
Luffy!
They have just split the wall with a kick?
Thanks to our speed, we can create Kamakaze.
[Kamakaze = wind slicing]
It is Rankyaku.
One crossed on the boat, Roronoa.
Then you were not engineer.
Thus boat diagnoses it was false?
Unfortunately, I carried out this diagnostic correctly.
It is well damage!
Luffy.
Remain there, Robin!
The discution is not finished!
If, it is it. We will not be re-examined any more.
Robin!
Luffy, hurries to catch up with Robin!
Are Roronoa, you sure that you look at the good place?
Zoro!
SHIGAN!
We do not need balls to transpierce the human body.
You… Dumb… Release me.
He stopped Luffy so easily.
Go ahead, Nico Robin.
Robin!
Shit.
Luffy!
Zoro.
From where does this force come to them?
Who be you?!
We come all from various places.
Us, the CP9, which were selected to be used the government for the danger of our lives…
We involve ourselves in order to exceed the limits of the human body.
And thus, we acquired the six super-capacities:Rokushiki.
You could return account to you yourself…
Difference in power between you, simple pirates…
And us, to whom was entrusted most important of the missions.
This mission is a business of state.
We will not let to you interfere.
Lucci.
It is time of déclancher the fire. We must hurry.
As long as one is there…
I would like to show you something.
It is…
Lucci, which are you?!
Enormous!