Then, how long that will last?
We can pay as long as you will want. One has full of money.
The wounds of the engagements are too deep.
Does that want to say that repair will take much time?
Not.
To be honest, your boat…
Is not reparable, even by us.
It is not possible…
But until now,
we always could sail without problems!
Even if we repair it best than we can, the chances to reach the next island are of…
Zero.
Merry, you…
Donot can sail really any more?
Kidnapping of pirate.
Last days of the pirate boat.
Good…
Afflicted, Sanji. I was distracted by the books.
You do not have to excuse yourself for that.
I am certain that the person with Robin-chan had an human form.
Then, which was this camouflaged guy?
It is strange also that they disappear also suddenly.
Ouais, the odor of Robin also evaporated.
I hope that nothing low register did not arrive,
But I feel badly at ease.
Hein? You require that I examine you?
I AM NOT SICK!
The words of Ao Kiji trottent me in the head.
He said what?
He spoke about a serious event in the past of Robin-chan.
And it added that we will regret it one day.
Now that you say it…
Could there be a relationship with the disappearance of Robin?
I know anything of it.
In any case, that is not used for nothing to remain the arms crosseds here.
Let us turn over to Merry for the moment.
If all is well, perhaps it will return.
It is true.
More quickly, please.
Merry is foutu?!
Why?!
Do not be you not the best naval engineers?!
Look at, money, one has some more than enough!
The money does not have importance.
It does not matter what you will pay,
This boat cannot return in its country of origin.
I wonder besides how you could make all this way,
With a boat in this state.
What that wants to say?!
It is what the problem with Merry?!
Do you know the role of the “skittle”, dépravée?
Déprav…
The trick at the bottom of the hold?
Yes.
It is the most important element, which leaves the prow to the poop of the boat.
The construction of a boat starts from there.
Then the prow, the poop, the frames comes…
Frames, the stem then the bridge.
All the parts are thoroughly adjusted between them, with the skittle like reference.
It is the showpiece of the boat.
The life of a boat depends on the skittle.
When it is damaged, one cannot replace it.
It would be like building a boat starting from a wreck.
This is why…
Nobody can repair it.
Your boat saw its last days.
He, did not say a similar thing!
It is however the truth.
Then manufacture a new boat!
Build another Going Merry!
It is also impossible.
Why?!
We could manufacture a similar boat, but…
Strictly to speak, nobody can duplicate a boat.
Everywhere in the world, you will never find two boats identical.
What does that want to say?
Did you already see two identical trees?
Most of the time, a ship is built containing boards.
The size and the shape of the boat are then determined by the type of wood used.
This is why we cannot build a boat with identical with the same sketches.
If we manufacture a boat like that one…
That which will realize that it is not exactly the same one…
Will be doubtless, you!
Impossible…
Then we cannot sail really any more with Going Merry?
It is true… Either you wait until it runs, or…
You disassemble it immediately.
A caravel!
What a splendid boat!
Yosh, they is good!
Maintaining the boat pirate, Going Merry, is ready!
Nmaaa… The life of this boat touches at its end.
Isn't this the occasion?
Give up it and buy a new boat.
You have money.
I intended to say that it was a caravel.
To sail with an old boat like this one, would become too difficult.
Not, we do not intend to change.
Luffy.
It is our…
It is our boat, Going Merry!
If we repair it, it will still sail!
They is good! Still today, we sailed without problem!
And of a blow, to say that we cannot sail any more…
I cannot believe in it!
You said that because you do not know with what a not this boat is robust!
Do you intend to sail until his shipwreck?
Ca surprises me…
However, you are the captain of this boat?!
This conversation is finished until new order.
Reflect there and return when you decide to buy a boat.
I will help you.
If you can pay 300 million, we will be able to build our new model of boat.
Kalifa.
Yes…
Throw an eye on top…
It is a catalog of all our range.
The standard prices are listed there.
Iceberg-san.
We have customers at the entry.
There is however no go envisaged.
It would seem that they are still representatives of the government.
Do I have to say to them to leave?
Nmaaa, ouais.
Say their that I am not there.
Another thing still…
Your hair draws up straight to the alarm clock, Lulu.
Oops, that fears.
Afflicted.
Thus I will say to them to leave.
Go ahead.
Wait a little, Iceberg-kun.
Then you are there.
Oi, you, hide you!
They are representatives of the government!
Nmaa, Re-hello, Kogi…
I am absent today.
Yes, you are it!
Good, I made all this way up to now by Umi Ressha.
I do not want to be of bad mood.
I do not know why, but that feels the pirate here.
Ca does not do anything.
In any event, I came to speak to you.
You me drunk! You break!
Be to you a kid?
I am incontestably an adult.
Would not be so obstinate.
Today, we have something of special to ask you. I will like that you listenings.
Come, will discuss into private.
They will thus stop never.
What do they want to him with Iceberg-san?
Ca does not concern us.
Surely a political matter.
Would I owe them botter the bottom?
Drop, they belong to the international government.
What?
What is there?
I noticed a trick when one hid with the bags.
They are light.
Why?
Oh, stops your conneries.
They cannot be light inside with as much money.
It is what these cries?
Baka, why you ridges as much of noise?!
Oi, young girl, while sitting you like that, one will see…
It is…
Impossible…
Ca may not be…
200 MILLION BERRYS!
FLOWN AWAY! THEY SE ARE FLOWN AWAY!
While looking at more closely, they are not our bags!
Oi, you ridges far too much noise. What does it occur?
The money disappeared.
More no trace.
What?
Paulee, it is still you?!
It is not me!
Really?!
How if I were a liar, whore!
Be really sure for you of you?!
Which din.
I am really, really sure!
By the way, Kaku, were you with Franky Family?
Really, really, really?!
Hey, await… ouch!
It is the plain truth, it is not me!
What do you tell?
I did not see Franky Family.
Odd,
I was however sure to have seen your long nose.
Wait a little!
It is Usopp!
It with Franky Family was?!
Either it accompanied them,
either it was made trimbaler.
It is a kidnapping!
Luffy, we must quickly find it!
Included/understood!
He, wait!
Where you will seek, Luffy?!
Await me, Usopp, the money!
Is He, where the cushy job of Franky Family?
It is more one building site which a cushy job.
Of where you accosted on the rock coast, it is the house in the North-East called…
Franky House.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Luffy!
Good, it will never find anybody all alone!
I do not have time to seek Luffy.
I must initially bring back the money to the boat.
If I make them understand that they have only 200 million and that I have 100 million with me…
They will leave to my research.
Please, Yagara-chan! The shortest way towards the store of hiring of bulldozer!
I take Zoro and the others with the passage and I will tell them.
Franky Family, you should never have flown of the pirates!
First level, here the street of the market!
Advance prudently!
I count on you, Yagara-chan!
It is what that?
Look at where you go, Born-chan!
Afflicted!
I hope that Usopp succeeded in escaping.
Ca fears.
From which does this type come?
Oi, somebody knows this guy?!
There are many people.
Yagara-chan, stops one moment!
Usopp!
Usopp, hold good!
He, you are well?!
He! He!
Usopp! Usopp!
Oi, are you pirates?
The farm! There remain not planted!
Was Usopp, it Franky Family?
It was them?!
Yes… Because I am too weak…
They took…
All money.
Nami…
How will I… tell that with the others, now?
Just at the moment when… we could finally repair Merry…
I have shame so much…
Putaiiin…
Usopp.
I include/understand. It is not serious for the money.
We will recover it, all together.
It is dirtily reached.
I will make better not move it.
Usopp, remains there for the moment.
I turn over quickly to the boat to call of the assistance.
I will also ask Chopper to look after you.
Do not make any you for the money.
It appears that they hide in the surroundings.
One will deal with them and will put an end to all that!
He, it is not a spectacle!
Usopp, continues to lie here, ok?!
I return as fast as possible!
More quickly, Yagara-chan!
It is insane this bulldozer!
He!
Just at the moment when we could finally repair Merry…
It does not matter what you will pay, this boat cannot return in its country of origin.
Either we decide to buy a new boat…
Either we repair and improve ourself Merry…
If we do not put the totality of the 300 million in the boat…
To sail possible further will be certainly difficult.
We need really this money!
We must find it!
It is true?
It is what the naval engineer said.
This boat…
Is not reparable?
Even if we have money?
But then… What will it arrive at Merry?
Who knows… All will depend how Luffy and the others will react by learning that.
These three there will find surely a solution with the shipyard.
But it is so cruel!
Look at, the boat seems in good state…
And it made us travel of East Blue up to now!
It is for that…
That the men become stronger when they face the difficulties.
But the ships are different.
Their wounds accumulate.
I do not include/understand anything.
How will react Usopp by learning that?
I like Merry!
Like everyone. But the wounds are too deep, it does not have nothing there to make.
I worry for Merry and Robin-chan.
Ca returns nutcase to me.
Everyone!
He, Nami returns!
It seems to be alone.
Where are Luffy and Usopp?
Nami-saan, it occurred something?!
200 million?!
Yes, 200 million!
What do you think about it, Aniki?
Enormous! It is brilliant the guy!
Now that we have as much money…
We will be able to offer what we wish more than all!
Indeed, Aniki.
Our honesty towards you since three years.
We dream some since so many years.
That made so a long time…
If there were a little money, one could bet in the races of Yagara.
And ever mown!
If one reported a setting at price, one could drink and have fun the festival…
We finally collected the 200 million Berrys necessary. So difficult to recover!
Indeed! You made crowned good job!
Then now…
It is not large thing, but here 5 million Berrys, to show you my gratitude.
Drink and eat at will!
It is well our Aniki!
Banzai!
C-C' is what?!
Whore!
Who dares to rub in Franky Family?!
It is this poor guy which one crossed.
What, do you hold still upright?
Return to me the money!
“To me the money”, say you Return?
Does that want to say that you are a man of the Straw hat?
It is him, Aniki!
I wanted to know if a man of Luffy to the Straw hat were so strong that!
But it is only one weakling!
Ca does not concern you!
What it fout?!
I appreciate your courage to want to bring back only the money…
But I cannot you leave it.
Return it to me.
It is…
The money which we go…
to use for…
to repair our boat.
With this money…
We will be able to finally look after the wounds of Merry!
I will not leave it to you!