You left the crew of the Straw hat,
but you did not give up for as much piracy.
Since you are a pirate, one will have to take you along with us.
MERRY!!!
I will say to you what I know.
You do not know the sorrows that I endured
in my life because of the world government!
Then why you help this government,
if you hate it as much as that?!
Because I wish to protect something at all costs.
They gave again me taste with the life,
saved my heart and the dreams which I had lost.
I was made friends who believe in me.
But then n the other hand…
I could authorize the 6 members of the crew of
Luffy me excluded to leave this island alive!
And for that, you are ready to awake the old ones
weapons with the risk to destroy the world?!
Completely.
In spite of all the human lives of this world…
it is you six whom it chose.
All that for us…
Chopper! Upright!
One will seek the others!
Chopper! Hey! Upright! Chopper!
Oï, oï, it is seriously wounded!
Well, the CP9 soon will arrive.
Nico Robin…
go up in first in Umi Ressha.
There do not remain not planted!
The guy, dispatch you to take it along!
Yes!
Hauts fonctionnaires of the government,
Navy and Robin-chan.
Now, how will I have to act?
I carry a darkness in me that none you knows.
It would be said that it is made remove…
But with this kind of the types, if she wanted it
she could easily escape to them.
She has something at the head…
or there is a reason which prevents it from fleeing.
Afflicted to have made you wait, Robin-chan!
I awaited you, my Prince!
Or after all, it does all that
in the hope which I come to save it!
kougi-san!
Here is the CP9.
How?
Whoa, it is Rob Lucci-san!
Which power.
It is thus that the CP9.
You do not want to include/understand?! Release me, whore!
Where you take me along?!
I will never forgive it to you!
You do not lose anything to wait!
Hey! I have an army of 8000 Ho…
Usopp?
THE WHISTLE SEPARATES THE GROUP!
UMI RESSHA LEAVES
Where you take me along, band of dumbs?!
I will never forgive it to you!
You do not lose anything to wait!
I have an army of 8000 Ho…
Usopp?
Thank you very much for your efforts during the mission!
Lucci-san, your coat.
They exaggerate
Put an end to all that.
O-Oui, immediately.
It is not a play!
Be vigilant!
Get all into the train!
Everyone on train!
You for the departure prepare towards Enies Lobby!
I said to you to release me…
But which is with the Juste?
However…
he had said “Afflicted, I caused you only troubles”…
Even left the crew, it continues with us emmerder.
A little on the right!
Sprinkle this part well!
One needs more water!
Still a little.
It is regulated on this side!
You occupy casualties!
Yosh, included/understood!
There is still somebody inside?
Pay attention where you steps!
Then Robin does not hate us?!
Ouais!
It is brilliant!
It was transformed into raccoon!
An raccoon…
Oï, it became an raccoon…
Chopper, it is necessary that one finds Luffy
and the others and which one seeks Robin!
It is included/understood, one will seek them.
Where are they?
It is for that one must go to their research.
Yosh!
I will do my better!
It became a gorilla!
Wait…
I card-index myself that you seek Nico Robin…
but this night with 23:00, Umi Ressha
will leave with people the government.
Nmaa~ and thus…
there are strong chances that they are on board.
What wants to say that Nico Robin will be there too.
It will be the last departure of
Umi Ressha before one good moment…
because of the imminent arrival of Aqua Laguna.
That would like to say…
If you loupez this train, you will be retained here…
since you cannot take boat of course.
Not that! It is terrible! What a hour is it?!
22:30.
What?! There remains to us nothing any more but half an hour!
Can't Hey, you do something?
Please, delay the departure of Umi Ressha!
Nmaa~ the destination is Enies Lobby…
It is a place which only members
government can reach.
Even technicians of the train
belong to the government.
They will not listen to me.
Not that!
It is necessary that I go to the station in a manner
or of another, and to convince Robin to remain.
Chopper!
I will indicate to you towards which direction Luffy and Zoro
fell, so that you can find them.
If you find them, say to them
to return immediately to the station!
Well, I included/understood!
Oï, the guy!
Paulee-san, nothing of broken?!
Give a knack to these deux-là!
Their to give a knack?!
But Paulee-san, it is not them
who tried to kill Iceberg-san?!
They would have rather to be stopped at once!
Lucci-san and Kaku-san are always carried disp…
The assassins are not the members
of the crew of the Straw hat!
They are innocent!
They were made have by truths assassins
and showed we them wrongly!
I do not know which they is, but the crew of
Straw hat fought against these masked types!
If me and Iceberg-san naps still in life…
it is thanks to them.
It is not the sorrow to seek Lucci and Kaku.
They any more will not be re-examined.
What?
You know what became Lucci-san and the others?!
They returned on their premises.
You pleasant?! Why they would go
on their premises in a similar moment?!
Close it and seeks the team-members of the Straw hat!
Hey, the streetwalker!
Do not call me like that!
You want to go to the station, not? I will take you along there.
Euh… Thank you.
Paulee-san, hey…
You are serious?
STOP FEELING SORRY FOR YOU AND
SHOWN GOOD SENSE!
YOU WISH TO DISHONOR THE GALLEY IT?!
Yes, owner!
Forgiveness!
We are sorry!
One will give you a knack,
say to us what it is necessary to do!
Leave will yagaras them!
Open the cages!
“Returned on their premises”, hein?
It is preferable not to say too much of it.
It is already sufficient which this frustration
that is to say felt by us two.
Chopper, I count on you!
Ouais! I hope well to return with them.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
MUGIWARA-TEAM
Oï!!
The guy!!
Oï! Luffy!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Usopp, please, return…
Everyone with me!
Well, it is included/understood! The guy, you heard?!
Oï, Luffy!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Usopp, please return…
Turn by here!
It is a short cut for the station!
There remain to us nothing any more but 20 minutes before the departure.
Does not leave, Robin.
It Will not be forgiven if you endure that without us!
Yagara-shan, please!
More quickly!
The last train of 23:00.
At the beginning of the station Blue Station of
Seven toilets in direction of Enies Lobby.
Remain quiet.
Bandage dumbs!
Treat us with more precaution! BA-KA!
Ouais, ouais! BA-KA!
Small shits of the government!
Euh… not, it is a little…
Because of an abrupt rise of water,
the schedules changed. The departure is imminent.
Shit, it leaves already.
Our mission touches at its end.
Would not be also optimistic, us
sums not arrived yet.
Idiot.
Afflicted.
If you miss this train, you will not have any more
no chance to leave this island in time.
Please, it is necessary that one arrives in time!
Franky…
Dumb… How are you?
Straw hat!
Roronoa!
Luffy!
Where are you?
Hey, where are you?
Make signs to us!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Usopp, please return…
Luffy!
Robin will be made remove!
Please, answer!
Where be you?!
What makes Luffy and the others?
None of them will be there in time.
I repeat…
The last train is leaving soon.
Chuuuchain!
“Whore!”
Cheee them…
“I them…”
will chaaardonnerai chaaamais!
“will never forgive!”
Ch' uis coinché.
Pitches, I lost balance.
Shit!
I am wedged…
Luffy!
Zoro!
Sanji!
You show!
One must save Robin!
Roronoa!
Where can they be well?!
That gives what by here?!
Straw hat!
Zoro!
They are surely not here…
Perhaps what are they in the low city?
If it is the case, they had to be
carried by the shrinking of water.
Moreover, they is well too dangerous to go over there.
Fact of shitting!
Straw hat!
Roronoa!
Lucci-san!
The waves are increasingly large,
we thus will have to leave a little earlier than envisaged.
That poses it pro…
Not, let us leave.
Yes, very well.
We lived here during 5 years…
but I however do not regret any to leave this place.
He, you did not hear like
a whistle of train?!
Ouais, but it is odd…
It is not yet the hour of the departure!
But they do not transport
passengers, this time.
It is possible that they have advanced
the departure because of the weather.
We dispatch! The station is just opposite!
Stop, Umi Ressha!
The last voyage day of Umi Ressha,
in departure of Seven Toilets towards Enies Lobby.
We leave. You sit.
It is the departure.
I do not have any more any reason to live.
Leave me.
And then initially, why should I obey you?
You forced me to live, me which wished only to die.
It is of your fault.
I do not have nowhere where to go nor where to return.
Then lets remain to me on your boat.
Mellorin~! Mello~! Mellorin~!
Oh, I see. Then I do not have the choice. They is good, remains.
LUFFY!!
Of made you not.
It is not a bad person.
It is impossible, Rio Ponéglyphe is…
Therefore, Ponéglyphes which I study since all
this time is guiding me…
with more far from Large Line, Rough tel.
Robin!
How do you feel you?
He starts to move…
Whores of dumbs of the government…
We are there! Thank you very much, Yagara-chan!
Take the staircases of the central entry!
Yes!
Robin!
Do not leave!
Hey, which are you?!
Move back, they are dangerous!
Robin, get out of the train!
We will fight against no matter whom!
Luffy!
Zoro!
Where are you?
I am not able to leave me…
Wait!
Stop this train!
ROBIN!!!