Among all the human lives of this world…
It is you six whom eille chose.
Robin, get out of the train!
One will fight against no matter whom!
Wait!
ROBIN!!!
One did not arrive in time…
SANJI ENTERS BY EFFRACTION!
The STORMY BATTAILLE OF UMI RESSHA!
Whore, but what it wanted this type?
It does not matter its intentions, after all
it is a train reserved for the government.
If it is made take, it will be cooked.
Hein? It is the type of Galley it…
Paul…
Reflected before acting.
It would seem that they are separating.
The station is a place where meetings
and separations are currency.
And it is our duty, with us the controllers,
to watch for all that discreetly.
Yes, it is true.
Discreetly.
It left bloody in advance.
Roasted!
Ah yes!
All the passengers were already on board…
And the sea was very agitated…
This is why they thought that
Aqua Laguna was going to arrive earlier than envisaged,
and they thus have advanced the hour of the departure.
They is dangerous to remain here.
It would be preferable to join
shelters of the high city.
That is also worth for this lady.
Ah yes.
Hey, you.
One cannot stop a train which already left.
It is difficult to say…
but Enies Lobby…
She cries?
Hum, good…
I include/understand your feelings…
ONE GOES HAS THEIR CONTINUATION!!!
IT WAS FURIOUS!
I will not forgive them with
this puffiness of the government!
Hey, lends to me a boat!
What takes to you suddenly?
Large and solid!
You intend to take the sea by a similar time?
Do not say anything, you do not have any
idea of the power of Aqua Laguna!
It will be crossed!
The force of this tide is incomparable
with those which you have the practice to see.
The state of the sea will do nothing but worsen!
You cannot leave any more at sea, now!
It would be suicide!
But Robin gave up his own life for us…
One was hot…
Thank you…
Paulee-san, thank you infinitely!
One failed to be made carry by the sea…
Look at, even the large table of information which
was anchored on the ground was made carry by the waves.
That had never arrived before.
What a force!
And that does nothing but start…
The speed of the waves of this Aqua Laguna…
is abnormal!
Hey, is there a risk for Umi Ressha
in which Robin is?
Umi Ressha will leave the zone
storm before the large wave does not arrive.
Besides this one, it will be able all them
to pass if he does not face them face.
Is Hey, your name, it well Nami, not?
Yes?
There was this letter for you in the station.
It is a companion with you, not?
A letter on behalf of which?
How did you make to find a so small letter?
Here! It was deposited here!
“Nami-Saaaan, Lily this…”
The other cretin…
What did it mark there above?
Wait a little.
All the beginning, it is a love letter without hope.
A love letter?
It is this third man who would have made him advances?
Not, to judge some by the state of the things, that must be…
You want my photograph?
The true letter starts here.
“Post Scriptum,”
“I checked that Robin-chan was well has edge of
Umi Ressha of 23:00, therefore I am assembled there me too. “
What?
Is Sanji-kun on train which has just left?
And Usopp too?
And there is also “a hooligan with funny of hairstyle”.
That perhaps only Franky.
Yes, it is sure.
A fourth lover.
And thus the fifth lover it is Franky…
I have sorrow for Paulee-san.
It would make well give up.
It is what your problem?!
Ah, there was also this with the letter.
there should be Den-Den Mushi in il' Umi Ressha.
I will contact you earliest possibile.
Please, guard this baby
Den-Den Mushi close to your body.
Yes, imagines that this baby Den-Den Mushi,
it is me, which dedicates you a love without…
I see, it will contact us with that.
It would thus have envisaged the intrigues of Nico Robin?
Impressing.
Therefore, Robin has Sanji-kun near it.
It is sure, we will go in Enies Lobby.
Whore…
I cannot even smoke here.
I see.
Thus had Sanji gone to the station?
Yes.
Usopp is him also in this train.
Such an amount of better.
But before continuing Umi Ressha,
it is necessary at all costs to find Luffy and Zoro.
Yosh, it is included/understood.
I am sure that they flew away on this side,
then will seek them over there.
You also the guy!
With the job, the guy! Let us do our better!
Count on us!
Now, how I am
to make to infiltrate me in it?
The storm makes rage, outside.
COLLAR SHOT!
Be to you which, you?!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
MUGIWARA-TEAM
Stop!
Where you believe outward journey like that?
Do not move!
I observed his kick.
It is not an ordinary type!
When…
you say that opposite me…
that pleases to me.
It WAS NOT a COMPLIMENT!
It fout of our mouth…
He, warn Lucci-san, there is an intruder on board!
Wait!
It is not worthwhile to go to disturb the CP9 for that.
It does not matter the force of this intruder,
there is no reason to be afraid, since…
in this coach…
It is smoked out by here!
I am there!
Jerry-san!
I am originating in an island in
South Blue considered for its karate.
Yes, I am a champion of boxing!
Show us your karate.
You will regret this arrogance
when you taste with my punch.
Do not use such an attack here!
Jerry-san, your adversary is behind you…
Hum? He fled.
Snotty-nosed kid! Do not think that I am handicapped
in a reduced space, because of my big size.
It is the first time that a guy
with the head in the bottom threatens me.
My style of boxing is more
effective in the narrow places.
It is YOGA STYLE!
YOGA ONE TWO…
ONE TWO…
You ace right tiny room your lengthening-piece!
It is what you believe…
SCREW…
DROP KICK!
Do you know at least the rules of boxing?!
Which waste of time.
SKEWER!
First of all in the last of the 7 coaches…
we have the personnel of the government.
Then, in the 5th coach, we have 40 powerful
soldiers of the marine. At their head is…
a Captain of the HQ of the Navy…
and former Royal Knight, T-Bone.
Then the 4th Coach comes…
where that is which is at the same time
the cook of this forwarding…
and specialist in martial arts in Cipher pol. 7, Wanze.
And in the 3rd Coach…
the novel member of the CP9…
Nero, which is in alarm.
Hum, it has no risk of attack there on this convoy…
but if, we have enough
men ready to fight effectively.
Straw hat!
Roronoa!
We are allied!
You show!
Straw hat, where you are?!
Foreman, that must be
painful D, E to move in your state.
Take a little rest.
Imbecile, it is nothing.
Hurry to find the two others.
Of agreement!
Was iceberg-san informed of the situation?
They went to submit a report/ratio to him.
Where do you go, Mister?
Iceberg-san?
Roronoa!
Straw hat!
Answer if you hear us!
Luffy!
Zoro! Where you are?!
You said food well?
Yes, of the meat will make the deal, much meat!
Bring back all that here! Quickly!
Why one should work for it?!
Not, it is not for it.
Let us do our better for Paulee-san,
this girl has just plated it.
It is true!
She must surely be very hungry.
She is in full growth.
It is sure!
Here also… As I suspected it, it there
more only one shop opened has now.
I see! Ca would say to you to go to make
a turn in the kitchen of the station?
It is impossible! It is
under water, in the low city.
And well there are not the choice, one must
to find a means of going there!
Yes, but…
Allons-y! You think that it us it
will forgive if one returns the empty handeds?!
It rains?
They is not good.
My sense of smell is ineffective with this time.
Hey, that made one moment that they are called,
but there is no answer. That would like it to say…
Would not be stupid, do what you have to do!
Or are you, Luffy?
Zoro, you cannot be beaten
by isn't a man leopard?
One knows finally why Robin left us!
Where you are, Straw hat?!
Please, answer!
Await to us Robin.
One has to come to save you with Luffy and the others!
Oï, what occurs?!
Ah, Paulee-san, look at!
More the sea is withdrawn and…
more extremely will be the return of the waves.
One can predict the power of one
vagueness only by observing its backward flow.
I fly!
And if one evaluates the fall of the level of water this year…
Look at, Chimney.
Wow, brilliant!
It is as if the sea had been just drained…
I never saw anything of such before.
How it is possible that it
does level of water go down so low?
It is well the first time that I see that.
Which will be the power of this wave?
The low city will be completely absorbed.
Let us hope that there is nobody any more in the low city!
They would die on the blow…
Noise of the sea…
What is it?
Olalalalalalala!
Grandmother, looks at, looks at!
Y' has a trick there!
Ah yes?
There is something between these two houses!
Hey, look at-look at-looks at!
Kokoro-san!
Oya, you are the pirate girl.
Ah, the pirate big sister!
Hey, looks by here! Y' has a trick there!
A trick?
About what you do speak, Chimney?
Waits!
Why all is drained?!
Wouldn't this be Straw hat?
Your Lord of the Pirates?
What?
This imbecile.
He, you? Where you like that run?!
Does not go in the low city!
The low city?
Hey, that somebody stops this girl!
You want to die?!
Aqua Laguna arrives!
Return!