One Piece Treasure Sweepstakes!
The first letter is...
The way to win will be
explained at the end of the show!
Luffy and the others
arrived at Enies Lobby.
We have from the Main Gate
to the Gate of Justice,
to get Nico Robin and
Franky back, or we lose.
Why's that? Wherever Robin is taken away, we
just have to follow after her until we succeed!
I told you before we
left Water 7, didn't I?
If we pass that gate, our destination will either be
the Marines' Headquarters or the Great Submarine Prison!
No matter what, we must
settle things before that.
That's how it is.
But still, even if we
all get on the island,
the ones who really stand a chance
to win against the CP9 are...
Just you guys!
I came to understand your strength
while travelling on this train with you.
That's why you should wait here for five minutes and
then bash into the Main Island with the Rocketman!
We'll go fight first and open a passage so that the train
can pass between the Main Gate and the Main Island Gate.
After that, we want you to go
on, no matter how many of us fall.
We only have around sixty members, but the other side
should have around two or three thousand soldiers.
You Straw Hats should try to avoid unnecessary
battles and concentrate on just following the CP9.
Yeah, I got it!
Hey guys, this is the
front of the island!
Look well at the sky behind Enies Lobby.
That is the Gate of Justice!
SO HUGE!!
Saa! There is no time to hesitate!
Then we'll infiltrate the
island according to the plan!
Let us cover you!
Oi!! Aren't those two with us?
Luffy burning with desire
to get Robin back...
Hey, where's Luffy?
Eh? He was here until just now...
Hey, it's Straw Hat-san!
What the hell is he
doing all by himself!?
That guy doesn't
understand the plan at all!
It didn't serve any purpose...
He said he understood, right?
Waiting five minutes
is impossible for him.
I guess so.
...sneaked in to Enies Lobby alone.
On the other side, Chief
Spandam is leading the CP9...
And then...
This is the wonderful day when the eight
members of the CP9, including myself,
will finally be
gathered together, but...
What's the meaning of this article!?
In our new plan to assassinate
the leader of the revolution,
the orders were to take out three people
and your mission would have been over...
But you just had to kill
twenty three people, right!?
If you have excuses, try them!
Yoyoi!!
I make all my apologies, chief!
In the commanding center of Enies
Lobby, the Judiciary Tower...
Everything is my...
Spandam was awaiting the arrival of Lucci and
the others, with the rest of the CP9 members.
Responsibility!
Stop that, Kumadori!
A man shouldn't lower
his head so easily!
I'll explain everything
to the chief, so sit down!
I can't die!
Hurry up and commit
suicide! You bastard!
We'll be in trouble if he dies, chapapa!
It's okay, I understood!
Forget it, guys...
Acha!! I spilt my coffee! Shit!!
And I heard Nero wasn't of any use!
Mah, it's okay...
What's up with this place?
There's such a huge hole! It
looks like the island is floating!
There's a town, too. Robin...
I wonder if she's in there.
There's someone up there!
Shoot him down immediately!
Ah, I've been spotted!
He passed the gate!
And Luffy, who already
passed the Main Gate...
This is the Main Gate!
This is a message for the chief
officer on the Main Island!
What do you want? What's happening?
There's an intruder who passed the Main
Gate and is heading towards the Main Island!
What? Surely you can at least
take care of just one intruder.
But, that...!
This is the Main Island Gate!
We confirm the presence of an intruder.
...continues rushing the same way,
heading to the Main Island Gate.
Hey there little guy, stop running.
Don't you know where you are?
Please be careful when dealing with him!
If my eyes serve me
right, this man could be...
Straw Hat Luffy!
What!? What did you just say!?
I think he's the man
with a 100 million bounty!
The Straw Hat pirate!!
Robin...
Where is Robin!?
This is an extremely urgent
report from the Main Gate!
What is it this time!?
A group of intruders passed the
front barrier riding monsters!
We need reinforcements!
Reinforcements...
Don't waste a moment, let's go!
What's up!? Gatekeepers, answer!
What's happening!?
What is it, Nico Robin?
Don't stop.
Guys, are you prepared?
What about your wounds?
I'm okay. It's because...
I'm Sogekiiing
-!
Seatrain Rocketman!
Only four minutes left and...
We'll assault them!
I'm really sorry, but...
Could you let me pass, please?
Even if you ask politely...
When I say no, I mean...
No!!
Understood!
Then...
Get ready!
Damn you pirate!
Oh, that's dirty!
He got his arms!
Such a childish trick!
Don't falter!
Ah! Sorry!
Ah!! I'm so sorry! Sempai!
Stop fooling around!
Your back is completely open!
That guy...
Stop him!
It's only one mere human!
What's this? His body seems so light!
I'll hurry in first.
Let's meet again!
See ya!
Wait!
He went inside! Hurry up and follow him!
He entered the Main Island!
Contact the chief!
Message from the Main
Island Gate to the chief!
Straw Hat Luffy
intruded the Main Island!
What!? You let an intruder
enter the Main Island?
What the hell is happening!?
What about Oimo and Kaashii?
Did those two get beaten too?
No, it should be night
time in their country, so...
They must be asleep...
Is this the time to sleep!?
Smack them awake now!
Do the same to the soldiers
sleeping on the Main Island!
Yes!
Is it alright for you to scream this
much for a mere intruder, director?
We are here...
Don't be stupid!
As the entrance of the World Government,
the Judiciary Island wears its sacred crest!
Any idiot is supposed to at least understand
what it means to invade this place!
That guy went all the way to the Main
Island just to get one nakama back!
Acha!
Acha! Looking down on us!
The Straw Hat crew and
their damn subordinates...
Gatekeepers! Tell me about
the situation at the Main Gate!
Oi, gatekeepers!
How many enemies are there!?
Where are they now!?
Answer, Main Gate!
Oi, what's wrong!?
Eheh! As if I'd waste bullets for this!
Try entering this door! Open the gates!
Don't let them open it!
You're in the way!
Mozu, go left!
Understood!
I won't let you pass!
A hair came from my nose!
You shouldn't get distracted!
Hurry up!
I owe you one!
Not done yet!?
Mozu! Kiwi!
This keyhole won't last long against
a member of the Franky Family!
It's done!
Here too!
Yosh! It's time to open the gates!
Kairiki Destroyers!
Don't let them through! Shit!
Scram! You're in the way!
Let's break through!
We breached the first
one, the Main Gate!
Oooh! What's this hole!?
We don't have time, don't look down!
Move forward!
Continue running to the Main Island!
It's a waterfall!
Yatta!
Hey guys, this way!
Hurry up and lend a hand!
Kaashii-san!
Oimo-san!
Please wake up quickly!
The Main Gate was
opened by the intruders!
He said that the Main Gate was opened...
Oimo.
We can't just let that go.
Kaashii...
It's hard since we just woke up...
We have work to do. Let's go...
Here!
I still haven't gotten enough sleep...
Let's take care of them
quickly and get back to sleep.
Oimo!
G-Gi-Giants!
I don't know what you
guys came here for...
But you should go back home
before you get squashed!
Right, Oimo?
Yeah, Kaashii. I think so too.
Let's squash their bones flat...
Having giants as
gatekeepers... That's not fair!
So big! The Kairiki Destroyers
look tiny in front of them!
Saa, go home!
I won't let you pass through this gate.
Oimo!
They're coming!
No matter who the enemy
is, we musn't falter!
Franky Family!
If it's for aniki!
Oi, you understand that?
Yeah...
Yosh!
Only us three can do it!
Even those giants can't resist the superhuman
strength we got from dismantling ships!
Destroyers!
The three Kairiki Destroyers were...!
They got done in an instant!
We were born fighters!
Compared with tiny humans slightly larger than normal,
the blood that flows through our veins is way different.
I won't let any of you pass through!
Oimo!
Don't be afraid! Don't
let your morale decrease!
That's right! Our aniki
Franky is behind those doors!
Fight so we won't put shame
over aniki's name! Franky Family!
Two minutes left, huh?
Oi! Straw Hat Luffy!
How many nakama did you bring with you?
Enies Lobby has over
ten thousand soldiers!
Yeah. I'm alone.
Open the way!
I won't let even one
of you pass this gate!
Let's follow Straw Hat-san!!
Next time, One Piece: Battle with
the Giants! Open the Second Door!
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Here's how you can get your present!
Write the four letters that appeared in the
show, your address, your full name, your age,
your opinion of the show and
you may win a lot of prizes!
The last keyword is... this!