Wealth, Fame, Power.
The man who had acquired everything in this
world, the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The final words that were said at his execution sent people to the seas.
My wealth and treasures?
If you want it, I'll let you have it.
Look for it, I left it all in that place.
Men now, chasing their dreams, head towards the Grand Line.
The world enters the Great Age of Pirates!
Those are...
You couldn't possibly...
The blueprints of the ancient weapon, Pluton.
It's the real thing.
Do you believe me?
Hey, Spanda.
What Tom-san and Iceburg tried to protect with their lives is...
Hurry up and give it to me!
If the ancient weapon were to fall into the hands of an idiot like you and let loose,
then a weapon would be needed to be built in order to resist that.
To contain a reckless outbreak is this designer's wish.
It's true...
If you use Nico Robin, then you could revive the ancient weapon.
Even if it's not her intention,
as long as there's a chance that she could be used to do so, then she's a dangerous woman.
But for her, she has nakama that don't hesitate when looking into the face of death.
That's why I'm...
...gonna make a bet.
What are you doing?!
It's burnt to a crisp!
Now, there's no power to resist the ancient weapon.
If Nico Robin is to be taken by you now, the world will end.
But if the Straw Hats win...
What you'll have left, is absolutely nothing at all.
Personally, I'm betting on their victory.
Cutty Flam.
How dare you...
...to my blueprints?
ANIKI!!
ANIKI'S FALLING INTO THE WATERFALL~!!
FRANKY!!
Oi, you pirates!
Jump into the waterfall with all you've got!
Rocketman?!
IT FLEW!!
Seems like the old times, Tom-san!
I did indeed help a man named Roger...
AND I'M MIGHTY PROUD OF IT!!
I'm Luffy.
I'm the man who's gonna be the Pirate King.
Really?
Yeah.
That guy Roger was also...
He was an idiot too, wasn't he?
And you helped him out, didn't you?
Outrageously,
the entire Tom's Workers' family are helping the Straw Hat now.
You would've done the same, wouldn't you?
Tom-san?
WE'RE GONNA HIT IT!!
WE'RE GONNA CRASH!!
Capture The 5 Keys! The Straw Hats Verses CP9
They came...
Yoyoi!
THEY CAME!!
DAMN IT!!
Come on, you!
If only I could unlock these Sea Stone handcuffs.
Now, I'm setting you guys loose!
CP9!
Pulverize them on this Tower of Justice!
I give you permission to butcher them!
Lucci!
You come with me!
Besides everything else, you need to protect me first!
You got that?!
FUNKFREED!!
That's a good boy!
A Devil's Fruit?
An elephant with a sword's ability?
Nope, exactly the opposite.
It's a sword that swallowed the elephant fruit.
Therefore, it's an Elephant Sword!
Along with the CP9, I have this especially reserved sword.
If I think about it calmly, I have nothing to fear.
Now, let's head to the Gates of Justice.
If you think you can take this woman back, then just try it, Straw Hat!
Franky aniki is okay!
The Straw Hat-san's have finally reached the Tower of Justice!
Aniki's no longer captured!
Looks like he's joining the battle!
That's right, that's the kind of guy he is!
Go get 'em!
Aniki!!
Straw Hat, do your best!!
We'll leave it up to you now, Straw Hat.
Oi, are you okay?
Old lady Kokoro? Little ones?
Why the hell are you here?
To have brought something as dangerous as the Rocketman...
Though we were saved thanks to it...
Hey! Oi, old lady!
Pull yourself together!
Oi, please! Don't die, okay?!
DON'T DIE~!!
We got bloody noses...
You should have more than just bloody noses!
WE'RE HERE!!
Straw Hat!
Oi~!
Monster baasan!
Thank you!
Oi, you guys!
Hurry and get up!
That was nothing!
Don't compare us to a rubber guy like you...
For people of flesh and blood like us to make an entrance like that...
...there's no way we could be okay.
Everyone's okay.
You guys are a bit strange, too!
Just so you know...
There are some stairs over there!
Let's hurry and get to Robin!
Wait.
What the hell is that?!
Chapapapa!
We've been invaded!
Even if you get to that last room, Nico Robin's no longer there.
Lucci already took her to the Gates of Justice.
Oh, and the Chief, too.
Is that right?
Thank you for that valid piece of information.
Chapapa...
I told them...
What an odd guy...
That's okay.
Where they're headed now...
I'm not gonna tell you how to get there,
nor will we of CP9 allow you to get there.
We've been given orders to eliminate you guys, chapapa.
Orders of elimination?
You guys will all have to get through us in order to free Nico Robin.
Yeah!
We don't need you to tell us that, that's our intention.
Chapapa.
You have such good spirit!
But, let me just tell you one more thing.
What is it?!
Do what you want.
Thank you.
Then, frankly speaking...
Look at this!
A key?
What's that for?
It's the key needed to unlock Nico Robin's Sea Stone handcuffs!
Sea Stone?
It's a stone that nullifies the Devil's Fruit abilities.
It has the same effect as falling into the ocean.
So that's why Robin was being so timid...
When she's really so strong...
Yeah...
The usual Robin-chan wouldn't be so weak as to be kept captive by these assholes.
It must be eating her up...
I see.
Just in case you guys are able to save Nico Robin,
the Sea Stone is as hard as a diamond.
Those handcuffs can never be taken off.
Chapapa...
I told them again...
He really is an oddball.
If you're still okay with that, then keep going and save Nico Robin.
Chapapapapa!
Then...
GIVE IT HERE!!
Looks like he can use that technique, too.
Don't panic.
I haven't said whether or not this is the real key yet.
WHAT THE HELL?!
j& It may be a key to some other handcuffs~! j&
j& Chapapapa~! j&
...may not be real?
j& In this tower... j&
j& Including me, there are five CP9 members! j&
j& Each one of us has a key, j&
One, two! Come on!
One, two! Dance!
j& and we're waiting for you guys! j&
Then if we don't capture you, take your key and try it out on Robin's handcuffs,
we won't know if it's real or not?
What a stupid way to gain time...
And while we're doing that,
you're planning on taking Robin-chan in, aren't you?
j& Exactly~! j&
I told them again...
In this situation, Robin comes first.
We have to get Robin herself first.
The key can come later.
Just leave that idiot and hurry on.
Chapa!
Chapapa...
You're a smart one!
But if you do that,
then I'll just have to...
...throw this key into the ocean, chapapa!
We're giving you a chance.
See ya.
Hey!
Hold on a second!
Oi, wait up!
Why don't you  wait?!
Just hold up a bit!
Just wait until we decide what we're each gonna do individually!
Let me go! Just let me go!
Calm down, Straw Hat-kun.
Is Lucci that pigeon guy?
Yeah, that's right.
If that guy and Robin-chan are together,
then we should send Luffy ahead after them.
Luffy.
You go ahead and blast that pigeon guy away.
Let me go! Let me go!
Excluding Luffy, there are the six of us here.
From the five CP9 that are here,
we'll grab the five keys that can unlock Robin-chan's handcuffs,
then follow Luffy.
five keys which include the one that will unlock Robin-chan's handcuffs.
Yeah.
If Robin-kun crosses the gates, then everything is over!
Everything is a race against time!
Losing is a waste of time!
Everyone must win, even if you die trying!
Yeah!
Do your best!!
Let me go, Zoro!
Excluding Luffy, there are the six of us here.
From the five CP9 that are here,
we'll grab the five keys that can unlock Robin-chan's handcuffs,
then follow Luffy.
If Robin-kun crosses the gates, then everything is over!
Losing is a waste of time!
Everyone must win, even if you die trying!
Yeah!
Do your best!!
Go, pirate niichans!
Chimney?
Gonbe?
Where did they go?
They were just there!
I'm bound to run into them somewhere!
I'm not letting you get to the Gates of Justice!
ROBIN!!
A secret passage way!
A passage way!
A bucket!
A block!
A mushroom!
Bats?
I... I wonder how far this thing goes.
I can hear something.
I have nothing to fear!
Let's go!
Help isn't coming for you, Nico Robin.
First of all, they don't even know how to get to the Gates of Justice.
Come out!
Pigeon bastard!
Is it this way?!
Is it that way?!
Which way is it?!
It's that way!
Is it that way?!
It's this way!
Which way is it?!
Is it this way?!
It's this way!
Robin!
Even those guys can't make it here.
What a weird room.
Do this here, that there, then this...
I wonder what they're doing.
Door! Open up!
Awesome!
This is bad!
Before I fight...
Where's the kitchen?
Coup de Boo!
'Coup de Boo' uses up a bottle and a half of cola,
so I've already used up over two bottles today.
I need to have the max amount of three, or I can't fight the CP9!
That room! It seems like a kitchen!
CHAPAPAPAPAPAPAPAPA!!
Fukurou = Owl
I'm the gossip loving 'Silent Owl'.
Do you want my key?
Shit!
Not before I refill my cola!
Chapa.
I wonder what it is?
This dungeon like corridor...
YOYOI!
You damn pirate!
We finally meet, here in the hundredth year!
Hey now, hey now!
Hold on right there!
YOYOI!
He's so loud...
Wasn't in there...
Not there.
Not in there.
Good, not there.
What's this?
There isn't anybody anywhere.
Well, it's okay that they're not, but...
I see, so you're afraid of me!
Someone's here!
He's sleeping?
Is he a CP9 member too?
H-He's sleeping with the key out!
Could I possibly be so  lucky!?
A huge chance, perhaps?!
How about here?!
Shit!
No one's here, either...
Please, relax and enjoy yourself.
How about...
...I put on some tea?
e& Yes, please~! e&
You've already drawn your swords?
They're groaning that they wanna taste some blood, so...
Where the hell did you fall from, Zoro?!
Why the hell are you with a werewolf?!
But you're with a giraffe...
I guess they both have Devil's Fruit abilities, huh?
What the hell is going on with the CP9?!
Oi, oi!
Is this place a zoo?!
Next time, One Piece: The Power of The Devil's Fruit!
Kaku and Jyabura's Transformation.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!