Wealth, Fame, Power.
The man who had acquired everything in this
world, the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The final words that were said at his execution sent people to the seas.
My wealth and treasures?
If you want it, I'll let you have it.
Look for it, I left it all in that place.
Men now, chasing their dreams, head towards the Grand Line.
The world enters the Great Age of Pirates!
The bridge is being lowered!
Looks like those guys did it.
What great timing.
T-Trembles from excitement....
Robin!
We'll save you no matter what!
Hurry up and lower it.
What an evil looking face...
I heard you're a bad guy.
You're still here?
Being publicly humiliated in a place like this...
Are you really strong?
That's none of your business!
Geez, I ended up in quite a place just for partnering up with Luffy.
The Ways of a Man's Life! Zoro's Technique and Usopp's Dreams
You're weak as usual, huh, Zoro?
I made a promise.
There's no way I can die in a place like this.
You again? You must have nothing better to do.
I'll untie your ropes, so become my nakama.
What was that?
I'm looking for nakama to become pirates with.
No thanks!
Willingly become a criminal?
How dense can you be?
What's wrong with being a pirate?
Pirates are scum, why would I become one?
Who cares?
You're already known as a bad pirate hunter.
I don't care what society says about me...
But I've never done anything I regret.
I will survive no matter what,
and I'm going to do what I want to do!
Okay...
But I've already decided that I'm gonna make you my nakama.
Don't decide that by yourself!
You use a sword right?
Yeah, but that stupid son took them away.
I'll get it back for you.
What?
So if you want your sword back, you have to become my nakama!
THAT'S BLACKMAIL!!
Does he intend to take on the base by himself?
After him! Don't let him escape!
Major! There's someone in the execution field!
What?
Rebels coming one after another, huh?
Please escape, Zoro-san.
They'll kill you if I did that!
I can't watch these Marines any longer.
I want to be a good Marine.
Stop it! I can't escape now!
I have ten more days to...
You're being executed tomorrow.
What?
Helmeppo had no intention of keeping his word with you from the beginning.
That's why Luffy-san got angry and punched him.
He did?
Luffy-san is currently being chased by the Marines.
I'm not telling you to become a pirate.
But please...
Please help Luffy-san.
The only one that can save Zoro-san is Luffy-san.
And now, I think the only person that can help Luffy-san is you.
Hold it right there!
You guys have done some interesting things.
Are the two of you...
...trying to start a Coup d'Etat along with the Straw Hat?
-
I have always fought alone.
Unlike you, hiding arrogantly behind your henchmen!!
Roronoa Zoro.
Don't underestimate me.
Your strength is nothing compared to my authority!
Take aim!
I cannot...
...die in a place like this!
You're weak as usual, huh, Zoro?
Gomu Gomu no Rocket!!
Fire!
You!
Luffy-san!
Straw Hat!
That's not gonna work!
See, I told you. I'm strong!
What the hell are  you?
I'm Monkey D. Luffy.
I'm the man who's going to become the Pirate King!
Become the Pirate King?
Do you even understand what you're saying?
A Pirate King is a Pirate King.
Does it mean anything else?
I was surprised too!
But Luffy-san is serious. That's the kind of person he is!
He's going to become the pirate king and intends to obtain
the world's ultimate treasure, One Piece!
Here you go, your treasure.
Which one is it?
I didn't know, so I brought all three of them.
Santoryu = Three Sword
All three are mine, I use the santoryu style.
You'll take them, right?
If you fight with me now, you'll become a criminal for going up against the government.
Or you can be killed by the Marines now, which would you prefer?
Are you the son of the devil?
It doesn't matter.
If I'm gonna die here, then I'd rather become one.
A pirate!
Yeah! You're going to be my nakama!
Great! That's fantastic!
Alright, alright! Hurry up and untie me!
What is that guy?
He deflected the bullets!
That Straw Hat is no ordinary human.
He must have eaten one of the rumored Devil Fruits.
The Devil Fruits?
Damn, this knot is hard...
Oi, hurry up!
No matter what the person is, anyone who opposes me will be executed!
If guns don't work, then slice him up!
Uh oh, that's weird. The knot's getting tighter.
Hurry up and give me my swords!
Luffy-san!
Roronoa Zoro.
He's so cool!
If any of you move, I'll cut you.
He's too scary!
I'll become a pirate, that's a promise.
And now that I'm opposing the Marines, I guess that makes me a criminal.
But let me just say one thing.
I will achieve my ambition.
Ambition?
To become the world's greatest swordsman.
But if you ever do anything to jeopardize my ambition...
Then you'd better make it up to me with your life!
The world's number one swordsman...
That's good.
I expect nothing less if you're gonna be a nakama of a Pirate King.
Big talker, eh?
Then I guess I have no choice but to let the world know of my name, even as a criminal.
What are you just standing there for?
Hurry up and finish them off!
Get down, Zoro!
Gomu Gomu no Muchi! (Whip)
H-He did it! So amazing!
What in the world are you?
I ate the rubber fruit.
The rubber fruit?
He's a rubber man!
Just as I suspected, he did eat one of the Devil Fruits.
Major! There's no way we can match him!
These guys are crazy!
We can't even match up with Roronoa Zoro!
This is a Major's order.
All those that just complained, shoot yourselves in the head!
I don't need any weak subordinates!
There is definitely something wrong with these Marines.
Luffy-san!
Demolish these damn Marines!
There's no one who can overpower my authority!
I'm the Marine Major, Axe-Hand Morgan!
I'm Luffy.
Pleased to meet ya.
M... Major!
You little brat!
DIE!!
I don't wanna!
Major Morgan is...
Completely losing...
What kind of a Marine are you? Destroying Coby's dream like that!
Wait! Straw Hat!
Look at this!
I said wait, didn't I!? Are you an idiot!?
I went out of the way to take a hostage and you don't even notice!
Helmeppo-sama...
Oi.
If you want this kid to live, then don't move!
Make even the slightest move and I'll shoot him!
Luffy-san!
I don't ever want to get in your way!
Even if I die!
Yeah, I know.
Give it up, stupid son.
Coby's determination is the real thing.
Don't move!
I said not to move, didn't I!?
I-I'll shoot him!
Behind you!
I am the Marine Major, Axe-Hand Morgan!!
Dad! Hurry up and get him!
Nice!
Zoro.
Not a problem... Captain.
The bridge stopped!
Don't interfere!
What the hell! Damn it!
Who is it!?
Don't worry, Robin...
These tremors are... just tremors of excitement.
We will save you, no matter what.
But, there are a lot of enemies, right?
You've got fear written all over your face.
M-M-Me? Scared!? I'll be fine even if there's many of them!
Because I am the courageous warrior of the sea, Captain Usopp!
Damn it! Damn it!
Don't judge me!
These guys are Klahadore's pirates!
Scary is scary!
So what!?
I don't want any sympathy from you!
You guys get out of here! Get lost!
We're not laughing...
We're going to help you because we think you're noble.
I'd never bet my life out of sympathy.
You guys!
Usopp!
D-Damn it...
My body won't move.
Even if you catch up with Jango, you don't stand a chance against him.
That's probably safer for you.
Even if...
Even if I don't stand a chance, I'm gonna protect them.
I'm gonna protect those guys.
I'm the captain of the Usopp Pirate crew, and a courageous warrior of the sea!
I won't let you lay a finger on anyone from this village!!
He's screaming something.
Hey! Look at him, he's crying!
What's so damn funny!?
Luffy!
I'm going after the hypnotist with Usopp.
Any problems with that?
Nope! Hurry!
You were a bit too late, haramaki!
Haramaki = The cloth band that wraps around Zoro's midsection.
Not really.
Yes! That branch was in the way!
What?
Usopp-san...
Hissatsu Kayaku Boshi
Killing Weapon Gunpowder Star!
So you're setting out to sea like I thought, Usopp-san?
Yeah, I'm gonna get outta here before my determination wavers.
Don't try to stop me.
I won't stop you, I had a feeling this would happen.
That's a bit lonely too though.
The next time I come back to this village,
I'll tell you even more outrageous adventure stories more unbelievable than the lies I used to tell you.
I'll be looking forward to it.
You guys take care too.
Maybe we can run into each other again somewhere.
Why?
"Why?"
Man, you're a cold guy.
We're gonna be pirates from now, so we'll eventually meet at sea...
What are you talking about?
Hurry up and get on.
We're already nakama, aren't we?
The captain...
The captain better be me!
Don't be stupid! I'm the captain!
Oi, you pirates! What are you lingering around for?
Lingering? But the bridge is only halfway...
Halfway is more than enough.
I'll be there in four more seconds.
So jump into the waterfall with all you've got!
Was it the baasan? What did she mean?
I don't know, but she said to jump into the waterfall.
The sea train?
What's the meaning of that smile...
HERE WE GO!!
Robin, it must have been hard.
But you're not alone anymore.
Wait for us Robin, we're all on your side.
So believe in your nakama, believe in Luffy!
Luffy will definitely answer you.
Next time, One Piece: Tears Which Weaved the Bond of Nakama!
Nami's Map of the World.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!