This odor…
But it is…
Chopper, that is there?
Oi, Chopper!
Oi, Chopper, that go?!
Is Oi, Comment that?
You hurt yourself?
What is there? You start to run of a blow and… and…
I was sure. It is there.
Robin!
I did not come to join you.
They is here that our ways separate, in this city.
I carry in me this “darkness” that none you knows.
This darkness will destroy you, one day.
In the beginning, I am supposed to make you accuse and flee.
The things will be worsened for you.
Robin-chan! I do not include/understand anything so that you say!
That there is?!
Robin! Let us return together!
One all got along well, but from today…
We will not be re-examined any more.
Thank you to have been so nice with me until now.
Goodbye.
Wait…
Wait!
I cannot accept that.
WAIT!
Stop your conneries!
Wait, Robin-chan!
ROBIN!
It was lost.
Ouais.
Chopper…
Join Luffy and the others, will tell them what it occurred.
All in detail.
And you?
I will try something of other.
Do not worry you, I will remain careful.
To catch Robin!
The decision of the crew of the Straw hat.
Wait!
Do not let them escape!
What you ace foutu!?
It was inevitable!
How I could hide me? They are too numerous!
You will not escape!
By there!
What? Where are parties?
Seek everywhere!
Nothing in the lane?
Are they assembled on the roofs?
Shit, they are make the trunk!
Good, they had to leave in this direction.
Do you have to seek by over there?
Then let us check inside the buildings!
Yosh!
One separate in two groups!
It is good now?
Not yet.
They disappeared by here!
And now?
Still a little.
Please.
Not now. We leave to put ourselves at the shelter!
Stop insisting!
Please. I have money.
In exchange, I need boards. Like a little tar and ropes.
And then nails, locks and outcry.
I will close the store.
Excuse me, but…
Good, but you will not be able all to have with this sum.
A-Alors, do you accept tools in the place of the money which misses?
Oi, oi, would not be stupid. Stop.
I make only the sale.
It is what these chicaneries? From which area do come you?
Good, then I do not have the choice.
Will O-Oi, you leave itself there with all your wounds?
You do not have companions who can help you?!
Oi!
Here, I had said to you!
Oi, wait a little, kid!
They is good. I manage very well.
Oi!
It is what? I do not need your aid…
Not. Here, take that.
You hungry, isn't this is?
Thank you.
Would be careful.
Would be careful!
Delicious!
They is really good.
This old man was really simpa.
The waves increased volume.
Do not make any you, all is well.
You are the boat which ace stolen in the airs.
Do not make any you!
What is there still?
What is there, Franky?
Aniki?
Whore, I am irritated!
It is the moment for any Peter!
Aniki, await us!
Thank you for the meal, Blueno.
It is what the problem, Kokoro-san? Why did Franky leave so quickly?
Who knows. I do not know…
...com lies function the cretins.
Ca was finally calmed.
Calmed?
If you had not been done driven out by the carpenters, one would not have been made locate!
I said to you that it was inevitable.
Moreover, Chopper. How you have to find us?
With the odor.
Ah, played well.
Is Heu, where Sanji?
On this subject…
ROBIN REALLY SAID THAT?!
One could expect it.
One left Robin, formerly our enemy,
to go up on board boat.
It realized that they was too dangerous and east flees.
Isn't this the moment to have the heart Net of it?
If this woman is our enemy…
Or our friend.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
The things will be worsened for you. Henceforth…
We will not be re-examined any more.
If I remember well, it is what said Robin, isn't this Chopper?
Since we will not re-examine it any more…
She says that as if something of low register were going to arrive to us.
If it intends to make a thing of worse in this city…
Considering the panic created by the attempted murder of the mayor, there remains only one option.
To assassinate the mayor, at sure cost this time.
Ca appears obvious.
But now that we know that she wants to make us wear the hat…
It is perhaps only one trap to attract us on the spot of the crime.
A trap?
If we are in trimmings at the time of the crime, we will be definitively marked.
He!
You say that as if Robin were our enemy!
I say just that it is possible.
I do not have an opinion.
To believe or doubt, if I lean on a side…
My reaction time is affected…
If my spirit thinks the reverse of my choice.
If something occurs, it will be this evening. One goes there?
One goes there.
It does not matter if one goes there…
Isn't the problem, it is that Sanji saw Robin going with a person?
And Iceberg saw it too.
“It was accompanied by a masked person.”
It is none among us.
It is because of him that Robin suddenly changed.
It makes make dirty tricks with Robin!
Ca holds upright.
But the worst would be than Robin and are to him partners.
We do not have any index on that which hides behind this mask.
It is the problem.
Which is our goal?
To catch Robin.
It is the only means of more.
It is true, one wastes time to reflect. But…
To find a woman whom the government did not succeed in catching in twenty years seems difficult.
But it is the only way of knowing the truth.
Yosh, I will do my better, me too.
Then, let us go in Galley it Company.
Shit. The sun lay down.
Paulie-san, that fears!
The low city is too dangerous now!
Ouais, let us drop. I return to the office.
Included/understood!
Oi, the guy! One gives up!
STRAW HAT! SHOW YOURSELF!
WHERE ES YOU?!
STRAW HAT!
This dumb is malignant…
But it will not be shown.
Aniki, they are pursued in all the island.
Yes, they are surely already far.
Is He, it what the problem? What you ridges?
We are too sensitive…
Vis-a-vis the wind.
Aniki, you act bizarement today.
You forget that there remains to you money.
The farm! I am like that all the time.
Aha! Aniki!
It is Zambai and the others.
Aniki, do you have to crush them?
Not, not yet. I had unforeseen, then they are flee.
What?!
They have escaped with the anger of Aniki?!
They had much chance.
I see. But the dead loss with the long nose repaired the all alone boat…
Then it was thought that Aniki had overcome them.
You know where I can find one of them?
Yes, with the boat.
If there remains one about it, all becomes easier.
One will make use of it to trap the others.
The face of Aniki is terrifying.
The guy, you in all the city move while howling
“We have the length-nose!”
“If you do not want to see it running at the ocean floor, go to the warehouse, under the bridge!”
“On behalf of Franky”.
And now, I go choper length-nose.
Of agreement, Aniki! Trust us!
It is what? You are enormous, but your luggage too.
It is a floating bed.
Aqua Laguna, Aqua Laguna, Aqua Laguna arrive!
It is Aqua Laguna!
News on the criminals?
It would seem that they are always in freedom.
It is what one said to me. I do not like that.
People say that they will benefit from the storm to tackle this evening again.
Aqua Laguna is there!
All will be well this evening. The craftsmen of Galley will protect it the fortress.
It is not to take with the light one.
At how much pirates is estimated the crew of Straw hat?
Some say 50, others say 100.
After all, the setting at price of the captain is of 100 million.
Perhaps that 3000 men will emerge from the ocean this evening?!
It is madness!
Open the eye, do not leave any opening, Galley it Company!
Do not let even a mouse enter!
APPROACH IF YOU DARE!
You shout too extremely! Calm remainder, Tileston!
They did not take the train of the sea.
Then they are always on the island.
It would be necessary to be insane to try to penetrate this surprotégé place.
I heard that this idiot came here head lowered in full day.
There is no more logic.
Maaa…
They did not need to do all that.
They all are voluntary…
I have the impression to be a king.
Another thing Iceberg-san, why do you have the research opinion of Nico Robin in your room?
Does Ca disturb you?
A little.
It is preferable that you would not be with the current.
It is…
A demon.
Guards of everywhere.
It is too far.
You will not have that to lengthen your arms until over there if there is grabuge.
Yes, if we act initially, they would benefit from it.
Attention, be attentive with the least movement!