Wealth, Fame, Power.
The man who had acquired everything in this
world, the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The final words that were said at his execution sent people to the seas.
My wealth and treasures?
If you want it, I'll let you have it.
Look for it, I left it all in that place.
Men now, chasing their dreams, head towards the Grand Line.
The world enters the Great Age of Pirates!
Is Lucci that pigeon guy?
Yeah, that's right.
If that guy and Robin-chan are together,
then we should send Luffy ahead after them.
Luffy.
You go ahead and blast that pigeon guy away.
Let me go! Let me go!
Excluding Luffy, there are the six of us here.
From the five CP9 that are here,
we'll grab the five keys that can unlock Robin-chan's handcuffs,
then follow Luffy.
Yeah.
If Robin-kun crosses the gates, then everything is over!
Everything is a race against time!
Losing is a waste of time!
Everyone must win, even if you die trying!
Yeah!
Do your best!!
Help isn't coming for you, Nico Robin.
First of all, they don't even know how to get to the Gates of Justice.
Come out!
Pigeon bastard!
CHAPAPAPAPAPAPAPAPA!!
I'm the gossip loving 'Silent Owl'.
Fukurou = Owl
Do you want my key?
Shit!
Not before I refill my cola!
Chapa.
YOYOI~!
You damn pirate~!
We finally meet, here in the hundredth year~!
I see, so you're afraid of me!
Someone's here!
How about here?!
Shit!
No one's here, either...
Please, relax and enjoy yourself.
The Power of The Devil's Fruit! Kaku and Jyabura's Transformation
Yo~!
Yoyoi!
Yoyoi~!
Now, now!
Prepare yourself!
Are you ready~?!
Prepare myself?
No matter how I look at it, he's not a good match.
Getting the key is my first priority.
Yo! Assassin!
Where's the key?
Since you asked...
Let me tell you~!
The key is...
Yes, yes?
The key is...?
The key is~...
Yes, yes!
And then?
The key is~...
Just tell me a bit more!
The key is right here~!
Oh~! My key is right here~!
Oh~! It's right here~!
He's so loud and troublesome.
That's not how you do it.
What?
Young lady.
In order to drink delicious tea, your water must be hotter.
The golden rule of making good tea is...
...to boil fresh water, and pour it into a warm-kept pot.
The standard is when you see bubbles starting to form.
By doing that,
the hot water circulates and allows the tea leaves to dance,
which then helps to bring out the aroma and color.
Then you must immediately cover the pot,
and let it steam for a minute.
Then pour the tea into cups that have also been kept warm.
Just the slightest attention to detail can change the flavor.
You sure know a lot.
I'm a cook.
Thank you for letting me know.
e& So beautiful~! e&
This should be it.
I'm finally here.
I ended up going all up and down the stairs...
Robin!
Oi! Robin!
It's me~!
Robin!!
Where are you?!
Damn it...
Just as I thought, nobody's here.
Damn pigeon guy...
That's right!
I already know where they're headed.
So all I have to do is head towards the Gates of Justice too!
You have the keys to Robin's handcuffs, don't you?
You wanna hand them over before I kill you?
What a stupid question.
I was disappointed that I didn't get to see your true strength back at the Galley-La mansion.
I never would've thought you pirates would make it out here either.
I'm a lot stronger than the last time we met.
Be careful.
That's for sure.
Your energy is overflowing.
Energy like that of a monster.
You're truly a terrifying man.
However...
My swordsmanship is the best in all of CP9.
Don't underestimate me.
Nitouryu, huh?
Nitouryu = Two Sword Technique
Rankyaku
Not quite...
Sorry, but I'm a Yontou.
Yontou = Four Swords
Not a problem!
Come to think of it, your whole body's a weapon, isn't it?!
Nanajyu Ni... (Seventy two)
Rankyaku
Pondo Ho! (Pound Wind)
Haku Rai (White Lightning)
Soru (Shave)
This is fun!
I don't have time for games.
Well, then you'll just have to kill me.
Rankyaku. Run! (Break)
For him to be able to control this so freely...
Bastard...
Are you messing with me?!
No, I'm impressed.
But if you're in such a rush, then I'll show you...
Witness my new-found power.
Wh-What's this?
What the hell is  this room?
There's such a thing as too much gardening.
It's practically as though we're outside.
No, no, no!
That's beside the point, Robin's handcuffs come first.
That key!
Quietly...
Quiet...
There's nothing to ponder!
Just be cautious and quiet!
One step at a time, without making a peep.
That was close!
Okay, one more time.
If I just take it quietly,
and quietly run away,
then my purpose will be served.
I'll have an unwounded victory.
That's right, I'm...
I'm a Lucky King!
Hey, heart!
You're beating too loudly!
Stop that!
My heart stopped!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
You can't stop now!
Oh yeah, times like this call for a heart massage!
That sure scared me...
Calm down. Just calm down!
Come on now!
I'm the sort of man who can get anything I want done!
Probably...
I'm a man that can do anything...
I'm a man that...
Wh-What? A bee?!
Don't come here! Oi!
Go away! Go!
What are you doing?!
The end of that hana isn't a flower!
It doesn't have any honey!
Hana = Nose/Flower
Go away!
I said go away!
Wh-What are you doing looking over here with that gleam in your eye?!
You... You wouldn't! Stop it!
Stop it! S-Stop! Stop!
My nose! My nose!
It hurts~!
Damn it!
I'm right back where I started.
But damn, he's still asleep.
He's one big sleepyhead.
If I do it without panicking, I can make it this time!
Quietly...
Quietly, quietly...
Just a bit more...
Just a bit more.
Just a bit more~!
Th-This time it's a rooster?!
No good!
Why is a bird that's so far from being quiet here?!
This isn't good!
If he cries out, it's over!
If he cries out, he'll wake up and kill me!
Oi! What are you looking at me for?
Are you going to cry?
Is that it? Is it?!
Rooster-kun? Rooster-san? Rooster-sama?!
Please! I beg of you! Please don't cry!
Don't cry! Please stop!
There aren't any roosters who do that!!
Huh? So you're here, pirate?
Da-Damn you, rooster...
Well then, guess it's time to get wild.
Damn you, rooster...
H-He's strong...
So you're here!
The one who shot the Government's flag down.
You definitely have a good arm.
That was his first shot after he just got up?!
Sorry, sorry for that half-assed attack.
Sorry about that.
That hurt, didn't it?
But it's okay...
Despite the way I look, I don't like to torture.
A Devil Fruit?!
Inu = Dog
The Inu Inu Fruit. Model 'Wolf'.
All I have to do is cut your windpipe, and it'll be over.
If you're gonna die, there's no reason to suffer.
Isn't that right?
A wolf?!
Shit!
What's this? You wanna fight?
You don't look very strong...
Wh-Whatever! I-I'm gonna do it!
Shut up!
I... I came here to help Robin!
The ceiling!
It's falling apart!
Oh, no!
I only meant to be half beast, but I became a full giraffe!
THERE'S A TALKING GIRAFFE FALLING DOWN!!
Kaku! Your new power is so hilarious!
A wolf?!
What is this place?! A zoo?!
Ushi = Cow (to which giraffes are related)
The Ushi Ushi Fruit! Model 'Giraffe'!
You poor bastard, having to be a giraffe-man for the rest of your life!
What's wrong with being a giraffe?!
I told you that I happen to like it!
That pigeon bastard was a leopard, wasn't he?
For them to have two more with Devil Fruit abilities...
Is this the type of organization that CP9 is?!
S-So he has the Devil Fruit ability of the Zoan type?
A werewolf and a giraffe-man?
We really bumped into some winners.
However, I've been saved since he came falling down with Zoro.
I'll just go with the flow of two against two,
and just let him beat them both.
"I told you that I happen to like it!!"
I'm sure you would!
Giraffes are so cool, right?!
Wh-What exactly are you saying?!
But really, they have no sense of teamwork even though they're nakama.
What's that?
Looks like an open safe.
Could those weird handcuffs really be...?!
I told you not to laugh!
Oi, giraffe!
How long do you plan to keep arguing there?
I already told you I don't have time.
If you're okay like that,
then I'll just cut you the way you are.
You poor thing...
Don't underestimate the full destructive power of a giraffe.
Henkei Jinjyugata! (Transformation Half Man Half Beast Form)
I'll show you...
...my reborn powers.
You look like shit!
Gabeen = Sound Effect for a Dropped Jaw
Gabeen!
You! Did you just...?
Wh-What a shallow thing for me to say...
This isn't good, the absurdity of all this made me slip my tongue.
Don't lose concentration. It will only dull the sword.
How long are you gonna keep laughing, Jyabura?!
So-Sorry.
I can't do it!
It's too hilarious.
Why the hell are all his body parts so square?
Wh-What the hell are these handcuffs?!
Whoops! I'm so sorry, Zoro-kun!
Oi! What's the meaning of this, you dumbass?!
Th-They're probably...
...the same Sea Stone handcuffs as Robin's.
Since both the enemies have Devil Fruit abilities,
I thought that if I cuffed them, they'd become weak.
Then why did you put them on me?!
You idiot!!
Bu-But...
That giraffe's face is so hilarious!
My hand slipped!
You're a 'square giraffe'!
No doubt!
Damn you! All of you!
Enjoy the fighting powers of the Devil Fruit's ability!
Rankyaku!
Wh-What the hell?! Something's coming!
Amane Dachi! (Rottating Cut!)
This is bad!
Get down, Usopp!
No!
This is no time to be having tea!
Oh, that's too bad.
Are you in a hurry?
Robin-chan's life is on the line.
If you're gonna get in my way, there's no holding back just because you're a woman!
Then, it's okay that tea time is over?
Next time, One Piece: I Won't Kick You Even If I Die!
Sanji's Way of Chivalry.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!