Wealth, Fame, Power.
The man who very acquired of this world,
the Lord of the pirates, Gold Roger.
Its last words during its execution
pushed people to take the sea.
My richnesses, my treasures?
If you want them, I leave them to you.
Seek them, I very left over there.
Men, pursueing their dreams,
ventured on Grand Line.
The world now entered the golden age of piracy!
What will you make, now?
Hurry to deposit me with ground.
Like that, I will be able to beat you.
No need talk.
I will make so that you buckle it good once for all.
[Fast Spinning top & Swell of Steel]
CHOU SOKUTEI TEKKAI DAMA
I will propel you on the lathe by the centrifugal force.
I see…
I will surely not leave there alive.
[Centaur]
FRANKY KENTAUROS
Chapa?
I hold you by the legs.
You lose any freedom of movement thus.
How that?
Even with that, you will not be able anything against this centrifugal force.
Not inevitably.
Gauge 70 mm, Canon de Cola 0,2!
Small…
STRONG GALE
It countered the force!
The spinning top stopped.
Whore!
That is enough!
One is soon on the dry land.
Take-that!
Gauge 70 mm, 1,5 max Power Cola!
COUP DE
You insane what, dumb?
Give up!
COUP DE
VENT
SUPER!
Yoyoi!
This voice…
It opened the door of the refrigerator?
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you…
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you…
Thank you for this meal.
It grew bigger!
You goinfré yourself or what?
What…
Perfect, Sogeking.
Remain quite right.
You are my saber!
I want my lawyer!
One day, you will pay it to me!
As you will want.
While waiting, I will see what you have in the belly.
Do not say that!
It is surely a dream!
I must awake!
You made odd tricks.
Laughing.
ONI
He! Wait!
You really will do it?
I do not want to be mingled with that!
[Edge of the Demon]
GIRI
Stars in my eyes…
Do not move.
[Tiger]
TORA
There is a problem! There is a problem!
Shit!
Stars in my nose, now…
I said to you not to move!
I cannot! You want to kill me?
They are stupid or what?
They hope to fight like that?
One will have to play janken.
That which loses cuts the wrist.
Wait!
You ace not a better idea?
Not, none.
Do not say that so coldly.
It is not the moment of chamailler.
Give up, Large-Conk!
“Gives up, Large-Conk”!
Hurry, Chopper!
Unverifiable!
Rumble prohibited of Chopper
Yoyoi!
I never saw somebody also neglected.
How can you grow bigger in if little time?
, It is not you…
Pas la pains, pas-pas-pas the sorrow…
I have anything with foutre you of it!
Express yourself normally!
“Not is the sorrow to worry”, it that?
… to worry!
I am grateful to you…
For your compassion.
I included/understood, then buckles it!
“Not the sorrow that I do worry”, it is that?
He, return-there!
Yes, yes, completely!
Because…
As you can see it…
[Return to the life]
SEIMEI KIKAN
It is what?
[Digestion]
SHOUKA
[Absorption]
KYUSHU
[Return to the normal]
MOTOR BIKE DOURI
But be to you which, you?
It was what, that?
You can start again?
As you will want…
SEIMEI KIKAN
SHOUKA
KYUSHU
Enormous!
Still!
Still?
SEIMEI KIKAN
SHOUKA
KYUSHU
It is brilliant!
How you do that?
He well, thank you for your question.
One millenium in water, then one millenium in the mountain…
[Sennin: Master]
Breathing the air of the wind and drinking pure water,
I followed the drive of Sennin.
And all these efforts enabled me to control Seimei Kikan.
Hair with the toes, while passing by
intestines or even hairs…
Each human is able to drive each one of its members,
Allowing ansi a total control of each part of the body.
To drive each one of its hair?
It seems me to have read something on this subject.
A trick called “Genetic Control”.
Then it is thanks to this capacity that you can make
to move your hair like an octopus?
Yoyoyoi!
An octopus, do you say? What a impoliteness!
Actually, I am…
… what is called… what is called: a lion.
One of fout a little, not?
SEIMEI KIKAN
[Throttling by the hair]
KAMISHIBARI
Yoyoi!
Yoyoyoyoi!
Shit!
If it catches me, I am foutu.
SORU
Where is it?
[Cue: stick]
SHIGAN CUE
And its stick is not even pointed.
CUE
HEAVRY NOT
TEKKAI
Yoi!
What is there?
Whore…
I should have doubted to me it, only the attacks
ARM Not or Horn Point are effective.
But I should not consume more
of Rumble every six hours.
Beyond this limit, I endanger my body.
And then…
A second would return my transformations
not easily controllable.
As for a third, I would not be any more aware
of my acts and I could not any more beat me.
What to make?
If it is only one moreover, I can leave myself there.
Prepare to roast.
[Shishi: Lion]
SHISHI KEBAB
Yoi!
I do nothing but waste time.
RUMBLE
The risks are raised, but I have a chance.
Yoyoi!
It is that or nothing.
I will put a term at all that in three minutes.
Take-that!
HORN NOT
Yoyoi!
Oh not!
That burns, that burns, that burns, that burns!
KEBAB
JUMPING NOT
It is not true!
Yoyoi!
I have evil to control them.
Whore.
So only I could reach the ARM Not.
I could strike it my ultimate Kokutei.
The place becomes dangerous with this fire.
I should not waste time with
this guy who does not even have a key.
I must quickly find the key number two and…
I must release them.
If not, I will not be able to save Robin.
It is that.
Robin.
It is well that.
I…
I fight to help my companions.
You are hard to cook.
SEIMEI KIKAN
Its hair transorment in hands.
I must do it.
I cannot die here.
I am their only hope!
SHISHI SHIGAN
Yoyoi!
I will be without pity!
Never the lion would allow that!
That hurt…
I risk my life with a second rumble ball.
The transformations are with the number of Sept.
Thus my chances to reach the ARM Not…
Are of one over Sept.
If I reach that point, I could manage to him
my more powerful attack.
I do not have the choice.
ARM NOT
SHISHI KEBAB
It is for my companions.
ARM NOT
Yoyoi!
Failure.
Why I do not arrive there?
My body reaches its limits.
I must cost whom the ARM costs to reach Not.
Yoyoi!
I changed. It arrived when?
Prepare!
I setting all on top.
All on this blow.
[Shoe Slicing]
KOKUTEI
SHISHI SHIGAN
If I fail now, I will not have any more an other chance.
KOKUTEI
[Gou: powerful]
TEKKAI GOU
[Storm of flower]
ROSEO MICHIERI
Take-that!
It is my more powerful attack.
Played well.
Which beauty…
… this storm of petals.
It is…
It is really…
I succeeded?
It is absolutely unforgivable!
You now will taste with the howling of the lion!
Yoyoyoiyoi!
[Renge: Fleur of lotus]
RANKYAKY RENGE
I cannot.
I do not have enough any more of forces to counteract.
Chopper…
Chopper, what you ace foutu?
I do not remember it…
It is not because you lost
the memory which you will be excused.
It is already although nobody is killed.
Whereas you slept, you sowed chaos this night at the village.
I do not know how to punish you.
It was so horrible?
You almost destroyed a whole village.
I insane that you want to make
experiments like your father,
But you must pay attention to the consequences of such acts.
It is like that.
To pay attention?
I include/understand well that you did not do that to amuse you.
This is why…
You must remain all the more vigilant.
A doctor holds the life of a person between his hands.
The least error can be irreversible.
We walk constantly on a steep slope.
To act without reflecting can bring to the catastrophe.
If you do not manage to take this in consideration,
Then you would make better give up.
Good blood, even with deepest of you…
You inherited this blasted charlatan.
I imagine that one can nothing make there.
I am afflicted, Doctorine.
I will not start again any more.
I will not remake it any more, then do not punish me.
Imbecile, starts initially by curing.
I cannot go even any more to make the races.
SEIMEI KIKAN
KAMISHIBARI
… Do not cry! Do not cry!
While crying, you lose your virility…
It will kill me.
This place is not a peaceful village
rocked by the song the cicadas.
You were ready but you were mislaid…
… during this mortal voyage towards the flames of the Hell.
When you leave, I will make in kind
that you return one day to the life…
The sheets crimsons fall from the oak!
Do not move and accepts them!
Now, now, now!
A bright crimson!
[Languorous Song of the Oak]
YANA GIN JOU
I will die…
Robin…
Not, I should not give up.
He dodged my Kamishibari!
RUMBLE
I am afflicted, Doctorine.
Just like the Doctor who put its
life concerned to save the country…
I want me to also put my life concerned
in order to save my companions.
Even if I die,
I will do it.
Please, that nobody…
Do not return in this part.
I used three rumble ball…
Then I lost consciousness.
And after…
Surely the hidden side of the Fruit of the Demon.
Give the feet never again over there.
This terrible capacity destroys your friends,
your enemies, but also your own body.
It is as if you became true…
Monster.
Oyabun, it is horrible! It is horrible! It is horrible!
He, that is there of so horrible, Usopp?
We are of return.
Buggy and its men are there too and sow chaos.
Good, good, good.
Come to be restored and calms itself.
Of agreement…
Not! It is horrible, Oyabun!
Soon, in One Part:
The return of Luffy Oyabun!
Risks of the dreams and reality.
I will become the Chief of the police force!