I am Capitaine of the Q.G of the Navy!
I will leave you this life of disgrace!
I will slice you into two to stop you!
That will not arrive.
Because the place which we want to reach…
is far behind you!
APPROACHES!!
I hate the indirect combat!!
** TECHNICAL ** Chokkaku Hichou!
** TECHNICAL ** Santouryuu Gyuuki
** TECHNICAL ** Bone Oudori!
It cut it!?
** TECHNICAL ** Yuuzume!
Roronoa!
It overcame trenching boat!
To run since the taken down coaches,
to catch up with Umi Ressha by this storm,
is admirable.
But nothing will stop us.
Your justice is certainly imposing,
But also let us have we a strong motivation.
Sha! When one has that mouth, one finishes like that.
Sift!! You are sure not to be to you made berner by this woman?
She betrayed, and still betrayed, in the world of darkness where she lived until today. The worst of the women.
Your life is with me!
** TECHNICAL ** Cutting!!
What would you say to say some words of good-bye, frangin?
** TECHNICAL ** Ultimate Hammer!!
From where you come, you?
You finished other noodle?
Yes, at the moment.
It became quite noisy suddenly…
Were all the soldiers of escort beaten?
One did not expect any better them…
Then it is them… which removed Robin-chan.
Pay to, they use odd techniques.
It is which that one?
It is surely the new recruit of the CP 9 about which Corgi spoke.
I believe that it is called Nero and used four styles.
Shit…
You will pay it to me, sho… one calls me the wonder of the combat…
I have of it more anything to make…
I will kill you!
Oi, the new one!
You are Rob Lucci, not true?
It is a little late for the greetings…
Wait a little, I will kill this type…
Franky must be captured alive.
To let your emotions affect your mission…
Not, drops.
I give you three seconds, then starts to run.
Three
To run? Which?
Two
, You wait pleasant?!
One.
Stop! Do not talk cock!
The rescue of Robin! The clever plan of Sogeking!
I give you three seconds, then starts to run.
Three
To run? Which?
Two.
, You wait pleasant?!
One
Stop! Do not talk cock!
** TECHNICAL ** Soru!
Somebody with half involved, like you…
its place does not have among the CP9!
We are superhuman because we control Rokushiki, kid.
Kalifa.
Yes?
Later you will transmit this to the chief…
“The new recruit was too weak, it was used for nothing.”
Included/understood.
It is guy fight for justice?
Who are the malicious ones here?
The government officials have really bad manners.
It is my duty.
You see, my nose does not mislead me, Nico Robin!
Why wouldn't you remove this coat?
Then? Then?  Then?!
Is shit… it the end?
Wait!
My name is Sogeking.
I am that which comes from the island of the snipeurs.
Soge?
, You wait really believe to be able to draw you with that?
Yes! Do not look at a high somebody who is prepared with going until there…
LUCCI-SAN!!!
What you made here… I make fun about it too much for you to ask it, intruder.
Considering how you opened the door…
It would seem that you are rather impatient…
Ouais, I was badly high.
Drop Nico Robin.
What occurs here is too large for you.
In this world, there are people who were born under an unlucky star…
whose death would only make people happier.
About what you do speak?
For example:
If there was a demon able to destroy the world,
And even if the only person able to awake it…
is only one eight years innocent little girl.
You do not think…
that this young girl…
should be killed for the good of all?
Where do you want to come from there?
I speak to you about the life of this woman, Nico Robin.
Now, it is true criminal.
But at the beginning, it was only that.
At the moment when it came in the world,
its existence even became a crime.
It carries such a burden that only its death would make people happy…
Logically, it should have died twenty years ago.
The fact that this woman dies,
is really a good thing.
Stop your is delirious!!
Jerk!
Do not open any more your mouth!
Only, the government surely will take several years,
to extract all knowledge and the experiment from Nico Robin.
Finally, how atrocious you she will die?
Think there seriously
I WILL NOT LET TO YOU MAKE CA!!!
Oi, oi, wait, Robin!
Do not go by there…
Serious, wait!
Oi! Wait!
Robin-chan!
They is not good…
God thank you! You are well? You are not wounded?
It is not true…
Whereas I had succeeded in infiltrating me up to now and to cut down this agent.
It is it Nico Robin?
It really resembles the portrait on the research opinion…
This time, let us find the others together!
I will smash these quickly made guy!
Of agreement? Robin-chan!
Usopp! But what do you make, Robin-chan?
It would seem that the words… are useless with you.
What do you make, Robin-chan?
Franky-kun!
Take down the third car!
Why make?
TO FLEE!
To flee?
Do Oi, what you want to say?
Dispatches too! Ca will be played in one moment.
Do not let Franky escape!
Yes.
** TECHNICAL ** Sogeking Smoke Star!
What a stupid gesture!
I have Nico Robin!
Wait…
Let me leave!
Yosha!
One bars oneself!
SPLASHES!!!
Note:Kaeru = frog or verb “to return”, from where ambiguity.
Oi, it says that one returns.
REALLY? It IS WELL!
Well, one must prepare to make half-turn.
OUAIS.
HEIN?!!
Why?! At the point where one is!
And for Robin? And Usopp? What will one make?
What will one make? What will one make?
Hm? It is the hour to puff out?
Does this idiot, of what it think?
DOES MUGIWARA, WHY ONE HAVE TO RETURN?
Mugiwara-san!
It is true that! Say to us why!
BUT NOT!!
Hein?
THIS FROG…
WITH CHANGE ON…
RAILS!!
Yokozuna!
He?
It is what this giant frog?
Pay to! Release from there, frog!
One will strike you!
One succeeded! Robin was recovered!
Which surprise, being able to make a plan of escape so quickly.
One écran de fumée is so useless usually that I would not have thought of it.
Against this kind of guy…
Most important is succeedto have succeeded
our mission without of having had to fight…
But…
I do not know if that will be so simple.
Ouais, until coaches
are completely moved away, remain careful.
What?
A whip with points?
I have them, Blueno.
Well.
They want to cross?
They draw us towards them!!
Which force…
Écran de fumée was really useless…
I suspected that would not go…
Do not kill anybody of the crew of Mugiwara!
We have a market.
Sogeking.
Yes?
Protect Robin-chan with the danger from your life!
Hein? … Yes!
You will owe us…
let leave!
Why it is so hard?
I had said to you that they had odd techniques!
** TECHNICAL ** Crushes!
A rather powerful kick…
It almost broke its Tekkai.
Blueno, does not underestimate it.
It does not have a premium, but it is one
the their strongest combatants.
You just come from you to give of it an account, band of dumbs?
R- R-Robin, Have-HAVE-HAVe-Await!
Qu-Qu'est-ce-que you
** TECHNICAL ** Ocho Fleur!
** TECHNICAL ** Clutch!
Length-conk!
P-Pourquoi, Robin-chan?
Combiens of time should I say it to you?
Leave me quiet!
It is…
Do Eho, where you look at?
Twisted eyebrows!
Bong blood, you then. Ones like the others…
Why are you if limited when they are your comrades?
This is not there…
a single chance to escape to you?!
Franky!
What you interfere yourself…
You sought it!
And initially why do you help these guy?
I cannot remain to look at a team if welded to be separate their dreams.
I wonder who you speak…
Ow! The guy, you of made not for me! I have a plan!
Once you will be with Straw hat, clear up you for turn over downtown!
Franky!
Wait!
I do not seek to flee!
Wait, Robin-chan…
Why you continuous say that?
We had just saved with full knowledge of the facts.
We will find something
for Buster Cal of the government,
thus Robin-chan you do not have any more any reason to want to remain with them!
Buster Cal…
is precisely the problem.