One Piece Treasure Sweepstakes! The first letter is... this!
The way to win will be explained at the end of the show!
I won't let any of you pass through this door!
The men of the Franky Family were trying to open the way, having to pass by the two giant gatekeepers who suddently appeared at the Main Island Gate, Oimo and Kaashii.
Timber Hitch Tug
Paulie and Zambai reversed the situation and were about to succeed in forcing the gate open.
On the other side, Luffy who already passed the Main Island Front Gate was unavoidably facing retardement from the enourmous amount of military force there.
Five people? You mistook it for only five people?
Geez, can't you even report properly?
Five hundred people...
Lucci's party was taking Franky and Robin in the Judiciary tower where Spandam was waiting.
It's great you returned!
Lucci
Kaku
Blueno
Kalifa
It's sexual harassment.
Just because I said your name?
You guys did a really good job on your five years mission.
That's right! It's not like a reward for this job but I have something to give you.
Mah, we'll put that aside from now.
For now, let me meet with them.
With the whole world's hope.
And the Straw Hat's party boarding the Rocketman was making its preparations to break in.
Guys, the time has come!
It's getting late, how about we go?
Samurai-man! I leave that barrier to you!
I'll take care of it.
Hurry up and enter!
You too!
Chapapa... PA!
This couldn't make me happier!
Good job on surviving that incident eight years ago,
Cutty Flam.
And the woman the whole world considers a threat,
Nico Robin.
Open the escape road!
The Rocketman flying through the sky!
I feel great!
It's too bad, the people of the world may still not know at what point our achievements today were glorious.
As a matter of fact, it may still take a couple of years until those events are known.
If you ask me, the justice of those old men is still too soft!
You can't achieve your goals without any sacrifice!
We are working the best we can to atteint peace for all humanity
It's okay to kill those fools who hinder our work, as sacrifices for the grand peace.
Everyone should just give us what we demand obediently, you giant...
As outlaws for the Justice, it's evident they should be killed!
Evident, evident!
I'm getting pissed off! Tom-san threw his life away to protect the plans!
Because idiots like you exist!
What are you doing!? Help me guys!
Kumadori!
Yoyoi!
What are you saying?
Hurry to save me, oi!
Saa, saa, saa!
Yoi!
Sorry...! No need to thank me, chief Spandam.
Gomu gomu no gatling gun
Gomu gomu no muchi (whip)
oogama (giant sickle)
kane (bell)
tonkachi (hammer)
bazooka
Gomu gomu no stamp
Message from the Main Island to the chief! Chief Spandam? I request an answer!
It's no good, it's not getting through...!
Maybe isn't the reciever connected again?
Again?
Geez, at such an important time too..!
Hey, where did Straw Hat disappear to?
Just under you!
Eh? Under?
Attack all at once!
He's down there!
Shit, got cornered!
Gomu gomu no kazan (volcano)
The wall is... The wall is falling!
Run away!
Gomu gomu no
gatling gun
It's dangerous!
Chief Spandam, I request an answer! Give us your orders, Straw Hat Luffy won't stop!
Straw Hat Luffy is heading toward the courthouse!
Harden our defences, hurry!
Shut up!
What's this fuss all about?
I just woke up!
Judge!
Enies Lobby's presiding judge:
3 headed Baskerville
Right! No need to hide it, I am Enies Lobby's presiding judge!
I am the one who writes with the left hand, Left-Baskerville!
I am the one who writes with the right hand, Right-Baskerville!
And me in the center, I'm Center-Freeway!
Why's that!?
J-Judge! There is a pirate alone making a mess in the Main Island.
It seems we can't get in touch with Chief Spandam. Please take commandment in his place!
A pirate, huh? A pirate is guilty!
Stop saying such things, let him be innocent!
Then I'll take the neutral part.
DEATH SENTENCE!
Why's that!?
We are in trouble! Judge! We had a report from the Main Island Gate that Kaashi was down because of the Straw Hat's nakamas and that Oimo won't last long too!
What? The Gate musn't be breached!
Order 100 Houbantais to rush to the Main Island!
Shit! The promised 5 minutes is over!
This is bad... Hurry up and open the way for the Rocketman!
I won't let you get to this gate!
We opened the gate's lock!
You just need to push it so it opens!
Shit!
Yosh, well done! Let's go!
Don't touch that door!
Rope Action
Top Knot
There!
Awesome! As expected from a Galley-La foreman!
What are you trying with such a rope...?
Franky Familly, pull!
Leave it to us! Let's go, Sodome and Gommorha! Seize the rope!
Let's charge in this way!
W-wait a sec! I'm getting dizzy...!
Push the gate!
The door is...!
The door is opening!
What about Oimo!?
Just a little more...
We breached the gate!
Oi, oi!
Oi...
The... The seatrain?
What is this about?
What!? It's charging directly at us!
No way! It can't pass the fence!
Hurry up! We must stop them!
Close the door!
Oi, baa-san
Ah, what is it?
Changement in the plan! Give me as much speed as you can!
Roger!
Guys, seems like there's a modification in our plan. Samurai-man is telling you to hold firmly onto something in the car.
So he said!
To hold firmly onto something?
Why?
Hey, stupid swordman! Did something happen?
The Main Gate was closed.
What did you say!?
This is bad, we'll really crush in there!
What do we do? What do we do? WHAT DO WE DO!?
We can't dodge it! We'll get killed!
It's unnecessary to worry. There's a way.
As expected from Zoro!
Break that fence down, frog!
Don't tell me...! We'll run over the fence this way!
THAT CAN'T BE TRUE!
The Seatrain...
...is flying!
We'll die!
Are we going to die?
Nami-san! Hurry to get in my chest!
Don't you think I have enough problems like this, idiot!?
Zoro! You must be thinking about a plan, right!?
Leave it...
To luck.
Leave it to luck!?
Ahh! Oimo was defeated!
Y-you guys are.. From the Straw Hat crew?
THAT'S RIGHT!
Is that so!?
That kind of thing doesn't matter at all.
We must hurry to advance further in.
All right! Guys! All we need to do now is to advance as far as we can!
Yeah!
Paulie!
Shit!
Who are you?
We are Enies Lobby first class guards, the Hou no Banken Butai also shortened as Houbantai!
Under Judge Baskerville's orders, we'll have you go through death punishment!
Shit! They keep coming one after the other, hindering us!
Oimo! What are you doing, allowing such pirates to pass through the gate! What's happening with you?
Ouch!
I passed out...
Damn! He is back on his feets!
I won't forgive you... I will absolutly not forgive you!
What... The Rocketman just... from the sky!
We didn't even need to open the gates!
W-What happened!?
Are they okay after such a landing?
They aren't coming out...
Oi, what's wrong!?
What are those two!?
Ah... Should we have greeted them first?
Don't be absurd. As if we'd need to.
It's Roronoa and the others!
We were waiting!
It went as I ordered...
For real?
Gomu gomu no storm
He went there!
Shit! Don't let him escape!
Wait!
We finally cornered you!
You don't have anywhere to run now!
All of you...!
DON'T GET IN MY WAY!
Why are there so many enemies out there!?
Isn't it a good thing? It'll let us get some exercise too!
Next time, One Piece: Catch up with Luffy, the Straw Hats all-out war.
I'll become the pirate king!
Here's the way to get your present!
Write the four letters that appeared in the show, your adress, your full name, your age, your opinion on the show and you may win a lot prices !
The last keyword is... this !