Wealth, Fame, Power.
The man who had acquired everything in this
world, the Pirate King, Gold Roger.
The final words that were said at his execution sent people to the seas.
My wealth and treasures?
If you want it, I'll let you have it.
Look for it, I left it all in that place.
Men now, chasing their dreams, head towards the Grand Line.
The world enters the Great Age of Pirates!
Robin!
We'll save you no matter what!
The bridge is being lowered!
Robin, it must have been hard for you.
But you're not alone anymore.
You have us now!
There's no way Nami would kill Usopp!
We're nakama!
Who did you say your nakama is, Luffy?
Nami.
What did you come here for?
What are you saying?
You're my nakama, right?
I came to get you.
A complete nuisance.
Nami?
Nakama...
Don't make me laugh.
Isn't that just a pathetic group of helpless morons?
You really trashed this place.
Nami, what's wrong?
Nothing, I just came to take a break.
I don't know if I could take it if you broke the furniture every time you came to take a break.
If it was nothing, would you be looking at that treasure map?
Something happened that pissed me off, that's all.
Those guys, huh? Who are they anyway?
You met them?
Yeah, some guy who called himself captain.
Seemed like he was lying though.
I heard you were laughing and having a great time while you were traveling with them.
But I haven't seen you happy like that in years.
Talk to me. Who exactly are those guys?
Didn't you promise you could talk to me about anything?
I had intended...
...to totally forget about those guys.
I thought I had erased them from my heart.
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU THINK OF YOUR NAKAMA!?
If it was possible, I wanted to stay with them forever...
I seriously thought that.
I see.
No wonder you had a fit.
For this girl to actually have someone come for her...
Nakama, huh?
To her,
that's the most...
...painful word.
What's wrong little girl?
Do you want me to return that village back to you that bad?
Then how about this? Why don't we make a deal?
A deal?
That's right...
If you can bring $100,000,000 to me,
then I'll set you and your village free.
Really?
Of course!
I would never break an agreement over money, even if I'd die.
I don't care how many years it takes, I'll keep my promise.
I'm definitely going to save up $100,000,000.
ARLONG!
Yo, what's wrong, my most prized map surveyor?
What's with that look on your face?
The Marines you sent took all of my money!
Didn't you say you'd never break a promise over money, even if you die?
DIDN'T YOU!? WHY!?
When did I ever break our promise?
Don't play innocent! You made a deal with those Marines-!
Tell me.
Damn it!
Damn it! Damn it!
So, all your money was taken, right?
That was really unfortunate, wasn't it?
But, a promise is a promise!
Unless you bring $100,000,000 in front of my eyes,
I won't release the village.
You scum!
It's only $100,000,000!
All you have to do is start saving again!
Or would you rather escape from here?
However, if you escape, I'll kill everyone in Kokoyashi Village.
Nami, we all pretended not to know.
So when you ever wanted to escape from Arlong...
...our expectations wouldn't get in your way.
This is it!
Take your weapons! We're going to fight!
We already swore once not to throw away our lives!
No matter how bitter and degrading their abuse was,
as long as Nami was okay, we would continue to fight this battle of endurance!
But this is their answer!
Now that we've lost our only key to freedom, we have no hope to live for!
Furthermore!
We can't forgive those mermen for taking advantage of Nami's kindness!
Any objections!?
Of course not! Let's go!
Wait! Everyone!
Nami.
Just a little bit...
Can you wait just a little bit longer?
I'm gonna work really hard,
and save up the money again.
It's easier this time.
I'm used to it now!
It's okay, there's nothing to worry about.
This is nothing compared to that other time...
I don't want anymore people to die!
Everybody! I'm okay.
I'm fine so...
That's enough, you know it's useless.
You fought enough by yourself with our lives on your back.
For you, being a part of their group
must have been more painful than being stabbed.
You fought well.
Gen-san...
Now keep going and leave this village from here.
Gen-san!
Do as he says, Nami.
But...!
Na-chan...
Nami...
You have street smarts, and also your dreams.
Nojiko! Everyone!
I won't let you go!
Stop it everyone!
I don't wanna see anymore people getting hurt by them!
You're gonna die!
We know.
It's useless. We've already decided with our hearts.
GET OUT OF THE WAY, NAMI!!
Let's go, everyone!
Even if we can't win, we'll show them our pride!
Arlong!
Arlong! Arlong!
Arlong! Arlong! Arlong!
Arl...
Luffy...
What?
You don't even know anything.
You don't know what this island has been through in the last eight years.
Yeah, I don't know.
This has nothing to do with you, so...
I told you to leave this island!
Yeah, you told me.
Get out of here!
You... Just get out of here! Get out! Get out!
Get out of here...
Get out of here!!
Luffy...
Help me!
OF COURSE I WILL!!!
Don't touch my treasure!
Luffy...
Let's go!
Yeah!
What the...!?
Which one of you is Arlong?
There's no escaping now.
This is the top floor of Arlong Park.
What's up with this room?
Nothing but paper.
It's not just ordinary paper.
This room is for that woman to continue drawing me maps of the sea.
The cartography room...
Nami's room?
These are all...
...maps of the sea that Nami drew.
That woman is going to continue drawing sea maps.
All to fulfill my ambitions!
Then, when I have all the sea maps of the world,
we mermen will become invincible, and the whole world will be my empire!
The foothold of all of this is this island,
and East Blue as well.
Do you really think you could...
...use that woman so efficiently!?
USE!?
What's that!?
A desk?
What the hell are you doing!?
What the hell's going on?
What's with all that stuff flying out?
Stop it!!
The sea maps!
My sea maps!
It must be one hell of an intense battle.
Yeah, must be a fight to the death.
No doubt about it.
Thank you.
You've gone too far shitty rubber.
I don't know how great mermen are,
or about your sea maps,
or what's been going on here.
But now I finally know how to save her!
It's because this room exists.
A place she doesn't even want to be...
I'm going to destroy it all!
Gomu Gomu no Axe!
It's gonna collapse!
Run! Everybody hurry and run!
Nami-aneki! Hurry!
But Luffy's still in there!
Aneki!
Luffy! Luffy is..!
LUFFY!!
Luffy...
Who won?
After collapsing like that...
Could he...?
Luffy...
Luffy!
ANIKI~!!
Is he alright?
NAMI!!
YOU ARE MY NAKAMA!!
Back then, I was saved by my nakama.
This time, I'm going to fight for my nakama.
So Robin, believe in us...
Believe in Luffy!
Luffy will be sure to answer you.
Oi, you pirates! What are you lingering around for?
What's the meaning of that smile?
HERE WE GO!!
Robin used to always be alone,
just like I used to be.
But we all met and became nakama.
You're no longer alone, Robin-chan.
That's right, Luffy and we are all with you now.
We won't let anyone else be a victim.
Wait for us, Robin!
We'll save you no matter what!
Next time, One Piece: A Farewell Improves a Man!
Sanji and Chopper.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!