If you are ready to die, then follow me.
I will lend to you…
Umi Ressha!
Here it is!
It was baptized Rocket Man.
It cannot transport passengers.
Rocket Man!
It with the fast air!
Take it.
I prepared it.
Water and coal are charged,
the vapor is pressurizing itself.
Did Ossan, you prepare it for us?
You will celebrate that only on your return.
This Rocket Man, it does not matter how
it is regulated, his speed remains unverifiable.
It is a missed prototype going back to before Puffing Tom.
I cannot guarantee your safety.
Ah! Thank you, Ice-Ossan!
STRAW HAT!
Please…
TAKE US ALONG WITH YOU!
Franky-Aniki is taken along over there by the government,
one wants to continue them…
but one cannot pass Aqua Laguna all alone!
Pity!
We want to save Aniki!
Go up.
In speed!
Straw hat…
AFFLICTED!
You will be revaudra that!
Prepare you to leave!
Now, dear pirates…
Take care not to fall from the train!
We leave Water Seven, in direction
of Enies Lobby, on board Umi Ressha…
Rocket Man!
Yosh! Departure!
It left!
Everyone is brought back!
LET US HELP OUR FRIENDS!
MUTUAL OATH ENEMIES!
One can really leave from here?
They are the sewers!
Is Luffy, all well?
Water returned to me in the nose…
What you insane up there too?!
Would be careful!
I was well afraid.
But that becomes interesting!
Oï-oï! Granny head of shark!
One is going down!
The exit is close.
One directly will be propelled outside!
Yosh! Umi Ressha is there!
Go the guy! One moves from there!
Jump! Sodome, Gomorrhe!
It is what that?
Straw hat!
All the members of Franky Family are with your service!
Lance-harpoon! Fire!
Brilliant!
It is of King bulldozers of higher class!
Too much cool!
Brothel, which load of cretins…
SPECIES OF SHINGLE!!
Count on us!
Which sympathetic nerve skewer of damaged.
Is He, Granny Head of Shark, it that maximum speed?
It is not fast finally…
Would be patient. You will see when one will be on the rails…
Rails?
I see some nowhere…
They had to derive a little.
No problem, I supervised it
Umi Ressha since its whole beginning.
Do not underestimate me!
It left!
Urgent message of the pulpit!
Once we will be on the rails,
our speed will increase considerably.
You stud well,
and you will be only slightly wounded!
Thus one will be wounded no matter what it arrives…
Missed Zut……
But… it is not finished yet!
Go! Do what I say to you!
Almost, Granny, almost! A little more towards the line!
Look at well!
Now I go…
Chimney! Gonbe!
You followed us?!
Eh yes!
What a catastrophe!
Quickly return to put to you at the shelter!
You will be made carry!
All is well granny!
Chimney!
I will fall!
Hold good!
I will fly away!
Have-await a little!
I stop all!
I had forgotten!
There are no brakes on that one it is true!
What? Oh that with the funny air!
It is Nii-chan with the Straw hat! Oooï!
Straw hat, brings back them quickly inside!
You will be projected in the air if the train enraille!
Of agreement!
Yatta! They were put on the rails!
Really? It is my turn. Let me see!
It is true… I-see-I-see-I-see…
One did not expect from it less Kokoro-san.
It is completely incredible.
Indeed. During one moment,
I was not badly anxious nevertheless.
Indeed, indeed! It is right!
That must be difficult enrailler
with similar waves.
I am of agreement!
Indeed, indeed… It is right.
Indeed, indeed, indeed…
Oui-oui-oui-oui… It was well played indeed…
Played well, indeed… yes…
In effect!
We should inform Iceberg-san of it…
Yes, it is right…
It must worry about their fate.
Oui-oui-oui, it is that, yes…
Jan!
Ken!
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Worry you, I am sure that it is well.
Even when it was made press
by Umi Ressha, it knew to be raised.
You heard ace?
It appears that the violent one apprentice of Tom,
Cutty Flam, died.
It was made reverse by Umi Ressha.
Iceberg.
You can arrive there
You are the first disciple of Tom,
the largest naval engineer in the world.
You can arrive there.
You… can…
Kokoro-san, one will drink glass one day.
It will be pleasant.
Tom-san…
Look at me.
I will perpetuate your dream.
I will protect it.
Entire.
This city…
And these plan!
- 4 years with paravant -
Iceberg-san, you have a visitor.
He is called Cutty Flam, and claims to know you.
Do I have to let it enter?
Not.
Renew the outside.
You ace a strange way of accommodating people.
Nmaa… And you, what arrived at your body?
Your mouth!
My body useless, I due was thus modified
with ends of scrap to survive!
And one of fout of that!
Apparently, you ace agreed to build
ships for the government!
I will never forgive myself to have helped the government!
They took Tom-san and…
The weapons which started all that…
Who built them?!
You do not have any right to reproach me anything!
Will not imagine you that I forgave you after 4 years!
How oses you to return here after what occurred?!
What?!
I thought that you had died.
It is what the government said to us.
Even if Tom-san forgave you…
I do not intend to do as much of it.
O… Oï! It is what that?!
It is the plan of the old weapon which it had shown us?!
From now on, you should not be made any more call “Cutty Flam”.
The government was not
able to take it in Tom-san.
It is only one matter of time
before it is caught some with me.
Take it and leaves this island, Franky.
To leave the island?
Cutty Flam of Tom' S Workers died.
If you exchanges of name, it will not have there
more bond between you and me.
Moreover, if you free the island,
any trace of the plan will disappear.
Wait one minute! What will it occur if they come to find you, and that you do not have the plans?
It is all that I had to say.
Oï! Iceberg!
One will not undoubtedly be re-examined more.
Oï! Wait!
Do you want to know the same fate as Tom-san?
Take the plan.
Keep it and if that becomes too dangerous,
you will have to only give them!
Or if you ace not desire for keeping it, burns it.
If you had to choose, that would you make?
Tom-san was a hero.
He sacrificed his own life to protect this plan.
As long as there will be a risk to see
Nico Robin to awake the old weapon…
one will need them like forces countermeasure.
Even if I keep them with me, I would prefer
to die to give it to the government!
Be sure for you of you?
I could build this trick if I wanted.
You ace really confidence in me?
The fact that I entrusted them to you
doesn't he answer your question?
One will never change, not truth?
One engueule always when one sees oneself.
And I will never forgive myself, even after that.
And you will probably never forgive me but…
Franky…
Dumb…
I am…
really content that you would be alive!
Wait, Bakaberg!
I will not leave this island!
I will make as I hear it!
I will never take your advice,
even if I must die about it!
Never!
Species of Bakanky!
Dumb, why you do not want to include/understand?!
It is to protect the plan!
Your mouth! Be the only one to you not to include/understand!
I will not leave, not bars!
Why I think of him in one similar moment?
And this cretin…
Is iceberg in life?
We killed it.
I believed that I was going to die…
Obviously that you will die!
I had said you well that you would be made carry.
It was an acceleration of nutcase!
I really was afraid.
I was done badly with the back…
Wait one minute.
There is several guy suspects here.
What? Who that?
They IS YOU WHOM ONE SPEAKS!
AND OF YOU TOO!
I decided to come with you.
One did not can stop you in spite of
all the evil which one gave oneself.
The types which hold your
friend who is so expensive to you…
are also those which tried to assassinate Iceberg-san.
I have many things to say to these people!
PAULEE! ONE WILL NOT LEAVE YOU
NOT TO AMUSE You ALL ALONE!
ONE THOUGHT OF FINDING THE ATTACKERS
ICEBERG-SAN IF YOU WERE FOLLOWED…
THEN ONE IS CUSHY JOBS
IN THE COACH COAL HAS!
And here… it is like that.
We saw just.
We will also join the combat.
And of course, our enemies have
also removed Franky-Aniki.
It is true! And one knows even exactly who they are!
He, galériens! If it arrives some
thing in our Aniki, you will pay it to us!
Silence! That which suffers more is Iceberg-san!
BUT ABOUT WHAT YOU SPEAK AT THE END?!
PAULEE!
EXPLAIN us! THAT IS PASSES
Do Ouais, Paulee, you know guilty truths, not truth?
One wants to hear it your own mouth.
One is not if idiots.
There were already suspicions…
One will not be surprised.
Well, you had surely included/understood it
when they disappeared from a blow without reason.
Then, I will say it frankly to you.
These types with the masks were…
Lucci, Kaku, Kalifa and Blueno the barman.
They tried to kill Iceberg-san.
It IS NOW THAT YOU STRIKE?!!
But you had said that they had returned on their premises!
HOW If THEY HAD THAT has FOUTRE!!
It was thought that it was Michael and Hoikel of the low city.
OUAIS OUAIS.
BUT It IS WHICH THESE?!
Q-what?! You do not know them?!
They are really famous in the low city.
OUAIS OUAIS.
AND HOW I COULD THE KNOWLEDGE?!
Yosh! I fix
Lastly, my stomach is full…
Well, then…
With Franky Family and the engineers of Galley it…
there were not badly problems downtown.
But from now on, we have common enemies.
Most extremely of them,
it is without any doubt the guy with the pigeon!
And it is me which will massacre it!
It is true. It is a combat to recover
four people that they removed us.
One will not stop so much
that they will not have been caught up with.
Granny! Granny! It is Aqua Laguna!
Oh? It is already there.
Chimney, lets see me!
They is bad! Kokoro-san, would not owe you
not to be in the pulpit?
One must absolutely pass this giant wave!
I already said it to you, Rocket Man is unverifiable.
My job was right to put the train on the rails.
Neither the direction nor the brakes function.
It is for that this train always runs at bottom.
Nobody any more can stop it now.
I do not believe in it…
Luffy! If that continues, the train
will crash to pieces itself against these waves…
He, Luffy!
Now that we all go the same direction…
there is no reason but one fights separately.
Well…
Listen, we are allied!
In Umi Ressha left in front of,
there is already a member of my crew!
Our force will be larger still!
The guy!
One will not let a large wave stop us!
One all will achieve our goal!
It LEFT!!