Did Naaa, you want to speak to me, pirate young person?
I came to know the truth!
Last night, I saw Nico Robin of my own eyes.
And it is a member of your crew. Here is the truth.
It was really Robin?!
Keep silent yourself.
You do not inspire any more confidence to me.
If I made you call, it is because I have a thing to ask you.
Let meet Nico Robin once again to me.
Breaking news!
The culprits in the attack of Iceberg-san are the crew of Straw hat!
Soon in the Mizu-Mizu newspaper, the accounts of eyewitnesses!
I repeat.
Let meet Nico Robin to me.
It is impossible.
We do not know where Robin is.
A shot!
Ca comes from the room!
Iceberg-san!
You… You are well?
Yes.
I believed capacity to bring me closer to the truth.
Stop all the members of the crew.
With your orders!
He, Luffy.
You spoke with Iceberg-san?
Ouais. He said that he had really seen Robin.
Impossible. Why would Robin have done that?
I do not believe a mot. of them.
Eternal good-byes?
Nico Robin, the woman vêtue of black
One arrived! Hurry, Kokoro grandmother!
Calm yourself.
Toilets 7, that made a lease.
Grandmother, hurries! Quickly!
Ouais, ouais.
Passengers of the train of the sea. The wearing of mask is prohibited.
Passenger, show your face please.
But it is my face.
He you.
Kokoro-san, which surprise.
It is what all this agitation?
Yes. We seek the crew of Straw hat, those which tried to assassinate Iceberg-san.
Assassins of Iceberg-san…
It is what?
These people-there…
One falls! One falls! One falls!
Yosh! One is there.
I am burst, me.
You SICK ES! I BELIEVED AI THAT I WAS GOING TO DIE!
There were not the choice.
You have say that one would be made take if the elevator were used!
But it was not the sorrow to jump in the vacuum! Do not be to you the engineer with the square nose!
Sorry die……
Good, that goes, since one is there.
IF They IS GOOD, DOES NOT STRIKE ME!
But that is spoiled.
Is Ca spoiled? About what you do speak?
Topography and climate of this island.
If the wind is so strong, and if the pressure of the air falls quickly…
A hurricane could appear this evening.
It is the “City of Water”…
If one thinks of it, the floods are a weak point.
What wants to say?
And well, that worries me, then one will see later.
At all events, let us turn over to the inn.
Ah, welcome.
How you are, Blueno?!
Fishing?!
I believe that is rather well.
Why “I believe”? Do not be clear for you like guy.
As usual. The full one please.
You have money?
Dispatch, filled to me that of cola!
How can you make turn this bar if you requests constantly of the money to your customers?!
We have money.
There remains to us a million our purchases of yesterday.
WHAT?!
It remains so much of money since yesterday?!
What a shame! Ca fears!
I kept this money with me lasting all during the night!
Give me that!
Dear customers, it is your day of chance!
It is me which levels!
Drink as much as you will want!
Played well, Franky!
What a generosity!
Ouais, the hidden side of Toilets 7, thank you with you!
Whoa! Cool!
Oi, I want me too!
Are Oi, Blueno, where the cola?
Gone, hurries!
I see that the businesses go well for you, Franky.
The Kokoro old woman! You were there!?
I had believed to see a statue of monster.
Can He, I still have fruit juice, Franky?
One is in a bar here, not with the crib.
Are the businesses well, not truth?
Good, make as you want.
Youpi! Juice!
In fact, the businesses go well, but I am of very bad mood.
This week was the worst of my life…
Because of this stupid pirate!
And here, the full one.
Not too early.
The full one, the full one, the full one, the full one…
Go! Go! Go!
BRILLIANT!
I live again!
Dumb, until I wait you tankard!
By the way, the old woman, what you insane there?
Aqua Laguna arrives.
Did Ah ouais? Not astonishing whereas wind either so extremely.
Did you finish the preparations for your house?
Nan, I do not have any more a house, then I do not have anything which can run.
I would have liked to drink glass with Iceberg, but it appears that it was made flinguer.
Ouais, it appears.
They then say that they would be the pirates, Galley it and the craftsmen are insane of rage.
Did a pirate do that?
You believe in it, you?
That you know something, you would be said.
Spit the piece, the old woman!
Is iceberg constantly badgered by the government, not true?
Then you claim that it is Kogi, the representative, who made the blow?
This large bacon does not have the fabric of a killer.
Not, the underground operations are assigned to the CP9.
You knew it, Blueno?
It is only one rumor.
If that pleases to you to accept the rumors on this secret organization…
Imbecile, they exist.
But they are never shown.
It is a secret brigade which operates in the shade.
Does Ca want to say what all that? You know something?
I heard it over there…
It IS THAT a WHORE OF RUMOR! STOP YOUR CONNERI…
Everyone is afraid because this rumor exists for a long time.
They eliminate people without leaving the least trace.
If you find yourself implied, you will leave your life there.
Impressing! The mission of yesterday proceeded perfectly.
Good work, Nico Robin.
No difficulty.
Obviously, you are now required in all the city.
Yes.
But it is only temporary.
Most important, it is this evening.
You will enter again to Iceberg.
In the event of pip, it is not serious but erases all the evidence.
Of all the apprentices of Tom who could have it in their possession…
Only still in life is Iceberg.
It does not matter how you reach that point…
In the name of the CP9, we will take it to him this evening.
Remember that this mission is for the good of justice.
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
Because of the imminent arrival of Aqua Laguna…
We inform you that all the docks of the shipyard will be used as refuges.
In order to limit agitations, we ask you as fast as possible to shelter.
However, the dock n°1 is in bad condition…
Yosh, I will install barricade.
You did not forget anything?
Not, they is good. Let us leave quickly to the refuge the shipyard.
Dad, quickly, quickly!
Quickly, quickly!
A little patience. I must do that properly.
If water infiltrates, all will be foutu.
Oi, attaches that one too.
Oi, the wind rises more and more!
You prepare, the waves start to be formed!
And made attention, the pirates also will come!
Balls.
By where did it go?
It left by there.
It is inevitably in the corner!
Yosh, let us seek by over there.
Of agreement.
It is what this brothel?
Why they drive out me?
I include/understand anything.
It is for that I am required?
One of the assassins?
Then I cannot turn over any more to the inn.
Who is there?!
Here! There is a suspect guy!
You are sure, Mister?
Yes, they rented a room last night.
They were still there it does not have there very a long time…
In this inn?
Yes, they left full with luggage in their room, they surely will return.
Yosh! You, remain here.
The others, come with me to seek in the surroundings.
Excavate in the least recesses!
Oi, it has nobody there here.
You are sure that it is this boat?
Some! Look at, it is the standard of Straw hat.
They probably gave up it.
It is in bad condition.
Then, they are there?
Not, that flagstone.
It is so worn…
That it certainly will run.
Let us seek elsewhere.
It is which these guys?
What does it occur downtown?
They are there?
Not.
Are whore, but where?
He, Luffy.
What is there, Nami?
You believe that the others are well?
The city is attacked by the craftsmen.
Chopper and Sanji-kun were not discovered yet, then that must be good for them.
At all events, we dispatch!
The train of the sea is except service.
The train of midday already left…
But another share this evening, in spite of this foul weather.
In direction of Enies Lobby at 11 p.m.
The train of the sea is hefty man.
Oi, not of news of the pirates?!
Nothing by here!
If one manages to capture one of the three, the others will be easily identifiable.
We dispatch, before the waves do not arrive!
Did Robin perhaps travel by the train of the sea?
In this case, one will have evil to find it.
One already did not succeed in finding it in Water 7…
I perhaps opposed it with the bookstore.
Baka, it has no reason there that it is that.
He, you! Would you have seen a splendid woman like this one?
Ah, it? It twenty years old less, isn't this was?
If somebody finds it, the newspaper will immediately inform Galley it.
It is an assassin…
In any event…
It is very well to seek the criminals…
But you would make better find a shelter quickly.
You will make you carry by Aqua Laguna
With more.
The situation does not improve.
Luffy and the others are well?
Luffy is well. I worry more for Nami-san.
Everyone left in one anything time.
The wind is more and more extremely too.
Everyone was put at the shelter.
Whore. Oi, Robin-chan! Passed to you where?!
This odor… But it is…
Chopper, That is there?
Chopper?!
Oi, wait a little!
It is not far.
Oi, I said to you to wait! What it arrives to you?!
It is there.
Oi, Chopper! Chopper!
Oi, that goes?!
Is Chopper, how that?
You hurt yourself?
Do not do anything.
What is there?
You start to run of a blow and… and…
I was sure. It is there.
Robin!
Robin-chan!
Where you stays last?! You everywhere were sought!
Everyone worried.
Good, let us return to the inn now.
In more one had full with concern. One will explain you after…
But you cannot join us.
Wait! I come to seek you!
Not, they is good. Remain where you are.
Because I did not come to join you.
They is here that our ways separate, in this city.
What do you tell, Robin-chan?
I see, it is in connection with the newspaper, it is that?
You do not have with you to make some for that!
One does not believe a word of it…
It is traditional, the pirates are always shown with twists.
Yes. I am sorry to have made you accuse in this horrible crime.
But the charges against me are true.
Last night, that which infiltrated in the mayor, it was…
Me, without any doubt.
Impossible.
I carry in me this “darkness” that none you knows.
This darkness will destroy you, one day.
All the organizations that Nico Robin could infiltrate all were destroyed.
Excluded it.
In the beginning, I am supposed to make you accuse then to flee.
The things will worsen for you.
What?! Why you would make a thing parei…
You do not need to know why.
Robin-chan! I do not include/understand anything so that you say!
That there is?!
Robin! Let us return together!
One all got along well, but from today…
We will not be re-examined any more.
Thank you to have been so nice with me until now.
Goodbye.
Wait…
Wait!
I cannot…
To accept that.
He…
WAIT!
Stop your conneries!
Wait, Robin-chan!
Robin-chan!
ROBIN!