Good, then…
Franky Family and engineers of Galley it…
There were the small different ones downtown,
but now, there is a common enemy.
Listen. We are allied!
One will be crushed!
ONE… ONE PASSED!!
Yo, Luffy!
Ah, Sanji!
How does that do without tone with dimensions? Where is Robin?
Robin-chan is always captive.
Nami-san put to me with the current
circumstances of our situation.
I see.
Ah, it is thus that.
Them foutre goes a beating.
Luffy, do not say anything!
Say to him to await us.
He, cook? You hear me?
There are dangerous types in this train…
That will go.
Zoro…
What would you have made?
When you known ace that Robin had lied and
that it had been let capture to save us…
Could you have remained without anything to make?
Useless to stop it.
Oï, Marimo-kun! You worry for me?!
In your dreams! Cretin!
But unfortunately…
When I learned the reasons from Robin-chan…
Even an order of the captain…
could not stop me!
I…
do not come.
That does not relate to me any more.
Moreover, if the world government is against us…
I do not want to be implied, and…
Will Luffy and the others arrive, not truth?
I am sorry for Robin,
but me…
I am not obliged to go to save it!
I left the crew!
Hello.
Ah! I found them!
Ah, shit!
Who is there?!
Me was explained all the situation.
I believed to understand that you wish
to save an young woman.
I do not need another reason to help you.
Let to me fight with your with dimensions!
My name is…
Sogeking!
SOGEKING
TIREUR D'ÉLITE
ON the ISLAND OF the SNIPERS
I AI CONSIDERING the DAY
100 SUCCESSFUL SHOOTINGS, 100 BLOWS
LU LU LU ~
THAT IT IS the EYE Of a MOUSE
LOCKED TARGET!!
OR YOUR HEART
VIS-A-VIS THE MAN WHO COMES FROM THE ISLAND OF THE SNIPERS
LU LU LU LU LU IT
YOU WOULD MAKE BETTER FLEE!
SOGEKING SOGE SOGE
SOGE KINGU
A MYSTERIOUS APPEARANCE!?
ITS NAME EAST SOGEKING!
But what it fout bong blood?
He well, leaves it in its is delirious.
I suppose that he thinks of not being able
to save his/her friend directly.
It has these ideas with the idiot.
Oï, is brought back!
Ah, yes.
Yosh, the mission of rescue
of Robin-chan can finally begin.
Dear Sirs, it is the first time that one
meets, do not have you any question?
First of all, you were in coach N. 6.
There thus remain still five about it.
Like, “Where the island of the snipers is?”
Robin-chan is inevitably in one of them.
The answer is, “In your hearts”.
Good, be to you hefty man?
I am super hefty man! Cretin!
And I am to it even more this week.
Our mission will end when us
will have recovered Robin-Chan…
But there is a good package of enemies.
One cannot sink lowered head, one would be
handicapped in these narrow cars.
It should be avoided the useless combat,
and to take strongest one by one.
Ouais, it is true.
It is a good way of apprehending the combat.
You are somebody of intelligent, Sanji-kun.
Consequently, I have a plan.
Listen attentively.
It… It is…
Superb…
Yosh! I am ready for the combat!
What does it arrive to you?
WHAT IT ARRIVES TO THEM, HAS YOUR OPINION?!
How you can change here, trailed?!
Pretty trail!
I did not have the choice! There is only one coach.
COVER YOUR BELLY! YOUR BELLY AND YOUR LEGS!
THAT APPLIES TO YOU ALSO THE PUBLIC GARDEN!
It IS BECAUSE OF PEOPLE LIKE YOU
HOW COMPANY SE DÉVERGONDE!
The farm, wedged!
Wedged!
SPECIES OF…
Perhaps what should I also change me?
PLEASE!
FOR the Love of god, MADE NOT THAT!
Which band of insolents.
Whore…
These black pants… it have pockets,
but why they are not larger?
Mets not of meat in your pockets!
You all seem very justified the young people.
I see that you are ready to leave.
Of course! We there will save Robin, after all!
This time, I all will massacre them!
Of course!?
If you are made beat once again,
I will not forgive myself it!
That will go. I have a good reason for
not to lose this time!
A reason?
Nami, you changed ace of weapon?
When the celestial islands were left…
Usopp used of Dials to make a better weapon of it.
Perfect Climate Tact!
I see, it is Usopp which…
Ouais, Usopp has…
Its posthumous work…
Stop depressing!
Loans? Ok, allons-y.
Of the intruders?
Yes. We received this report/ratio.
It is impossible to go up on board of
Puffing Tom once this one moving.
So intruding, there is…
they were to be on board from the beginning.
It is pathetic.
You are right. We are sorry…
But to leave the train moving is also impossible.
The intruders and the criminals are
still on board Umi Ressha.
Excavate all and find them.
Yes!
“Coach N. 7”
T-Bone captain.
It is impossible to hide in a so small coach.
Good evening!
THEY ARE!
They are behind the door!
They are three with the intruder!
They are in coach N. 7,
wedge them and capture them!
You donot can even use a hammer.
The farm!
Do not slacken your effort!
Open this door!
Hurry to nail it!
Received B-Bien.
Everyone by here! Criminals
are in coach N. 7.
They were there?!
Prevent also those of coach N. 3!
Wedge them and capture alive Franky!
They do not have nowhere where to go!
Capture them!
Oï! Move back!
They opened fire!
Magne, Soge!
I helps then!
Do not draw anywhere! They should not be killed!
Shit!
T-Bone captain!
You draw aside!
I hate the indirect combat.
CHOKKAKU SENKO
BONE SOWARU
CYB3RFR34K-ISO
I hate the indirect combat.
CHOKKAKU SENKO
BONE SOWARU
They left!
On the roof.
You dispatch, the enemy is in the last coach!
It is the moment, quickly!
That cannot be.
How everyone turns over in the preceding coach!
It is a trap!
A trap?!
What…
Made half-turn! It is a trap!
What?!
One cannot go back there, the door was closed!
Who did that?
The coach was detached!
WHAT?!
Shit!
It was them!
You will regret it!
It is too late.
Hello everyone.
Made attention with the monstres marins. And good voyage.
Good-bye.
Already two coaches in less, one reduced
the number of enemies from approximately fifty.
But, Sanji-kun,
Luffy with the Straw hat and the others
travel on the same rails, not?
Bah, they will manage.
B-band of refuse!
I will smash the door!
Ah, you us free already?
Go, more than five coaches.
Born do not think of drawing you like that!
How you could do that with the T-Bone Captain?!
He, bring back-that with the CP9!
There remain still the null ones here.
STRONG RIGHT!
Heavy weapons, DRAW!
It was touched!
That hurt.
Draw, car!
Why my balls do not do anything to him?!
O-Oï! What be to you?!
I am a cyborg.
Cyborg?!
Ouais. I have steel plates and
weapons integrated into my body.
When me above am drawn,
I have a little badly and it sometimes happens to me to bleed…
but that cannot kill me.
This kind of thing thus exists?
The world is vast.
Impressing!
AIIEE!!!
What you insane, dumb?!
A simple needle should not hurt you?
Be weak for you! You want me to dissect or what?
First of all, my back is different! Listen…
I had to modify me all alone…
thus my hands could not go behind!
Only half of front is cyborg!
As long as we are there,
let to me say another thing.
My belly is always cold. Do you know why?
I know anything of it.
Because in my belly,
there a refrigerator has to keep the Coke with the expenses.
Oh, it is impressive!
It is brilliant! For the days when the weather is hot!
It is not the moment to speak about that!
There are no more enemies in it
coach! Let us pass to the following!
It is with the turn of the fourth coach.
“Coach N. 4”
It is Wanze!
It is Wanze theinsane one!
Sift, it is Wanze!
Hello the guy!
You are hungry? I am Wanze.
It is the kitchen, I can do everything.
Ramen? Ok, I make you ramen!
But initially, I would like to teach you something.
The hairs of my nose have this provision,
they are like a strainer.
Do not forget it!
First of all, I put flour
in my mouth and I mix well.
Here! Good appetite!
One does not want any!!
Much time was lost.
Wanze, there is a person who awaits us.
We are pressed, go… hello.
Attendeeeez!!
If you want to cross this coach…
you will have initially to overcome me!
Would you try to stop us?
I will do it, sift!
If something arrives during the mission
of escort of this Umi Ressha, I am lààà!
If you want to save the criminal one,
try to beat my Ramen Kenpo.
Ra-Ramen Kenpo?!
“Ra-Ramen Kenpo?!”
Stop me imitating, dumb!
Do not answer its provocation, cretin!
It is until it waits!
Sifsaaa!
You like my weak imitations?
I said, do not answer!
Sift!!
Which energetic guy.
What? However the balls should have touched it…
That did not even make it react. What a coolness!
J-J' believed well that I was going to remain there…
You flippais?!
Stop making this mug with the idiot!
I undertake this clown!
Wait, wait!
Of the guy as you are too easy to cause…
that would be a waste of time.
I will undertake some quickly made well done.
That me fout nerves that a cretin
like you says itself to being a cook chief.
I SPEAK TO YOU, DUMB!!
It IS YOU WHO YIELDS TO the PROVOCATION!!
But looks at! It avoided the blow
of foot of Sanji so easily.
How does it make to have as much insurance?
I believed well that I was going to remain there!
THEN YOU FLIPPAIS?!
WOULD BE SERIOUS, BROTHEL!
At all events…
let to me take care some…
and go in the next coach.