Bong blood, you then. Ones like the others.
Why are you if limited
when they are your comrades?
This is not there…
A single chance to escape to you?!
Wait!
I do not seek to flee!
Wait, Robin-chan…
Why you continuous say that?
We had just saved with full knowledge of the facts.
We will find something
for Buster Call of the government,
thus Robin-chan, you do not have any more any reason
to want to remain with them!
Buster Call… is precisely the problem.
** TECHNICAL ** Rankyaku
Sanji!
It is what this type…
It left null leaves!!
They is not good… I must do something…
Stop!
Is Que'?
Let make!
He you, I am your H!
Left! When it has…
Where did it go? Where it is?!
The legal island!
The portrait of Enies Lobby!
Did Blueno disappear?
It did not disappear.
It is the capacity of its fruit of the demon.
With truth capacity of the fruit doa-doa, Air-Door,
It created a door in the atmosphere even.
It is impossible to escape to us.
To in no case.
Leave Robin…
… by!
** TECHNICAL ** Shigan
Usopp!
** TECHNICAL ** Tekkai
You did not hear me presently?
Your kicks are weak.
You are persistent…
Stop!
I do not hope to flee…
That should suffir you.
It is them which came to me.
I did not have the choice.
In this case let us leave from here immediately.
Wait!
All is well.
Robin…
All well will occur.
You…
we still hide something.
That does not have… not importance.
Only, one pirate…
cannot leave…
the crew without the agreement…
of the Captain.
Then…
you…
must believe in Luffy.
Wait, Robin-chan!
Useless.
Nico Robin will not romprera his promise.
Why you say that?
A long time ago, an island was destroyed.
This island, on which was launched Buster Call of the navy,
was entirely reduced in ash.
The only surviving one of then was…
a young girl still in low age:Nico Robin.
What do you say?
Five vice-admirals and ten men-of-war.
For this woman, who had to face this insurmountable power,
Buster Call represents a demon which it cannot flee.
This terror which it traumatize since its childhood…
… is now turned against his companions.
It lost the will to be opposed to us.
Me known as step… knowing all that…
It is obvious.
Bandage refuse…
Where your rot stops?!
It is for the good of justice!
I test a deep compassion for it.
Insane steps of me!
MAKE CHIEEER ~!
You!
Dépèche you and will sit you, Nico Robin.
We will arrive at Enies Lobby soon.
Wait one second! I wait said!
Is this reasonable? To leave these two there together…
I entrust them to you until one arrives.
Before that, which could occur?
They do not have any more the possibility of fleeing.
Soon, criminals vis-a-vis their death…
will not be able that to deplore their fate.
A liking…
One…
A frog!!
Y has of “Gero” which holds, idiotic!
Because of your surprised attack, one east left the rails!!
Release! Move! One will strike you!
Whereas one was on the point of
to catch up with Sanji and others!
Why you ace does that?!
Dumb, I will puff out you!!
What occurs at the end, with this Umi Ressha?
Is everyone well?
More or less…
My… My kidneys…
It is what this bins?
King bulldozers disappeared!!
They are there?
Not, it is we who disappeared.
One probably ran off the line.
It is still worse!!
What will one make?
It does not matter what one tries, one can nothing make!
Zoro?
You want to laugh, there?
Semi… Miracle!
And here.
Bong blood, crowned Yokozuna.
In here are in the manners.
Does Ca go?
Yes, about…
This dirty Yokozuna!
Good, it would be said that all is well.
You are well?
I hope that one can always reach Enies Lobby!
Close it a little!
Wait one second!
It is easy to say.
It would be said that one is taken in an odd current…
What this master key?
Kokoro-san?
You know the direction of the island?
Yes, Umi Resha contains Eternal Poses
from each island where there is a station.
Then all is well.
I will look at the ocean, I leave you with the operation!
You are…?
Me?
Navigatrice.
I see. It is promising.
But initially…
Yokozuna! Bring back yourself two minutes here!
It jumped!
How that you is content that I do not have anything! Good blood!
I was not kidnapped.
Do not draw from hasty conclusions!
Baa-chan speaks with Yokozuna
You made what the guy?
The frog of presently speaks with the old woman.
Then is the old woman a frog?
It is true that it resembles more one frog than with human…
When that is finished it will knock you…
It is clear.
Mugiwara-san! Rocket Man!
You find them?
Not, nowhere.
Shit. This large frog…
Where did it send Straw hat and the others?
The guy!! It is not the moment for that!!
One took the sea to go to save Franky-aniki!
It is true! We must believe that Rocket Man will return…
and to direct us towards Enie Lobby!
Put the package Sodom, Gomura!
Look in front!
There are still coaches detached on the rails!
Friends or enemies, it is not known!
Everyone, you with the combat prepare!
Who is inside?
We are Franky Family!
You show!
Somebody left!
It is… twisted eyebrow?
Here the chef de gare of Enies Lobby.
Is the situation normal?
Yes.
Without delay,
We bring two prisionners.
We can see the island, therefore we will arrive soon.
Included/understood. We will be ready to receive you.
I missed it.
Not astonishing after being parties five years.
The island without night:Enies Lobby.
It is alive?
Really? It is true?
Yes.
It is what he said to me.
I see.
I see…
I am happy.
Imbecile of bakaberg. I really believed that he had died…
I see.
I am relieved.
Didn't the CP9 want to kill it?
It would be preferable that you do not speak about it.
It would not be…
what one calls kindness?
This being,
The government has the plans now
old weapon, by me;
and can awake the weapons which still exist, with you.
What wants to say that it has skilfully
put the hand on the two keys.
Once such a capacity will be of return in the world…
The government will put an end to the era pirates.
This unverifiable military power will unbalance
the world and will cause its destruction…
Old weapons…
are such threats.
Our Master…
its life sacrificed to protect the plans.
By for a future also merdic.
Consequently,
even if I can flee, only that does not have any direction.
In one way or another, you must turn over
near Straw hat.
Impossible.
The only fact of being at their sides would wound them.
At the moment when it came in the world,
its existence even became a crime.
But it is not you who will wound them, hein?
People of the government have beautiful
to regard your existence as a crime,
some is the plague which one carries in oneself,
the fact of being there cannot be a crime.
Whatever the ship…
What you build is neither good nor bad.
This is why…
Its existence even is a crime.
Forgery!
The fact of existing cannot be a crime.
Frankly…
what you ace made with your body?
You are covered with scars!
You…
since 8 years, this famous day…
where Tom-san was taken along, since this business…
day after day,
you face Umi Resha without répis.
You wanted to become stronger, not true?
More never not to lose a expensive being,
to protect those which are expensive to you…
Yokozuna!
It is the moment to show the result of this drive.
Your dear Franky…
was taken along in the same way that Tom-san.
In this moment this train moves towards him.
You want to come with us?
Mugiwara! We have a new ally!
Ouais, I included/understood!
Impressive, the old woman-monster.
Not, it would not be the old woman-frog?
Which is this?
Ca does not have any importance!
Kokoro-san!
I found a good running at eight hours!
Go.
We lost much,
then all let us recover!
Allons-y, frog!
The CP9 arrived! Dépéchez you!
Beautiful work for this long mission!
Seek the prisoners! They are in the first car!
Dumb!
Take better care of me, poor idiot!!
Who you think that I am brothel?!
Does not approach!
Ridges attention!! It bites!!
You understand anything my word?!
Go ahead molo! Morons!
Which noisy man.
It is well the CP9…
Which impressive imposing presence.
He, it is well Cutty Flam?
Then, this woman would be…
Nico Robin.
What a beautée!
Open the Main door.
It is what this place?!
It is… a cascade…
It is what this island good blood?!